<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gunshot the Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Gunshot le zombi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gunshot the Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sparo la Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Gunshot the Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Gunshot the Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gunshot the Zombie</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gunshot may have been ungraciously shot in the head, but that won't stop him from shuffling his way into your heart, and then devouring it. Dress up in the full Gunshot costume with this bundle. Includes Gunshot the Zombie's Head, Gunshot the Zombie's Torso, Gunshot the Zombie's Legs, Gunshot the Zombie's Hands, and Gunshot the Zombie's Feet.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Coup de feu peut avoir été de mauvaise grâce une balle dans la tête, mais cela ne l'empêche pas de brassage sa manière dans votre coeur, et ensuite la dévorer. Habillez-vous avec le costume complet Gunshot avec cet ensemble. Comprend Gunshot le zombi tête,Gunshot le zombi torse,Gunshot le zombi jambes,Gunshot le zombi mains, et Gunshot le zombi pieds.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gunshot wurde möglicherweise ungnädig in den Kopf geschossen haben, aber das wird ihn nicht davon ab schlurfenden seinen Weg in dein Herz, und dann verschlang sie. Dress up in voller Gunshot Kostüm mit diesem Bundle. Inklusive Gunshot der Zombie Head, Gunshot der Zombie Torso, Gunshot der Zombie Beine, Gunshot der Zombie Hände und Gunshot der Zombie Feet.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Arma da fuoco potrebbe essere stato sgarbatamente colpito alla testa, ma questo non gli impedirà di mischiare la sua strada nel tuo cuore, e poi divora. Dress up in costume Gunshot pieno con questo pacchetto. Include arma da fuoco Head Zombie, Zombie arma da fuoco il Torso, Gambe arma da fuoco il Zombie, arma da fuoco le mani del Zombie, e l'arma da fuoco Piedi Zombie.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Por arma de fuego puede haber sido mala gana un disparo en la cabeza, pero eso no le impedirá barajar su manera en su corazón, y luego devorando. Se visten con el traje completo de bala con este paquete. Incluye bala en cabeza del zombi, la bala Zombie Torso, Piernas por arma de fuego del zombi de bala Manos del zombi, y arma de fuego Pies del zombi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_13 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_13 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Gunshot may have been ungraciously shot in the head, but that won't stop him from shuffling his way into your heart, and then devouring it. Dress up in the full Gunshot costume with this bundle. Includes Gunshot the Zombie's Head, Gunshot the Zombie's Torso, Gunshot the Zombie's Legs, Gunshot the Zombie's Hands, and Gunshot the Zombie's Feet.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_13 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_13 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gunshot may have been ungraciously shot in the head, but that won't stop him from shuffling his way into your heart, and then devouring it. Dress up in the full Gunshot costume with this bundle. Includes Gunshot the Zombie's Head, Gunshot the Zombie's Torso, Gunshot the Zombie's Legs, Gunshot the Zombie's Hands, and Gunshot the Zombie's Feet.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>