<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Devastator (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le dévastateur (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Zerstörer (Weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Devastatore(donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Devastador (femenino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Devastator (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This extremely heavy weapon is capable of firing over 4200 rounds per minute and is rightly feared for its ability to lay down a withering hail of fire. BONUS: Unlocks the Devastator for use in MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette arme extrêmement lourde, qui peut tirer plus de 4200 coups par minute, est à juste titre redoutée pour sa capacité à cracher une grêle de projectiles impitoyable. BONUS : Déverrouille le dévastateur utilisable dans MiniBots multijoueur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese äußerst schwere Waffe kann über 4200 Schuss pro Minute abfeuern und wird zu Recht wegen ihrer Fähigkeit gefürchtet, einen wahren Feuerhagel abzugeben. BONUS: Gibt den Zerstörer für den Einsatz im MiniBots-Multiplayer-Modus frei. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quest'arma estremamente pesante è capace di scaricare 4200 spari al minuto ed è giustamente temuta per la sua capacità di produrre una fulminante grandine di fuoco. BONUS: sblocca il Devastatore per l'uso in modalità multigiocatore in MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este arma sumamente pesada es capaz de disparar más de 4200 ciclos por minuto y es temida, con razón, por su capacidad de emitir una lluvia fulminante de fuego. BONUS: Desbloquea el Devastador para usarlo en modo de varios jugadores de los MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This extremely heavy weapon is capable of firing over 4200 rounds per minute and is rightly feared for its ability to lay down a withering hail of fire. BONUS: Unlocks the Devastator for use in MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>