<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Audi Cap M Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hats off to the Audi Team’s performance at Le Mans – and caps off too: ideally this baseball cap with a printed bill. The left front panel shows part of an original pit ticket from 1964.  Colour: black. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Coup de chapeau à la performance de l’équipe d’Audi au Mans, et coup de casquette également : la casquette de baseball idéale avec un billet imprimé. La visière porte une partie du billet original de 1964. Couleur : noire. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Audi-Team beeindruckt in Le Mans durch seine Leistungen. Hut ab! Oder besser Basecap ... und zwar am besten dieses Basecap mit bedrucktem Schirm. Mit Detail eines Original Pit-Tickets von 1964 auf der linken Vorderseite. Farbe: schwarz. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tanto di cappello alla performance del Team Audi a Le Mans! E c’è da levarsi anche i cappellini, soprattutto se si tratta di questo cappellino da baseball con visiera stampata. Sulla sinistra il pannello frontale mostra parte di un biglietto originale per l’autodromo del 1964. Colore: nero. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hay que quitarse el sobrero ante la actuación del equipo de Audi en Le Mans. Y la gorra también. Y qué mejor gorra que ésta, con un estampado en la visera y el símbolo original de 1964 en la parte frontal izquierda. Color: negro. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Audi Cap M Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Le Mans baseball cap: male</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Casquette de baseball Le Mans : homme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Le Mans Basecap: Herren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cappellino da baseball di Le Mans da uomo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Gorra Le Mans: hombre</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>