<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Radec's Body Armour</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">de Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Radecs Körperpanzer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">di Radec (busto)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Armadura corporal de Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">라덱 대령의 전투복 상의</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Radec's Body Armour</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Radec護甲</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Radec護甲</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Radec's Body Armour</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Descr</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">After his final showdown with Tomas Sevchenko, Colonel Radec’s personal body armor was recovered from Visari’s Palace by the ISA. Although it still bears the Helghast regalia marking the Colonel as a member of Visari’s inner circle, his optical camouflage unit is mysteriously missing. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Après son dernier affrontement avec Tomas Sevchenko, l'armure blindée du colonel Radec a été retrouvée au palais de Visari par l'ISA. Bien qu'elle porte encore l'insigne helghaste identifiant le colonel comme un membre du cercle rapproché de Visari, son unité de camouflage optique a mystérieusement disparu. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nach seiner letzten Begegnung mit Tomas Sevchenko wurde Colonel Radecs Körperpanzer von der ISA aus Visaris Palast geborgen. Obwohl er noch immer die Helghast-Insignien trägt, die den Colonel als Mitglied von Visaris innerem Kreis ausweisen, fehlt seine optische Tarnungseinheit aus unerklärlichen Gründen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tras su enfrentamiento final con Tomas Sevchenko, la armadura corporal personal del coronel Radec fue recuperada por los ISA en el Palacio de Visari. Aunque aún conserva los distintivos Helghast que relacionan al coronel con el círculo más íntimo de Visari, su unidad de camuflaje óptico ha desaparecido misteriosamente. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">토마스 세브첸코와의 마지막 대결 후, 라덱 대령의 개인 전투복은 ISA에 의해 비사리 황궁에서 수거되었습니다. 헬가스트의 독특한 문양이 남아 있는 전투복은 라덱 대령이 비사리 수뇌부의 일원이었음을 증명합니다. 그러나 대령의 광학 은폐장비는 이미 이 전투복에서 분리되었습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">After his final showdown with Tomas Sevchenko, Colonel Radec’s personal body armor was recovered from Visari’s Palace by the ISA. Although it still bears the Helghast regalia marking the Colonel as a member of Visari’s inner circle, his optical camouflage unit is mysteriously missing. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在Radec上校與Tomas Sevchenko進行最後決戰後，ISA在賓沙利的宮殿發現了他的護甲。雖然護甲上仍有著赫爾蓋斯特的皇室標誌，顯示Radec是賓沙利心腹的地位，但他的隱形裝置卻離奇地不見踪影。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在Radec上校與Tomas Sevchenko進行最後決戰後，ISA在賓沙利的宮殿發現了他的護甲。雖然護甲上仍有著赫爾蓋斯特的皇室標誌，顯示Radec是賓沙利心腹的地位，但他的隱形裝置卻離奇地不見踪影。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">After his final showdown with Tomas Sevchenko, Colonel Radec’s personal body armor was recovered from Visari’s Palace by the ISA. Although it still bears the Helghast regalia marking the Colonel as a member of Visari’s inner circle, his optical camouflage unit is mysteriously missing. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>