<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gift in a Box</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cadeau dans une boite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Geschenk in einer Schachtel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Regalo in scatola</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Regalo en una caja</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ギフトボックス</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">상자 안의 선물</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Gift in a Box</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">禮品盒</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">禮品盒</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gift in a Box</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A fantastic gift in a box, just what you have always wanted.This was won from playing the OMG Trap-O-Matic in Aurora. Don't forget to check out the other fantastic companions from nDreams. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un formidable cadeau dans une boite, exactement ce que vous avez toujours désiré. Cet objet a été gagné dans le jeu Trap-O-Matic d’Aurora. N’oubliez pas de jeter un œil aux autres compagnons formidables de nDreams. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein fantastisches Geschenk in einer Schachtel, genau was du immer gewollt hast. Dies wurde beim Spielen von OMG Trap-O-Matic in Aurora gewonnen. Vergiss nicht, dir die anderen fantastischen Begleiter von nDreams anzuschauen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un fantastico regalo in una scatola, proprio quello che hai sempre voluto. Vinto dopo aver giocato a Trap-O-Matic in Aurora. Non dimenticare di dare un'occhiata ai fantastici compagni di nDreams. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un magnífico regalo en una caja. Justo lo que siempre has querido. Conseguido al jugar a la Tramp-a-mática en Aurora. No te olvides de echar un vistazo a otros compañeros fantásticos que nDreams te ofrece. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">もらって嬉しい贈り物がつまったポータブルアイテム。オーロラのトラップ大作戦で獲得したもの。nDreamsの他のポータブルアイテムをチェックするのもお忘れなく。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">당신이 항상 원했던 상자 안에 든 환상적인 선물. 이것은 Aurora에서 트랩-오-마틱을 플레이하면서 얻을 수 있습니다. nDreams에서 다른 환상적인 친구들도 잊지 말고 확인하세요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A fantastic gift in a box, just what you have always wanted.This was won from playing the OMG Trap-O-Matic in Aurora. Don't forget to check out the other fantastic companions from nDreams. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">盒中擁有您夢寐以求的美妙禮品。是在極光群島中遊玩「超級陷阱」所獲得的。不要忘記確認nDreams其他不錯的隨身夥伴。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">盒中擁有您夢寐以求的美妙禮品。是在極光群島中遊玩「超級陷阱」所獲得的。不要忘記確認nDreams其他不錯的隨身夥伴。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A fantastic gift in a box, just what you have always wanted.This was won from playing the OMG Trap-O-Matic in Aurora. Don't forget to check out the other fantastic companions from nDreams. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>