<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Seaside Coconut Crab Set</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set crabe de cocotier de bord de mer</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Satz aus Küsten-Kokosnuss-Krabben</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set di granchi da noce di cocco in riva al mare</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de cangrejo cocotero en la costa</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">海辺のヤシガニセット</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">해안의 야자게 세트</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Seaside Coconut Crab Set</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">海邊的椰子蟹組合包</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">海邊的椰子蟹組合包</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Seaside Coconut Crab Set</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">This is a set of the Seaside Coconut Crab portable item and the Face-hugging Coconut Crab head accessory. This set contains the following portable item and avatar customization items:\n\n- Face-hugging Coconut Crab (Head accessory/Men)\n- Face-hugging Coconut Crab (Head accessory/Women)\n- Seaside Coconut Crab (Portable Item)\n\n* Upon purchase, the items will be added to their respective categories of Portable Items and "Avatar Customization" items.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">C'est un set d'objets portables de crabes de cocotiers de bord de mer et de l'accessoire crabe de cocotier agrippeur de tete.
 Ce set contient les objets portables suivants et des objets de personnalisation d'avatar:\n\n
- Crabe de cocotier agrippeur de visage (Homme)\n
- Crabe de cocotier agrippeur de visage (Femme)\n
- Crabe de cocotier de bord de mer (Compagnon)[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Satz aus portablen Küsten-Kokosnuss-Krabben und dem Gesichtsumarmenden Kokosnuss-Krabben-Accessoire. Dieser Satz enthält die folgenden tragbaren und Avatar-Gegenstände:\n\n- Gesichtsumarmende Kokosnuss-Krabbe (Kopfbedeckung/ für Männer)\n- Gesichtsumarmende Kokosnuss-Krabbe (Kopfbedeckung/ für Frauen)\n- Küsten-Kokosnuss-Krabbe (Tragbarer Gegenstand)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie tragbarer und "Avatar Gegenstände" zugeordnet.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Questo è un set comprendente l'oggetto portatile Granchio da noce di cocco e l'accessorio per il viso Granchio da noce di cocco avvinghiato al viso.\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Granchio da noce di cocco avvinghiato al viso (accessario per il viso/da uomo)\n- Granchio da noce di cocco avvinghiato al viso (accessario per il viso/da donna)\n- Granchio da noce di cocco (oggetto portatile)\n\n*Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettive categorie di "Oggetto portatile" e in tutte le categorie specifiche all'interno di "Personalizzazione dell'avatar". [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Este es un juego de objetos portátiles del cangrejo cocotero en la costa y el accesorio de cabeza del cangrejo cocotero en la cara. Este juego contiene los siguientes objetos portátiles y objetos de personalización de avatar:\n\n- Cangrejo cocotero en la cara (Accesorio de cabeza/hombre)\n- Cangrejo cocotero en la cara (Accesorio de cabeza/mujer)\n- Cangrejo cocotero en la costa (objeto portátil)\n\n* Después de la compra, cada objeto será agregado a la categoría a la de los Objetos Portátiles y objetos de "Personalización de Avatar".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">海辺のヤシガニのポータブルアイテムと、ヤシガニが顔に貼り付いたヘッドアクセサリーのセットです。本セットには、ポータブルアイテムとアバターカスタマイズ用の下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・顔に貼り付いたヤシガニ（ヘッドアクセサリー/男性）\n・顔に貼り付いたヤシガニ（ヘッドアクセサリー/女性）\n・海辺のヤシガニ（ポータブルアイテム）\n\n※購入すると、ポータブルアイテムと「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">해안의 야자게의 포터블 아이템과, 야자게가 얼굴에 달라붙은 머리 액세서리의 세트입니다. 본 세트에는 포터블 아이템과 아바타 꾸미기용의 하기 아이템이 포함되어 있습니다. \n\n●얼굴에 달라붙은 야자게(머리 액세서리/남성)\n●얼굴에 달라붙은 야자게(머리 액세서리/여성)\n●해안의 야자게(포터블 아이템)\n\n※구입하면, 포터블 아이템과 「아바타 꾸미기」내의 해당 카테고리에 각 아이템이 추가됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">This is a set including portable item "Seaside Coconut Crab" and "Coconut Crab Attached onto Face". This set includes the following items: \n\n・Coconut Crab Attached onto Face (Head Accessory, Men)\n・Coconut Crab Attached onto Face (Head Accessory, Women)\n・Coconut Crab by the Sea (Portable Item)\n\n※Upon purchase, all items will be placed into respective categories in portable items and “Avatar Customization”. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">這是海邊的椰子蟹隨身道具及椰子蟹黏在臉上的髮飾組合包。本組合包包括以下道具。\n\n●黏在臉上的椰子蟹（頭飾/男用）\n●黏在臉上的椰子蟹（頭飾/女用）\n●海邊的椰子蟹(隨身道具)\n\n※購買後，各道具將被加進隨身道具及「進入衣帽間」內的相對類別內。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">這是海邊的椰子蟹隨身道具及椰子蟹黏在臉上的髮飾組合包。本組合包包括以下道具。\n\n●黏在臉上的椰子蟹（頭飾/男用）\n●黏在臉上的椰子蟹（頭飾/女用）\n●海邊的椰子蟹(隨身道具)\n\n※購買後，各道具將被加進隨身道具及「進入更衣室」內的相對類別內。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">This is a set of the Seaside Coconut Crab portable item and the Face-hugging Coconut Crab head accessory.
 This set contains the following portable item and avatar customization items:\n\n
- Face-hugging Coconut Crab (Men)\n
- Face-hugging Coconut Crab (Women)\n
- Seaside Coconut Crab (Portable Item)[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
