<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mishmash of Female stuff</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Méli-mélo de trucs de filles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mischmasch aus weiblichem Zeug</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Romanticherie da Donna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mezcolanza de cosas femeninas</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Some things are worth more than words, others cannot be described by words, while others simply remind you of what it feels like to be kissed gently on the lips. \n

1. Rolling Sounds \n
2. Livy \n
3. YOU CAN TAKE THE GIRL OUT OF THE SHOE BUT... \n
4. MR CUDDLES [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Certaines choses valent bien plus qu'un long discours, d'autres appartiennent au domaine de l'indicible et d'autres encore se contentent de vous rappeler comme il est doux de recevoir un simple baiser. \n

1. Rolling Sounds \n
2. Livy \n
3. ON PEUT OTER LA FILLE DE LA CHAUSSURE, MAIS... \n
4. MONSIEUR CALIN [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Manche Dinge sind mehr wert als Worte. Andere können mit Worten nicht beschrieben werden. Wiederum andere erinnern einen einfach nur daran, wie es sich anfühlt, sanft auf die Lippen geküsst zu werden. \n

1. Rolling Sounds \n
2. Livy \n
3. HOCH HINAUS \n
4. KUNDDELBÄR [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Certe cose valgono più delle parole; altre non possono essere descritte dalle parole, mentre altre ancora ti ricordano semplicemente cosa si prova ad essere baciati delicatamente sulle labbra. \n

1. Rolling Sounds \n
2. Livy \n
3. CALZANDO IN ROSA... \n
4. MR COCCOLE [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Algunas cosas valen mucho más que palabras; otras no se pueden describir con palabras; mientras que otras solo te recuerdan lo que se siente al recibir un delicado beso en los labios. \n

1. Sonido Rolling \n
2. Livy \n
3. PUEDES QUITARLE LOS ZAPATOS, PERO... \n
4. SR. ABRAZOS [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>