<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">French Chateau Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack de meubles du Château à la française</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Französisches Schloss: Möbelset</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto arredamento Castello francese</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de muebles château francés</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">フレンチシャトー家具セット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">프랑스 저택 가구 번들</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">French Chateau Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">法式別墅家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">法式別墅家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">French Chateau Furniture Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Adorn your majestic French Chateau in this wonderful furniture bundle pack made specifically for it. Bundle includes a bed, chair, couch, and tables. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Décorez votre majestueux Château à la française avec ces magnifiques meubles fabriqués sur mesure. Le pack comprend un lit, une chaise, un canapé et une tables. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schmücke dein majestätisches französisches Schloss mit diesem wundervollen Möbelset. Das Set enthält ein Bett, einen Stuhl, eine Couch und einen Tisches. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Abbellisci il tuo maestoso Castello francese con questo fantastico pacchetto di arredamento ideato su misura. Il pacchetto include letto, sedia, divano e tavolos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Adorna tu majestuoso château francés con este maravilloso pack de muebles diseñado a tal fin. El conjunto incluye cama, silla, sofá y mesas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">フレンチシャトーにぴったりな美しい家具セットです。\n\n本セットには以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n・「チェア（フレンチシャトー）」（チェア）\n・「テーブル（フレンチシャトー）」（テーブル）\n・「カウチ（フレンチシャトー）」（ソファー）\n・「ベッド（フレンチシャトー）」（アドバンスド家具）\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。\n\n※本セットには、アニメーションや機能が追加されているアドバンスド家具が含まれています。この種類のアイテムは配置できる数に制限があります。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">장엄한 프랑스 저택을 위한, 그리고 프랑스 저택을 꾸밀 수 있는 환상적인 가구 번들입니다. 이 번들은 다음 아이템을 포함합니다.\n
●프랑스 저택 침대\n
●프랑스 저택 의자\n
●프랑스 저택 소파\n
●프랑스 저택 탁자\n
●프랑스 저택 사이드 테이블\n\n

*구매 후 각 아이템은 해당 카테고리에 추가됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Adorn your majestic French Chateau in this wonderful furniture bundle pack made specifically for it.\n
This bundle includes the following items.\n\n

・French Chateau Bed\n
・French Chateau Chair\n
・French Chateau Couch\n
・French Chateau Tables\n
・French Chateau Side Table\n\n

*When purchased, each item is added to its respective category.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用這套專為法式別墅而造的家具組合包來裝飾您那充滿氣派的法式別墅。\n
本組合包包括以下道具：\n\n

●法式別墅床\n
●法式別墅椅子\n
●法式別墅長沙發\n
●法式別墅桌子\n
●法式別墅的邊桌\n\n

※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別內。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用這套專為法式別墅而造的家具組合包來裝飾您那充滿氣派的法式別墅。\n
本組合包包括以下道具：\n\n

●法式別墅床\n
●法式別墅椅子\n
●法式別墅長沙發\n
●法式別墅桌子\n
●法式別墅的邊桌\n\n

※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別內。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Adorn your majestic French Chateau in this wonderful furniture bundle pack made specifically for it. Bundle includes a bed, chair, couch, and tables. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>