<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Weapon Pad – Vorpal Blade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plateforme d'arme – Épée vorpale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Waffenpad – Tödliche Klinge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pedana armi - Lama vorpale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Panel de armas - Espada vorpal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Weapon Pad – Vorpal Blade</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Place this item in your MiniBots Training Facility to allow Vorpal Blades to be equipped. Anyone who owns the Vorpal Blade hand item can equip the Vorpal Blade at this pad during a multiplayer game.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Placez cet élément dans votre centre d'entraînement MiniBots pour qu'il soit possible de s'équiper avec les épées vorpales. N'importe qui peut s'équiper avec l'épée vorpale de cette plateforme pendant une partie multijoueur s'il possède l'élément de main épée vorpale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Platzieren Sie dieses Objekt in Ihre MiniBots-Trainingsanlage, damit Tödliche Klinge damit ausgestattet werden kann. Jeder der das Tödliche Klinge-Handobjekt besitzt, kann das Tödliche Klinge in diesem Pad in einem Multiplayer-Spiel bestücken. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Colloca questo elemento nella struttura di addestramento Minibot per consentire l'equipaggiamento con Lama vorpale. Chiunque possieda l'elemento Lama vorpale può dotarsene in questa pedana durante una partita in modalità multigiocatore. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Coloca este artículo en tus instalaciones de entrenamiento de MiniBots para permitir que las Espadas vorpales estén equipados. Cualquier propietario del artículo de mano Espada vorpal puede equipar la Espada vorpal en este panel durante una partida para varios jugadores. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Place this item in your MiniBots Training Facility to allow Vorpal Blades to be equipped. Anyone who owns the Vorpal Blade hand item can equip the Vorpal Blade at this pad during a multiplayer game.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>