<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Japanese Teahouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Maison de thé japonaise </LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Japanisches Teehaus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stanza per la cerimonia del tè giapponese</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Casa de té japonesa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Japanese Teahouse</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A remote mountain location, with abundant vegetation and water. A small teahouse stands past the gate, beyond the garden stepping stones.The confined teahouse built according to the principles of wabi and sabi allows one to draw near to visitors. Spend a brief moment in silence.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un endroit reculé dans les montagnes, avec une végétation abondante et de l'eau. Une petite maison de thé se trouve derrière la porte, après le jardin de pierres. La maison de thé confinée, construite selon les principes de wabi et sabi, permet de se rapprocher des visiteurs. Venez passer un petit moment dans le silence.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine abgelegene Bergortschaft mit üppiger Vegetation und Wasserläufen. Hinter dem Tor liegen einige Trittsteine, an deren Ende sich ein kleines Teehaus befindet. Das Teehaus, das nach dem Prinzip von Wabi und Sabi ("Die Schönheit der Schlichtheit") gebaut wurde, lädt zum Verweilen in einem kurzen Moment der Stille, ein.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un remoto luogo di montagna, ricco di vegetazione e acqua. Oltre il cancello, superato il sentiero di pietre attraverso il giardino, si trova una piccola stanza per la cerimonia del tè. Costruita secondo i principi di wabi e sabi, essa permette di ridurre la distanza tra i visitatori. Passa un po' di tempo in silenzio.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un lugar remoto entre las montañas, rodeado abundante vegetación y agua. Una pequeña casa de té se alza pasada la puerta, tras el sendero de piedras del jardín. Esta pequeña construcción, edificada según los principios de wabi-sabi, le permite a uno sentirse cercano a sus visitantes. Disfruta de un instante de silencio.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A remote mountain location, with abundant vegetation and water. A small teahouse stands past the gate, beyond the garden stepping stones.The confined teahouse built according to the principles of wabi and sabi allows one to draw near to visitors. Spend a brief moment in silence.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>