<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Festival Braid</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Festival Braid</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Festival Braid</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Trenza de festival</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tresse de festival</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Festival-Zopf</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Treccia da festival</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">フェスティバルブレイド</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">페스티벌 브레이드</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">節慶辮髮</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">節日辮髮</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A chic fusion of structure and flow. Featuring a neat top bun and long side braid, this style is ideal for special occasions or standout everyday wear. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A chic fusion of structure and flow. Featuring a neat top bun and long side braid, this style is ideal for special occasions or standout everyday wear. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A chic fusion of structure and flow. Featuring a neat top bun and long side braid, this style is ideal for special occasions or standout everyday wear. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una combinación elegante de estructura y movimiento. Con un moño superior ordenado y una larga trenza lateral, este peinado es ideal para ocasiones especiales o para destacar a diario. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une fusion chic entre structure et fluidité. Avec un chignon soigné sur le dessus et une longue tresse sur le côté, cette coiffure est parfaite pour les grandes occasions ou un look marquant au quotidien. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine elegante Verbindung aus Struktur und Leichtigkeit. Mit ordentlichem Dutt oben und langem Seitenzopf – ideal für besondere Anlässe oder auffällige Alltagslooks. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una fusione chic di struttura e fluidità. Con uno chignon ordinato in alto e una lunga treccia laterale, è perfetta per occasioni speciali o per distinguersi ogni giorno. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">きちんとまとめたお団子と長いサイドブレイドが特徴の、構造美と流れるような動きが融合したシックなスタイル。特別な日にも日常のおしゃれにも最適です。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">깔끔한 상단 번 헤어와 긴 사이드 브레이드가 조화를 이루는 세련된 스타일. 특별한 날은 물론 일상에서도 돋보이기에 제격입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">結合結構與飄逸感的優雅造型。俐落的高丸子頭搭配側邊長辮子，是節慶或日常亮眼造型的理想選擇。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">結合結構與流動感的時尚髮型。整齊高髻配上長側辮，是節日或日常搶眼造型的不二之選。 [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>