<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Monk Armor Set (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble d’armure de moniale (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rüstungssatz Mönch (Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set di armatura da monaca (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de armadura de la monje (chica)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_36</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_36</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_36</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_36</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_36</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Monk Armor Set (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You are a holy warrior. Decimate foes with your physical and spiritual prowess in this iconic Monk armor set from Diablo III. The set includes the Monk's Master Crown, Monk Cuirass, Monk Legwraps, Monk Treads, and Monk Fists.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous êtes une guerrière sainte. Utilisez vos prouesses physiques et spirituelles pour décimer vos ennemis grâce à cet ensemble complet d’armure emblématique de la moniale de Diablo III. Il comprend : couronne de maître de moniale, cuirasse de moniale, couvre-jambes de moniale, bottines de moniale, poings de moniale.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie sind eine heilige Kriegerin. Lichten Sie die Reihen Ihrer Feinde mithilfe Ihrer physischen und geistigen Fähigkeiten, die in diesem unverwechselbaren Mönchsrüstungssatz aus Diablo III verborgen sind. Der Rüstungssatz umfasst die Mönchskrone des Großmeisters, Mönchskürass, Mönchsbeinwickel, Mönchstreter und Mönchsfäuste.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sei una guerriera sacra. Annienta i nemici grazie alla tua potenza fisica e spirituale con questo set di armatura da monaca di Diablo III. Il set include Corona del Maestro da monaca, Corazza da monaca, Cosciali da monaca, Stivaletti da monaca e Pugni da monaca.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Eres una guerrera sagrada. Tus enemigos sucumbirán a tu poderío físico y espiritual con este simbólico conjunto de armadura de la monje de Diablo III. El conjunto incluye la corona de maestro de la monje, la coraza de la monje, las perneras de la monje, los botines de la monje y los puños de la monje.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_36 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_36 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_36 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_36 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_36 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You are a holy warrior. Decimate foes with your physical and spiritual prowess in this iconic Monk armor set from Diablo III. The set includes the Monk's Master Crown, Monk Cuirass, Monk Legwraps, Monk Treads, and Monk Fists.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>