<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Spunbot Mega Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Méga pack Spunbot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spunbot-Riesenpaket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mega Pacchetto Spunbot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Megapack Spunbot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Spunbot Mega Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Get the whole Spunbot set, includes: 3 LMOs (Flapper Saucer, Copter Saucer and Classic Saucer), Spunbot legs ( male and female ) and the Spunbot anim pack for those flashy Spunbot Leg moves! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Profitez du pack Spunbot complet, qui comprend : 3 LMO (Soucoupe à ailes, Soucoupe-coptère et Soucoupe classique), les jambes Spunbot (pour homme et pour femme) et le pack d'animations Spunbot, pour faire des mouvements qui en jettent ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hol dir das komplette Spunbot-Set! Es beinhaltet: 3 LMOs (Flatter-Untertasse, Helikopter-Untertasse und Klassische Untertasse), Spunbot-Beine (männlich und weiblich) und das Spunbot-Animationspaket für schicke Spunbot-Beinbewegungen![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ottieni un set Spunbot completo: 3 LMO (navicella spaziale alata, elicottero spaziale e navicella spaziale classica), gambe Spunbot (da uomo o da donna) e il pacchetto animazione Spunbot per aggiungere un po' di movimento alle gambe! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Consigue todo el conjunto Spunbot, incluye: 3 LMO (platillo flapper, platillo helicóptero, platillo clásico), piernas de Spunbot (hombre y mujer) y el pack de animaciones de Spunbot para esos deslumbrantes movimientos de piernas de Spunbot. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Get the whole Spunbot set, includes: 3 LMOs (Flapper Saucer, Copter Saucer and Classic Saucer), Spunbot legs ( male and female ) and the Spunbot anim pack for those flashy Spunbot Leg moves! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>