<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Backup Luv Jacket - Grass Roots (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Blouson Backup Luv - Herbe (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Backup Luv Jacke - Grünbraun (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Backup Luv Giacca - Radici d'Erba (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Backup Luv Chaqueta - Tono raíz (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our Backup Luv jacket is sure to be the most beautiful bomber you've ever seen. Very street-chic and also romantic with a quilted body detailed with embroidery at the zip placket. The sleeves feature a contrast print of vibrant paisleys. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Notre blouson Backup Luv est sûrement le plus beau blouson aviateur qu'il vous ait été donné de voir. Très chic citadin et également romantique, avec son corps matelassé orné de broderies au niveau de la fermeture zippée. Les manches comportent un imprimé contrasté de motifs cachemire enthousiasmants. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Backup Luv ist unter Garantie die schönste Bomberjacke, die Sie je gesehen haben. Die gesteppte Jacke mit Kontrastärmeln im Paisleymuster und feinen Stickereien an der Reißverschlussleiste strahlt echten Straßenchic mit einem Hauch von Romantik aus. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La giacca Backup Luv è di sicuro il bomber più bello che tu abbia mai visto. Con un tocco street-chic e allo stesso tempo romantico, la giacca presenta corpo trapuntato con ricamo sulla patta della zip. Le maniche presentano una stampa a contrasto con vivace motivo cachemire. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nuestra chaqueta Backup Luv es de lejos la bomber más hermosa que jamás hayas visto. Perfecta mezcla de "chic" y urbano a la par que romántica con un cuerpo guateado y detalles de bordado en las solapas con cremallera.  Las mangas presentan un vibrante estampado cachemir en contraste. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>