<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Forsaken Planet – Turret (Active)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Forsaken Planet - Tourelle (Active)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Forsaken Planet – Turret (Active)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Forsaken Planet – Torretta (Active)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Forsaken Planet – Torreta (Activa)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Forsaken Planet – Turret (Active)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Guard your HOME with this Active Turret from Forsaken Planet, a LOOT™ Entertainment videogame for tablets and smart phones! When you purchase this item, you unlock a UFO Gun* for use in the Forsaken Planet game. This exclusive UFO Gun can only be unlocked in PlayStation®Home! To retrieve your reward, create or access your LOOT™ Entertainment account at the log-in station located at the Forsaken Planet globe logo in the LOOT Space Station Hub. Looking for even sweeter Forsaken Planet deals and in-game rewards? Check out the Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle in the LOOT™ Store! (*UFO gun unlocks specialized gameplay perks within the Forsaken Planet videogame!) www.lootentertainment.com [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Protégez votre HOME avec cette Tourelle Active de Forsaken Planet un jeu vidéo de  LOOT™ Entertainment  pour tablettes et téléphones intelligents ! En achetant cet article, vous gagnez un Canon OVNI* à utiliser dans le jeu Forsaken Planet. Ce Canon OVNI exclusif ne peut être gagné que dans  PlayStation®Home ! Pour collecter votre récompense, créez ou accédez à votre compte  LOOT™ Entertainment à la station de connexion située dans le logo globe de Forsaken Planet sur la plateforme de la station spatiale LOOT. Vous cherchez des affaires Forsaken Planet encore plus intéressantes et des récompenses dans le jeu ? Allez voir les Lots Forsaken Planet dans la Boutique LOOT™  !  (*Le Canon OVNI permet d'obtenir certains avantages spécifiques de jouabilité dans le jeu vidéo Forsaken Planet !) www.lootentertainment.com [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schütze dein HOME mit diesem Active Geschützturm aus Forsaken Planet, einem LOOT™ Entertainment Videospiel für Tablets und Smartphones! Wenn du diesen Gegenstand erwirbst, schaltest du eine UFO-Gun* für den Einsatz im Spiel Forsaken Planet frei. Diese exklusive UFO Gun kann nur in PlayStation®Home freigeschaltet werden! Um deine Belohnung zu erhalten, erstelle oder öffne dein LOOT™ Entertainment Konto mit dem GRATIS Forsaken Planet – Globe Logo (Active), es ist erhältlich im LOOT™ Store. Möchtest du noch bessere Deals Forsaken Planet und Spielgegenstände abgreifen? Schau dir die Forsaken Planet-Bundles im LOOT™ Store an! (*Dieser Spielgegenstand schaltet besondere Gameplay-Vorteile im Videospiel Forsaken Planet frei!) www.lootentertainment.com [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Difendi la tua HOME con questa Torretta Active di Forsaken Planet, un videogioco di LOOT™ Entertainment per tablet e smartphone! Con l'acquisto di questo articolo, sblocchi una arma UFO* da utilizzare nel gioco Forsaken Planet. Questa arma UFO esclusiva può essere sbloccata solo in PlayStation®Home! Per recuperare il tuo premio, crea o accedi all'account LOOT™ Entertainment con il LOGO Globe (Active) GRATUITO di Forsaken Planet disponibile nel LOOT™ Store. Cerchi altre offerte e altri premi Forsaken Planet? Dai un'occhiata al Pacchetto Forsaken Planet nel LOOT™ Store! (*L'arma UFO sblocca elementi di gioco particolari all'interno del videogioco Forsaken Planet!) www.lootentertainment.com [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Protege tu espacio HOME con esta torreta activa de Forsaken Planet, un videojuego de LOOT™ Entertainment para tabletas y smartphones! Cuando compres este artículo, desbloquearás una pistola de OVNI* que podrás usar en el juego Forsaken Planet. ¡Esta exclusiva pistola de OVNI solo se puede desbloquear en PlayStation®Home! Para conseguir tu premio, crea o accede a tu cuenta de LOOT™ Entertainment con el logotipo del planeta GRATUITO de Forsaken Planet (Activo) disponible en la tienda LOOT™. ¿Quieres ofertas y premios aún más jugosos de Forsaken Planet? ¡No te pierdas el Gran lote Forsaken Planet en la tienda LOOT™! (*La pistola OVNI desbloquea extras especiales para el videojuego de Forsaken Planet) www.lootentertainment.com [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Guard your HOME with this Active Turret from Forsaken Planet, a LOOT™ Entertainment videogame for tablets and smart phones! When you purchase this item, you unlock a UFO Gun* for use in the Forsaken Planet game. This exclusive UFO Gun can only be unlocked in PlayStation®Home! To retrieve your reward, create or access your LOOT™ Entertainment account at the log-in station located at the Forsaken Planet globe logo in the LOOT Space Station Hub. Looking for even sweeter Forsaken Planet deals and in-game rewards? Check out the Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle in the LOOT™ Store! (*UFO gun unlocks specialized gameplay perks within the Forsaken Planet videogame!) www.lootentertainment.com [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>