<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Highest Peak Denim Shorts - Medium Vintage (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Short en denim Highest Peak - Vintage Medium (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Highest Peak Jeansshorts - Vintage (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Shorts in denim Highest Peak - Vintage medio (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Highest Peak Pantalón vaquero corto - Medium Vintage (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Perfectly fitted 5-pocket denim shorts features a slightly longer inseam and a cuffed hem. We've treated the fabric to hand sanding and light distressing for a slightly worn-in look. We've also include belt loops and a zip fly. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce short en denim à 5 poches parfaitement ajusté comporte un entrejambe légèrement rallongé et un ourlet à revers. Nous avons traité le tissu au ponçage manuel pour lui donner un aspect légèrement usé, pour un look décontracté. Nous avons également ajouté des passants de ceinture et une braguette zippée. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Optimal angepasste Jeansshorts mit fünf Taschen, längerer Beininnenlänge und umgeschlagenem Saum. Die Shorts wurden von Hand mit Sand bearbeitet und leicht abgewetzt, um den modisch abgetragenen Look zu erzeugen. Mit Gürtelschlaufen und Reißverschluss. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Shorts in denim dalla vestibilità perfetta con cavallo leggermente più lungo e orlo doppio. Il tessuto è stato trattato con carta vetrata e sottoposto a un leggero distressing per dargli un aspetto un po' vissuto. Sono dotati anche di asole per la cintura e cerniera lampo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pantalón vaquero corto de cinco bolsillos y perfecto ajustado, que presenta un tiro ligeramente largo y los bajos enrollados. Se ha tratado la tela con chorro de arena y presión para un aspecto ligeramente usado. También se incluyen trabillas en la cintura y bragueta de cremallera. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>