<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Street Style - Street Pack 05 - Orange (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Street Style - Pack Street 05 - Orange (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Street Style - Paket 05 - Orange (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Street Style - Pacchetto Street 05 - Arancione (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Street Style - Pack Street 05 - Orange (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wear the whole package with this Street Style Outfit Pack!\n
This bundle contains:\n
(1) Street Style - Metallic Tracksuit Jacket With Bling - Orange (Men)\n
(2) Street Style - Jogging Bottoms and High Tops - Navy (Men)\n
(3) Street Style - Round Tinted Glasses - Yellow (Men) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Portez l'ensemble complet avec ce pack Street Style !\n                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                        
Ce lot contient :\n                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                               
(1) Street Style - Veste de survêtement effet métal avec accessoires bling-bling - Orange (homme)\n
                                                                                                                                                                  (2) Street Style - Pantalon de jogging et baskets montantes - Marine (homme)\n                                                                                                                                                                                                                      
(3) Street Style - Lunettes rondes teintées - Jaune (homme) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tragen Sie das gesamte Outfit in diesem Street Style Outfit-Paket!\n
Dieses Paket enthält:\n
(1) Street Style - Metallicfarbene Tracksuit-Glitzerjacke - Orange (Herren)\n
(2) Street Style - Jogginghose und Hi-Top-Sneaker - Marineblau (Herren)\n
(3) Street Style - Brille mit runden getönten Gläsern - Gelb (Herren) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Indossa tutti i capi con questo Pacchetto di Abbigliamento Street Style!\n
Il set comprende:\n
(1) Street Style - Giacca da tuta metallizzata e luccicante - Arancione (Uomo)\n
(2) Street Style - Pantaloni da jogging e scarpe da ginnastica a stivaletto - Blu scuro (Uomo)\n
(3) Street Style - Occhiali tondi con lenti colorate - Giallo (Uomo) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Ponte el conjunto entero con este Pack de Ropa Street Style!\n
Este pack contiene:\n
(1) Street Style - Chaqueta de chándal metalizada con joyas - Naranja (Hombre)\n
(2) Street Style - Pantalón de chándal y zapatillas altas - Azul marino (Hombre)\n
(3) Street Style - Gafas redondas tintadas - Amarillo (Hombre) [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>