<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Treasure hunt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chasse au trésor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schatzjagd</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caccia al tesoro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Caza del tesoro</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Treasure hunt[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chasse au trésor [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schatzjagd [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caccia al tesoro [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Caza del tesoro [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kIntro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Evil ghost pirates have attacked and robbed this coach!  They've stolen a treasure chest containing the cursed tricorn of Captain Kevin Keelhaul, the legendary mad pirate king.  They've buried the chest somewhere in Home Square.  Find the 5 fragments of the treasure map in order to locate the chest and grab the hat for yourself!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">De diaboliques pirates fantômes ont dévalisé ce carrosse ! Ils ont volé un coffre contenant le tricorne maudit du capitaine Gaspard de Subord, le légendaire roi pirate fou. Ils ont enterré le coffre quelque part sur le Square Home. Réunissez les 5 morceaux de la carte pour trouver le coffre et mettre la main sur le chapeau !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fiese Geisterpiraten haben diese Kutsche angegriffen und ausgeraubt! Sie haben eine Schatzkiste gestohlen, die den verfluchten Dreispitz von Kevin Kielhol enthält, dem legendären, verrückten Piratenkönig. Die Kiste haben sie irgendwo auf dem Home-Platz vergraben. Beschaffe die 5 Fragmente der Schatzkarte, um zur Truhe zu finden und dir den Hut selber schnappen zu können!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dei malvagi pirati fantasma hanno attaccato e saccheggiato questo carro, rubando un forziere che conteneva il tricorno maledetto del Capitano Girodichiglia, il leggendario re pirata pazzo. Il tesoro è stato sepolto da qualche parte sotto Piazza Home. Trova i 5 frammenti della mappa del tesoro per localizzare il forziere e trovare il cappello!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Los fantasmas de unos malvados piratas han atacado y robado este coche! Se han llevado un cofre del tesoro que contenía el tricornio maldito del capitán Kevin el Cruel, legendario y demente rey de los piratas. Han enterrado el cofre en algún lugar de la Plaza Home. Encuentra los 5 fragmentos del mapa del tesoro para localizar el cofre y hacerte con el sombrero.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDig</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [CROSS] to dig</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyez sur [CROSS] pour creuser\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücke [CROSS], um zu graben\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi [CROSS] per scavare\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa el botón [CROSS] para excavar\n</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kContinue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [ACCEPT] to continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Continuer\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Fortfahren\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Continua\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Continuar\n</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDecline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [DECLINE] to decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Annuler\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE] Ablehnen\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE] Rifiuta\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] Rechazar\n</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kTake</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [ACCEPT] to pick up the map fragment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyez sur [ACCEPT] pour ramasser le morceau de carte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücke [ACCEPT], um das Kartenfragment aufzuheben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi [ACCEPT] per raccogliere il frammento della mappa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa [ACCEPT] para recoger el fragmento del mapa</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kSearching</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hunting for treasure...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cherche un trésor...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine Schatzjagd ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">A caccia di tesori...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">En busca del tesoro...</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
   <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kFound1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have found the first fragment of the map! Continue your quest for the remaining four pieces.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez trouvé le premier morceau de la carte ! Continuez votre quête pour trouver les quatre autres.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast das erste Kartenfragment gefunden! Setze deine Suche nach den restlichen vier Teilen fort.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai trovato il primo frammento della mappa! Continua a cercare gli altri quattro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has encontrado el primer fragmento del mapa! Continúa con la misión hasta encontrar los otros cuatro.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
   <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kFound2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have found the second fragment of the map! Things are looking interesting.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez trouvé le deuxième morceau de la carte ! Ça commence à devenir intéressant...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast das zweite Kartenfragment gefunden! Das könnte interessant werden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai trovato il secondo frammento della mappa! Le cose si fanno interessanti.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has encontrado el segundo fragmento del mapa! Las cosas se ponen interesantes.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
   <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kFound3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is the third fragment of the map! Only two more to find.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Et voilà le troisième morceau de la carte ! Plus que deux.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das ist das dritte Kartenfragment! Nur noch zwei weitere.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo è il terzo frammento della mappa! Ne mancano solo altri due.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Este es el tercer fragmento del mapa! Solo quedan dos más.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
   <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kFound4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is the fourth fragment of the map! It is nearly complete.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C'est le quatrième morceau de la carte ! Vous y êtes presque !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das ist das vierte Kartenfragment! Sie ist fast vollständig.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo è il quarto frammento della mappa! È quasi completa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Este es el cuarto fragmento del mapa! Ya casi está completo.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
   <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kFound5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The final fragment. The map is complete! Go and dig for your treasure. X marks the spot.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le dernier morceau. La carte est complète ! Allez déterrer votre trésor. Un X marque l'emplacement.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das letzte Stück. Die Karte ist vollständig! Jetzt grab nach deinem Schatz. Das X kennzeichnet die richtige Stelle.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'ultimo frammento. La mappa è completa! Vai a scavare per trovare il tesoro. Il posto è indicato dalla X.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El último fragmento. ¡El mapa está completo! Ve a desenterrar el tesoro. La X marca el lugar.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
   <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kFoundTreasure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have found the chest containing the Pirate Captains hat! It's even in a nice colour!  Enjoy your pirate booty.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez trouvé le coffre qui contient le chapeau du capitaine pirate. Même sa couleur est jolie ! Profitez bien de votre butin.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast die Truhe mit dem Hut des Piratenkapitäns gefunden! Und er hat sogar eine schöne Farbe! Viel Spaß mit deinem Piratenschatz.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai trovato il forziere contenente il cappello del capitano pirata! Ha anche un bel colore! Goditi il tuo bottino.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has encontrado el cofre que contiene el sombrero del capitán pirata! ¡Pues el color es bastante bonito! Disfruta de tu botín pirata.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>

</LOCALISATION>