<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Cheerful Yellow Monkey Set</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack singe jaune joyeux</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">„Fröhlicher gelber Affe“-Set</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set vivace scimmia gialla</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de mono amarillo alegre</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">陽気な黄色い毛のサルセット</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">활발한 노란 털의 원숭이 세트</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Cheerful Yellow Monkey Set</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">開朗的黃色猴子組合包</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">開朗的黃色猴子組合包</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Cheerful Yellow Monkey Set</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A set that contains a small, yellow monkey as a portable item and a monkey clinging to your head as a head accessory.\n
This set contains the following portable item and avatar customising items.\n\n
・Head-clinging Yellow Monkey (Head Accessory, Men)\n
・Head-clinging Yellow Monkey (Head Accessory, Women)\n
・Cheerful Yellow Monkey (Portable Item)\n\n
*When purchased, the portable item is added to the appropriate category and  each avatar customising item is added to the appropriate category in your wardrobe.  [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un pack qui contient un petit singe jaune que vous pourrez emmener partout, et un singe perché sur votre tête qui fera office de couvre-chef. \n
Ce pack contient le compagnon et les éléments de personnalisation de l'avatar suivant :\n
・Singe jaune perché sur votre tête (accessoire, homme)\n
・Singe jaune perché sur votre tête (accessoire, femme)\n
・Singe jaune joyeux (compagnon)\n\n
Après achat, chaque élément est ajouté à la catégorie appropriée.
 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Set enthält einen kleinen, gelben Affen als tragbaren Gegenstand und einen Affen, der sich als Kopfschmuck am Kopf festhält.\n
Dieses Set enthält folgenden tragbaren Gegenstand und folgende Gegenstände für das Anpassen deines Avatars:\n\n
・Auf dem Kopf sitzender, gelber Affe (Kopfschmuck, Herren)\n
・Auf dem Kopf sitzender, gelber Affe (Kopfschmuck, Damen)\n
・Fröhlicher gelber Affe (tragbarer Gegenstand)\n\n
*Beim Kauf wird der tragbare Gegenstand und jeder Gegenstand zum Anpassen des Avatars der entsprechenden Kategorie im Kleiderschrank zugeordnet. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set che contiene una piccola scimmia gialla come oggetto portatile e una scimmia aggrappata alla testa come accessorio.\n
Il set contiene il seguente oggetto portatile e le seguenti personalizzazioni.\n\n
・Copricapo scimmia gialla (accessorio, uomo)\n
・Copricapo scimmia gialla (accessorio, donna)\n
・Vivace scimmia gialla (oggetto portatile)\n\n
*Quando viene acquistato, l'oggetto portatile viene aggiunto alla propria categoria e ogni oggetto per personalizzare l'avatar viene aggiunto nell'apposita categoria del tuo Abbigliamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Un conjunto que incluye un monito amarillo como objeto portátil y un mono aferrado a la cabeza como complemento.\n
Contiene el siguiente objeto portátil, así como los siguientes elementos de personalización de avatar:\n\n
・Mono amarillo aferrado a la cabeza (complemento para la cabeza, hombre)\n
・Mono amarillo aferrado a la cabeza (complemento para la cabeza, mujer)\n
・Mono amarillo alegre (objeto portátil)\n\n
*Al comprarlo, tanto el objeto portátil como los elementos de personalización de avatar se añaden a su categoría correspondiente del Vestuario. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">黄色い毛の小さなサルのポータブルアイテムと、サルが頭にしがみついたヘッドアクセサリーのセットです。本セットには、ポータブルアイテムとアバターカスタマイズ用の下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・頭にしがみついた黄色い毛のサル（ヘッドアクセサリー/男性）\n・頭にしがみついた黄色い毛のサル（ヘッドアクセサリー/女性）\n・陽気な黄色い毛のサル（ポータブルアイテム）\n\n※購入すると、ポータブルアイテムと「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">포터블 아이템인 노란 털의 작은 원숭이와 원숭이가 머리에 달라붙은 머리 액세서리의 세트입니다. 본 세트에는 포터블 아이템과 아바타 꾸미기용의 하기 아이템이 포함되어 있습니다\n\n
●머리에 달라붙은 노란 털의 원숭이(남성)(머리 액세서리）\n
●머리에 달라붙은 노란 털의 원숭이(여성)(머리 액세서리)\n
●활발한 노란 털의 원숭이(포터블 아이템）\n\n
※구입하면 포터블 아이템과 「아바타 꾸미기」내의 해당 카테고리에 각 아이템이 추가됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">A set that contains a small, yellow monkey as a portable item and a monkey clinging to your head as a head accessory.\n
This set contains the following portable item and avatar customizing items.\n\n
・Head-clinging Yellow Monkey (Head Accessory, Men)\n
・Head-clinging Yellow Monkey (Head Accessory, Women)\n
・Cheerful Yellow Monkey (Portable Item)\n\n
*When purchased, the portable item is added to the appropriate category and  each avatar customizing item is added to the appropriate category in your "Avatar Customization" screen.  [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">本組合包包括黃色小猴的隨身道具及騎在頭上的猴子頭飾。本組合包包括以下道具，可用來自訂隨身道具及個人造型。\n\n
●騎在頭上的黃色猴子（男用）（頭部配件）\n
●騎在頭上的黃色猴子（女用）（頭部配件）\n
●開朗的黃色猴子(隨身道具)\n\n
※購買後，各道具會被追加至隨身道具及「前往衣帽間」的對應類別中。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">本組合包包括黃色小猴的隨身道具及騎在頭上的猴子頭飾。本組合包包括以下道具，可用來自訂隨身道具及個人造型。\n\n
●騎在頭上的黃色猴子（男用）（頭部配件）\n
●騎在頭上的黃色猴子（女用）（頭部配件）\n
●開朗的黃色猴子(隨身道具)\n\n
※購買後，各道具會被追加至隨身道具及「前往更衣室」的對應類別中。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A set that contains a small, yellow monkey as a portable item and a monkey clinging to your head as a head accessory.\n
This set contains the following portable item and avatar customising items.\n\n
・Head-clinging Yellow Monkey (Head Accessory, Men)\n
・Head-clinging Yellow Monkey (Head Accessory, Women)\n
・Cheerful Yellow Monkey (Portable Item)\n\n
*When purchased, the portable item is added to the appropriate category and  each avatar customising item is added to the appropriate category in your wardrobe.  [#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
