<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Brigitte - Brimstone Dancer Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Brigitte - Souffre Danseuse Ensemble</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Brigitte - Zitronenfalter Tänzerin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Brigitte - Zolfo Ballerino</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Brigitte - Bailarina Azufre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Brigitte - Brimstone Dancer Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Meet Brigitte, female Guardian of Graves.  Her dance moves captivate all.  Brigitte will put a hex on you because when she dances, you can’t take your eyes off her.  Put this full sized…"active object" in your personal space and show her miniature version around Home as a dancing companion.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rencontre Brigitte, la femme gardienne des tombes. Sa danse captivera tous. Brigitte va jeter un sort sur vous parce que quand elle danse, vous ne pouvez pas arrêter de la regarder dans ses yeux. Mettez cette pleine grandeur... "objet actif" dans votre espace personnel et montrez sa version miniature autour de Home comme un compagnon de danse. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Treffen Brigitte, weiblich Vormund von Graben. Ihre tanzschritte bestechen alle. Brigitte wird ein hex auf sie gesetzt, weil, wenn sie tanzt, sie nicht an Ihr aus den augen. Setzen sie diese in voller größe ... "aktives objekt" in ihrem persönlichen bereich und zeigen ihre miniaturausgabe um Home wie ein tanzender begleiter. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Incontra Brigitte, Guardiano femminile di Graves. I suoi passi di danza affascina tutti. Brigitte sarà fatto un incantesimo su di voi perché quando lei balla, non si può staccare lo sguardo di lei. Metti questa full size... "oggetto attivo" nel tuo spazio personale e mostrare la sua versione in miniatura in giro per Home come un compagno di ballo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conoce a Brigitte, mujeres Guardián de Graves. Sus movimientos de baile cautivar a todos. Brigitte le hace un hechizo en ti, porque cuando ella baila, no se puede quitar la vista de ella. Añadir este tamaño completo ... "objeto activo" en su espacio personal y mostrar su versión en miniatura alrededor de Home como un compañero de baile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Meet Brigitte, female Guardian of Graves.  Her dance moves captivate all.  Brigitte will put a hex on you because when she dances, you can’t take your eyes off her.  Put this full sized…"active object" in your personal space and show her miniature version around Home as a dancing companion.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>