<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Audi R15 TDI - Le Mans 2010 - (1)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Audi R15 TDI - Le Mans 2010 - (1)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Audi R15 TDI - Le Mans 2010 - (1)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Audi R15 TDI - Le Mans 2010 - (1)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Audi R15 TDI - Le Mans 2010 - (1)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">On Sunday 13th June, after winning in 2000, 2002 and 2004, Audi managed to achieve a one-two-three triumph at Le Mans for the fourth time.  The winning car broke the record for the furthest distance travelled set back in 1971.  For Audi, Le Mans is more than simply a race. It’s also the perfect opportunity to test Audi's latest innovations in the most extreme conditions. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le dimanche 13 Juin, après avoir remporté en 2000, 2002 et 2004, Audi a réussi à atteindre un triomphe un-deux-trois au Mans pour la quatrième fois. La voiture gagnante a battu le record de la plus longue distance parcourue en retrait en 1971. Pour Audi, Le Mans est plus qu'une simple course. C'est aussi l'occasion idéale de tester les dernières innovations d'Audi dans les conditions les plus extrêmes.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Am Sonntag den 13. Juni gelang Audi nach 2000, 2002 und 2004 in LeMans zum vierten Mal ein Dreifachtriumph. Mit der zurückgelegten Distanz von 5.410 Kilometern brach der Audi R15 TDI  mit Timo Bernhard (Deutschland), Romain Dumas (Frankreich) und Mike Rockenfeller (Deutschland) dabei ausserdem den aus dem Jahr 1971 stammenden Rekord für die längste gefahrene Strecke. Le Mans ist für Audi mehr als nur ein Rennen. Es ist auch die perfekte Möglichkeit für Audi seine neuesten Innovation in einer der schwierigsten Situationen zu testen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Domenica 13 giugno, dopo aver vinto nel 2000, 2002 e 2004, Audi è riuscita a realizzare una relazione uno-due-tre trionfo a Le Mans per la quarta volta. La vettura vincitrice ha battuto il record per il più lontano distanza percorsa in arretrato 1971. Per la Audi, Le Mans è più di una semplice gara. E 'anche l'occasione perfetta per testare Audi più recenti innovazioni nelle condizioni più estreme. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El domingo 13 de junio, después de ganar en 2000, 2002 y 2004, Audi conseguido un triunfo uno-dos-tres en Le Mans por cuarta vez. El coche ganador rompió el récord de mayor distancia recorrida establecido en 1971. Para Audi, Le Mans es más que una simple carrera. También es la oportunidad perfecta para probar las últimas innovaciones de Audi en las condiciones más extremas. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>