<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Lilith - Brimstone Dancer Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lilith - Souffre Danseuse Ensemble</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lilith - Zitronenfalter Tänzerin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lilith - Zolfo Ballerino</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lilith - Bailarina Azufre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Lilith - Brimstone Dancer Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">According to legends, Lilith was turned into a demon for refusing to obey so don't try to tame this wild animal.  Lilith means "belonging to the night" and that's just when she's at her finest. Put this full sized…"active object" in your personal space and show her miniature version around Home as a dancing companion.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Selon les légendes, Lilith a été transformé en un démon parce que elle a refusé d'obéir, alors n'essayez pas d'apprivoiser cet animal sauvage. Lilith signifie "appartenant à la nuit" et celui-la est quand elle est à son meilleur. Mettez cette pleine grandeur... "objet actif" dans votre espace personnel et montrer sa version miniature autour de Home comme un compagnon de danse. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der legende nach war Lilith in einen dämon für die ablehnung der so gehorchen nicht versuchen, dieses wilde tier zu zähmen gedreht. Lilith bedeutet "aus der nacht " und das ist nur, wenn sie bei ihrer besten freunde.  Setzen sie diese in voller größe ... "aktives objekt" in Ihrem persönlichen bereich und zeigen ihre miniaturausgabe um Home wie ein tanzender begleiter.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Secondo le leggende, Lilith è stato trasformato in un demone per essersi rifiutato di obbedire, quindi non provare a domare questo animale selvatico. Lilith significa "appartenente alla notte", e che solo quando lei è al suo culmine. Metti questa full size ... "oggetto attivo" nel tuo spazio personale e mostrare la sua versione in miniatura in giro per Home come un compagno di ballo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Según las leyendas, Lilith se convirtió en un demonio por negarse a obedecer lo que no se trata de domar este animal salvaje. Lilith significa "perteneciente a la noche" y eso es sólo cuando está en su mejor. Añadir este tamaño completo ... "objeto activo" en su espacio personal y mostrar su versión en miniatura alrededor de Home como un compañero de baile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">According to legends, Lilith was turned into a demon for refusing to obey so don't try to tame this wild animal.  Lilith means "belonging to the night" and that's just when she's at her finest. Put this full sized…"active object" in your personal space and show her miniature version around Home as a dancing companion.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>