<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Shimmer Sphere</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La boule scintillante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Glanzkugel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sfera scintillante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La esfera resplandeciente</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スーパーミラーボール</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">반짝이 구체</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Shimmer Sphere</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">閃亮舞台鏡球</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">閃亮舞台鏡球</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Shimmer Sphere</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This fantastic active item will have all of your friends begging for an invite to your party. Marvel at the ever changing neon flooring, boogie around the dance pole and be in awe of the animated disco ball that sends specks of psychedelic light all around your apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avec ce formidable objet d’archive, vos amis vous supplieront de les inviter à vos fêtes. Admirez les changements incessants du plancher en néon, déhanchez-vous autour de la barre de danse et émerveillez-vous devant la boule à facettes inondant votre appartement de lumière psychédélique. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser fantastische Aktivgegenstand wird dafür sorgen, dass alle deine Freunde dich um eine Einladung zu deiner Party anbetteln werden. Bewundere die immer wieder wechselnden Neonfarben des Bodens, tanze um die Tanzstange und bestaune die animierte Discokugel, die psychedelisches Licht in deinem Apartment verbreitet. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo fantastico oggetto attivo farà sì che tutti i tuoi amici vorranno essere invitati alla tua festa. Ammira il pavimento cangiante, scatenati attorno al palo da discoteca e venera la sfera disco che spara luci psichedeliche nel tuo appartamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este objeto activo fantástico hará que tus amigos te supliquen que los invites a tu fiesta. Maravíllalos con el suelo de neón variable, baila el boogie alrededor de la barra asómbralos con la bola de discoteca animada que llenará el apartamento de lucecitas psicodélicas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このファンタスティックなアイテムがあれば、フレンドみんながあなたのパーティに絶対参加したいと頼み込んでくるでしょう。色鮮やかに変化していくフロアやダンスポールに驚嘆。生命を吹きこまれたかのようなディスコボールに驚愕。あなたの家をサイケデリックな光で飾り立てましょう。 \n※このアイテムは、アニメーションや機能が追加されているアドバンスド家具です。この種類のアイテムは配置できる数に制限があります。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 환상적인 액티브 아이템은 당신의 모든 친구들이 당신의 파티에 참석하고 싶어 안달나게 만들 것입니다. 시시각각 변하는 네온 바닥에 감탄하고, 댄스 폴을 돌며 춤을 추고, 아파트 전체에 몽환적인 빛의 입자를 뿌리는 움직이는 디스코 볼에 경외심을 가지세요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This fantastic active item will have all of your friends begging for an invite to your party. Marvel at the ever changing neon flooring, boogie around the dance pole and be in awe of the animated disco ball that sends specks of psychedelic light all around your apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這種夢幻般的動態道具會讓您所有的好友渴望受邀參加您的派對。不斷變化的霓虹地板讓您歎為觀止，環繞鋼管舒展舞姿，驚歎動感迪斯科球向公寓各個角落營造出微弱迷幻的燈光。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這種夢幻般的動態道具會讓您所有的好友渴望受邀參加您的派對。不斷變化的霓虹地板讓您歎為觀止，環繞鋼管舒展舞姿，驚歎動感迪斯科球向公寓各個角落營造出微弱迷幻的燈光。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This fantastic active item will have all of your friends begging for an invite to your party. Marvel at the ever changing neon flooring, boogie around the dance pole and be in awe of the animated disco ball that sends specks of psychedelic light all around your apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>