<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Locomotion - Zen Flight</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Transport - Vol Zen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bewegung – Zen-Flug</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Locomozione - Volo zen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Locomoción: vuelo zen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LMO-ゼンフライト</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">LMO - 선의 비행</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">LMO - Zen Flight</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">LMO - 禪意飛行</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">LMO - 禪意飛行</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Locomotion - Zen Flight</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Achieve Zen with this fantastic locomotion item. You will no longer walk or run, you will float in the air in the lotus position. You can also travel faster than the normal run, simply by holding the square button. Just because you have achieved spiritual enlightenment, does not mean that you do not have places to go in a hurry. Speed: ◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆ 
LMO (Locomotion) is a Portable item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Devenez zen grâce à ce formidable objet de transport. Plus besoin de courir ni de marcher, flottez simplement en position du lotus. Vous voyagerez aussi bien plus vite que la normale en maintenant simplement la touche carré. Ce n’est pas parce que votre esprit est illuminé que vous n’êtes pas pressé. Vitesse : ◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆ LMO (Transport) est un objet portable. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erlange das Zen mit diesem fantastischen Fortbewegungsmittel. Du läufst oder rennst nicht mehr, sondern schwebst in der Lotus-Position in der Luft. Du kannst dich auch schneller bewegen als beim normalen Rennen, indem du einfach die Quadrat-Taste gedrückt hältst. Nur weil du die spirituelle Erleuchtung erlangt hast, heißt das nicht, dass du nicht an Orte eilen musst. Geschwindigkeit: ◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆ Das Fortbewegungsmittel ist ein portabler Gegenstand. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Raggiungi lo zen con questo fantastico oggetto di locomozione. Invece di camminare o correre, fluttuerai nell'aria nella posizione del loto. Tenendo premuto il tasto quadrato potrai anche muoverti più velocemente rispetto a una corsa normale. Solo perché hai raggiunto l'illuminazione spirituale, non vuol dire che non vai mai di fretta. Velocità: ◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆ LMO (locomozione) è un oggetto portatile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Alcanza el zen con este extraordinario artículo de locomoción. Ya no caminarás ni correrás, sino que flotarás en el aire en la posición de Lotus. También podrás viajar más rápido de lo normal si mantienes pulsado el botón cuadrado. Solo porque hayas alcanzado la iluminación espiritual, no significa que no tengas prisa por llegar a según qué sitios. Velocidad: ◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆. LMO (locomoción) es un artículo portátil. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このアイテムで禅を極めましょう。もはや歩く必要も走る必要もありません。座禅を組んで空中に浮かぶのです。悟りを開いたからといって、目的地に急がなくていいわけではありませんからね。\n\n※このアイテムを装備する事で、移動スピードがアップします。移動中に□ボタンを押す事で、さらに早く移動できるようになります。\n移動速度アップ：◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆\n LMO（ロコモーション）はポータブルアイテムです。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 환상적인 로코모션 아이템으로 선의 경지에 도달하세요. 더 이상 걷거나 뛰지 않고 가부좌 자세로 하늘을 떠다니게 됩니다. 네모 버튼만 누르고 있으면 보통 달리기보다 훨씬 더 빨리 이동할 수 있습니다. 영적인 깨달음을 얻었다고 해서 어딘가를 갈 때 항상 느긋하게 갈 필요는 없습니다. 이동속도: ◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆\n
※이 아이템은 휴대 아이템입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Achieve Zen with this fantastic locomotion item. You will no longer walk or run, you will float in the air in the lotus position. You can also travel faster than the normal run, simply by holding the square button. Just because you have achieved spiritual enlightenment, does not mean that you do not have places to go in a hurry. Speed: ◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆ 
LMO (Locomotion) is a Portable item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">使用該神奇的Locomotion物品實現禪宗。不要走路或跑步，只用打坐即可漂浮在空中。您只需按住方塊按鈕，即可大大提高運行速度。由於得到了心靈啟蒙，您去哪裡都不用慌慌張張。 移動速度：◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆\n
※本道具是一款隨身道具。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">使用該神奇的Locomotion物品實現禪宗。不要走路或跑步，只用打坐即可漂浮在空中。您只需按住方塊按鈕，即可大大提高運行速度。由於得到了心靈啟蒙，您去哪裡都不用慌慌張張。 移動速度：◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆\n
※本道具是一款隨身道具。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Achieve Zen with this fantastic locomotion item. You will no longer walk or run, you will float in the air in the lotus position. You can also travel faster than the normal run, simply by holding the square button. Just because you have achieved spiritual enlightenment, does not mean that you do not have places to go in a hurry. Speed: ◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆ 
LMO (Locomotion) is a Portable item. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>