<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Black Naveen Dress Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Panoplie Dress Noir Naveen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schwarz Anzung Naveen Bündel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Nero di Naveen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lote Negro de Naveen</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Occasions Collection brings you style, elegance and class, all wrapped up in the perfect outfit to wear to any of life's big occasions.  Go for the full, colour block look or mix and match for a touch of individuality.Make an impression, whatever the occasion! This bundle contains: Black Naveen Earrings, Black Naveen Flower Fascinator, Black Naveen Shoes, Black Corsage and Chain Ring and Black Naveen Dress [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La Collection Occasions vous apporte style, élégance et classe grâce à la tenue parfaite à porter pour fêter tous les grands moments de votre vie. Optez pour un ensemble coloré ou mélangez le tout selon vos envies pour une touche plus personnelle.Ne passez plus jamais inaperçu, quelle que soit l’occasion ! Ce bundle contient: Boucles d'oreille Noir, Accessoire Noir Naveen, Chaussures Noir Naveen, Bracelet Noir avec Anneau et Dress Noir Naveen [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Anlass-Kollektion bringt Ihnen Stil, Eleganz und Klasse, alles in einer perfekten Ausstattung, die man zu jedem großen Anlass im Leben tragen kann. Entschließen Sie sich für den vollständigen, einfarbigen Look oder mischen und stellen Sie sie für Ihren individuellen Touch zusammen.Machen Sie Eindruck, zu jedem Anlass! Dieses Bundle enthält: Schwarz Ohrringe Naveen, Schwarz Zubehörteil, Schwarz Schuhe Naveen, Schwarz Ring Armband und Schwarz Anzung Naveen [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Collezione Occasioni ti regala stile, eleganza e classe, il tutto combinato nell'abito perfetto da indossare in tutti i grandi momenti della tua vita. Scegli un look a tinta unita o mescola i colori per un tocco più personale.Fai sempre una buona impressione, qualunque sia l'occasione! Questo pacchetto contiene: Orecchini Nero di Naveen, Accessori Nero di Naveen, Scarpe Nero di Naveen, Bracciale Nero di Naveen e Vestito Nero di Naveen [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La Collección Ocasiones te trae el estilo, la elegancia y la clase combinadas en el vestuario idóneo para las grandes ocasiones. Elige prendas lisas o multicolores, combínalas para dar un toque de individualidad o conjúntalas. ¡Causa una buena impresión sea cual sea la ocasión! Este lote contiene: Pendientes Negros de Naveen, Accesorio Negro de Naveen, Zapatos Negros de Naveen, Pulsera Negra con Anillo y Vestido Negro de Naveen[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>

