<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LOOT™ Night Talk Show Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot Talk Show LOOT™ Nuit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LOOT™ Night Talk Show Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Notturno LOOT™ - Completo Talk Show Notturno</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto Programa LOOT™ Noche</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LOOT™ナイト トーク・ショー パック</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LOOT™ Night Talk Show Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Who needs a public access channel? Get your late night talk show career started now with the LOOT™ Night Talk Show Set for the LOOT™ Stage Set Personal Space. Purchasing this stellar bundle is the only way to get the LOOT™ Night Microphone. Start talking, LOOTers! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Qui a besoin d'un canal communautaire ? Lancez votre carrière d'animateur de talk show avec le lot Talk Show LOOT™ Nuit pour votre espace personnel Décor de plateau LOOT™. L'achat de ce lot épatant est la seule façon d'obtenir le Micro LOOT™ Nuit. Allez-y, parlez, LOOTers ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer braucht schon einen öffentlichen Fernsehkanal? Started eure Karirere in Late Night Shows jetzt mit dem LOOT™ Night Talk Show Set für den persönlichen Raum des LOOT™ Stage Set. Nur mit diesem himmlischen Bundle kommt ihr an das LOOT™ Night Microphone. Redet, LOOTers! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">A chi serve una rete televisiva pubblica? Inizia la tua carriera di presentatore di talk show notturni con il Completo Talk Show Notturni per il tuo spazio personale Scenografia LOOT™.  Acquistare questo strepitoso Completo è l'unico modo per ottenere il Microfono della serie Notturno LOOT™. Iniziate a parlare, appassionati di LOOT™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Quién necesita un canal de acceso público? ¡Que empiece tu carrera en un programa nocturno con el conjunto de LOOT™ Programa de Noche para personalizar el estudio de LOOT™. ¡Comprar este conjunto estelar es la unica manera de conseguir el Micrófono de LOOT™ Noche! ¡Empezad a hablar, LOOTers! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">本コンテンツは、パーソナルスペース「LOOT™スタジオ・ステージ・セット・バンドル」用にカスタマイズされております。このため、本コンテンツに含まれるアイテムの一部は、パーソナルスペース「ベーシック」などの天井の低いプライベートラウンジ（パーソナルスペース/クラブハウス）において、正常に設置できない場合があります。予めご了承ください。\n\n
くだらないテレビなんてもういらない！LOOT™ナイト トーク・ショー パックでレイトナイト トーク・ショーをはじめましょう！\n本コンテンツには、プライベートラウンジのカスタマイズ用の以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n\n
・「LOOT™ナイト – ゲスト・チェア」（チェア）\n
・「LOOT™ナイト - デスク」（テーブル）\n
・「LOOT™ナイト – ホスト・チェア」（チェア）\n
・「LOOT™ナイト - マイク」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT™ナイト - 都市の景観A」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT™ナイト - 都市の景観B」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT™ナイト - 都市の景観C」（装飾品）\n\n
※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。
 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Who needs a public access channel? Get your late night talk show career started now with the LOOT™ Night Talk Show Set for the LOOT™ Stage Set Personal Space. Purchasing this stellar bundle is the only way to get the LOOT™ Night Microphone. Start talking, LOOTers! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>