<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Dream Yacht</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Yacht de Rêve</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Traumyacht</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dream Yacht</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Yate de ensueño</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドリーム・ヨット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">드림 요트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Dream Yacht</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">夢幻遊艇</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">夢幻遊艇</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Dream Yacht</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Have the lifestyle you always dreamed of with the Dream Yacht from Figment. Three decks of opulent living, two hot tubs and more than 20 collectable rewards, plus an exclusive commerce point only available through the Dream Yacht. Live the dream![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vivez comme vous l'avez toujours imaginé avec le Yacht de rêve de Figment. Trois ponts somptueux, deux jacuzzis et plus de 20 récompenses à collectionner, en plus d'un point de vente exclusif uniquement disponible sur le Yacht de Rêve. Vivez le rêve ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hol dir den Lifestyle deiner Träume mit der Traumyacht von Figment. Drei Decks opulenter Lebensraum, zwei Whirlpools und mehr als 20 Belohnungen zum Sammeln sowie ein exklusiver Handelspunkt, der nur durch die Traumyacht erhältlich ist. Lebe den Traum![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vivi la vita che hai sempre sognato con Dream Yacht di Figment. Tre ponti di vita opulenta, due vasche riscaldate e più di 20 premi collezionabile, più un esclusivo punto vendita disponibile solo con Dream Yacht. Vivi il sogno![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Disfruta del estilo de vida con el que siempre has soñado en el yate de ensueño de Figment. Tres cubiertas de vida opulenta, dos jacuzzis y más de 20 premios coleccionables, además de un exclusivo punto de venta solo disponible en el yate de ensueño. ¡Vive el sueño![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">夢のようなライフスタイルをおくりましょう。甲板がみっつに分かれており、２つのジャグジーを完備しております。夢を大事に！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">피그먼트의 드림 요트로 항상 꿈에 그리던 라이프스타일을  즐겨 보세요. 3개 층에서의 화려한 생활, 2개의 더운 물 욕조 및 20개 이상의 수집용 보상품, 그밖에도 독점적인 커머스 포인트를 오직 드림 요트를 통해서만 받을 수 있습니다. 당신의 꿈을 성취하세요![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Have the lifestyle you always dreamed of with the Dream Yacht from Figment. Three decks of opulent living, two hot tubs and more than 20 collectable rewards, plus an exclusive commerce point only available through the Dream Yacht. Live the dream![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Figment精心打造夢幻遊艇，讓你享受自由的夢幻生活。船上共有三層甲板，裝潢奢華，設有兩個浴缸，還有20多個讓你收集的寶物，加上夢幻遊艇專屬的Sodium商店。快來實現夢想吧！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Figment精心打造夢幻遊艇，讓你享受自由的夢幻生活。船上共有三層甲板，裝潢奢華，設有兩個浴缸，還有20多個讓你收集的寶物，加上夢幻遊艇專屬的Sodium商店。快來實現夢想吧！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Have the lifestyle you always dreamed of with the Dream Yacht from Figment. Three decks of opulent living, two hot tubs and more than 20 collectable rewards, plus an exclusive commerce point only available through the Dream Yacht. Live the dream![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>