<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Twingate Castle Mega Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Twingate Château Méga Lot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Twingate Schloss Mega-Bündel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Twingate Castello Mega Pacchetto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Twingate Castillo Megaconjunto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Twingate Castle Mega Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Including: Twingate Castle Apartment, 2 x Leather and Lace Shorts, 2 x Leather and Lace Top, 2 x Leather Gloves, 2 x Leather and Lace Boots and 2 x Hair (for her). 2 x Leather Trousers, 2 x Leather Top, 2 x Leather Boots and 2 x Hair (for him).[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Comprend: Twingate Château - Appartement, 2 x Short en Cuir et Dentelle, 2 x Haut en Cuir et Dentelle, 2 x Gants en Cuir et Dentelle, 2 x Cuissardes en Cuir et Dentelle et 2 x Coup de cheveux (pour elle).  2 x Pantalon en Cuir, 2 x Haut en Cuir, 2 x Bottes en Cuir et  2 x Coup de cheveux (pour lui).[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Einschließlich: Twingate Schloss - Wohnung, 2 x Leder- und Spitzen- Kurze Hosen, 2 x Leder- und Spitzen-Oberteil, 2 x Leder- und Spitzen-Handschuhe, 2 x Leder- und Spitzen-Enge Stiefel und 2 x Frisuren (für sie). 2 x Leder-Hose, 2 x Leder-Oberteil, 2 x Lederstiefel und 2 x Frisuren (für ihn).[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Comprende: Twingate Castello - Appartamento, 2 x Pantaloncini in Pelle e Pizzo, 2 x Top in Pelle e Pizzo, 2 x Guanti in Pelle e Pizzo, 2 x Stivali alti in Pelle e Pizzo e 2 x Capigliatura (per lei). 2 x Pantaloni in Pelle, 2 x Top in Pelle e Pizzo, 2 x Stivali in Pelle e 2 x Capigliatura (per lui) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Incluye:  Twingate Castillo - Apartamento, 2 x Pantalones cortos de Cuero con Encajes, 2 x Top de Cuero con Encajes, 2 x Guantes de Cuero con Encajes, 2 x Altas de Cuero con Encajes y 2 x Peinado (para ella). 2 x Pantalones de Cuero,  2x Top de Cuero con Encajes, 2 x Botas de Cuero y 2 x Peinado (para él).[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Including: Twingate Castle Apartment, 2 x Leather and Lace Shorts, 2 x Leather and Lace Top, 2 x Leather Gloves, 2 x Leather and Lace Boots and 2 x Hair (for her). 2 x Leather Trousers, 2 x Leather Top, 2 x Leather Boots and 2 x Hair (for him).[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>