<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Caserne S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">S.V.E.R.-Kaserne</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caserma S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Barracones de S.V.E.R</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">兵舎 セイバー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">S.V.E.R. 병영</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">SVER軍營</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">SVER軍營</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">S.V.E.R. Barracks</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Caserne S.V.E.R. - Votre petite escapade en Asie Centrale. Profitez de couchers de soleil époustouflants pour vous détendre sur un balcon spacieux, nettoyer votre arme et admirer les chasseurs zébrer le firmament. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">S.V.E.R.-Kaserne: Die S.V.E.R.-Kaserne ist Ihr privates Refugium im fernen Zentralasien. Es bietet einen fantastischen Blick auf den Sonnenuntergang, also entspannen Sie sich auf Ihrem großen Balkon, putzen Sie Ihre Waffe und beobachten Sie, wie die Jagdbomber über den sonnigen Himmel fliegen.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caserma S.V.E.R. - La caserma S.V.E.R. è la vostra destinazione privata nelle terre lontane dell'Asia Centrale. Vanta tramonti spettacolari da ammirare rilassandosi sul proprio balcone mentre si lucida il fucile e si osservano i caccia sorvolare il cielo azzurro e soleggiato.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Barracones de S.V.E.R. - Si quieres realizar una escapada a las aisladas zonas del centro de Asia, vente a los barracones de S.V.E.R. Las vistas de la puesta de sol son magníficas y puedes relajarte en el balcón, limpiar el rifle y ver cómo los aviones de guerra cruzan los anaranjados cielos.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">セイバーの兵舎　―　中央アジアの避暑地とも呼べる兵舎。壮観な夕日にリラックスできるバルコニー、天と地が交わるかのような幻想的な景色で疲れきった体を休めるには最適だ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">S.V.E.R. 병영 - S.V.E.R. 병영은 중앙아시아로 통하는 당신만의 통로입니다. 믿을 수 없을만큼 아름다운 노을을 감상하며, 발코니에서 총기를 손질하고 굉음과 함께 날아가는 요격기들이 태양 속으로 사라지는 것을 지켜 보세요.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">SVER軍營，SVER軍營是你通往遙遠的亞洲中部之私人通道。這裡有壯麗的日落景色，你可以在大型的露台上稍作休息、清潔一下機槍，並舉頭望著戰機在陽光親吻下的天堂中飛行。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">SVER軍營，SVER軍營是你通往遙遠的亞洲中部之私人通道。這裡有壯麗的日落景色，你可以在大型的露台上稍作休息、清潔一下機槍，並舉頭望著戰機在陽光親吻下的天堂中飛行。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">S.V.E.R. Barracks - The S.V.E.R. barracks is your private getaway to remote Central Asia.  It features a spectacular sunset view, so you can relax on your large balcony, clean your rifle and watch strike fighters fly through the sun kissed heavens.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>