<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Forefront DX Afterburners</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Postcombustion  Forefront DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Forefront DX-Nachbrenner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Postbruciatori Forefront DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Postquemadores Vanguardia DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Forefront DX アフターバーナー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Forefront DX 재점화 장치</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Forefront DX Afterburners</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Forefront DX  加力燃燒裝置</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Forefront DX  加力燃燒裝置</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Forefront DX Afterburners</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">With great power comes great instability. Leave your opponents standing but be careful that the reduced stability doesn’t slam you into a wall. That would be embarrassing. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une grande puissance implique une grande instabilité. Vous laisserez vos opposants sur place, mais attention à ne pas finir dans un mur à cause de la perte de stabilité. Ce serait plutôt ennuyeux. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Große Kraft bring große Instabilität mit sich. Lass die Konkurrenz hinter dir, aber pass auf, dass du durch die verringerte Stabilität nicht in eine Wand fliegst. Das wäre wirklich peinlich. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una maggior potenza comporta maggiore instabilità. Lascia sul posto i tuoi avversari ma fai attenzione a non schiantarti contro un muro a causa della ridotta stabilità: sarebbe davvero imbarazzante. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una gran potencia conlleva una gran inestabilidad. Deja atrás a tus contrincantes, pero cuidado, que la estabilidad reducida no te lleve a estamparte contra una pared. Sería humillante. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">大いなる力には大いなる不安定さが伴います。敵をビュンと追い越しても構いませんが、安定性が落ちていますので壁にぶち当たらないように注意してください。恥をかかないようにしましょうね。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">가속력과 동체의 불안정함은 정비례합니다. 경쟁자들을 멀찌감치 따돌리는 건 좋지만, 벽과 충돌하는 참사를 피하기 위해 많은 주의를 기울여야 합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">With great power comes great instability. Leave your opponents standing but be careful that the reduced stability doesn’t slam you into a wall. That would be embarrassing. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">龐大的能量會令飛行非常不穩定。遠遠拋離你的對手，但小心穩定性減低也不會導致你撞向牆壁，那是很尷尬的。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">龐大的能量會令飛行非常不穩定。遠遠拋離你的對手，但小心穩定性減低也不會導致你撞向牆壁，那是很尷尬的。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">With great power comes great instability. Leave your opponents standing but be careful that the reduced stability doesn’t slam you into a wall. That would be embarrassing. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>