<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stan the Salesman Suit Jacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Veste de Stan the Salesman</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stan, der Verkäufer, Jackett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Giacca completo Stan il Venditore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chaqueta de Traje de Stan the Salesman</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Stan the Salesman Suit Jacket</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">I am here to make YOU a deal. I want YOU to walk out of here happy. If you're not happy, I'm not happy! This jacket is all mine now, until someone makes me a good deal. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Je suis ici pour VOUS faire une proposition. Je veux que VOUS sortiez d'ici content. Si vous n'êtes pas content, je ne suis pas content ! Cette veste est à moi maintenant, sauf si quelqu'un me fait une proposition intéressante. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mein Ziel ist es, mit DIR ins Geschäft zu kommen. Ich will, dass DU diesen Ort glücklich verlässt. Bist du nicht glücklich, dann will ich es auch nicht sein! Dieses Jackett gehört noch mir allein, es sei denn, ich erhalte ein gutes Angebot dafür. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sono qui per farTI fare un affare. Voglio che TU esca felice da qui . Se tu non sei felice, non lo sono nemmeno io! Questa giacca ora è solo mia , fino a quando qualcuno non mi proporrà un buon affare. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estoy aquí para proponerte un trato. Quiero que salgas de aquí contento. ¡Si no estás contento, yo tampoco estoy contento! Ahora esta chaqueta es toda mía, hasta que alguien me proponga un buen trato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">I am here to make YOU a deal. I want YOU to walk out of here happy. If you're not happy, I'm not happy! This jacket is all mine now, until someone makes me a good deal. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>