<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rosy Angelic SpeedWings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">SpeedWings Angéliques Roses</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rosiger Engel SpeedWings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">SpeedWings angeliche rosate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">SpeedWings angélicas rosadas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Rosy Angelic SpeedWings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rosy Angelic SpeedWings</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blaze through your favorite places with SpeedWings!  Pull out these wings for a major speed boost with custom animations.  You can wear anything you want with SpeedWings, including shirts, gloves, or even full-transformation outfits!\n\nYour SpeedWings can be accessed from the personal inventory.  Once activated, the wings will appear on your avatar's back. The speed boost is engaged when the avatar is moving at its full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mettez le feu à vos endroits préférés avec les SpeedWings! Sortez ces ailes pour obtenir un boost de vitesse majeur avec des animations personnalisées. Vous pouvez porter ce que vous voulez avec les SpeedWings, y compris des gants, des T-shirts et même des tenues de transformation totale.\n\nVos SpeedWings sont accessibles depuis votre inventaire personnel. Une fois activées, les ailes apparaîtront sur le dos de votre avatar. Le boost de vitesse est activé quand l'avatar se déplace à sa vitesse maximale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Durchfliege deine Lieblingsplätze mit den SpeedWings!  Fahre diese Flügel für einen wesentlichen Geschwindigkeitsschub mit benutzerspezifischen Animationen aus. Der Geschwindigkeitsschub setzt automatisch ein, wenn der Avatar sich mit voller Geschwindigkeit bewegt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scorrazza nei luoghi che preferisci con le SpeedWings! Spiega queste ali per accelerare notevolmente con effetti animati personalizzati. Puoi indossare gli abiti che preferisci con le SpeedWings: camicie, guanti, e addirittura completi per la trasformazione totale!/n/nPuoi accedere alle tue SpeedWings dal tuo inventario personale. Una volta attivate, queste compariranno sulla schiena del tuo avatar. Potrai dare una spinta di accelerazione quando l'avatar avrà raggiunto la massima velocità. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Resplandece a través de tus lugares favoritos con SpeedWings! Saca estas alas para un gran incremento de velocidad y animaciones personalizadas. ¡Puedes vestir lo que quieras con SpeedWings, incluyendo camisas, guantes o incluso trajes de transformación completa!/n/nTus SpeedWings pueden ser accedidas desde el inventario personal. Una vez activadas, las alas aparecerán en la espalda de tu avatar. El turbo se activa cuando el avatar se mueve a su velocidad de carrera completa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Blaze through your favorite places with SpeedWings!  Pull out these wings for a major speed boost with custom animations.  You can wear anything you want with SpeedWings, including shirts, gloves, or even full-transformation outfits!\n\nYour SpeedWings can be accessed from the personal inventory.  Once activated, the wings will appear on your avatar's back. The speed boost is engaged when the avatar is moving at its full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blaze through your favorite places with SpeedWings!  Pull out these wings for a major speed boost with custom animations.  You can wear anything you want with SpeedWings, including shirts, gloves, or even full-transformation outfits!\n\nYour SpeedWings can be accessed from the personal inventory.  Once activated, the wings will appear on your avatar's back. The speed boost is engaged when the avatar is moving at its full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>