<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LMO-Xi: Continuum Code Flight</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Envol du code de LMO-Xi: Continuum</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LMO-Xi: Continuum Code-Flug</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">LMO-Xi: Continuum - Codice di volo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LMO-Xi: Continuum: código de vuelo</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Continuum code has fused with your body to gift you the power of flight! This is a reward for playing Xi: Continuum Day 0. By holding the square button you will fly through the air faster than the normal run. \n
Speed: ◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆ \n
LMO (Locomotion) is a Portable item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le code du Continuum et votre corps ont fusionné, vous dotant du pouvoir de voler ! C'est une récompense pour avoir joué le Jour 0 de Xi:Continuum. En maintenant le bouton carré appuyé, vous volerez dans les airs plus rapidement qu'en courant normalement. \n
Vitesse : ◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆ \n
LMO (Locomotion) est un objet portable. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Continuum-Code verbindet sich mit deinem Körper und verleiht ihm Flügel! Dies ist eine Belohnung für das Spielen von Xi: Continuum Tag 0. Drücke die Quadrat-Taste, um schneller durch die Luft zu fliegen. \n
Geschwindigkeit: ◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆  \n
Das Fortbewegungsmittel ist ein portabler Gegenstand. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il codice del Continuum si è fuso con il tuo corpo donandoti la capacità di volare! Questo è un premio per aver superato il Giorno 0 di Xi: Continuum. Tenendo premuto il tasto quadrato ti muoverai in aria più velocemente rispetto alla corsa normale. \n
Velocità: ◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆ \n
LMO (Locomozione) è un oggetto trasportabile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡El código del Continuum se ha fusionado con tu cuerpo y te ha otorgado el poder de volar! Es una recompense por haber jugado a Xi: Continuum, Día 0. Cuando pulses el botón cuadrado, volarás por el aire aún más rápido de lo normal. \n
Velocidad: ◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆ \n
LMO (Locomoción) es un artículo portátil. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>