<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Avedic Kitchen - Corner Unit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avedic Cuisine – meuble d’angle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Avedic Küche - Eckschrank</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Avedic Cucina – Unità angolare</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Avedic Cocina – Unidad de esquina</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Avedic Kitchen - Corner Unit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LIVING launches as a luxury furniture brand with this modular kitchen.  Designed in base and wall unit sections, they will fit into almost any position in any order.  They certainly will add that touch of top class quality.  Whatever your preferred style, LIVING will provide the answer to your catering needs with these marvellous modular kitchens; remember..Fashion passes, style remains, LIVING is the key! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">LIVING, marque de meubles haut de gamme, sort cette toute nouvelle cuisine fonctionnelle. Déclinée en éléments bas et muraux, elle s’adaptera à toutes les pièces et à toutes les envies. Les éléments proposés sont de la plus belle qualité. Quelles que soient vos préférences, LIVING s’imposera comme une évidence en matière de cuisine modulable et fonctionnelle. N’oubliez jamais : la mode passe, le style reste, et LIVING en est la preuve! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LIVING startet mit dieser modularen Küche als eine luxuriöse Möbelmarke. Entworfen als Stand- und Hängeeinheiten, werden sie überall und in jeglicher Anordnung passen. Sie fügen sicherlich auch einen Hauch von erstklassiger Qualität hinzu. Wie auch immer Ihr bevorzugter Stil sein mag, LIVING liefert mit diesen fabelhaften modularen Küchen die Antwort auf Ihre Kochbedürfnisse; denken Sie daran ...Mode vergeht, Stil bleibt, LIVING ist der Schlüssel[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">LIVING presenta un nuovo marchio di arredi di lusso con questa cucina modulare. Le unità base e pensili che la compongono si adattano a qualunque situazione e combinazione e aggiungeranno quel tocco di classe che fa la differenza. Qualunque sia il vostro stile, LIVING è in grado di rispondere alle vostre necessità grazie a queste meravigliose cucine modulari. Ricordate... le mode passano, lo stile resta, LIVING è la risposta! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LIVING se abre paso como marca de muebles de lujo con esta cocina modular diseñada con secciones unitarias de base y pared, que encajan en casi cualquier posición y orden, y que sin duda añaden ese toque de distinción de la clase alta. Sea cual sea tu estilo, LIVING será la solución a tus necesidades de catering con estas magníficas cocinas modulares. Recuerda: La moda pasa, pero el estilo permanece. ¡LIVING ES LA RESPUESTA! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LIVING launches as a luxury furniture brand with this modular kitchen.  Designed in base and wall unit sections, they will fit into almost any position in any order.  They certainly will add that touch of top class quality.  Whatever your preferred style, LIVING will provide the answer to your catering needs with these marvellous modular kitchens; remember..Fashion passes, style remains, LIVING is the key! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>