<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Elvish Fantasy Bundle (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack elfique (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Elfenfantasie - Paket (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completo elfo fantasy (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de fantasía élfica (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">판타지 엘프 세트 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Elvish Fantasy Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">小精靈夢幻服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">小精靈夢幻服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Elvish Fantasy Bundle (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Suit up in this devilish looking piece of armour. Bundle includes a helmet, top, bottom, boots, and a pair of gauntlets. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette armure vous donnera un look diabolique. Le pack contient un casque, un haut et un bas de vêtement, des bottes et une paire de gantelets. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine teuflisch gut aussehende Rüstung. Zum Paket gehören Helm, Oberteil, Unterteil, Stiefel und ein Paar Stulpenhandschuhe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un'armatura fantastica che include elmo, parte superiore, parte inferiore, stivali e un paio di guanti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Vístete con una armadura de aspecto diabólico. El conjunto incluye: tocado, top, perneras, botas y guanteletes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">화려한 판타지 갑옷을 입고 활보하십시오. 이 세트는 판타지 엘프 헬멧, 판타지 엘프 상의, 판타지 엘프 하의, 판타지 엘프 부츠, 그리고 판타지 엘프 장갑을 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Suit up in this devilish looking piece of armor. Bundle includes the Elvish Fantasy helmet, Elvish Fantasy Top, Elvish Fantasy Bottom, Elvish Fantasy Boots, and a pair of Elvish Fantasy Gauntlets. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">穿上這套邪惡風格的盔甲。組合包包括小精靈夢幻頭盔、小精靈夢幻服裝-上身、小精靈夢幻服裝-下身、小精靈夢幻靴及一對小精靈夢幻護手。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">穿上這套邪惡風格的盔甲。組合包包括小精靈夢幻頭盔、小精靈夢幻服裝-上半身、小精靈夢幻服裝-下半身、小精靈夢幻靴及一對小精靈夢幻護手。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Suit up in this devilish looking piece of armor. Bundle includes a helmet, top, bottom, boots, and a pair of gauntlets. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>