<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Storm of the North - Direwolves - Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tempête du nord - Loups terribles - Lot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Storm of the North - Dire-Wolf - Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tempesta del Nord - Meta-lupi - Set</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tormenta del Norte - Lobo Terrible - Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Be part of the pack with this Direwolves Bundle.\n
\n
This bundle contains:\n
(1) Storm of the North - Direwolf Companion - White\n
(2) Storm of the North - Direwolf Companion - Grey\n
(3) Storm of the North - Direwolf Companion - Copper\n
(4) Storm of the North - Direwolf Companion - Scarface [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Faites partie de la meute avec ce lot Loups terribles.\n
\n
Ce lot contient :\n
(1) Tempête du nord - Compagnon loup terrible - Blanc\n
(2) Tempête du nord - Compagnon loup terrible - Gris\n
(3) Tempête du nord - Compagnon loup terrible - Cuivre\n
(4) Tempête du nord - Compagnon loup terrible - Scarface [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Laufen Sie mit dem Rudel - mit diesem Dire-Wolf Paket.\n
\n
Dieses Bündel enthält:\n
(1) Storm of the North - Dire-Wolf als Gefährte - Weiß\n
(2) Storm of the North - Dire-Wolf als Gefährte - Grau\n
(3) Storm of the North - Dire-Wolf als Gefährte - Kupferrot\n
(4) Storm of the North - Dire-Wolf als Gefährte - Narbengesicht [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Unisciti al branco con questo Set Meta-lupi.\n
\n
Il set comprende:\n
() Tempesta del Nord - Compagno Meta-lupo - Bianco
() Tempesta del Nord - Compagno Meta-lupo - Grigio
() Tempesta del Nord - Compagno Meta-lupo - Rame
() Tempesta del Nord - Compagno Meta-lupo - Scarface [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Forma parte de manada con este Pack de Lobo Terrible.\n
\n
Este pack contiene:\n
(1) Tormenta del Norte - Compañero Lobo Terrible - Blanco\n
(2) Tormenta del Norte - Compañero Lobo Terrible - Gris\n
(3) Tormenta del Norte - Compañero Lobo Terrible - Cobre\n
(4) Tormenta del Norte - Compañero Lobo Terrible - Cara Cortada [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>