<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Centre Sodium</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sodium Hub</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Centro Sodium</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Centro de Sodium</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sodium Hub</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sodium fait son arrivée dans votre monde ! Bienvenue au cœur du divertissement du futur dans un monde en évolution constante construit sur la créativité et la joie. Explorez les mini-jeux, les activités sociales populaires et un méta-jeu passionnant associé à des objectifs de communauté. Il y en a pour tous les goûts.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sodium ist in deiner Wirklichkeit angekommen! Willkommen im Unterhaltungszentrum der Zukunft – einer sich ständig weiterentwickelnden Welt voll Kreativität und Spannung.  Minispiele-Präsentation, beliebte soziale Aktivitäten und süchtige machende Metaspiele mit Community-Zielen – für jeden ist etwas dabei.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sodium è arrivato nella tua realtà! Benvenuto al cuore dell'intrattenimento del futuro – un mondo in evoluzione costante e incentrato su creatività ed emozione. Minigiochi, attività sociali e meta-giochi coinvolgenti con obiettivi per la community – ce n'è per tutti.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Sodium ha llegado a tu realidad! Bienvenido al centro de entretenimiento del futuro: un mundo en constante evolución creado alrededor de la creatividad y la emoción. Aquí encontrarás minijuegos, actividades sociales populares, y otras actividades con objetivos comunitarios; siempre hay algo para todos los gustos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sodium has arrived in your reality! Welcome to the entertainment hub of the future – an ever-evolving world built around creativity and excitement. Showcase mini games, popular social activities, and addictive meta-gaming with community objectives – there’s something for everyone.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>