<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">8 Hex Tokens</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">8 Hex jetons</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">8 Hex-Token</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">8 Hex gettoni </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">8 Hex fichas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">8進数のトークン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">8 Hex Tokens</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">8 Hex Tokens</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">8 Hex Tokens</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">8 Hex Tokens</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">8 Hex Tokens</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use Hex tokens to buy tiles for Hexx. Once purchased this will add 8 Hex Tokens to your Hexx account. These tokens are for use within the Hexx game only. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez jetons Hex pour acheter des tuiles pour Hexx. Une fois acheté cela va ajouter 8 jetons Hex à votre compte Hexx. Ces jetons sont pour une utilisation dans le jeu Hexx seulement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verwenden Tokens bis Hex Fliesen Hexx kaufen. Nach dem Kauf wird es 8 Chips auf Ihr Konto Hexx Hex hinzuzufügen. Diese Chips sind zur Verwendung in dem Spiel nur Hexx. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Utilizzare gettoni per acquistare Hex Hexx piastrelle. Una volta acquistato si aggiungerà 8 gettoni al vostro conto Hex Hexx. Questi chip sono destinati alla Hexx unico gioco. #Legal] [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Utilice las fichas para comprar azulejos Hexx Hex. Una vez comprado se agregará 8 fichas para el hexagonal Hexx cuenta. Estos chips son para uso en la Hexx único juego. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Hexxためにタイルを購入するには、Hexトークンを使用しています。一度購入したこれはあなたのHexxアカウントに6六角トークンを追加します。これらのトークンは、Hexxゲーム内でのみ使用されます。サービス·ダウンロード規約このアイテムに適用されるPlayStation®Networkのサーバー/ユーザー契約の条項および特定の追加条件に従うものとします。あなたがこれらの条項に同意したくない場合は、この項目をダウンロードしないでください。ダウンロードは購買PSNアカウントでPlayStation®のホーム内だけで使用するために、あなたにライセンスまたはサブライセンスされています。コンテンツは、他のアカウントで使用することはできません。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Hexx 위해 타일을 살 설사약 토큰을 사용합니다. 일단 이번이 Hexx 계정에 6 설사약 프로그램 토큰을 추가합니다 구입했습니다. 이 토큰은 Hexx 게임 내에서 사용하는 전용입니다. 서비스 다운로드 약관 서버 / 사용자 계약 및이 항목에 적용되는 특정 추가 조건의 플레이 스테이션 ® 네트워크 약관의 적용을받습니다. 여러분이 이러한 조건에 동의하지 않으려면,이 항목을 다운로드하지 않습니다. 다운로드는 구매 PSN 계정에 의해서만 플레이 스테이션 ® 홈페이지 내에서 사용하기 위해 귀하에게 허가 또는 sublicensed있다. 내용은 다른 계정에서 사용할 수 없습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Use Hex tokens to buy tiles for Hexx. Once purchased this will add 8 Hex Tokens to your Hexx account. These tokens are for use within the Hexx game only.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Use Hex tokens to buy tiles for Hexx. Once purchased this will add 8 Hex Tokens to your Hexx account. These tokens are for use within the Hexx game only.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Use Hex tokens to buy tiles for Hexx. Once purchased this will add 8 Hex Tokens to your Hexx account. These tokens are for use within the Hexx game only.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Use Hex tokens to buy tiles for Hexx. Once purchased this will add 8 Hex Tokens to your Hexx account. These tokens are for use within the Hexx game only.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>