<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hummingbird DX Hover Engine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Réacteur de suspension Hummingbird DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hummingbird DX - Hover-Triebwerk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Motore Hover Hummingbird DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Motor de planeador Hummingbird DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Hummingbird DX ホバーエンジン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Hummingbird DX 호버 엔진</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Hummingbird DX Hover Engine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Hummingbird DX 漂浮引擎</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Hummingbird DX 漂浮引擎</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hummingbird DX Hover Engine</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Adding the more powerful motor in this Hover Engine to your Sodium2 racer will increase stability and reduce slow-down from crashes at the cost of turning response. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'ajout du Moteur de Suspension plus puissant à votre engin Sodium2 améliorera sa stabilité et réduira les ralentissements dus aux accidents au détriment de la maniabilité. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Durch einen stärkere Antriebseinheit verleiht dieses Hover-Triebwerk deinem Sodium2-Gleiter eine größere Stabilität und weniger Geschwindigkeitsverlust bei Kollisionen auf Kosten einer schlechteren Kurvenlage. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Equipaggiando il motore più potente possibile all'interno di questo motore a propulsione verticale, il tuo veicolo Sodium2 diventerà molto più stabile e rallenterà di meno dopo uno scontro. L'unico svantaggio è un minore risposta in curva. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si sumas el motor más potente de este Motor de planeador a tu corredor de Sodium2, aumentarás la estabilidad y reducirás la desaceleración por culpa de los choques a cambio de perder ángulo de giro. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">あなたのSodium2 racerにより強力なモーターを積んだホヴァリングエンジンを。レスポンスの良さによりクラッシュによる減速や安定性を増します。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">여러분의 Sodium2 레이서 호버 엔진에 보다 강력한 모터를 추가하면 회전력은 떨어지지만 안정성이 늘어나고 충돌 시에도 속도가 떨어지는 것을 줄여 주지만 회전반응은 감소합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Adding the more powerful motor in this Hover Engine to your Sodium2 racer will increase stability and reduce slow-down from crashes at the cost of turning response. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在這部Sodium2賽車漂浮引擎內加上動力更強的馬達，不但穩定性增加，撞擊時對速度的影響也更小，但過彎反應速度變慢。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在這部Sodium2賽車漂浮引擎內加上動力更強的馬達，不但穩定性增加，撞擊時對速度的影響也更小，但過彎反應速度變慢。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Adding the more powerful motor in this Hover Engine to your Sodium2 racer will increase stability and reduce slow-down from crashes at the cost of turning response. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>