<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ninjutsu Warrior - Master of Lightning  稲妻のマスター(Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guerrier Ninjutsu - Maître des éclairs 稲妻のマスター(Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ninjutsu-Krieger - Meister der Blitze 稲妻のマスター(Frau)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guerriero Ninjutsu - Maestro del fulmine 稲妻のマスター(donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guerrero Ninjutsu: maestro de la luz 稲妻のマスター (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">忍者・稲妻のマスター（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">닌자 워리어 - 번개의 대가 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ninjutsu Warrior - Master of Lightning  (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">忍者 — 閃電上級忍者（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">忍者 — 閃電上級忍者（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ninjutsu Warrior - Master of Lightning  稲妻のマスター(Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Become the master of lightning, one of the highest ranking Ninjutsu Warriors. Creep silently in the shadows or back flip out in the open - either way everyone will know to treat you with respect. One glance of your glowing weapons and your enemy will be sure to flee.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Devenez le maître des éclairs, l’un des guerrier Ninjutsu les plus redoutables. Faufilez-vous dans l’ombre en silence, ou faites un salto arrière en pleine lumière – quel que soit votre choix, chacun vous devra le respect. À la seule vue de vos armes scintillantes, vos ennemis prendront la fuite à coup sûr.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Werde der Meister der Blitze, einer der höchsten Ränge der Ninjutsu-Krieger. Schleiche stumm durch die Schatten oder  katapultiere dich mit einem Rückwärtssalto aus ihnen heraus – was du auch machst, alle werden dich mit Respekt behandeln. Wenn deine Feinde deine glühenden Waffen sehen, werden sie die Flucht ergreifen.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Diventa maestro del fulmine, uno dei ranghi più alti dei guerrieri Ninjutsu. Stai silenziosamente nell'ombra o esci allo scoperto - in entrambi i casi tutti sapranno trattarti col dovuto rispetto. Un'occhiata alle tue armi splendenti e il tuo nemico scapperà via.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conviértete en el maestro de la luz: uno de los guerreros Ninjutsu de mayor rango. Muévete sigilosamente por entre las sombras o aparece de un salto ante tu enemigo. Sea lo que sea, todos te respetarán. En cuanto el enemigo vea tus brillantes armas, saldrá corriendo como alma que se lleva el diario.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">忍者の最高ランクである稲妻のマスターになろう。影の中を静かに忍び寄る姿やバク転をしながら移動している姿に誰もが憧れるだろう。暗闇で淡く光るキミを見れば敵は迷わず逃げるだろう。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">최고급 닌자 워리어 중 하나인 번개의 대가가 되십시오. 그림자 속에서 소리 없이 살며시 다가가거나 트인 공간에서 뒤로 공중제비를 도세요. 어떤 방식으로 접근하든 사람들은 당신을 존중해야 할 것입니다. 은은하게 빛나는 당신의 무기를 보여주기만 해도 적들은 도망갈 것입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Become the master of lightning, one of the highest ranking Ninjutsu Warriors. Creep silently in the shadows or back flip out in the open - either way everyone will know to treat you with respect. One glance of your glowing weapons and your enemy will be sure to flee.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">成為最高級忍者之一：閃電忍者。在黑暗中無影無聲地穿梭，亦或在光天化日下猝不及防地現身殺敵。任您來去無蹤，世人無不敬佩。一看到您銳利閃光的武器，敵人便逃之夭夭。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">成為最高級忍者之一：閃電忍者。在黑暗中無影無聲地穿梭，亦或在光天化日下猝不及防地現身殺敵。任您來去無蹤，世人無不敬佩。一看到您銳利閃光的武器，敵人便逃之夭夭。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Become the master of lightning, one of the highest ranking Ninjutsu Warriors. Creep silently in the shadows or back flip out in the open - either way everyone will know to treat you with respect. One glance of your glowing weapons and your enemy will be sure to flee.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>