<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Magnetico</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le magnético</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Magnetiko</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Magnetico</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Magnético</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">マグネーティコ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">마그네티코</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Magnetico</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">磁鐵</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">磁鐵</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Magnetico</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If you're wanting to catch Curios from the Aurora Sky Fishing game, then this is the lure you will be needing! This will increase your chances of catching Curios items dramatically.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'appât  indispensable si vous voulez attraper des Curios dans le jeu de pêche d'Aurora Sky ! Vous augmenterez radicalement vos chances d'attraper des Curios. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn du beim Aurora Sky Fishing Kuriositäten fangen willst, dann brauchst du diesen Köder! Er wird deine Chancen darauf, Kuriositäten zu fangen, erheblich steigern. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se vuoi catturare Curios del gioco Pesca del cielo di Aurora, allora quest'esca è ciò di cui hai bisogno! Aumenterà le tue possibilità di cattura degli oggetti Curios in maniera considerevole.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si quieres atrapar Curios en el juego de pesca espacial de Aurora, ¡este es el cebo que necesitas! Aumentará con creces las probabilidades de atrapar Curios.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラのスカイフィッシングゲームでガラクタ？を釣ろうとしているならば、このルアを使いましょう！ガラクタ？を釣る確率がグンと上がります！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">오로라 스카이 피싱 게임에서 큐리오를 잡고 싶다면, 이 미끼가 필요할 것입니다! 이 미끼는 큐리오를 잡을 확률을 크게 높여줍니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">If you're wanting to catch Curios from the Aurora Sky Fishing game, then this is the lure you will be needing! This will increase your chances of catching Curios items dramatically.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">若您想在極光空中釣魚遊戲中釣到古玩，那麼這正是您需要的魚餌！這將大大增加您釣到古玩的機會。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">若您想在極光空中釣魚遊戲中釣到古玩，那麼這正是您需要的魚餌！這將大大增加您釣到古玩的機會。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">If you're wanting to catch Curios from the Aurora Sky Fishing game, then this is the lure you will be needing! This will increase your chances of catching Curios items dramatically.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>