<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Red and White Swimsuit Set (One-piece Type, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set maillot de bain rouge et blanc (modèle une pièce, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Rot-weißes Badeanzug-Set (Einteiler, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set costume da bagno pezzo unico (rosso e bianco, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de bañador rojo y blanco (de una pieza, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">赤と白の水着セット（ワンピースタイプ・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">Red and White Swimsuit Set (One-piece Type, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* 赤と白の水着セット（ワンピースタイプ・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">Red and White Swimsuit Set (One-piece Type, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">Red and White Swimsuit Set (One-piece Type, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Red and White Swimsuit Set (One-piece Type, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Set of a small hat, one piece-type swimsuit, and long-type boots coordinated with red and white.\n
Defensive Strength: None~★\n
Sexiness: None~★★★\n
This set includes the following items:\n
\n
- Small Pom-pom Hat (Loose, Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Small Pom-pom Hat (Normal, Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Small Pom-pom Hat (Close, Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Red Swimsuit with Boa (One-piece Type, Women) (Outfit)\n
- Snow-white Boots (Long Type, Women) (Shoes)\n
\n
* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set accordé en rouge et blanc contenant un petit chapeau, un maillot de bain modèle une pièce et des bottes longues.\n
Défense : Sans~★\n
Sex-appeal : Sans~★★★\n
Ce set inclut les objets suivants :\n
\n
- Petit chapeau avec pompon (flottant, femme) (Accessoire de tête)\n
- Petit chapeau avec pompon (normal, femme) (Accessoire de tête)\n
- Petit chapeau avec pompon (serré, femme) (Accessoire de tête)\n
- Maillot de bain rouge avec boa (modèle une pièce, femme) (Tenues)\n
- Bottes blanc neige (modèle long, femme) (Chaussures)\n
\n
* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein in rot und weiß gehaltenes Set bestehend aus einer kleinen Mütze, einem Badeanzug und langen Stiefeln.\n
Verteidigung: Keine~★\n
Sexappeal: Keine~★★★\n
Dieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n
\n
- Kleine Weihnachtsmütze mit Bommel (lose, für Frauen) (Kopfbedeckung)\n
- Kleine Weihnachtsmütze mit Bommel (normal, für Frauen) (Kopfbedeckung)\n
- Kleine Weihnachtsmütze mit Bommel (enganliegend, für Frauen) (Kopfbedeckung)\n
- Roter Badeanzug mit Pelzrand (Einteiler, für Frauen) (Kombination)\n
- Schneeweiße Stiefel (lang, für Frauen) (Schuhe)\n
\n
* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set comprendente un cappellino, un costume da bagno modello intero e degli stivali alti, tutti coordinati in rosso e bianco.\n
Difesa: Nulla~★\n
Sensualità: Nulla~★★★\n
Nel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n
\n
- Piccolo cappello pompon, largo (da donna) (accessorio per la testa)\n
- Piccolo cappello pompon, normale (da donna) (accessorio per la testa)\n
- Cappellino pompon, stretto (da donna) (accessorio per la testa)\n
- Costume da bagno modello intero (rosso con boa, da donna) (completo)\n
- Stivali alti (bianco candido, da donna) (scarpe)\n
\n
* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettiva categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego con prendas rojas y blancas que incluye gorro pequeño, bañador de una pieza y botas altas.\n
Defensa: Ninguno~★\n
Sensualidad: Ninguno~★★★\n
Este juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n
\n
- Gorro pequeño con pompón (suelto, mujer) (accesorio de cabeza)\n
- Gorro pequeño con pompón (normal, mujer) (accesorio de cabeza)\n
- Gorro pequeño con pompón (apretado, mujer) (accesorio de cabeza)\n
- Bañador rojo con boa (de una pieza, mujer) (combinación)\n
- Botas Blancanieves (altas, mujer) (zapatos)\n
\n
*Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">赤と白を基調とした小さな帽子、ワンピースタイプの水着、ロングタイプのブーツのセット。\n
防御力：　（なし）～★\n
セクシー度：　（なし）～★★★\n
本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n
\n
・小さなポンポン帽（浅め・女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n
・小さなポンポン帽（ふつう・女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n
・小さなポンポン帽（深め・女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n
・ボアの付いた赤い水着（ワンピースタイプ・女性）/組み合わせ\n
・純白のブーツ（ロングタイプ・女性）/靴\n
\n
※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Set of a small hat, one piece-type swimsuit, and long-type boots coordinated with red and white.\n
Defensive Strength: None~★\n
Sexiness: None~★★★\n
This set includes the following items:\n
\n
- Small Pom-pom Hat (Loose, Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Small Pom-pom Hat (Normal, Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Small Pom-pom Hat (Close, Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Red Swimsuit with Boa (One-piece Type, Women) (Outfit)\n
- Snow-white Boots (Long Type, Women) (Shoes)\n
\n
* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
