<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Macabre Skeletal SpeedWings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">SpeedWings Squelette Macabre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Makaberes Skelett SpeedWings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">SpeedWings Macabre Scheletriche</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esqueleto Macabro SpeedWings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LMO-マカブルスケレタル・スピードウィングス</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Macabre Skeletal SpeedWings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Macabre Skeletal SpeedWings</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blaze through your favorite places with SpeedWings!  Pull out these wings for a major speed boost with custom animations.  You can wear anything you want with SpeedWings, including shirts, gloves, or even full-transformation outfits!\n\nYour SpeedWings can be accessed from the personal inventory.  Once activated, the wings will appear on your avatar's back.  The speed boost is engaged by holding the SQUARE button while the avatar is moving at its running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mettez le feu à vos endroits préférés avec les SpeedWings! Sortez ces ailes pour obtenir un boost de vitesse majeur avec des animations personnalisées. Vous pouvez porter ce que vous voulez avec les SpeedWings, y compris des gants, des T-shirts et même des tenues de transformation totale.\n\nVos SpeedWings sont accessibles depuis votre inventaire personnel. Une fois activées, les ailes apparaîtront sur le dos de votre avatar. Le boost de vitesse est déclenché en gardant le bouton SQUARE appuyé lorsque votre avatar se déplace à vitesse de course. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Durchfliege deine Lieblingsplätze mit den SpeedWings!  Fahre diese Flügel für einen wesentlichen Geschwindigkeitsschub mit benutzerspezifischen Animationen aus. Du kannst mit den SpeedWings alles tragen, was du willst,  ob Shirts, Handschuhe oder sogar ganze Transformationsanzüge! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scorrazza nei luoghi che preferisci con le SpeedWings! Spiega queste ali per accelerare notevolmente con effetti animati personalizzati. Puoi indossare gli abiti che preferisci con le SpeedWings: camicie, guanti, e addirittura completi per la trasformazione totale!/n/nPuoi accedere alle tue SpeedWings dal tuo inventario personale. Una volta attivate, queste compariranno sulla schiena del tuo avatar. Puoi sfruttare l'accelerazione che ti conferiscono tenendo premuto il tasto SQUARE mentre l'avatar è in corsa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Resplandece a través de tus lugares favoritos con SpeedWings! Saca estas alas para un gran incremento de velocidad y animaciones personalizadas. ¡Puedes vestir lo que quieras con SpeedWings, incluyendo camisas, guantes o incluso trajes de transformación completa!/n/nTus SpeedWings pueden ser accedidas desde el inventario personal. Una vez activadas, las alas aparecerán en la espalda de tu avatar. El incremento de velocidad es activado presionando el botón SQUARE mientras el avatar está corriendo.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スピードウィングスでお気に入りの場所を突き進もう！ウィングを引っ張り出して、カスタムアニメーションつきの超スピードブースト！スピードウィングスでは、シャツ、グローブ、さらに変身スーツまで、好きなものを着用できます！\n\n※このアイテムを装備する事で、移動スピードがアップします。移動中に□ボタンを押す事で、さらに早く移動できるようになります。\n移動速度アップ：◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆\nLMO（ロコモーション）はポータブルアイテムです。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Blaze through your favorite places with SpeedWings!  Pull out these wings for a major speed boost with custom animations.  You can wear anything you want with SpeedWings, including shirts, gloves, or even full-transformation outfits!\n\nYour SpeedWings can be accessed from the personal inventory.  Once activated, the wings will appear on your avatar's back.  The speed boost is engaged by holding the SQUARE button while the avatar is moving at its running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blaze through your favorite places with SpeedWings!  Pull out these wings for a major speed boost with custom animations.  You can wear anything you want with SpeedWings, including shirts, gloves, or even full-transformation outfits!\n\nYour SpeedWings can be accessed from the personal inventory.  Once activated, the wings will appear on your avatar's back.  The speed boost is engaged by holding the SQUARE button while the avatar is moving at its running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>