<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mercian Fighter Eztil Wristguards and Amulet (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Protège-poignets et amulette de guerrier mercian Eztil (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mercia-Kämpfer-Eztil-Armschienen und Amulett (Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Polsiere guerriera Mercian Eztil e amuleto (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Muñequeras y amuleto de luchadora Eztil de Mercia (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mercian Fighter Eztil Wristguards and Amulet (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fighter Armour is strong enough to withstand attack yet light enough to allow the fighter to avoid incoming peril. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'armure de guerrier est assez solide pour résister aux attaques, mais aussi suffisamment légère pour permettre au guerrier d'éviter tout danger imminent. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Kämpferrüstung ist stark genug, um Angriffen standzuhalten, und leicht genug, um dem Kämpfer schnelles Ausweichen zu ermöglichen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'armatura da guerriero è abbastanza forte da reggere a un attacco, ma leggera a sufficienza da permettere al guerriero di evitare il pericolo che incombe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La armadura de luchador es lo suficientemente fuerte como para soportar un ataque y al mismo tiempo lo suficientemente ligera para que el luchador pueda esquivar un ataque. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fighter Armor is strong enough to withstand attack yet light enough to allow the fighter to avoid incoming peril. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>