<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Radec's Tactical Gloves</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Gants tactiques de Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Radecs Taktiker-Handschuhe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guanti tattici di Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guantes tácticos de Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">라덱 대령의 전술 장갑</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Radec's Tactical Gloves</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Radec戰術手套</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Radec戰術手套</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Radec's Tactical Gloves</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Descr</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Woven from a para-aramid synthetic fiber impervious to flames and cuts, Colonel Radec’s tactical gloves are state-of-the-art even by ISA standards. They were retrieved from the rubble of Visari’s Palace by Captain Narville and promptly submitted to ISA Command for DNA inspection. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fabriqués en fibre para-aramide synthétique anti-coupure et anti-chaleur, les gants tactiques du colonel Radec sont à pointe de la technologie, même pour l'ISA. Ils ont été retrouvés dans les décombres du palais de Visari par le capitaine Narville et aussitôt envoyés à l'ISA pour une recherche d'ADN. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Colonel Radecs Taktiker-Handschuhe sind durch die Para-Aramid-Synthetikfasern resistent gegen Flammen und Schnitte und gelten selbst nach ISA-Standard als hochmodern. Sie wurden von Captain Narville aus den Trümmern von Visaris Palast geborgen und dem ISA-Kommando sofort zur DNS-Analyse übergeben. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los guantes tácticos del coronel Radec, tejidos con fibra de para-aramida sintética, resistente al fuego y los cortes, son de última tecnología, incluso para los estándares ISA.  El capitán Narville los recuperó de los escombros del Palacio de Visari y los envió sin mayor dilación al mando ISA para realizar un análisis de ADN. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">열과 충격에 의한 변화가 전혀 없는 파라-아라미드 합성 섬유로 짜여진 라덱 대령의 전술 장갑은 ISA의 기준으로도 최첨단 방어구임이 틀림 없습니다. 나빌 대위에 의해 비사리 황궁의 폐허에서 수거된 이 장갑은 DNA 조사를 위해 ISA 지휘부에 전달되었습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Woven from a para-aramid synthetic fiber impervious to flames and cuts, Colonel Radec’s tactical gloves are state-of-the-art even by ISA standards. They were retrieved from the rubble of Visari’s Palace by Captain Narville and promptly submitted to ISA Command for DNA inspection. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Radec上校的戰術手套以對位芳香族聚醯胺合成纖維製成，可抵禦火燒及刀傷，即使以ISA的標準而言亦屬尖端科技產品。這對手套是由Narville隊長在賓沙利宮殿的瓦礫中找到，並即時送到ISA司令部進行DNA化驗。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Radec上校的戰術手套以對位芳香族聚醯胺合成纖維製成，可抵禦火燒及刀傷，即使以ISA的標準而言亦屬尖端科技產品。這對手套是由Narville隊長在賓沙利宮殿的瓦礫中找到，並即時送到ISA司令部進行DNA化驗。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Woven from a para-aramid synthetic fiber impervious to flames and cuts, Colonel Radec’s tactical gloves are state-of-the-art even by ISA standards. They were retrieved from the rubble of Visari’s Palace by Captain Narville and promptly submitted to ISA Command for DNA inspection. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>