<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Pearl Diver Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le pêcheur de perles bundle de meubles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Perlentaucher: Möbelset</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto arredamento Pescatore di perle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de muebles Buscador de perlas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">The Pearl Diver Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">펄 다이버 가구 번들</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Pearl Diver Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">珍珠潛水員家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">珍珠潛水員家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Pearl Diver Furniture Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">What’s a personal space without any cool furniture items to place inside? For those of you looking for some of the most trendy furniture items around, look no further than The Pearl Diver Furniture Bundle. Bundle includes a bar stool, lounge chair, stool, couch and table. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Qu'est-ce qu'un espace personnel sans meubles cool de place à l'intérieur? Pour ceux d'entre vous à la recherche de certains des éléments de mobilier les plus branchés autour, ne cherchez pas plus loin que Le pêcheur de perles bundle de meubles. L'ensemble comprend un tabouret bar, chaise longue, tabouret, canapé et une tableau. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Was ist ein Home-Apartment, wenn man keine coolen Möbel dafür hat? Für alle, die die trendigsten Möbelstücke aller Zeiten suchen, ist das Perlentaucher-Möbelset die Lösung. Im Paket enthalten sind ein Barhocker, ein Lounge-Sessel, ein Hocker, eine Couch und ein Tisch. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Che spazio personale sarebbe senza dei fantastici oggetti d'arredamento da posizionare al suo interno? Per tutti quelli che cercano gli oggetti d'arredamento più alla moda, controllate il Pacchetto arredamento Pescatore di perle. Il pacchetto include uno sgabello da bar, una chaise longue, uno sgabello, un divano e un tavolo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Qué es un espacio personal sin un mobiliario molón con el que decorarlo? Todos aquellos que vayan tras los objetos de mobiliario más modernos ya no tendrán que buscar más gracias al conjunto de muebles Buscador de perlas. El paquete incluye: un taburete de barra, un diván, un taburete y una mesa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">What’s a personal space without any cool furniture items to place inside? For those of you looking for some of the most trendy furniture items around, look no further than The Pearl Diver Furniture Bundle. Bundle includes a bar stool, lounge chair, stool, couch and table. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">여러분의 공간에 넣을만한 멋진 가구 아이템들이 없다면 퍼스널 스페이스가 무슨 소용인가요? 요즘 가장 유행하는 가구 아이템을 찾는 분이라면, 펄 다이버 가구 번들 말고는 볼 필요도 없을 거에요.\n 이 번들은 다음이 포함됩니다:\n\n ● 펄 다이버 바 의자 ● 펄 다이버 라운지 의자 ● 펄 다이버 소파 ● 펄 다이버 테이블  * 구매 후, 각 아이템은 해당 카테고리에 추가됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">What’s a personal space without any cool furniture items to place inside? For those of you looking for some of the most trendy furniture items around, look no further than The Pearl Diver Furniture Bundle.\n This bundle includes the following items.\n\n  ・The Pearl Diver Bar Stool\n ・The Pearl Diver Lounge Chair\n ・The Pearl Diver Stool\n ・The Pearl Diver Couch\n ・The Pearl Diver Table\n\n  *When purchased, each item is added to its respective category.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">個人空間怎能沒有精美的家具道具？如果您正在尋找最時髦的家具道具，那麼這個珍珠潛水員家具組合包便正是您要的東西。\n 本組合包包括以下道具：\n\n  ●珍珠潛水員酒吧高凳\n ●珍珠潛水員休息椅\n ●珍珠潛水員高凳\n ●珍珠潛水員長沙發\n ●珍珠潛水員桌子\n\n  ※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別内。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">個人空間怎能沒有精美的家具道具？如果您正在尋找最時髦的家具道具，那麼這個珍珠潛水員家具組合包便正是您要的東西。\n 本組合包包括以下道具：\n\n  ●珍珠潛水員酒吧高凳\n ●珍珠潛水員休息椅\n ●珍珠潛水員高凳\n ●珍珠潛水員長沙發\n ●珍珠潛水員桌子\n\n  ※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別内。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">What’s a personal space without any cool furniture items to place inside? For those of you looking for some of the most trendy furniture items around, look no further than The Pearl Diver Furniture Bundle. Bundle includes a bar stool, lounge chair, stool, couch and table. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>