<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Handheld Arc Drill (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Perceuse à arc portative (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Handbogenbohrer (weibliche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Trivella a scariche portatile (per donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Taladro de arco de mano (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">携帯型アークドリル（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Handheld Arc Drill (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Handheld Arc Drill (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fully capable of drilling into asteroids with both concentrated energy and physical cutting, the Handheld Arc Drill allows each miner to personally handle most detail work involved with the extraction of valuable minerals.  Please note that mining tools such as these can be extremely dangerous, and should never be used in a manner inconsistent with their approved functionality. This item passively absorbs Nebulon, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base Nebulon gains by about 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pleinement capable de percer des astéroïdes avec de l'énergie à la fois concentrée et une coupe physique, la perceuse à arc portative permet à chaque mineur d'effectuer personnellement tous les travaux de détail impliqués dans l'extraction de minéraux de valeur.  Merci de noter que les engins de mine tels que ceux-ci sont extrêmement dangereux et ne doivent jamais être utilisés de manière inconsistante à leur fonctionnalité approuvée. Cet objet absorbe passivement le Nébulon, augmentant efficacement vos gains en Nébulon de base Novus Prime d'approximativement 5%.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vollständig dazu in der Lage sich sowohl mit konzentrierter Energie als auch physischer Kraft in Asteroiden zu bohren, ermöglicht dieser Handbogenbohrer es einem Bergmann selbst feinste Arbeiten auszuführen, die für die Gewinnung von Mineralien notwendig sind. Achtung, Werkzeuge zum Bergbau wie diese können extrem gefährlich sein und sollten niemals außerhalb ihres vorgesehenen Einsatzbereiches verwendet werden. Dieser Ausrüstungsgegenstand absorbiert zusätzlich Nebulon und erhöht die Zufuhr von Nebulon deiner Novus Prime Basis effektiv um ca. 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Essendo in grado di perforare un asteroide grazie all'azione congiunta di energia concentrata e forza perforante, la Trivella a scariche portatile permette ad ogni minatore di gestire personalmente ogni operazione di estrazione di minerali preziosi. Ricordiamo che  attrezzi da minatore come questo possono essere estremamente pericolosi e non devono essere mai usati in maniera diversa da quella indicata. Questo oggetto assorbe passivamente l'energia nebulon, incrementando l'assorbimento della stessa da parte della base Novus Prime di circa il 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Completamente capaz de taladrar dentro de asteroides ya sea con energía concentrada y corte físico, el Taladro de arco de mano permite a cada minero portar personalmente con mayor detalle de trabajo que implica con la extracción de minerales valiosos.  Toma en cuenta que herramientas de minería como estas pueden ser extremadamente peligrosas, y nunca deben ser usadas en maneras inconsistente con su funcionalidad aprobada. Este objeto absorbe Nebulón pasivamente, incrementado efectivamente tu base Novus Prime cerca de un 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">集中エネルギーと物理的な切削による隕石に穴を開ける事が完全に可能。携帯型のアークドリルは鉱山労働者が個人レベルで貴重な鉱物の抽出に関わる詳細な作業の殆どを可能にする。これらのような掘削道具の取り扱いは極めて危険なので、許可されている使用方法と矛盾する使い方は絶対に行わないようにして気をつけて下さい。\n※購入すると、ミニゲーム「ノーバス・プライム」内でネブロンの増加量が5%上がります。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Fully capable of drilling into asteroids with both concentrated energy and physical cutting, the Handheld Arc Drill allows each miner to personally handle most detail work involved with the extraction of valuable minerals.  Please note that mining tools such as these can be extremely dangerous, and should never be used in a manner inconsistent with their approved functionality. This item passively absorbs Nebulon, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base Nebulon gains by about 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fully capable of drilling into asteroids with both concentrated energy and physical cutting, the Handheld Arc Drill allows each miner to personally handle most detail work involved with the extraction of valuable minerals.  Please note that mining tools such as these can be extremely dangerous, and should never be used in a manner inconsistent with their approved functionality. This item passively absorbs Nebulon, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base Nebulon gains by about 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>