<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Valor Gun Rack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Râtelier armes Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Valor-Waffenregal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Porta-armi Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estante para armas de Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">銃架 ベイラー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Valor 총기대</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Valor Gun Rack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Valor槍架</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Valor槍架</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Valor Gun Rack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This gun rack is where Valor operatives keep their tools of the trade.  Notice the organised fashion to how they store their firearms.  I dare you to touch one without asking.      [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C'est sur ce râtelier que les agents de Valor stockent leur matériel. Remarquez avec quel soin ils rangent leurs armes. Essayez un peu d'en toucher une sans demander la permission. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In diesem Waffenregal bewahren die Valor-Soldaten ihr Arbeitswerkzeug auf. Beachten Sie, wie geordnet sie ihre Waffen lagern. Es kann übrigens ziemlich ungesund sein, ungefragt eine anzufassen.      [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo porta-armi è usato dai soldati della Valor per riporre la loro attrezzatura. È organizzato alla perfezione e nessuno oserebbe toccarlo senza chiedere il permesso. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">En este estante es donde los soldados de Valor guardan sus armas. Mira qué organizadas las tienen. Atrévete a tocar una sin preguntar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ベイラーの銃架は分かりやすく整理されている。整理整頓はベイラーの基本だ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Valor의 병사들이 총기를 보관하는 곳입니다. 진정한 군인들답게 통일된 방법으로 진열되어 있습니다. 함부로 손을 댄다면 어떻게 될까요? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This gun rack is where Valor operatives keep their tools of the trade. Notice the organized fashion they store their firearms. I dare you to touch one without asking. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這款槍架是Valor工作人員安放所需工具之處。請注意他們存放的軍火多麼有系統。你有膽不問一下就碰這些工具嗎？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這款槍架是Valor工作人員安放所需工具之處。請注意他們存放的軍火多麼有系統。你有膽不問一下就碰這些工具嗎？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This gun rack is where Valor operatives keep their tools of the trade. Notice the organized fashion in which they store their firearms. I dare you to touch one without asking. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>