<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cutteridge Estate Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mobilier du manoir Cutteridge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Möbelgruppe des Cutteridge-Herrenhauses</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Arredi di Palazzo Cutteridge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de muebles para la mansión Cutteridge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Cutteridge Estate Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Cutteridge Estate Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Cutteridge Estate Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Cutteridge Estate Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Cutteridge Estate Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cutteridge Estate Furniture Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The abysmal darkness of Cutteridge Estate may imprison your soul for eternity, but at least you'll have some nice furnishings. This bundle includes the following 19 pieces of furniture: Occult Sideboard, Reading Chair, Horrifyingly Comfortable Ottoman, Antique Armchair, Carved Antiquities Cabinet, Inscribed Cabinet, Gothic Four Poster Bed, Antique Wood-Burning Stove, Suspicious Tomes, Mysterious Grimoires, Curious Chest of Drawers, Grotesque Statue, Square Picture Frame, Round Picture Frame, Intricate Candelabra, Victorian Sofa, Inlaid Wood Table, Victorian Dining Chair and the (probably) authentic Necronomicopedia!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les ténèbres incommensurables du Cutteridge risquent de réduire votre âme en esclavage pour l'éternité, mais au moins vous aurez de beaux meubles. Cet ensemble inclut les 19 meubles suivants : Fauteuil club, ottomane horriblement confortable, fauteuil antique, cabinet d'antiquités ouvragé, armoire gravée, lit à baldaquin gothique, fourneau à bois ancien, tomes cryptiques, grimoires mystérieux, commode énigmatique, statue grotesque, cadre carré, cadre rond, candélabre tourmenté, sofa victorien, table en bois marquetée, buffet occulte, chaise victorienne et l'authentique (probablement) Necronomicopedia !  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die untiefenartige Dunkelheit des Cutteridge-Herrenhauses kann Ihre Seele auf Ewig gefangen nehmen, aber wenigstens gibt es hier richtig schöne Möbel. Diese Gruppe umfasst die folgenden 19 Möbelstücke: Lesesessel, Schrecklich komfortabler Ottomane, Antiker Armsessel, Mit Schnitzereien verzierter Antiquitätenschrank, Schrank mit Inschrift, Grausiges Himmelbett, Antiker Kaminofen, Verdächtige Bände, Geheimnisvolle Zauberbücher, Seltsame Kommode, Groteske Statue, Viereckiger Bilderrahmen, Runder Bilderrahmen, Verschlungener Kronleuchter, Viktorianisches Sofa, Holztisch mit Intarsien, Geheimnisvolles Sideboard, Viktorianischer Esszimmerstuhl und die (vermutlich) authentische Necronomicopedia!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le abissali tenebre di Palazzo Cutteridge possono imprigionare il tuo spirito per l'eternità, ma almeno sarai attorniato da piacevoli arredi. Questo pacchetto include i 19 arredi seguenti: Poltrona di lettura, Ottomana spaventosamente comoda, Poltrona antica, Armadio di antichità intagliato, Armadio con iscrizioni, Letto a baldacchino gotico, Antica stufa per ardere, Loschi tomi, Misteriosi libri di magia, Cassettone bizzarro, Statua grottesca, Cornice quadrata, Cornice rotonda, Candelabri contorti, Sofà vittoriano, Tavolo in legno intarsiato, Credenza occulta, Sedia da pranzo vittoriana e Necronomicopedia (probabilmente) autentica!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La oscuridad abismal de la Mansión Cutteridge puede encarcelar de por vida a tu alma, pero al menos tendrán unos muebles bonitos. Este conjunto incluye los siguientes 19 muebles: Sillón de lectura, sofá otomano horripilantemente cómodo, butaca antigua, armario antiguo tallado, armario grabado, cama gótica con dosel, horno antiguo a leña, tomos sospechosos, grimorios misteriosos, extraña cajonera, estatura grotesca, marco de fotos cuadrado, marco de fotos redondo, candelabro intrincado, sofá victoriano, mesa de madera con incrustaciones, aparador oculto, silla de comedor victoriana y la (probablemente) auténtica Necronomicopedia.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Cutteridge Estate Furniture Bundle [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Cutteridge Estate Furniture Bundle [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Cutteridge Estate Furniture Bundle [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Cutteridge Estate Furniture Bundle [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Cutteridge Estate Furniture Bundle [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The abysmal darkness of Cutteridge Estate may imprison your soul for eternity, but at least you'll have some nice furnishings. This bundle includes the following 19 pieces of furniture: Occult Sideboard, Reading Chair, Horrifyingly Comfortable Ottoman, Antique Armchair, Carved Antiquities Cabinet, Inscribed Cabinet, Gothic Four Poster Bed, Antique Wood-Burning Stove, Suspicious Tomes, Mysterious Grimoires, Curious Chest of Drawers, Grotesque Statue, Square Picture Frame, Round Picture Frame, Intricate Candelabra, Victorian Sofa, Inlaid Wood Table, Victorian Dining Chair and the (probably) authentic Necronomicopedia!  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>