<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Mixed Falls Dress - Black (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Robe Mixed Falls - Noir (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Mixed Falls Kleid - Schwarz (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Abito Mixed Falls - Nero (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Mixed Falls Vestido - Negro (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A bustier style bandeau gets wild and styled with a mix of tribal and animal prints. A smocked back ensures an no-slip flit, but we've also included removable straps. What's more, the solid skirt flutters and lightly flows with pleating. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un bandeau style bustier donne une touche sauvage et stylée avec un mélange d'imprimés tribaux et animaliers. Le dos smocké assure un maintien, mais nous avons également prévu des bretelles amovibles. De plus, la jupe unie palpite et flotte légèrement avec son plissage. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Mixed Falls Kleid mit coolem Bandeau im BH-Stil ist in einer Mischung aus Folklore- und Tiermustern erhältlich. Die Smokarbeit auf der Rückseite sorgt für einen optimalen Sitz, auch bei abgenommenen Trägern. Besonders schön ist der weite fließende Rock mit Falten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il corpetto a bustino acquista un aspetto elegantemente selvaggio grazie al mix di motivi tribali e animalier. La lavorazione posteriore a nido d'ape assicura una perfetta vestibilità ma abbiamo aggiunto anche delle spalline staccabili. E, cosa ancora più importante, la gonna consistente ha un'arricciatura che la rende leggera, svolazzante e fluida. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un vestido entallado tipo corsé, de gran estilo y carácter, con una mezcla de estampado tribal y de animales. El nido de abeja en espalda ayuda a fijar el vestido contra posibles deslices, aunque también se incluyen tirantes opcionales. Y además, los pliegues de la falda, de color liso, crean un efecto de movimiento ondulado y ligero aleteo. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>