<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Valor Infiltrator</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Infiltrator Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Valor-Infiltrator</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Infiltrator Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Infiltrator de Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Infiltrator ベイラー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Valor "침입자" 장갑차</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Valor Infiltrator</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Valor「潛入者」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Valor「潛入者」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Valor Infiltrator</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Eight wheels, eight passengers and one hulking 30mm turret, the Infiltrator is the ultimate in armoured personnel carriers. With heavy combat armour, smoke screens and enough supplies to last a week this platform is guaranteed to get you in and out before the opposition knows what hit them.   [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Huit roues, huit passagers et une imposante tourelle de 30 mm... L'Infiltrator est le véhicule blindé de transport de troupes ultime. Grâce à son épais blindage, à son écran de fumée et à ses énormes réserves, cette plateforme vous fera entrer ou sortir avant que l'ennemi l'ait vue arriver. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit acht Rädern, acht Passagieren und einem mächtigen 30-mm-Geschütz ist der Infiltrator der ultimative MTW. Dieses Fahrzeug bringt Sie mit der schweren Panzerung, Rauchwänden und genug Vorräten für eine Woche ins Kampfgebiet und wieder heraus, bevor der Feind Sie überhaupt bemerkt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Otto ruote, otto passeggeri e una torretta sovrastante da 30 mm, l'Infiltrator è l'ultima novità tra i mezzi armati per il trasporto delle truppe. È dotato di corazza pesante, cortina fumogena e scorte per un'intera settimana. Vi permetterà di attaccare e fuggire prima che il nemico riesca a capire da dove è arrivato l'attacco.   [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con ocho ruedas, ocho pasajeros y una enorme torreta de 30 mm, el Infiltrator es el mejor vehículo blindado que existe. Gracias a sus cortinas de humo, blindaje pesado y provisiones para una semana, con este vehículo podrás entrar y salir de la zona enemiga antes de que se den cuenta de que pasa algo.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">車輪8つ、8人乗車可能、30mmタレット搭載のInfiltratorは究極の装甲兵員輸送車(APC)だ。重装甲、弾幕そして1週間分補給品を積める車両は敵陣深く進入しそのまま脱出もできてしまう。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">여덟 개의 바퀴. 여덟 명의 탑승인원. 괴물스러운 30mm 포탑 하나. "침입자"는 최고의 장갑차입니다. 두꺼운 장갑과 일주일 이상을 견딜 수 있는 연료와 물자까지, "침입자"는 적이 위협을 탐지하기도 전에 임무를 완수합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Eight wheels, eight passengers and one hulking 30mm turret, the Infiltrator is the ultimate in armored personnel carriers. With heavy combat armor, smoke screens and enough supplies to last a week, this platform is guaranteed to get you in and out before the opposition knows what hit them. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「潛入者」裝有八個輪子，可容納八名乘客，配有一座巨型30mm炮塔，是裝甲載具的極致。擁有重型戰鬥裝甲、煙霧彈、和足以維持一星期的補給量，這個武裝平台保證讓你能在無聲無息下擊倒敵人，並全身而退。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「潛入者」裝有八個輪子，可容納八名乘客，配有一座巨型30mm炮塔，是裝甲載具的極致。擁有重型戰鬥裝甲、煙霧彈、和足以維持一星期的補給量，這個武裝平台保證讓你能在無聲無息下擊倒敵人，並全身而退。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Eight wheels, eight passengers and one hulking 30mm turret, the Infiltrator is the ultimate in armored personnel carriers. With heavy combat armor, smoke screens and enough supplies to last a week, this platform is guaranteed to get you in and out before the opposition knows what hit them. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>