<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">WipEout® Ships Hologram Viewer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">WipEout® Ships Hologram Viewer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Afficheur holographique de vaisseaux de WipEout®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Holografischer WipEout®-Schiff-Betrachter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Visualizzatore ologramma navi WipEout®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Visor holográfico de naves de WipEout®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">WipEout® 기체 홀로그램 뷰어</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">WipEout® Ships Hologram Viewer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">WipEout®飛船瀏覽器</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">WipEout®飛船瀏覽器</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CYCLE_CONTROLS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFT][RIGHT] CYCLE MODELS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFT][RIGHT] PARCOURIR LES MODÈLES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFT][RIGHT] MODELLE DURCHBLÄTTERN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFT][RIGHT] VISUALIZZA MODELLI</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFT][RIGHT] CAMBIAR DE MODELO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[LEFT][RIGHT] 모델 변경</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[LEFT][RIGHT] CYCLE MODELS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[LEFT][RIGHT] 瀏覽模型</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[LEFT][RIGHT] 瀏覽模型</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ROTATE_CONTROLS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFTSTICK] ROTATE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFTSTICK] PIVOTER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFTSTICK] DREHEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFTSTICK] RUOTA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFTSTICK] ROTAR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[LEFTSTICK] 회전</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[LEFTSTICK] ROTATE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[LEFTSTICK] 回轉</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[LEFTSTICK] 回轉</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RESET_CONTROLS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[TRIANGLE] RESET</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[TRIANGLE] RÉINITIALISER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[TRIANGLE] ZURÜCKSETZEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[TRIANGLE] RIPRISTINA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[TRIANGLE] REINICIAR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[TRIANGLE] 리셋</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[TRIANGLE] RESET</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[TRIANGLE] 重置</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[TRIANGLE] 重置</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">EXIT_CONTROLS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CIRCLE] EXIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CIRCLE] QUITTER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CIRCLE] BEENDEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CIRCLE] ESCI</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CIRCLE] SALIR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[CIRCLE] 나가기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[CIRCLE] EXIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[CIRCLE] 離開</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[CIRCLE] 離開</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">FEISAR_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Spurred on by independent competition from one of its member states (in the form of Britain, with Icaras), the Federal European Industrial Science And Research team have produced what should be a legitimate contender for race wins in their FX350/FX400 race craft.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Piquée au vif par la concurrence indépendante de l'un de ses états membres (en l'occurrence, l'Angleterre, avec Icaras), l'écurie Federal European Industrial Science And Research a produit un vaisseau qui semble en mesure de remporter la victoire lors des courses de catégorie FX350/FX400.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Angespornt von der Konkurrenz durch einen seiner Mitgliedstaaten (Großbritannien, vertreten durch Icaras) hat das „Federal European Industrial Science and Research“-Entwicklerteam mit seinem FX350/FX400-Rennschiff etwas geschaffen, das als legitimer Titelanwärter gelten dürfte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Spronata dalla concorrenza di uno dei suoi stati membri (i britannici della Icaras), la squadra federale europea di ricerca scientifico-industriale ha realizzato la FX350/FX400, una nave che probabilmente sui tracciati di gara sarà una contendente legittima al podio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Motivado por la competición independiente de uno de sus estados miembros (Reino Unido, con Icaras), el equipo de desarrollo FEISAR ha creado una nave que será digna aspirante a la victoria en las carreras de FX350/FX400.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">유럽연방산업과학연구소(FEISAR)는 Icaras를 앞세운 영국의 독자적인 움직임을 견제하기 위해서 FX350 / FX400 시리즈 기체들을 양산해 내었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Spurred on by independent competition from one of its member states (in the form of Britain, with Icaras), the Federal European Industrial Science And Research team have produced what should be a legitimate contender for race wins in their FX350/FX400 race craft.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Federal European Industrial Science And Research車隊在其成員國（英國，連同Icaras車隊）獨立競爭的刺激下，製造出具備爭奪比賽冠軍實力的FX350／FX400飛船。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Federal European Industrial Science And Research車隊在其成員國（英國，連同Icaras車隊）獨立競爭的刺激下，製造出具備爭奪比賽冠軍實力的FX350／FX400飛船。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">QIREX_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">With massive investment in bleeding-edge facilities at their base on the outskirts of Moscow, Qirex, the Russian powerhouse of the early days of AG Racing, are poised to make a strong return to the front of the grid in the new FX400 Racing League. Director of Operations Feliks Levovich is set to field the talented young pilot Nadia Elenova in an attempt to steal the thunder from bitter rivals, Auricom.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Grâce aux investissements massifs consacrés aux installations vraiment très pointues de son siège aux environs de Moscou, Qirex, le poids lourd russe des débuts de la compétition anti-gravité, entend bien faire un retour fracassant sur l'avant-scène de la nouvelle catégorie FX400. Son directeur d'exploitation, Feliks Levovich, compte sur la jeune pilote Nadia Elenova pour priver l'écurie rivale majeure, Auricom, de toute chance de victoire.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit gewaltigen Investitionen in hypermoderne Technologien in ihrer Basis in den Moskauer Randbezirken meldet sich Qirex zurück. Das russische Kraftpaket aus den Pioniertagen des AG-Rennsports will sich damit in die vordersten Plätze der neuen FX400-Rennliga katapultieren und damit für ein perfektes Comeback sorgen. Produktionsleiter Feliks Levovich will die talentierte junge Pilotin Nadia Elenova ins Rennen schicken, um dem Erzrivalen Auricom den Rang abzulaufen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Investendo in modo consistente in impianti di ultimissima generazione nella propria base alla periferia di Mosca, la Qirex, casa russa prestigiosa fin dagli esordi delle gare AG, si prepara a un ritorno in grande stile sulla griglia di partenza della lega FX400. Il direttore delle operazioni, Feliks Levovich, farà scendere in pista una giovane pilota di talento, Nadia Elenova, nel tentativo di sottrarre il titolo agli odiati rivali della Auricom.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tras una gran inversión en instalaciones punteras para su sede a las afueras de Moscú, Qirex, la constructora rusa de los inicios de las carreras AG, está decidida a volver con fuerza a la parrilla de salida de la nueva liga FX400. El director de operaciones Feliks Levovich confía en la joven piloto Nadia Elenova para robar el protagonista a su amargo rival, Auricom.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">모스크바 외곽에 위치한 최첨단 연구소에 투자한 결과, 러시아의 이 회사는 FX400 레이스 리그에 화려한 컴백을 꿈꾸고 있습니다. 회사의 운영을 관장하는 펠릭스 레보비치는 젊은 파일럿 나디아 엘레노바를 앞세워 라이벌 Auricom으로 부터 챔피언의 자리를 탈환할 계획입니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">With massive investment in bleeding-edge facilities at their base on the outskirts of Moscow, Qirex, the Russian powerhouse of the early days of AG Racing, are poised to make a strong return to the front of the grid in the new FX400 Racing League. Director of Operations Feliks Levovich is set to field the talented young pilot Nadia Elenova in an attempt to steal the thunder from bitter rivals, Auricom.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在莫斯科郊外的基地大量投資尖端科技設備的Qirex，是AG Racing初期的霸者，並正準備強勢重返新FX400 聯賽的前線。營運總監Feliks Levovich準備派出年輕的天才駕駛員Nadia Elenova與死敵Auricom展開激烈的角逐。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在莫斯科郊外的基地大量投資尖端科技設備的Qirex，是AG Racing初期的霸者，並正準備強勢重返新FX400 聯賽的前線。營運總監Feliks Levovich準備派出年輕的天才駕駛員Nadia Elenova與死敵Auricom展開激烈的角逐。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PIRANHA_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Back with a vengeance after five years of uncertainty behind the scenes, Piranha bring what's claimed to be the engine with the fastest top end performance since the return of professional AG Racing in 2197. None, except maybe Icaras with their own extreme power-plant, are going to argue the point.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mue par sa soif de vengeance, l'écurie Piranha signe son retour après cinq années d'incertitude en coulisses, en inaugurant ce que certains considèrent comme le moteur le plus performant depuis la réintroduction de la compétition AG professionnelle en 2197. Aucune écurie - hormis peut-être Icaras, équipée de sa propre turbine ultra-puissante - ne semble en mesure de le contester.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nach fünf Jahren der Unsicherheit hinter den Kulissen schlägt Piranha zurück und hat einen Motor im Gepäck, der als schnellster Hochleistungsantrieb seit der Rückkehr des professionellen AG-Rennsports im Jahre 2197 gilt. Niemand, außer vielleicht Icaras mit ihrem außergewöhnlichen Triebwerk, wird das anzweifeln wollen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tornando alla ribalta dopo cinque anni di esitazioni dietro le quinte, la Piranha presenta un motore che, a sua detta, vanta le migliori prestazioni mai viste dal 2197, anno della riscoperta delle corse professioniste AG. Nessuno potrà controbattere questa affermazione, fatta eccezione forse per la Icaras con i suoi sistemi avanzati di motopropulsione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Piranha vuelve con ganas de venganza tras cinco años de incertidumbre interna, y nos trae el motor con mayor velocidad punta desde la vuelta de las carreras AG profesionales en 2197. Nadie, salvo quizás Icaras y su propia central de energía extrema, va a discutírselo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">5년 넘게 잊혀져 설욕을 다짐하던 Piranha는 이제 2197년 이후 개발된 엔진 중 가장 빠르다고 알려진 신형 엔진을 앞세워 경주에 참여합니다. 어쩌면 오직 Icaras만이 그들의 호언장담에 맞설 수 있을지도 모릅니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Back with a vengeance after five years of uncertainty behind the scenes, Piranha bring what's claimed to be the engine with the fastest top end performance since the return of professional AG Racing in 2197. None, except maybe Icaras with their own extreme power-plant, are going to argue the point.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Piranha在隱退5年進行充滿不確定因素的研究之後，懷著復仇之心捲土重來，帶來了號稱自2197年職業AG Racing重新開賽以來最快最高性能的引擎。也許除了擁有超強動力裝置的Icaras以外，沒人可以對此提出異議。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Piranha在隱退5年進行充滿不確定因素的研究之後，懷著復仇之心捲土重來，帶來了號稱自2197年職業AG Racing重新開賽以來最快最高性能的引擎。也許除了擁有超強動力裝置的Icaras以外，沒人可以對此提出異議。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TRIAKIS_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Triakis, keen to put the controversy of the 2206 season behind them, will compete with an evolution of their FX350 spec craft in their upcoming FX400 League campaign.  Without the reverse-inertia deceleration system – deemed illegal by the AG Racing Commission – the ship looked to be more of a handful than its FX300 counterpart during pre-season testing, although it sported good top end speed - eventually.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'écurie Triakis, impatiente d'oublier les controverses de la saison 2206, engagera une évolution de son vaisseau de catégorie FX350 lors du prochain championnat FX400. Dépourvu du système de décélération à inertie inversée, déclaré illégal par les autorités de la compétition AG, le vaisseau s'est révélé plus compétitif que son homologue de catégorie FX300 durant les essais de pré-saison, et a présenté une vitesse de pointe impressionnante... à qui a su l'attendre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Triakis will die Diskussionen aus der Saison 2206 hinter sich lassen und in der bevorstehenden FX400-Saison mit einer Weiterentwicklung des FX350-Schiffs antreten. Ohne das Antiträgheit-Bremssystem, das von der AG-Rennkommission für regelwidrig befunden wurde, wirkte das Schiff während der vorsaisonalen Testphase im Vergleich zu seinem FX300-Gegenstück eher unruhig, obwohl es eine achtbare Spitzengeschwindigkeit erreichte ... nach einer Weile.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Desiderosa di lasciarsi alle spalle le controversie del 2206, la Triakis sfoggerà nella prossima lega FX400 una nave che rappresenta l'evoluzione della FX350. Senza il sistema di rallentamento a inerzia inversa, giudicato illecito dalla commissione di gara AG, la nave è sembrata piuttosto difficile da manovrare rispetto alla sua controparte FX300 nelle sessioni di collaudo, ma ha dimostrato, alla fine dei conti, una buona velocità complessiva.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Triakis, ansiosa por dejar atrás la controversia de la temporada 2206, competirá con la versión posterior de su nave de FX350 en la futura liga FX400. Sin el sistema de deceleración de inercia invertida, declarado ilegal por la comisión de carreras AG, la nave ha dado una impresión muy similar a su predecesora de FX300 durante las pruebas de pretemporada, aunque con una buena velocidad punta al fin y al cabo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Triakis는 2206년 시즌의 논란을 종식하기 위해 FX350급의 기체를 개조하여 FX400 리그에 참여하게 되었습니다. AG 레이싱 위원회로부터 허용 불가 판정을 받은 감속 장치없이는 열등한 FX300급의 성능 밖에 나타내지 못한다는 소리도 있었지만, 결국 최고 속력은 경쟁사들과 비슷한 수치로 판명되었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Triakis, keen to put the controversy of the 2206 season behind them, will compete with an evolution of their FX350 spec craft in their upcoming FX400 League campaign.  Without the reverse-inertia deceleration system – deemed illegal by the AG Racing Commission – the ship looked to be more of a handful than its FX300 counterpart during pre-season testing, although it sported good top end speed - eventually.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">急於將2206年賽季的爭論拋諸腦後的Triakis，將利用其FX350規格飛船的進化機型參與即將到來的FX400聯賽。沒有了被AG Racing委員會認定為違規的反向慣性減速系統，Triakis的飛船在賽前測試中看上去比其FX300版本更難控制，儘管也總算可以造出頂級的超高速度。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">急於將2206年賽季的爭論拋諸腦後的Triakis，將利用其FX350規格飛船的進化機型參與即將到來的FX400聯賽。沒有了被AG Racing委員會認定為違規的反向慣性減速系統，Triakis的飛船在賽前測試中看上去比其FX300版本更難控制，儘管也總算可以造出頂級的超高速度。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">AGSYS_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">AG Systems have finally turned the corner after spending the best part of a decade fighting for the scraps in the FX300 League. Their strong performance in FX350 class events, coupled with confidence inspiring pre-season testing for the FX400 League show that their 2206 FX300 Championship title was no fluke.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">AG Systems a enfin tourné la page, après avoir lutté dans les profondeurs du classement pendant près d'une décennie en catégorie FX300. Ses bonnes performances lors des épreuves de catégorie FX350, associées à des essais de pré-saison prometteurs en FX400, indiquent que sa victoire en championnat FX300 de 2206 n'était pas qu'un simple coup de chance.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nachdem das Team fast ein Jahrzehnt lang den Kampf um die hinteren Plätze in der FX300-Liga führte, hat AG Systems endlich die Kurve gekriegt. Die starke Leistung bei Rennveranstaltungen der FX350-Klasse sowie die vielversprechende Saisonvorbereitung für die FX400-Liga beweisen, dass der FX300-Meisterschaftstitel 2206 nicht auf Glück allein zurückzuführen war.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La AG Systems è finalmente a un punto di svolta dopo essersi accontentata degli avanzi per quasi tutto il decennio di gara della lega FX300. Le ottime prestazioni nelle gare della lega FX350 e la fiducia ispirata dai collaudi prestagionali per la FX400 hanno dimostrato che la vittoria al campionato FX300 del 2206 non è stata un caso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">AG Systems ha dado un giro impresionante tras pasarse los últimos años luchando por las migajas en la liga FX300. Su sólida actuación en las carreras de clase FX350 y su prometedora pretemporada para la liga FX400 demuestran que su título en el campeonato FX300 de 2206 no fue cosa del azar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">AG Systems는 이제 지난 10년 동안 FX300 리그에서 쌓아온 오명을 벗으려고 합니다. FX350에서 보여준 좋은 성과와 FX400 시즌 시작 이전에 기록된 훌륭한 테스트는 FX400 리그에서도 반드시 통할 것으로 생각합니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">AG Systems have finally turned the corner after spending the best part of a decade fighting for the scraps in the FX300 League. Their strong performance in FX350 class events, coupled with confidence inspiring pre-season testing for the FX400 League show that their 2206 FX300 Championship title was no fluke.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">AG System在FX300聯賽經歷了十年的苦苦掙扎之後，終於再獲新生。他們在FX350級賽事中的超強表現，再加上在FX400聯賽的賽前測試中令人刮目相看的表現，證明了他們在2206年勇奪FX300冠軍頭銜並非偶然僥倖。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">AG System在FX300聯賽經歷了十年的苦苦掙扎之後，終於再獲新生。他們在FX350級賽事中的超強表現，再加上在FX400聯賽的賽前測試中令人刮目相看的表現，證明了他們在2206年勇奪FX300冠軍頭銜並非偶然僥倖。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GOTEKI_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Re-formed in 2202 after a 65 year gap in its history, the Goteki 45 team will look to improve on the disappointing mid-pack results they've achieved to-date in the FX300 League. Now bestowed with financial resources on-par with the leading teams, the new facilities at their base of operations on Makana Island are literally packed with equipment that's ahead of the curve.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Reformée en 2202 après une absence de 65 ans, l'écurie Goteki 45 cherche à améliorer les résultats médiocres obtenus jusqu'ici en catégorie FX300. S'appuyant désormais sur des moyens financiers dignes des meilleurs constructeurs, l'écurie a pu doter les nouvelles installations de son siège de l'île de Makana d'équipements résolument novateurs.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nachdem sich das Team nach einer Pause von 65 Jahren im Jahr 2202 neu formierte, versucht Goteki 45 jetzt, die enttäuschenden Mittelfeldplatzierungen zu verbessern, die das Team in der FX300-Liga bislang erreichte. Da das Team jetzt über finanzielle Mittel in der Größenordnung der führenden Teams verfügt, sind die neuen Anlagen seiner Zentrale auf der Insel Makana regelrecht mit modernster Technologie vollgestopft.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Riformatasi nel 2202 dopo una pausa di 65 anni, la squadra Goteki 45 si darà da fare per migliorare i risultati deludenti e mediocri conseguiti finora nella lega FX300. Grazie all'introduzione di nuovi capitali, che la rimettono in pari con le migliori squadre, i nuovi stabilimenti nella base operativa dell'isola di Makana sono rifornitissimi di strumentazioni all'avanguardia.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Reagrupado en 2202 tras un paréntesis de 65 años, el equipo Goteki 45 va a intentar mejorar los mediocres resultados conseguidos hasta el momento en la liga FX300. Ahora que posee recursos financieros equiparables a los de los equipos de cabeza, las nuevas instalaciones de su base de operaciones en la isla de Makana están literalmente repletas de equipamiento de vanguardia.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">65년 동안 개발을 중지한 Goteki 45팀은 2202년 재결성 되었습니다. FX300 리그에서는 평균 이하의 성적을 보였지만, 마카나 섬에 위치한 그들의 새로운 연구소에서는 이미 대다수 경쟁사들을 뛰어넘는 기체가 탄생하였습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Re-formed in 2202 after a 65 year gap in its history, the Goteki 45 team will look to improve on the disappointing mid-pack results they've achieved to-date in the FX300 League. Now bestowed with financial resources on-par with the leading teams, the new facilities at their base of operations on Makana Island are literally packed with equipment that's ahead of the curve.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Goteki 45在經歷了65年的空白期之後於2202年重組，並努力改善他們迄今為止在FX300聯賽中令人失望的戰績。現在他們獲得了與頂級車隊不相上下的財政資源支持，其設在Makana Island的基地所配置的全新設備皆是最先進的新穎裝備。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Goteki 45在經歷了65年的空白期之後於2202年重組，並努力改善他們迄今為止在FX300聯賽中令人失望的戰績。現在他們獲得了與頂級車隊不相上下的財政資源支持，其設在Makana Island的基地所配置的全新設備皆是最先進的新穎裝備。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">EGX_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Formed in 2172 when F9000 League superpowers Xios and EG-R merged, EG-X was something of an unknown quantity going into the inaugural season of the FX350 League. It turned out that they were more than ready to go racing, though, scoring a number of high placed finishes with relative ease for a team that did not contest the FX300 League.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Constituée en 2172 lors de la fusion des superpuissances de la catégorie F9000 qu'étaient Xios et EG-R, l'écurie EG-X demeurait une inconnue à l'instauration de la ligue FX350. Il s'est toutefois avéré qu'elle était largement prête à concourir, ce qu'elle a démontré en obtenant de bons classements avec une relative aisance... surtout pour une équipe absente du championnat FX300.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Im Jahr 2172, als sich mit Xios und EG-R zwei Supermächte der F9000-Liga zusammenschlossen, war EG-X nichts weiter als eine unbekannte Größe, die in die Premierensaison der FX350-Liga startete. Wie sich allerdings herausstellte, schöpfte das Team in den Rennen sein Potenzial optimal aus. Mit erstaunlicher Leichtigkeit für ein Team, das in der FX300-Liga nicht angetreten war, erreichte es Platzierungen in den vorderen Rängen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nata nel 2172 dalla fusione delle superpotenze Xios ed EG-R della lega F9000, la EG-X rappresentava l'incognita per la stagione inaugurale della lega FX350, ma ha saputo subito dimostrare di essere pronta a gareggiare, avendo tagliato il traguardo tra le prime posizioni in diverse occasioni e con una certa facilità, nonostante la squadra non avesse corso nella lega FX300.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fundado en 2172 tras la fusión de EG-R y Xios, dos superpotencias de la liga F9000; EG-X era un equipo desconocido que participó en la primera temporada de la liga FX350. Resultó estar más que preparado para la competición, y consiguió buenas clasificaciones con relativa facilidad para un equipo sin experiencia en la liga FX300.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">2172년, F9000 리그의 양대 산맥 Xios와 EG-R이 합병하자 EG-X는 들뜬 꿈을 안고 FX350 리그로 향했습니다. 결과는 예상보다 훨씬 좋았습니다! FX300를 거치지 않고 올라온 팀에 걸맞지 않게, 상위에 속하는 기록들이 배출되었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Formed in 2172 when F9000 League superpowers Xios and EG-R merged, EG-X was something of an unknown quantity going into the inaugural season of the FX350 League. It turned out that they were more than ready to go racing, though, scoring a number of high placed finishes with relative ease for a team that did not contest the FX300 League.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">EG-X是在F9000聯賽的超級車隊Xios和EG-R合併之後在2172年成立的車隊，在參加FX350聯賽的首個賽季時，其實力是一個未知之數。雖然他們沒有參加過FX300聯賽，但仍能多次在賽事中輕易奪得高名次，證明他們實力出眾。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">EG-X是在F9000聯賽的超級車隊Xios和EG-R合併之後在2172年成立的車隊，在參加FX350聯賽的首個賽季時，其實力是一個未知之數。雖然他們沒有參加過FX300聯賽，但仍能多次在賽事中輕易奪得高名次，證明他們實力出眾。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ASSEGAI_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Continuing in their tradition of producing craft with exceptional handling characteristics, the Assegai team have managed to improve the top end performance for their FX350/FX400 chassis, too.  Another welcome improvement is a minor upgrade to the shield durability over the FX300 craft, which means that Assegai fans can be confident of seeing strong performances at the head of the pack in 2207 and beyond.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fidèle à sa tradition de constructeur de vaisseaux dotés d'une maniabilité exceptionnelle, l'écurie Assegai est également parvenue à améliorer les impressionnantes performances de son châssis de catégorie FX350/FX400. La légère amélioration apportée à l'endurance du bouclier du vaisseau de FX300 a également été salutaire, permettant aux fans d'Assegai de s'attendre à voir évoluer les vaisseaux de l'écurie en tête de peloton en 2207 et au-delà.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ganz im Sinne seiner Tradition, Schiffe mit außergewöhnlichen Handling-Eigenschaften herzustellen, ist es dem Team Assegai gelungen, auch die Höchstleistungen seines FX350/FX400-Chassis zu verbessern. Eine weitere willkommene Verbesserung ist eine kleine Aufwertung der Widerstandsfähigkeit des Schildes gegenüber dem FX300-Schiff. Assegai-Fans können also zuversichtlich sein, im Jahr 2207 und darüber hinaus eine herausragende Rolle des Teams im vorderen Bereich des Feldes zu erleben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Proseguendo la tradizione di produrre navi con manovrabilità fenomenale, la squadra Assegai è riuscita anche ad affinare le prestazioni elevate dei telai FX350/FX400. Tra le migliorie va annoverato il ritocco alla durevolezza dello scudo del telaio FX300, che sembra promettere ai fan della Assegai ottime prestazioni nelle gare del 2207 e degli anni successivi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fiel a su costumbre, el equipo Assegai ha creado una nave con una capacidad de maniobra excepcional, y ha conseguido mejorar la velocidad punta de sus chasis para las ligas FX350/FX400. Otra mejora bien recibida ha sido una pequeña actualización en la resistencia del escudo que cubre la nave para la liga FX300, lo que significa que los fans de Assegai serán testigos de excepcionales actuaciones en cabeza de carrera desde 2207 en adelante.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">최고의 반응 속도를 지닌 기체를 양산하는 회사에 걸맞게 Assegai 팀은 FX350 / FX400 급의 기체들을 개조하는데 성공했습니다. FX300을 위한 기체에는 더욱 우수한 실드가 주어졌으며, 이는 Assegai의 팬들이 2207년도의 시즌부터 향상된 성적을 기대하도록 만들었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Continuing in their tradition of producing craft with exceptional handling characteristics, the Assegai team have managed to improve the top end performance for their FX350/FX400 chassis, too.  Another welcome improvement is a minor upgrade to the shield durability over the FX300 craft, which means that Assegai fans can be confident of seeing strong performances at the head of the pack in 2207 and beyond.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Assegai車隊在貫徹其精巧的操控設計的同時，亦不斷改進他們FX350／FX400底盤的高端性能。另一個讓人驚喜的改進是FX300飛船防護罩的耐久力獲得輕微的升級，意味著Assegai的擁護者們在2207年及以後將可看到車隊令人驚喜的突出表現。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Assegai車隊在貫徹其精巧的操控設計的同時，亦不斷改進他們FX350／FX400底盤的高端性能。另一個讓人驚喜的改進是FX300飛船防護罩的耐久力獲得輕微的升級，意味著Assegai的擁護者們在2207年及以後將可看到車隊令人驚喜的突出表現。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">AURICOM_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Auricom have been muted in their preparation for the inaugural season of the FX400 Racing League, with little being seen of their new ship outside of private testing. Their entry has also been uncharacteristically late, and nothing is known of their pilot roster for the 2207 campaign.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Auricom n'a guère communiqué sur ses préparatifs en vue de la saison inaugurale de la catégorie FX400, et peu d'informations ont filtré à l'issue des essais privés. L'inscription de l'écurie a également été fort tardive, et l'on ne sait rien de sa liste de pilotes pour la saison 2207.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Auricom hat sich bei den Vorbereitungen für die Premierensaison der FX400-Rennliga bedeckt gehalten. Das neue Schiff des Teams konnte folglich außerhalb privater Tests kaum begutachtet werden. Der Beitritt des Teams geschah zudem ungewöhnlich spät, und über die Pilotenliste für die Kampagne 2207 ist nichts bekannt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La preparazione Auricom per la sessione inaugurale della lega FX400 si è svolta nella massima segretezza: delle loro navi, collaudate privatamente, si sa ben poco. L'iscrizione è arrivata stranamente in ritardo e non si conosce nemmeno l'elenco dei piloti che parteciperanno alle gare del 2207.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Auricom ha guardado el más estricto silencio durante su preparación para la temporada de la liga de carreras FX400. Poco ha trascendido acerca de su nave. Su inscripción también ha sido una de las últimas, y no se sabe nada de su elenco de pilotos para la campaña de 2207.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Auricom은 FX400의 첫 시즌 개막 전까지 완벽한 기밀 작전을 지켜 욌습니다. 철저한 보안 수칙 속에 치러진 테스트에서도 아무런 정보가 유출되지 않았으며, 2207년 시즌에 임하는 그들의 기체에 대한 사항은 밝혀진 바 없습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Auricom have been muted in their preparation for the inaugural season of the FX400 Racing League, with little being seen of their new ship outside of private testing. Their entry has also been uncharacteristically late, and nothing is known of their pilot roster for the 2207 campaign.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Auricom已經開始為FX400聯賽的首個賽季秘密進行準備，他們的全新飛船除了在不對外公開的測試以外幾乎從未曝光。他們的參賽選手也一反常態的遲遲不明，參加2207年比賽的駕駛員名單到現時還沒有半點消息。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Auricom已經開始為FX400聯賽的首個賽季秘密進行準備，他們的全新飛船除了在不對外公開的測試以外幾乎從未曝光。他們的參賽選手也一反常態的遲遲不明，參加2207年比賽的駕駛員名單到現時還沒有半點消息。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">HARIMAU_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Harimau will be another team that are arriving late to the FX400 party, having focused most of their recent energies on promoting their international campaign to repopulate suitable parts of the world with genetically engineered tigers.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Harimau se distingue également par son arrivée tardive en FX400, dans la mesure où, dernièrement, la société s'est essentiellement concentrée sur sa campagne médiatique internationale pour l'introduction dans les régions adaptées de tigres issus du génie génétique.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Harimau ist ein weiteres Team, das den Anschluss an die FX400-Klasse erst spät gefunden hat. Den Großteil seiner Energie hat das Team in jüngster Zeit für sein internationales Projekt aufgewendet, an geeigneten Orten auf der Welt genetisch rekonstruierte Tiger neu anzusiedeln.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La squadra Harimau si è iscritta con un certo ritardo alle gare FX400, avendo di recente concentrato le proprie risorse sulla promozione della campagna internazionale per la ripopolazione di alcune zone del mondo con tigri clonate.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Harimau es otra incorporación de última hora a la liga FX400, tras centrar casi todas sus energías recientes en promocionar su campaña internacional para repoblar zonas apropiadas con tigres modificados genéticamente.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Harimau 역시 FX400 급의 기체에는 처음으로 참가하는 팀입니다. 그들의 이전 사업은 국제적으로 멸종 위기에 처한 호랑이들을 복원하기 위한 유전자 보호 분야였습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Harimau will be another team that are arriving late to the FX400 party, having focused most of their recent energies on promoting their international campaign to repopulate suitable parts of the world with genetically engineered tigers.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Harimau將成為FX400聯賽中另一個晚到的車隊，因為他們近來大部分的精力都集中在他們的國際活動上，在合適地區繁殖經基因改造的老虎。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Harimau將成為FX400聯賽中另一個晚到的車隊，因為他們近來大部分的精力都集中在他們的國際活動上，在合適地區繁殖經基因改造的老虎。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MIRAGE_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Formed in 2202 by the wealthy sand baron Sheikh Mani Zayed, the Mirage team will take the Mantis chassis perfected at the Mirage Anti-Gravity Excellence Centre (MAGEC) outside Dubai, and field elite pilots who have graduated from the centre's developmental programme.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fondée en 2202 par le riche baron du désert Sheikh Mani Zayed, l'écurie Mirage utilisera le châssis Mantis perfectionné au sein du Mirage Anti-Gravity Excellence Centre (MAGEC), près de Dubaï, et fera appel à des pilotes d'élite diplômés du programme de formation de ce centre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Team Mirage, das im Jahr 2202 vom wohlhabenden Sandbaron Scheich Mani Zayed gegründet wurde, perfektionierte seine Mantis-Karosserie im Mirage Anti-Gravity Excellence Centre (MAGEC) vor den Toren Dubais und wird erfahrene Elite-Piloten einsetzen, die das Entwicklungsprogramm des Zentrums absolviert haben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Formata nel 2202 dal ricco sceicco Mani Zayed, la squadra Mirage porterà in pista il suo telaio Mantis, perfezionato a Dubai presso il centro di perfezione antigravitazionale (MAGEC, Mirage Anti-Gravity Excellence Centre), e impiegherà piloti d'élite che hanno superato il programma di addestramento del centro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Creado en 2202 por el poderoso barón de las arenas, el jeque Mani Zayed, el equipo Mirage empleará el chasis Mantis, perfeccionado en el Centro Mirage para la Excelencia Gravitatoria (MAGEC) a las afueras de Dubái, así como los mejores pilotos de campo graduados en su programa de desarrollo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">2202년, Sheikh Mani Zayed라는 사막의 대부호에 의해 창설된 Mirage 팀은 두바이에 위치한 Mirage 반중력 초월 센터에서 엘리트 파일럿을 양성하며 준비를 거듭해 왔습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Formed in 2202 by the wealthy sand baron Sheikh Mani Zayed, the Mirage team will take the Mantis chassis perfected at the Mirage Anti-Gravity Excellence Centre (MAGEC) outside Dubai, and field elite pilots who have graduated from the centre's developmental programme.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">由富有的沙漠大亨Sheikh Mani Zayed於2202年組成的Mirage車隊，將採用在位於杜拜外的Mirage Anti-Gravity Excellence Centre (MAGEC) 製成的Mantis底盤，並派出在中心的發展項目畢業的精英駕駛員參賽。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">由富有的沙漠大亨Sheikh Mani Zayed於2202年組成的Mirage車隊，將採用在位於杜拜外的Mirage Anti-Gravity Excellence Centre (MAGEC) 製成的Mantis底盤，並派出在中心的發展項目畢業的精英駕駛員參賽。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ICARAS_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Icaras were the perennial underdogs in the F7200 era racing of the early 2100's. Scoffed at by the larger teams, but firm favourite with the fans, Burnston Burns' outfit never quite enjoyed the success of the elite teams. For them, finishing a race was a victory in itself – doing so in the top half of the field was cause for champagne and back slapping behaviour that those at the head of the grid would think beneath them.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Icaras n'a cessé de jouer de malchance à l'époque de la catégorie F7200, au début des années 2100. Raillée par les écuries plus puissantes, mais très appréciée des fans, l'équipe de Burnston Burns n'a jamais connu le succès embrassé par les écuries d'élite. Terminer une course était une victoire en soi, et terminer dans la moitié supérieure du classement donnait lieu à des libations qui consternaient les écuries championnes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Icaras zählte zu den ewigen Verlierern in der F7200-Rennsportära im frühen 22. Jahrhundert. Burnston Burns' Truppe, die von den größeren Teams verspottet wurde, aber bei den Fans überaus beliebt war, erreichte nie die Erfolge der Elite-Teams. Stattdessen wurde bereits die Beendigung eines Rennens fast wie ein Sieg gefeiert. Wenn dabei eine Platzierung in der ersten Hälfte des Starterfelds heraussprang, war dies sogar Grund genug für Unmengen Champagner und viel Schulterklopfen – ein Verhalten, das die Besten der Serie nur belächelten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Icaras non è mai stata la favorita nell'era delle corse F7200 agli inizi del 2100. Derisa dalle squadre più grandi, ma amata dai fan, la livrea di Burnston Burns non è mai riuscita a eguagliare il successo delle squadre maggiori. Arrivare al traguardo rappresentava di per sé una vittoria, arrivare a ridosso delle migliori era motivo di grandi festeggiamenti e compiacimento per aver saputo tener testa alle più forti in gara.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Icaras era el eterno perdedor de las carreras F7200 a comienzos del siglo XXII. La firma de Burnston Burns, objeto de las burlas del resto de los equipos pero muy querida por la afición, nunca disfrutó del éxito de las escuderías de élite. Para ellos, el simple hecho de terminar una carrera ya era una victoria. Hacerlo en la primera mitad de la tabla era motivo de celebración con champán y de grandes abrazos, algo que los que estaban por delante de ellos en la parrilla considerarían humillante.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Icaras는 2100년대 초반, 초기 F7200 시절의 약체였습니다. 그러나 팬들의 열화와 같은 성원에 힘입어 Burnston Burns의 팀은 이제 엘리트 조직의 칭호를 얻어가고 있습니다. 그들에게는 레이스를 완수하는 것 자체가 작은 승리이며 기쁨입니다. 그러나 그들의 겸소한 태도는 상위 랭커들의 경멸과 질시를 유발하며 경쟁의 드라마를 만들어가고 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Icaras were the perennial underdogs in the F7200 era racing of the early 2100's. Scoffed at by the larger teams, but firm favourite with the fans, Burnston Burns' outfit never quite enjoyed the success of the elite teams. For them, finishing a race was a victory in itself – doing so in the top half of the field was cause for champagne and back slapping behaviour that those at the head of the grid would think beneath them.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Icaras在2100年早期的F7200時代的比賽中長期處於下風。總是被大型車隊看扁，卻為支持者們所鍾愛的Burnston Burns的隊員們從未像頂級車隊一樣享受過勝利的喜悅。對他們來說，完成比賽本身就是一個勝利，能擠身參賽隊伍的前半排名更是值得開香檳慶祝，這對於那些在比賽中名列前茅的隊伍來說也許會覺得微不足道。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Icaras在2100年早期的F7200時代的比賽中長期處於下風。總是被大型車隊看扁，卻為支持者們所鍾愛的Burnston Burns的隊員們從未像頂級車隊一樣享受過勝利的喜悅。對他們來說，完成比賽本身就是一個勝利，能擠身參賽隊伍的前半排名更是值得開香檳慶祝，這對於那些在比賽中名列前茅的隊伍來說也許會覺得微不足道。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>