<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">High Rollers Vest - Reward (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Veste de Flambeur - Récompense (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">High-Roller-Weste - Preisversion (Weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Gilè dei Grandi Giocatori - Premio (Femmina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chaleco para Jugadores de Alto Calibre - Recompensa (Mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">High Rollers Vest Reward (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Congratulations on becoming one of our exclusive high rollers. The high rollers lounge is where you'll play the top casino gamers. This High Rollers Vest provides you with unlimited access to the highest stakes tables in our High Rollers Lounge. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Félicitations, vous êtes devenu(e) l'un de nos flambeurs exclusifs. Le salon des flambeurs est l'endroit où vous vous frotterez aux meilleurs joueurs du casino. Cette Veste de Flambeur vous garantit l'accès aux tables aux mises les plus élevées dans notre Salon des Flambeurs. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Herzlichen Glückwunsch, dass sie einer unserer exklusiven high roller geworden sind. In der high-roller-lounge werden sie mit den besten kasino-spielern spielen. Diese High-Roller-Weste bietet Ihnen in unserer High-Roller-Lounge unbegrenzten zugang zu den tischen mit den höchsten einsätzen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Congratulazioni per essere diventato uno dei nostri grandi giocatori di èlite. La sala dei grandi giocatori è il luogo dove potrete confrontarvi con il top dei giocatori del casinò. Questo Gilè per Grandi Giocatori vi consentirà un accesso illimitato ai tavoli della Sala dei Grandi Giocatori dove le puntate sono le più alte.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Felicidades por convertirte en uno de nuestros exclusivos jugadores de alto calibre. El salón para jugadores de alto calibre es donde jugarás con los mejores jugadores del casino. Este Chaleco para Jugadores de Alto Calibre te proporciona acceso ilimitado a las mesa de apuestas más altas en el Salón para Jugadores de Alto Calibre. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Congratulations on becoming one of our exclusive high rollers. The high rollers lounge is where you'll play the top casino gamers. This High Rollers Vest provides you with unlimited access to the highest stakes tables in our High Rollers Lounge. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>