<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Street Style - VIBEZ Bundle 02</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Street Style - VIBEZ Lot 02</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Street Style - VIBEZ Paket 02</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Street Style - Set VIBEZ 02</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Street Style - VIBEZ Pack 02</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The VIBEZ catalogue is out with a new collection of your favourite Street Style clothes in an arrangement of bright, vibrant colours.\n
\n
This bundle contains:\n
(1) Street Style - Superstar Cropped Jacket - Pink (Women)\n
(2) Street Style - Superstar Heart Sports Jersey - Purple (Women)\n
(3) Street Style - Megastar Dress and Jacket - Neon Pink (Women)\n
(4) Street Style - Shoulder Slung Top -  Purple (Women)\n
(5) Street Style - Trend Setter Denim Waistcoat -  Pink (Women)\n
\n
Exclusive to the VIBEZ collection! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le catalogue VIBEZ est désormais disponible, avec sa nouvelle collection de vêtements Street Style dans une gamme de couleurs chatoyantes.\n
\n
Ce lot contient :\n
(1) Street Style - Veste courte de superstar - Rose (Femme)\n
(2) Street Style - Tenue de sport Superstar jersey - Pourpre (Femme)\n
(3) Street Style - Robe et veste de superstar - Rose (Femme)\n
(4) Street Style - Haut à col échancré - Pourpre (Femme)\n
(5) Street Style - Gilet en jean Créateur de tendance - Rose (Femme)\n
\n
En exclusivité dans la collection VIBEZ ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der VIBEZ Katalog ist da! Hier finden Sie die neue Kollektion der beliebten Street Style Marke in vielen hellen, leuchtenden Farben.\n
\n
Dieses Bündel enthält:\n
(1) Street Style - Kurze Superstar-Jacke - Rosa (Damen)\n
(2) Street Style - Superstar Herz-Sporttrikot - Lila (Damen)\n
(3) Street Style - Megastar-Kleid und Jacke - Rosa (Damen)\n
(4) Street Style - Schulterfreies Oberteil - Lila (Damen)\n
(5) Street Style - Trendsetter Jeansweste - Rosa (Damen)\n
\n
Exklusiv von der VIBEZ Kollektion! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">È uscito il catalogo VIBEZ con una nuova serie di articoli di abbigliamento Street Style caratterizzati da colori brillanti e vivaci.\n
\n
Il set comprende:\n
(1) Street Style - Giacchina corta Superstar - Rosa (Donna)\n
(2) Street Style - Maglia sportiva Superstar con cuore - Porpora (Donna)\n
(3) Street Style - Vestito e giacca Megastar - Rosa (Donna)\n
(4) Street Style - Maglietta con spalle scoperte - Porpora (Donna)\n
(5) Street Style - Trend Setter Gilet in Denim - Rosa (Donna)\n
\n
In esclusiva per la collezione VIBEZ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ya ha salido el catálogo VIBEZ con una nueva colección de tu ropa favorita Street Style, en una composición de colores brillantes y vibrantes.\n
\n
Este pack contiene:\n
(1) Street Style - Chaqueta corta de Superstar - Rosa (Mujer)\n
(2) Street Style - Superstar Heart  Camiseta deportiva - Púrpura (Mujer)\n
(3) Street Style - Vestido y chaqueta de Megastar - Rosa (Mujer)\n
(4) Street Style - Top de tirantes - Púrpura (Mujer)\n
(5) Street Style - Trend Setter Chaleco vaquero - Rosa (Mujer)\n
\n
¡En exclusiva en la colección VIBEZ! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>