<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Radec's Combat Trousers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pantalon de combat de Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Radecs Kampfhose</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pantaloni da combattimento di Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pantalones de combate de Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">라덱 대령의 전투복 하의</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Radec's Combat Trousers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Radec戰鬥軍褲</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Radec戰鬥軍褲</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Radec's Combat Trousers</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Descr</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A modified version of the standard HPC combat trousers worn by Helghast army officers, Colonel Radec’s trousers are reinforced with ceramic-composite armor plates to cover the knees and shins. The flared thighs double as battery storage compartments for the optical camouflage unit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Version améliorée des pantalon de combat traditionnels portés par les officiers de l'armée helghaste, le pantalon du colonel Radec sont renforcés de plaques métalliques en composite céramique pour protéger les genoux et les tibias. Les poches au niveau des cuisses permettent également de ranger les batteries de l'unité de camouflage optique. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine modifizierte Version der HPC-Standard-Kampfhose, die von den Offizieren der Helghast-Armee getragen wird. Colonel Radecs Hose ist mit Panzerplatten aus einem Keramikverbund verstärkt, die Knie und Schienbeine bedecken. Die weiten Oberschenkel dienen als Batterielager für die optische Tarnungseinheit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los pantalones de Radec, una versión modificada de los estándar HPC de combate vestidos por los oficiales del ejército Helghast, están reforzados con placas antibalas de cerámica en las rodillas y en las espinillas. Los muslos cuentan con compartimentos para almacenar las baterías de la unidad de camuflaje óptico. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">헬가스트군 장교들에게 지급되는 HPC 전투복을 변형하여, 라덱의 전투복 하의는 세라믹 복합 판금을 덧대 무릎과 종아리를 보호합니다. 허벅지의 수납공간은 광학 은폐장비를 위한 배터리를 보관하는데 사용되었습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A modified version of the standard HPC combat trousers worn by Helghast army officers, Colonel Radec’s trousers are reinforced with ceramic-composite armor plates to cover the knees and shins. The flared thighs double as battery storage compartments for the optical camouflage unit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">此軍褲為赫爾蓋斯特士兵的標準HPC戰鬥褲的改良版。Radec上校的軍褲以陶瓷複合裝甲強化膝蓋和小腿部位，喇叭形的大腿部份亦經過加大，可用來儲存隱形裝置的電池。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">此軍褲為赫爾蓋斯特士兵的標準HPC戰鬥褲的改良版。Radec上校的軍褲以陶瓷複合裝甲強化膝蓋和小腿部位，喇叭形的大腿部份亦經過加大，可用來儲存隱形裝置的電池。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A modified version of the standard HPC combat trousers worn by Helghast army officers, Colonel Radec’s trousers are reinforced with ceramic-composite armor plates to cover the knees and shins. The flared thighs double as battery storage compartments for the optical camouflage unit. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>