<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Taisho-era Student Hakama Outfit Set (Light Blue/Black, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set hakama d'étudiante de l'ère Taishō (bleu clair/noir, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Set: Schüler der Taisho-Zeit (hellblau/schwarz, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set completo hakama da studentessa dell'era Taisho (azzurro e nero, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego con el atuendo del hakama de estudiante de la era Taisho (celeste y negro, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">大正時代風の学生袴着こなしセット（水色／黒・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Taisho-era Student Hakama Outfit Set (Light Blue/Black, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 5-piece set consisting of a ponytail &amp; ribbon, clothes with a hakama, boots, and umbrellas (locomotion and furniture) of a Japanese student in the Taisho era.\nClothing Defensive Strength: ★\nClothing Youth Level: ★★★\nLocomotion Speed: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Taisho-era Student Ponytail &amp; Ribbon (Blue, Women) (Head)\n- Taisho-era Student Clothes &amp; Hakama (Light Blue/Black, Women) (Outfits)\n- Taisho-era Student Boots (White, Women) (Feet)\n- Taisho-era Student Umbrella in Umbrella Stand (White) (Ornaments)\n- Locomotion - Taisho-era Student Umbrella (White) (Portables)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 5 pièces incluant une queue de cheval avec un ruban, des vêtements avec un hakama, des bottes et des ombrelles (locomotion et meubles) pour une étudiante japonaise de l'ère Taishō.\nDéfense : ★\nJeunesse : ★★★\nVitesse : ★★★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Q. de cheval et ruban d'étudiante de l'ère Taishō (bleu, femme) (Tête)\n- Hakama d'étudiante de l'ère Taishō (bleu clair/noir, femme) (Tenues)\n- Bottes d'étudiante de l'ère Taishō (blanches, femme) (Pieds)\n- Ombrelle d'étudiante de l'ère Taishō sur support (blanche) (Décoration)\n- Locomotion - Ombrelle d'étudiante de l'ère Taishō (blanche) (Objets portables)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 5-teiliges Set, das Pferdeschwanz und Schleife, Kleidung mit Hakama, Stiefel und Schirme (Bewegungsgegenstände und Dekoration) einer japanischen Schülerin der Taisho-Zeit enthält.\nVerteidigung (der Kleidung): ★\nJugendlichkeit (der Kleidung): ★★★\nBewegungsgeschwindigkeit: ★★★\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Schüler der Taisho-Zeit: Pferdeschwanz &amp; Schleife (blau, für Frauen) (Kopf)\n- Schüler der Taisho-Zeit: Kleidung &amp; Hakama (hellblau/schwarz, für Frauen) (Outfits)\n- Schüler der Taisho-Zeit: Stiefel (weiß, Für Frauen) (Füße)\n- Schüler der Taisho-Zeit: Schirm in Schirmständer (weiß) (Verzierungen)\n- Bewegungsgegenstand - Schüler der Taisho-Zeit: Schirm (weiß) (Tragbare Objekte)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set formato da 5 elementi comprendente un'acconciatura a coda di cavallo con fiocco, dei vestiti e un hakama, un paio di stivali e degli ombrelli parasole (Locomotion e da arredamento) da studentessa giapponese dell'era Taisho.\nDifesa dell'abbigliamento: ★\nLivello giovinezza dell'abbigliamento: ★★★\nVelocità di spostamento: ★★★\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Coda di cavallo e fiocco da studentessa dell'era Taisho (blu, da donna) (cappelli)\n- Vestiti e hakama da studentessa dell'era Taisho (azzurri e nero, da donna) (aspetti)\n- Stivali da studentessa dell'era Taisho (bianchi, da donna) (Piedi)\n- Ombrello nel portaombrelli da studentessa dell'era Taisho (bianco) (décoration)\n- Ombrello da studentessa dell'era Taisho (bianco) (oggetti portatili)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettiva categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de cinco artículos que incluye un uniforme con hakama, botas, y paraguas (locomoción y mobiliario) de una estudiante en la era Taisho.\nDefensa de la prenda: ★\nNivel de juventud de la prenda: ★★★\nVelocidad de locomoción: ★★★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Coleta con lazo de estudiante de la era Taisho (azul, mujer) (cabeza)\n- Uniforme y hakama de estudiante de la era Taisho (celeste y negro, mujer) (trajes)\n- Botas de estudiante de la era Taisho (blancas, mujer) (pies)\n- Paraguas de estudiante de la era Taisho en paragüero (blanco) (adornos)\n- Locomoción - Paraguas de estudiante de la era Taisho (blanco) (portátiles)\n\n* Adquiriendo este conjunto, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">日本の大正時代風の、ポニーテールとリボン、学生着物と袴、ブーツ、傘（ロコモーション、家具）を含む、計５点セット。\n服装の防御力：　★\n服装の青春度：　★★★\nロコモーションの移動速度：　◆◆◆\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・大正時代風の学生のポニーテールとリボン（青・女性）/頭\n・大正時代風の学生着物と袴（水色／黒・女性）/組み合わせ\n・大正時代風の学生ブーツ（白・女性）/靴\n・傘立てに入れた大正時代風の学生傘（白）/装飾品\n・LMO-大正時代風の学生傘（白）/ポータブルアイテム\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 5-piece set consisting of a ponytail &amp; ribbon, clothes with a hakama, boots, and umbrellas (locomotion and furniture) of a Japanese student in the Taisho era.\nClothing Defensive Strength: ★\nClothing Youth Level: ★★★\nLocomotion Speed: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Taisho-era Student Ponytail &amp; Ribbon (Blue, Women) (Head)\n- Taisho-era Student Clothes &amp; Hakama (Light Blue/Black, Women) (Outfits)\n- Taisho-era Student Boots (White, Women) (Feet)\n- Taisho-era Student Umbrella in Umbrella Stand (White) (Ornaments)\n- Locomotion - Taisho-era Student Umbrella (White) (Portables)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
