<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Supercar - Saragat F-Spec - Black &amp; Gold</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Supercar - Saragat F-Spec - Noir et Or</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Supercar - Saragat F-Spec - Schwarz und Gold</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Supercar - Saragat F-Spec - Nero e Oro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Supercar - Saragat F-Spec - Negro y Oro</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Saragat is probably the biggest name in motor sport and the Saragat F-Spec is their top tier race car.\n
Shrink your avatar down and jump into the driver's seat of this supercar locomotion.\n
\n
This locomotion object will boost your speed:\n
・Standard = 5.25 m/s\n
\n
※ This item is a portable item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Saragat est probablement le nom le plus célèbre en sport automobile et la Saragat F-Spec est leur voiture de course la plus en vue.\n
Réduisez votre avatar et sautez sur le siège conducteur de cette supercar.\n
\n
Ce moyen de déplacement vous permettra d'augmenter votre vitesse : \n
・Standard = 5,25 m/s\n
\n
※ Cet article est un article portable. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Saragat ist einer der bedeutendsten Namen im Autorennen und der Saragat F-Spec einer der besten Rennwagen.\n
Schrumpfe deinen Avatar und spring in den Fahrersitz dieser Supercar-Locomotion-Funktion.\n
\n
Dieses Locomotion-Objekt macht Sie noch schneller:\n
・Standard = 5,25 m/s\n
\n
※ Bei diesem Artikel handelt es sich um einen tragbaren Artikel. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Saragat è probabilmente il nome più importante nel settore degli sport automobilistici e la Saragat F-Spec è la sua auto da corsa d'alta classe.\n
Rimpicciolisci il tuo avatar e mettiti al volante di questa supercar.\n
\n
Questo oggetto di trasporto farà aumentare la tua velocità:\n
・Standard = 5,25 m/s\n
\n
※ Questo articolo è portatile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Saragat es probablemente el nombre más importante en el deporte del motor y el Saragat F-Spec es su coche de carreras más destacado.\n
Encoge tu avatar y ocupa el asiento de conductor de esta animación de súper coche.\n
\n
Este artículo dinámico potenciará tu velocidad:\n
・Estándar = 5,25 m/s\n
\n
※ Éste es un artículo móvil. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>