<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Emerald, Ruby, and Sapphire Suit Bundle (Male and Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack de tenues Émeraude, Rubis et Saphir (pour homme et femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Smaragd-, Rubin- und Saphiranzug-Paket (Herren und Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completi Smeraldo, Rubino e Zaffiro (uomo e donna) </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de traje esmeralda, rubí y zafiro (hombre y mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Emerald, Ruby, and Sapphire Suit Bundle (Male and Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bundle includes male and female Emerald, Ruby, and Sapphire suits each consisting of a jacket, cane, trousers, and shoes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce pack comprend les tenues Émeraude, Rubis et Saphir. Chaque tenue est composée d'une veste, d'une canne, d'un pantalon et de chaussures. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Paket beinhaltet einen Smaragd-, einen Rubin- und einen Saphiranzug für Herren und Damen, die jeweils aus Jacke, Stock, Hose und Schuhen bestehen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo pacchetto comprende completi Smeraldo, Rubino e Zaffiro da uomo e donna. Ciascun completo include una giacca, un bastone, pantaloni e scarpe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este conjunto incluye trajes esmeralda, rubí y zafiro para hombre y mujer y cada uno cuenta con chaqueta, bastón, pantalones y zapatos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Own the Shiny Diamond Suit (Male) and/or Diamond Suit (Female) and get these suits at a discount. Bundle includes the male and female Emerald, Ruby, and Sapphire suits each consisting of a jacket, cane, pants, and shoes. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>