<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Vampire 7-piece Set (White, Men)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set 7 pièces de vampire (blanc, homme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">7-teiliges Vampirkostüm-Set (weiß, für Männer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set vampiro 7 elementi (bianco, da uomo)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de siete artículos de vampiro (blancos, hombre)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ヴァンパイア７点セット（ホワイト・男性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* ドラキュラセット・白</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Vampire 7-piece Set (White, Men)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Vampire set of white items with two faces, a coat, a coat with a cape, trousers, boots, and gloves.\nDefensive Strength: None~★\nMagic Power: ★~★★\nUndeadness: ★~★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Fanged Vampire Face (White, Men) (Head)\n- Vampire Face (White, Men) (Head)\n- Vampire Coat (With Cape, White, Men) (Tops)\n- Vampire Coat (White, Men) (Tops)\n- Vampire Trousers (White, Men) (Bottoms)\n- Vampire Gloves (White, Men) (Hand)\n- Vampire Boots (White, Men) (Shoes)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.\n*"Vampire Face" cannot be used in combination with jewelry or accessories.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set d'objet de vampire blancs avec deux têtes, un manteau, un manteau avec une cape, un pantalon, des bottes et des gants.\nDéfense : None~★\nPouvoir Magique : ★~★★\nNiveau de non-vie : ★~★★★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Tête de vampire avec crocs (blancs, homme) (Tête)\n- Tête de vampire (blancs, homme) (Tête)\n- Manteau de vampire (avec cape, blanc, homme) (Hauts)\n- Manteau de vampire (blanc, homme) (Hauts)\n- Pantalon de vampire (blanc, homme) (Bas)\n- Gants de vampire (blancs, homme) (Mains)\n- Bottes de vampire (blanches, homme) (Chaussures)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.\n*La "Tête de vampire" ne peut être utilisée en combinaison avec des bijoux ou des accessoires.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Set eines weißen Vampirkostüms, das zwei Gesichter, einen Mantel, einen Mantel mit Cape, eine Hose, Stiefel und Handschuhe enthält.\nVerteidigung: Keine~★\nMagie: ★~★★\nUntot-Level: ★~★★★\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Vampirgesicht mit spitzen Eckzähnen (weiß, für Männer) (Kopfbedeckung)\n- Vampirgesicht (weiß, für Männer) (Kopfbedeckung)\n- Vampirmantel (mit Cape, weiß, für Männer) (Oberteile)\n- Vampirmantel weiß, für Männer) (Oberteile)\n- Vampirhose (weiß, für Männer) (Beinkleider)\n- Vampirhandschuhe (weiß, für Männer) (Hand)\n- Vampirstiefel (weiß, für Männer) (Schuhe)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.\n*"Vampirgesicht" kann nicht in Kombination mit Schmuck oder Accessoires verwendet werden.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set vampiro di colore bianco con due facce, una giacca, una giacca con mantello, pantaloni, stivali e guanti.\nDifesa: Nulla~★\nPotere magico: ★~★★\nLivello non-morto: ★~★★★\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti elementi:\n\n- Faccia di vampiro con i canini in mostra (occhi bianchi, da uomo) (testa)\n- Faccia di vampiro (occhi bianchi, da uomo) (testa)\n- Giacca da vampiro con mantello (bianca, da uomo) (parti superiori)\n- Giacca da vampiro (bianca, da uomo) (parti superiori)\n- Pantaloni da vampiro (bianchi, da uomo) (parti inferiori)\n- Guanti da vampiro (bianchi, da uomo) (mani)\n- Stivali da vampiro (bianchi, da uomo) (scarpe)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettiva categoria.\n* "Faccia di vampiro" non può essere usata in combinazione con gioielli o accessori.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de artículo vampíricos de color blanco, que incluye dos caras, chaquetón con y sin capa, pantalón, botas y guantes.\nDefensa: Ninguno~★\nPoder mágico: ★~★★\nInmortalidad: ★~★★★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Cara de vampiro con colmillos (blanco, hombre) (cabeza)\n- Cara de vampiro (blanco, hombre) (cabeza)\n- Chaquetón de vampiro (con capa, blanco, hombre) (torso)\n- Chaquetón de vampiro (blanco, hombre) (torso)\n- Pantalón de vampiro (blanco, hombre) (piernas)\n- Guantes de vampiro (blancos, hombre) (mano)\n- Botas de vampiro (blancas, hombre) (zapatos)\n\n*Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.\n*"Cara de vampiro" no se puede usar en combinación con joyas o accesorios.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">２種類のフェイス、コート、マント付きコート、ズボン、ブーツ、グローブがセットになった純白のヴァンパイアセット。\n防御力：　なし～★\n魔力：　★～★★\n不死度：　★～★★★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・牙を剥いたヴァンパイアフェイス（ホワイト・男性）/頭\n・ヴァンパイアフェイス（ホワイト・男性）/頭\n・ヴァンパイアのコート（マント付き・ホワイト・男性）/トップス\n・ヴァンパイアのコート（ホワイト・男性）/トップス\n・ヴァンパイアのズボン（ホワイト・男性）/ボトムス\n・ヴァンパイアのグローブ（ホワイト・男性）/手\n・ヴァンパイアのブーツ（ホワイト・男性）/靴\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。\n※「ヴァンパイアフェイス」はジュエリー、アクセサリーと合わせての使用は行えません。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Vampire set of white items with two faces, a coat, a coat with a cape, pants, boots, and gloves.\nDefensive Strength: None~★\nMagic Power: ★~★★\nUndeadness: ★~★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Fanged Vampire Face (White, Men) (Head)\n- Vampire Face (White, Men) (Head)\n- Vampire Coat (With Cape, White, Men) (Tops)\n- Vampire Coat (White, Men) (Tops)\n- Vampire Pants (White, Men) (Bottoms)\n- Vampire Gloves (White, Men) (Hand)\n- Vampire Boots (White, Men) (Shoes)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.\n*"Vampire Face" cannot be used in combination with jewelry or accessories.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
