<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gingerbread Advent Calender</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pain d'épices calendrier de l'avant</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Pfefferkuchen-Adventskalender</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Calendario dell'Avvento di Pan di Zenzero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Calendario de Adviento con pan de jengibre</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Come back each day to get your daily virtual chocolate.\n
\n
This is an active item. \n
\n
※ Active items provide more functionality than normal items. You may only place limited numbers of the active items in your apartment or clubhouse at any time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Revenez tous les jours pour avoir votre chocolat virtuel quotidien.\n
\n
Cet article est actif. \n
\n
※ Les articles actifs offrent davantage de fonctionnalités que les articles normaux. À tout moment, vous ne pouvez placer qu'un nombre limité d'articles actifs dans votre appartement ou votre club-house. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kommen Sie jeden Tag wieder und holen Sie sich Ihre tägliche virtuelle Schokolade.\n
\n
Dieser Artikel ist aktiv. \n
\n
※ Aktive Artikel bieten mehr Funktionalität als normale Artikel. Sie dürfen nur eine begrenzte Anzahl aktiver Artikel jeweils in Ihrem Apartment oder Clubhaus aufstellen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Torna ogni giorno per prenderti un cioccolatino virtuale.\n
\n
Questo articolo è attivo.\n
\n
※ Gli articoli attivi offrono maggiori funzionalità rispetto a quelli normali. Puoi posizionare solo un numero limitato di articoli attivi alla volta nel tuo appartamento o circolo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Vuelve cada día a por tu chocolate virtual diario.\n
\n
Éste es un artículo activo.\n
\n
※ Los artículos activos ofrecen más funcionalidad que los normales. Así, en todo momento, podrás ubicar sólo un número limitado de artículos activos en tu apartamento o tu club. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Denied</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sorry, this is not your advent calendar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Désolé, ce calendrier de l'avent n'est pas le vôtre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dies ist leider nicht Ihr Adventskalender.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Spiacenti, questo non è il tuo calendario dell'avvento</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lo sentimos, éste no es tu calendario de adviento</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Loading</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Please wait, loading calendar...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Veuillez patienter, chargement du calendrier en cours...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bitte warten Sie. Ihr Kalender wird geladen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caricamento calendario in corso, attendere...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Espere, por favor. El calendario se está cargando…</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Welcome</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to the VEEMEE Gingerbread Advent Calender; counting down the days until Christmas!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenu(e) au calendrier de l'avent en pain d'épices VEEMEE ; comptez les jours avant Noël !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen beim VEEMEE Lebkuchen-Adventskalender. Der Countdown bis Weihnachten läuft!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuto al Calendario dell'Avvento di Pan di Zenzero VEEMEE; facciamo il conto alla rovescia dei giorni che rimangono al Natale!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido al Calendario de adviento de pan de jengibre VEEMEE; ¡empieza la cuenta atrás hasta Navidad!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Legend_NoDoor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFT][RIGHT] Move Doors [DECLINE] Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFT][RIGHT] Déplacer les portes [DECLINE] Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFT][RIGHT] Türen verschieben [DECLINE] Abbrechen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFT][RIGHT] Sposta Porte [DECLINE] Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFT][RIGHT] Mover puertas [DECLINE] Salir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFT][RIGHT] Move Doors [ACCEPT] Open Door [DECLINE] Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFT][RIGHT] Déplacer les portes [ACCEPT] Ouvrir la porte [DECLINE] Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFT][RIGHT] Türen verschieben [ACCEPT] Tür öffnen [DECLINE] Abbrechen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFT][RIGHT] Sposta Porte [ACCEPT] Apri Porta [DECLINE] Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFT][RIGHT] Mover puertas [ACCEPT] Abrir puerta [DECLINE] Salir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Days</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Days To Go :</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nombre de jours restant :</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Noch xx Tage bis Weihnachten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Giorni rimanenti:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Días que faltan:</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">AllOpen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You've Opened All 24 Days! Hope you've been good this year!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez ouvert les 24 jours ! Nous espérons que vous avez été sage cette année !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben die Türen für alle 24 Tage geöffnet! Na, hoffentlich waren Sie auch schön brav dieses Jahr!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai aperto tutti e 24 i giorni! Speriamo che tu sia stato bravo quest'anno!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has abierto cada uno de los 24 días! ¡Espero que hayas sido bueno este año!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>