<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble – Classic</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble – Classique</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble – Klassisch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble - Classico</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cabin Boy en Problemas de trucha - Clásico</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble – Classic</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LOOT™’s Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble! is now available in this classic arcade style. This appliance lets you play the Cabin Boy game right in your very own PlayStation®Home Personal Spaces! Catch the fish Lil’ Dickie throws your way, keep Lil’ Missus from burning under the hot sun and watch out for Chairman Meow!! This awesome arcade is equipped with leaderboards, capers and unlockable items for your avatar! Start playing, LOOTers! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble! de LOOT™ est maintenant disponible dans ce jeu d'arcade classique. Cet appareil vous permet de jouer au jeu Cabin Boy dans votre espace personnel PlayStation®Home ! Attrapez les poissons que Lil’ Dickie envoie, empêcher Lil’ Missus de brûler au soleil et attention à Chairman Meow !! Ce fantastique jeu d'arcade contient des tableaux des meilleurs scores, des combines et des éléments impossibles à débloquer pour votre avatar ! Allez-y, jouez, LOOTers ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LOOT™’s Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble! gibt es jetzt in diesem klassischen Arcade-Stil. Mit dieser Anwendung kannst du das Spiel Cabin Boy  direkt in deinem eigenen persönlichen Raum auf PlayStation®Home spielen! Fang die Fische, die dir Lil’ Dickie zuwirft, pass auf, dass Lil’ Missus sich keinen Sonnebrand holt und gib immer acht auf Chairman Meow!! Dieses irre Arcadespiel ist ausgerüstet mit Leaderboards, Capers und aufzuschließenden Gegenständen für deinen Avatar! Spielt, LOOTers! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble! di LOOT™ è ora disponibile nella versione sala videogiochi. Questo apparecchio ti permetterà di giocare a Cabin Boy nei tuoi spazi personali su PlayStation®Home! Prendi i pesci che Lil’ Dickie ti getta, impedisci a Lil' Missus di ustionarsi sotto il sole e stai attento a Chairman Meow!! Questo stupendo gioco è completo di tabella dei punteggi record, trucchi e oggetti sbloccabili per il tuo avatar! Iniziate a giocare, appassionati di LOOT™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Cabin Boy en Problemas de trucha! está ahora disponible en estilo clásico arcade. ¡Esta aplicación te permite jugar a Cabin Boy directamente en el espacio personal de tu PlayStation®Home! ¡Atrapa el pescado que Lil’ Dickie tira en tu camino, evita que Lil’ Missu se tueste al sol y ten cuidado con Chairman Meow!! ¡Este arcade increíble viene equipado con tableros de piel, saltos y productos con cierre para tu avatar! ¡Que empiece el juego, LOOTers!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LOOT™’s Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble! is now available in this classic arcade style. This appliance lets you play the Cabin Boy game right in your very own PlayStation®Home Personal Spaces! Catch the fish Lil’ Bastard throws your way, keep Lil’ Missus from burning under the hot sun and watch out for Chairman Meow!! This awesome arcade is equipped with leaderboards, capers and unlockable items for your avatar! Start playing, LOOTers! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>