<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Aim Header</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">AIM</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">BUT DU JEU</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">ZIEL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">MIRA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">APUNTAR</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">All Time</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">All Time</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Général</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gesamt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Assoluti</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Absolutas</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Controls Header</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">CONTROLS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">COMMANDES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">STEUERUNG</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">COMANDI</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">CONTROLES</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Direction</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Direction</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Direction</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Richtung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Direzione</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dirección</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Scoring Text 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Feeding Oscar gives you extra points for each Lobster.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous obtenez des points supplémentaires pour chaque homard avalé par Oscar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn du Oscar fütterst, erhältst du für jeden Hummer Bonuspunkte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sfamando Oscar ottieni punti extra per ogni aragosta.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si das de comer a Oscar, obtendrás puntos adicionales con cada langosta.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Freeplay 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">For a chance to play the full game and win all 15 fantastic rewards, just buy yourself a Lobster Suit, available from the retail point beside the game.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour jouer au jeu complet et tenter de remporter les 15 fantastiques récompenses en jeu, il vous suffit d'acheter une tenue Homard, disponible dans la boutique située à côté du jeu.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Um die Vollversion spielen und alle 15 Belohnungen erhalten zu können, musst du dir nur ein Hummer-Kostüm kaufen. Das gibt es an der Kaufstation neben dem Spiel.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se vuoi provare il gioco completo e vincere tutti i 15 fantastici premi in palio, basta comprare un Costume da aragosta, disponibile presso il negozio accanto al gioco.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si deseas jugar al juego completo y hacerte con los 15 fantásticos premios, deberás comprar el traje de langosta en el puesto que está al lado del juego.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">End Game Game Over</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">GAME OVER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">FIN DE LA PARTIE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">SPIEL VORBEI</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">PARTITA TERMINATA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">JUEGO TERMINADO</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Scoring Text 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">High scores will appear on the Leaderboard.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les meilleurs scores apparaîtront dans le classement.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Highscores erscheinen auf der Bestenliste.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I punteggi più alti appariranno nella Classifica.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las puntuaciones más altas aparecerán en la clasificación.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Scoring Text 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hitting each target gives you points.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous marquez des points pour chaque cible touchée.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du erhältst Punkte, wann immer du ein Ziel triffst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ricevi punti ogni volta che colpisci un bersaglio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Obtienes puntos por golpear cada objetivo.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spielanleitung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Istruzioni</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Instrucciones</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Header</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spielanleitung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Istruzioni</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Instrucciones</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nom</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nome</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nombre</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Aim Text 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">On each stage you must hit the specified targets around Oscar within the time limit for him to open his mouth.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">À chaque niveau, vous devez toucher les cibles indiquées autour d'Oscar dans la limite du temps imparti de façon à ouvrir la bouche du géant.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In jeder Stufe musst du die festgelegten Ziele, die sich in Oscars Nähe befinden, treffen, bevor die Zeit abläuft. Dann öffnet er seinen Mund.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">In ogni livello devi colpire i bersagli indicati che ruotano attorno a Oscar entro un limite di tempo per fargli aprire la bocca.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">En cada nivel deberás golpear, dentro del límite de tiempo, los objetivos móviles que se especifican para abrir la boca de Oscar.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Aim Text 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Once Oscar has his mouth open throw in as many Lobsters as you can to feed him.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une fois la bouche d'Oscar ouverte, lancez-lui le plus de homards possible pour le nourrir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn Oscar seinen Mund öffnet, musst du möglichst viele Hummer hineinschießen, um ihn zu füttern.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quando Oscar ha la bocca aperta, lanciagli dentro quante più aragoste riesci per sfamarlo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuando tenga la boca abierta, lánzale tantas langostas como puedas para darle de comer.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Game Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Oscar's Lobster Mania</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Oscar's Lobster Mania</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Oscar's Lobster Mania</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Oscar's Lobster Mania</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Oscar's Lobster Mania</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Game Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Oscar's Lobster Mania [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Oscar's Lobster Mania [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Oscar's Lobster Mania [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Oscar's Lobster Mania [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Oscar's Lobster Mania [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Play Now</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Play Now</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jouer maintenant</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jetzt spielen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gioca ora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Jugar ya</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Power</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Power</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Force</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schwung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Potenza</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Energía</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Controls Text 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [CROSS] to launch a Lobster.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyez sur [CROSS] pour lancer un homard.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücke [CROSS], um einen Hummer zu werfen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi [CROSS] per lanciare un'aragosta.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa [CROSS] para lanzar una langosta.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Controls Text 4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [TRIANGLE] to show these instructions in-game.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyez sur [TRIANGLE] pour afficher ces instructions au cours de la partie.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücke [TRIANGLE], um diese Anweisungen im Spiel zu sehen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi [TRIANGLE] per visualizzare queste istruzioni durante il gioco.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa [TRIANGLE] para mostrar estas instrucciones durante el juego.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beenden</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Abbandona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Welcome Welcome</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Roll up, roll up! Come and play Oscar's Lobster Mania. Feed the giant machine the seafood he desires and win his special prizes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Approchez, approchez ! Tentez votre chance à Oscar's Lobster Mania. Envoyez les crustacés dans la bouche du géant et remportez des récompenses spéciales.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hereinspaziert, hereinspaziert! Tritt näher und spiele Oscar's Lobster Mania. Füttere die riesige Maschine mit den Meeresfrüchten, die sie haben will, und gewinne ihre einzigartigen Preise.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Avvicinatevi! Venite a giocare a Oscar's Lobster Mania! Nutrite la macchina gigante con i frutti di mare che ama e vincete premi speciali.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Acércate! Ven y juega a Oscar's Lobster Mania. Dale a la máquina gigante el marisco que desea y gana premios especiales.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Punktzahl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Punteggio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Puntuación</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Scoring Header</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">SCORING</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">MARQUER DES POINTS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">PUNKTE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">PUNTEGGIO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">PUNTUACIÓN</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Scroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Scroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Faire défiler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Scrollen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scorri</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Avanzar/retroceder</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Scroll_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Scroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Faire défiler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Scrollen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scorri</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Avanzar/retroceder</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Welcome Purpose</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">See if you can win all 15 fantastic reward items.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">À vous de jouer ! Essayez de remporter les 15 fantastiques récompenses en jeu.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Versuche doch, die 15 fantastischen Belohnungsgegenstände zu gewinnen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Provate a vincere tutti i 15 fantastici premi in palio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Veamos si consigues hacerte con los 15 fantásticos premios.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Select</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Select</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sélectionner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Auswählen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Seleziona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Seleccionar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Skip Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Skip Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Passer les instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spielanleitung überspringen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Salta istruzioni</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Omitir instrucciones</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Stage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Niveau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stufe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Livello</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nivel</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Start Game</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Start Game</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Démarrer la partie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spiel beginnen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Inizia il gioco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Iniciar partida</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Freeplay 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Thanks for playing the free demo version of Oscar's Lobster Mania.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Merci d'avoir joué à la démo gratuite d'Oscar's Lobster Mania.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Danke, dass du die kostenlose Demoversion von Oscar's Lobster Mania gespielt hast.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Grazie per aver giocato la demo gratuita di Oscar's Lobster Mania.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Gracias por jugar a la demo gratuita de Oscar's Lobster Mania.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Weekly</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Week</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Hebdomadaire</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese Woche</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa settimana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta semana</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Throw Time</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Throw Time</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Temps pour lancer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wurfzeit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tempo di lancio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">T. lanzamiento</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Throws</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Throws</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lancers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Würfe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lanci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lanzamientos</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Time Left</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Time Left</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Temps restant</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verbleibende Zeit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tempo rimasto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">T. restante</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Controls Text 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use [LEFTSTICK] to set the direction of your Lobster.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez [LEFTSTICK] pour orienter votre lancer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Benutze [LEFTSTICK], um die Richtung deines Hummers festzulegen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usa [LEFTSTICK] per impostare la direzione dell'aragosta.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Usa [LEFTSTICK] para establecer la dirección de la langosta.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Controls Text 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use [RIGHTSTICK] to set the power of your Lobster.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez [RIGHTSTICK] pour ajuster la force de votre lancer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Benutze [RIGHTSTICK], um den Schwung deines Hummer zu bestimmen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usa [RIGHTSTICK] per impostare la potenza di lancio dell'aragosta.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Usa [RIGHTSTICK] para establecer la potencia de la langosta.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Wear Outfit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wear the Lobster Outfit to Play</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Portez la tenue Homard pour jouer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Trage das Hummer-Kostüm, um zu spielen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per giocare indossa il Costume da aragosta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ponte el traje de langosta para jugar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Welcome Purchase</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Why not try the free-to-play demo level - or just buy the Lobster Suit from the retail point beside the game.  Wear the suit to gain unlimited access to the full game and your chance to win all 15 fantastic reward items.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous pouvez essayer la démo gratuite (un niveau) ou acheter la tenue Homard dans la boutique située à côté du jeu. Portez la tenue pour obtenir un accès illimité au jeu complet et une chance de remporter les 15 fantastiques récompenses en jeu.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Versuche doch einmal den Demo-Level, den du gratis spielen kannst. Oder kaufe dir das Hummer-Kostüm von der Kaufstation neben dem Spiel. Trage den Anzug, um unbegrenzten Zugang zum gesamten Spiel zu erhalten. Dann hast du auch die Chance, alle 15 fantastischen Belohnungsgegenstände zu gewinnen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Perché non provare il livello demo gratuito oppure comprare direttamente il Costume da aragosta nel negozio accanto al gioco? Indossate il costume per ottenere l'accesso illimitato al gioco completo e la possibilità di vincere tutti i 15 fantastici premi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Prueba la demo gratuita de un nivel o compra el traje de langosta en el puesto que encontrarás al lado del juego. Póntelo para tener acceso ilimitado al juego completo. ¡Hay 15 fantásticos premios en juego!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Aim Text 4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have limited time to make each throw.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous disposez d'un temps limité pour effectuer chaque lancer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Für jeden Wurf hast du nur begrenzt Zeit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai un tempo limite per ogni lancio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hay un límite de tiempo para efectuar cada lanzamiento.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Aim Text 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You need to feed Oscar at least one Lobster at the end of each level or it is Game Over.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si Oscar n'a mangé aucun homard au terme d'un niveau, la partie sera terminée.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du musst Oscar am Ende jedes Levels mit mindestens einem Hummer gefüttert haben, oder das Spiel ist vorbei.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Devi centrare la bocca di Oscar con almeno un'aragosta in ogni livello, altrimenti la partita termina.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Necesitas darle al menos una langosta a Oscar al final de cada nivel o el juego habrá acabado.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Aim Text 5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You will get a reward for feeding Oscar on each level and a special prize on completion of all levels.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Au terme de chaque niveau, vous obtiendrez une récompense pour avoir nourri Oscar. Une fois tous les niveaux terminés, vous remporterez une récompense spéciale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In jedem Level erhältst du eine Belohnung, wenn du Oscar fütterst. Beendest du alle Levels, erhältst du einen ganz besonderen Preis.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Riceverai una ricompensa per aver sfamato Oscar in ogni livello e un premio speciale dopo aver completato tutti i livelli.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Obtendrás un premio por dar de comer a Oscar en cada nivel. Además, obtendrás otro premio especial si consigues completer todos los niveles.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>