<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mystic Arcade Theatre Poster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Affiche de cinéma Arcade mystique</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mystikarkaden-Kinoplakat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cinema della "Sala giochi mistica"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Póster del cine de los recreativos místicos</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Mystic Arcade劇場ポスター</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Mystic Arcade Theater Poster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mystic Arcade Theater Poster</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Coming soon to a theatre near you! Announce your upcoming movies at the Mystic Theatre using this picture frame. Comes with one poster, or use a picture of your own. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Prochainement au cinéma près de chez vous ! Annoncez vos prochains films au Cinéma mystique au moyen de ce cadre photo. Livré avec une affiche, mais vous pouvez utiliser une image de votre choix. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bald im Kino bei dir in der Nähe! Kündige die demnächst vorgeführten Filme im Mystikkino mit diesem Bilderrahmen an. Er wird mit einem Plakat geliefert – du kannst aber auch ein eigenes Bild verwenden. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prossimamente al cinema! Annuncia i film di prossima programmazione presso il Cinema mistico utilizzando questa cornice. Usa il poster accluso o un'immagine personalizzata. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Próximamente en un cine cercano! Anuncia las películas que se van a estrenar en el cine místico con este póster. Puedes utilizar este póster o usar tu propia imagen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">もうすぐお近くの劇場に登場！この写真立てを使い、もうすぐMystic Theatreで上映される映画を発表しよう。ポスターが1枚ついてくるが、自分の写真も使える。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Coming soon to a theater near you! Announce your upcoming movies at the Mystic Theater using this picture frame. Comes with one poster, or use a picture of your own. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Coming soon to a theater near you! Announce your upcoming movies at the Mystic Theater using this picture frame. Comes with one poster, or use a picture of your own. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>