<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nebulon Booster (Portable Nebulon Purifier)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Améliorateur nébulon (Purificateur nébulon portable)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nebulon-Booster (Tragbares Nebulon-Filtergerät)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Potenziatore di nebulon (purificatore portatile di nebulon)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Propulsor de nebulón (Purificador de nebulón portátil)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ネブロンブースター（24時間利用券）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">네뷸론 증폭기 (이동식 네뷸론 정화기)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Nebulon Booster (Portable Nebulon Purifier)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Nebulon增幅器（攜帶式Nebulon淨化器）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Nebulon增幅器（攜帶式Nebulon淨化器）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Nebulon Booster (Portable Nebulon Purifier)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This portable device processes gathered nebulon-charged material, increasing the amount of pure nebulon extracted from it. All nebulon gains from defeating enemies are increased to 150% for the next twenty-four hours!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce dispositif portatif traite les matériaux riches en nébulon, permettant ainsi d'augmenter la quantité de nébulon pure qui en sera extraite. Pendant les prochaines 24 heures, toute la quantité de nébulon récoltée après vaincu des ennemis sera augmentée de 150 % ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses tragbare Gerät verarbeitet eingesammeltes nebulonhaltiges Material und erhöht die Menge des reinen Nebulons, das aus ihm gewonnen werden kann. Alle Nebulon-Erträge von besiegten Feinden steigen für die nächsten 24 Stunden um 150 % an! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo apparecchio portatile raffina la materia grezza, incrementando la quantità di nebulon puro estratto. Tutto il nebulon ottenuto combattendo contro i nemici viene aumentato del 150% per le successive ventiquattro ore!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este dispositivo portátil procesa el material cargado de nebulón, aumentando la cantidad de nebulón puro extraído. Todas las adquisiciones de nebulón obtenidas al derrotar enemigos se incrementan hasta el 150% durante las siguientes veinticuatro horas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このポータブルデバイスはネブロンを含む物質を集め、そこから抽出できる純粋なネブロンの量を増加させる。使用後の24時間、敵を倒したときに得られるネブロンが150％になる。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 이동식 장치는 수집한 네뷸론 농축 금속을 정제해 추출할 수 있는 순수 네뷸론의 양을 늘려줍니다. 향후 24시간 동안 적을 제거하고 획득할 수 있는 네뷸론의 양이 150% 증가합니다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This portable device processes gathered nebulon-charged material, increasing the amount of pure nebulon extracted from it. All nebulon gains from defeating enemies are increased to 150% for the next twenty-four hours!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這個攜帶式儀器能收集含有Nebulon的物質，增加可以抽取到的純Nebulon的量。在未來二十四小時，擊退敵人所獲得的Nebulon將增加至150%！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這個攜帶式儀器能收集含有Nebulon的物質，增加可以抽取到的純Nebulon的量。在未來二十四小時，擊退敵人所獲得的Nebulon將增加至150%！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This portable device processes gathered nebulon-charged material, increasing the amount of pure nebulon extracted from it. All nebulon gains from defeating enemies are increased to 150% for the next twenty-four hours! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>