<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MotorStorm® Tyre Footstool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MotorStorm® Tyre Footstool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tabouret pneu MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MotorStorm®-Reifenschemel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pneumatici-Poggiapiedi MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Escabel-neumático de MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">MotorStorm® タイヤの足載せ台</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">MotorStorm® 타이어 의자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">MotorStorm™ Tyre Footstool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">MotorStorm™ 輪胎脚凳</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">MotorStorm™ 輪胎脚凳</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MotorStorm® Tyre Footstool</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Balder than a desert mole rat, these tires wouldn’t get you very far in a MotorStorm® race, but add two planks of wood to the top and you’ve got yourself a handy stool. Genius![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Balder than a desert mole rat, these tires wouldn’t get you very far in a MotorStorm® race, but add two planks of wood to the top and you’ve got yourself a handy stool. Genius![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plus lisses qu'un crâne échevelé, ces pneus ne vous emmèneraient pas bien loin dans une course MotorStorm®, mais ajoutez deux planches de bois au-dessus et vous obtenez un tabouret très pratique. Génial![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit diesen Reifen, die glatter sind als ein Nacktmull, würde man in einem MotorStorm®-Rennen nicht mehr weit kommen, aber mit zwei Holzbrettern dran hat man einen praktischen Schemel. Genial![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Più lisci di una talpa senza pelo, questi pneumatici non ti porterebbero molto lontano in una gara di MotorStorm®, ma se ci metti sopra due assi di legno otterrai un pratico sgabello. Geniale![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Más desgastados que el pellejo de una rata del desierto, estos neumáticos no te llevarían muy lejos en una carrera de MotorStorm®. Añádeles dos tablas en la parte de arriba y tendrás un escabel realmente útil. ¡Mola![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">砂漠にいるハゲタカの頭よりもすり減ったタイヤ。この上に２枚の板を置けば便利な足載せ台の出来上がり！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사막의 두더쥐보다도 더 닳고 닳은 타이어들입니다. 레이스에서 사용할 수는 없지만, 널판지 두 장을 위에 깔면 훌륭한 의자로 변신합니다.천재적이죠![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Balder than a desert mole rat, these tires wouldn’t get you very far in a MotorStorm race, but add two planks of wood to the top and you’ve got yourself a handy stool. Genius![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這些比沙漠的鼴鼠還要光禿禿的輪胎很難讓你的車子去得多遠，但只要加上兩片木板便可搖身一變成為一個方便的脚凳。太利害了！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這些比沙漠的鼴鼠還要光禿禿的輪胎很難讓你的車子去得多遠，但只要加上兩片木板便可搖身一變成為一個方便的脚凳。太利害了！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Balder than a desert mole rat, these tires wouldn’t get you very far in a MotorStorm® race, but add two planks of wood to the top and you’ve got yourself a handy stool. Genius![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>