<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Pen Draig's Gauntlets (Legendary Armour)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Gantelets de Pen Draig (armure légendaire)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Pen Draigs Handschuhe (Legendäre Rüstung)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guanti d'armatura di Pen Draig (Armatura leggendaria)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guanteletes de Pen Draig (Armadura legendaria)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Pen Draig's Gauntlets (Legendary Armor)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Legendary Armour of Pen Driag, one the first Guardians of Mercia who allied with Queen Lidicea and denounced his Gods to unite the people of Mercia, now watched over by the Guardians. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'armure légendaire de Pen Draig, un des premiers gardiens de Mercia qui s'allia à la reine Lidicea et renonça à ses dieux pour unir les peuples de Mercia, sous la protection des gardiens. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die legendäre Rüstung von Pen Draig, einem der ersten Wächter Mercias , der sich mit Königin Lidicea verbündete und Göttern entsagte, um die Völker Mercias zu vereinen, über nun unter dem Schutz der Wächter stehen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La leggendaria armatura di Pen Driag, uno dei primi guardiani di Mercia che si alleò con la regina Lidicea e rinnegò i suoi dei per unire il popolo di Mercia; ora è custodita dai guardiani. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La legendaria armadura de Pen Draig, uno de los primeros guardianes de Mercia que se alió con la Reina Lidicea y renunció a sus dioses para unir al pueblo de Mercia, ahora defendido por los guardianes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Legendary Armor of Pen Driag, one the first Guardians of Mercia who allied with Queen Lidicea and denounced his Gods to unite the people of Mercia, now watched over by the Guardians. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>