<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Hot Zone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">The Hot Zone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">The Hot Zone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">The Hot Zone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">The Hot Zone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ホットゾーン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">핫존</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Hot Zone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Hot Zone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Hot Zone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Hot Zone</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Hot Zone Information [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Infos sur The Hot Zone [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">The Hot Zone-Informationen [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Informazioni su The Hot Zone [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Información sobre The Hot Zone [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ホットゾーン情報 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">핫존 정보 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Hot Zone Information [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Hot Zone資訊 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Hot Zone資訊 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Hot Zone Information [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kNameSCEA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Midway's Cash Carnival Sweepstakes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">The Midway's Cash Carnival Sweepstakes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">The Midway's Cash Carnival Sweepstakes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Midway's Cash Carnival Sweepstakes</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kTextInfo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Hot Zone is a smokin' space that serves as a hub for all three Midway mini-game collections and hosts a bunch of Hot Streak Air Hockey tables (2-player real-time games). You will also find a Tele-Port-A-Potty leading to Darla's Den, a Mass Media Store ticket booth, and the Lots O' Junk Redemption Center. We will also be introducing games behind the Speed Dial teleporter for your continued pleasure.\n\nTHE ECONOMY\nThe Hot Zone uses Green Tickets as money. The player can collect Hot Zone Points by playing Hot Zone games and then redeem them for reward items from the Lots O' Junk Redemption Center. \n\nTHE LOTS O' JUNK REDEMPTION CENTER\nSelect an item and redeem your accumulated Hot Zone Points to get the reward. We will continue to add new items and replace old items over time, so keep coming back for more!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">The Hot Zone est un espace génial rassemblant les trois compilations de mini-jeux Midway. Tu y trouveras plein de tables Hot Streak Air Hockey pour deux joueurs (parties en temps réel). Il y a aussi un Tele-Port-A-Potty menant à Darla's Den, un guichet Mass Media et le Lots O' Junk Redemption Center. D'autres jeux seront également intégrés derrière le téléporteur Speed Dial. Tu ne risques pas de t'ennuyer ! \n\nL'ARGENT Dans The Hot Zone, les Green Tickets constituent la monnaie d'échange. Le joueur peut accumuler des points Hot Zone en jouant à des jeux Hot Zone, puis les échanger contre des récompenses du Lots O' Junk Redemption Center.\n\nTHE LOTS O' JUNK REDEMPTION CENTER Sélectionne un objet et utilise tes points Hot Zone pour l'obtenir. Nous ajouterons d'autres objets et remplacerons les anciens régulièrement, alors reviens souvent !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">The Hot Zone ist ein echt heißer Bereich, der als Dreh- und Angelpunkt für alle drei Midway-Minispielsammlungen dient und in dem mehrere Hot Streak Air Hockey-Tische (Echtzeitspiele für je zwei Spieler) bereitstehen. Dort befinden sich auch ein Tele-Port-A-Potty, das zu Darla's Den führt, ein Mass Media-Ticketschalter und das Lots O' Junk Redemption Center. Und damit für noch mehr Entertainment gesorgt ist, gibt es sogar Spiele hinter dem Speed Dial-Teleporter.\n\nWÄHRUNG The Hot Zone verwendet Green Tickets als Geld. Spieler können in den Hot Zone-Games Hot Zone-Punkte sammeln und sie dann gegen Prämien aus dem Lots O' Junk Redemption Center einlösen.\n\nTHE LOTS O' JUNK REDEMPTION CENTER Wähl ein Objekt aus und lös die gesammelten Hot Zone-Punkte gegen die Prämie ein. Wir fügen regelmäßig neue Objekte hinzu und ersetzen alte – sieh also immer mal wieder vorbei!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">The Hot Zone è uno spazio che funge da anticamera alle tre raccolte di minigiochi Midway e include alcuni tavoli Hot Streak Air Hockey (giochi in tempo reale per due giocatori). Troverai anche un Tele-Port-A-Potty che conduce a Darla's Den, un botteghino Mass Media Store e il Lots O' Junk Redemption Center. Saranno aggiunti anche altri giochi nel teletrasportatore Speed Dial per un intrattenimento senza fine.\n\nL'ECONOMIA The Hot Zone utilizza Green Tickets come moneta. Il giocatore accumula punti Hot Zone nei giochi Hot Zone e poi li utilizza per richiedere articoli premio presso il Lots O' Junk Redemption Center.\n\nTHE LOTS O' JUNK REDEMPTION CENTER Seleziona un articolo e riscatta i punti Hot Zone accumulati per ottenere il premio. Continueremo ad aggiungere nuovi articoli sostituendo quelli precedenti nel corso del tempo, quindi torna per scoprire altre novità!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">The Hot Zone es el lugar de moda donde encontrarás las tres colecciones de minijuegos Midway, así como un montón de mesas Hot Streak Air Hockey (para 2 jugadores en tiempo real). También encontrarás un Tele-Port-A-Potty que lleva a Darla's Den, una taquilla de la tienda Mass Media y el Lots O' Junk Redemption Center. Además, añadiremos juegos detrás del teleportador Speed Dial para que sigas pasándolo en grande.\n\nTHE ECONOMY The Hot Zone utiliza Green Tickets como moneda. El jugador puede participar en los juegos Hot Zone para recoger puntos Hot Zone y, a continuación, canjearlos por objetos de recompensa en Lots O' Junk Redemption Center.\n\nTHE LOTS O' JUNK REDEMPTION CENTER Selecciona un artículo y canjea los puntos Hot Zone que hayas acumulado por tu recompensa. A medida que pase el tiempo iremos añadiendo nuevos objetos y retirando los antiguos, así que recuerda visitarnos con frecuencia.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ホットゾーン\n
ホットゾーンは2人プレイ対戦専用Hot Streak Air Hockey、ダーラの部屋へのテレポートマシーン、チケットブースやホットゾーンポイント交換所などがあるラウンジです。無限に楽しむために、ここから各アメリカン・カーニバルラウンジへアクセスが可能です。\n
\n
ホットゾーンポイント\n
ホットゾーンでプレイするためにはグリーンチケットが必要です。Hot Streak Air Hockeyではグリーンチケット3プレイ分を消費して、プレイ内容によってホットゾーンポイントを獲得できます。ホットゾーンポイントはホットゾーンポイント交換所でホームリワードと交換できます。\n
\n
ホットゾーンポイント交換所\n
貯めたホットゾーンポイントを消費して交換したいホームリワードを選択しましょう。今後の更新でアイテム入れ変わることがありますので、何回か訪ねてみてください！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">핫존은 Midway 게임 3종 콜렉션의 본거지 역할을 하며, 또한 여러대의 Hot Streak Air Hockey 테이블(2인용 리얼타임 게임)을 운영하는 끝내주는 스페이스입니다. 여러분은 이 곳에서 매스미디어 상점 티켓 부스, 고철 덩어리 교환 센터, 달라의 집으로 향하는 텔레포트 변기를 사용할 수 있습니다. 그리고 여러분의 만족을 위하여, 저희는 계속해서 Speed Dial 게임을 소개할 것입니다.\n\n지불 방법\n핫존은 티켓을 현금 대신 사용합니다. Hot Streak Air Hockey 테이블은 게임당 3장의 티켓을 지불하며 핫존 포인트를 획득할 수 있습니다. 플레이어는 핫존 게임을 플레이하며 핫존 포인트를 획득할 수 있으며, 이 포인트는 포인트 교환 센터에서 리워드로 교환할 수 있습니다.\n\n고철 덩어리 교환 센터\n아이템을 선택하고 여러분이 모은 핫존 포인트를 리워드와 교환하세요. 저희는 지속적으로 오래된 아이템을 새로운 아이템으로 교환할 예정이니 계속 방문해 주세요!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Hot Zone is a smokin' space that serves as a hub for all three Midway mini-game collections and hosts a bunch of Hot Streak Air Hockey tables (2-player real-time games). You will also find a Tele-Port-A-Potty leading to Darla's Den, a Mass Media Store ticket booth, and the Lots O' Junk Redemption Center. We will also be introducing games behind the Speed Dial teleporter for your continued pleasure.\n\nTHE ECONOMY\nThe Hot Zone uses Green Tickets as money. The player can collect Hot Zone Points by playing Hot Zone games and then redeem them for reward items from the Lots O' Junk Redemption Center. \n\nTHE LOTS O' JUNK REDEMPTION CENTER\nSelect an item and redeem your accumulated Hot Zone Points to get the reward. We will continue to add new items and replace old items over time, so keep coming back for more!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HOT ZONE\nHot Zone是所有三個的Midway大廳迷你遊戲集合中心，並且設有許多Hot Streak Air Hockey遊戲桌(2人即時對戰遊戲)。您也可以發現可前往達拉之家的傳送站、Mass Media售票處、以及一個大量廢物兌換中心。我們同時也以快速傳送讓您盡情遊玩遊戲。\n\n消費方式\n玩家遊玩Hot Zone遊戲收集Hot Zone積分便可以在大量廢物兌換中心兌換獎品道具。\n\n大量廢物兌換中心\n選擇道具並以您累積的Hot Zone積分來獲得獎品道具。我們會持續追加新道具以取代舊道具，所以您一定要常常回來確認！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">HOT ZONE\nHot Zone是所有三個的Midway大廳迷你遊戲集合中心，並且設有許多Hot Streak Air Hockey遊戲桌(2人即時對戰遊戲)。您也可以發現可前往達拉之家的傳送站、Mass Media售票處、以及一個大量廢物兌換中心。我們同時也以快速傳送讓您盡情遊玩遊戲。\n\n消費方式\n玩家遊玩Hot Zone遊戲收集Hot Zone積分便可以在大量廢物兌換中心兌換獎品道具。\n\n大量廢物兌換中心\n選擇道具並以您累積的Hot Zone積分來獲得獎品道具。我們會持續追加新道具以取代舊道具，所以您一定要常常回來確認！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Hot Zone is a smokin' space that serves as a hub for all three Midway mini-game collections and hosts a bunch of Hot Streak Air Hockey tables (2-player real-time games). You will also find a Tele-Port-A-Potty leading to Darla's Den, a Mass Media Store ticket booth, and the Lots O' Junk Redemption Center. We will also be introducing games behind the Speed Dial teleporter for your continued pleasure.\n\nTHE ECONOMY\nThe Hot Zone uses Green Tickets as money. The player can collect Hot Zone Points by playing Hot Zone games and then redeem them for reward items from the Lots O' Junk Redemption Center. \n\nTHE LOTS O' JUNK REDEMPTION CENTER\nSelect an item and redeem your accumulated Hot Zone Points to get the reward. We will continue to add new items and replace old items over time, so keep coming back for more!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kTextRules</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">We are delighted to introduce an exciting sweepstakes opportunity! Every time you use your Green Ticket to play any game in any Midway space or the Hot Zone, you will get a sweepstakes entry! There are 25 fabulous Sony prizes and a pile of money to give away too! Check out the Sweepstakes Prizes Board to see what you can win. Just read the Official Rules and, if you qualify, sign up for the Sweepstakes and start playing for fun and a chance to win real prizes! Once you enter the sweepstakes you can track your entries on the My Sweepstakes Entries Board. Have a ton of fun and good luck!\n\n\nOFFICIAL RULES\nThe following promotion is intended for viewing in the 50 United States and D.C. only and is construed and evaluated according to California law.  Do not enter this Promotion if you are not a legal resident of, and located in, the 50 United States or D.C. at the time of entry.\n\nNO PURCHASE NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN. A PURCHASE DOES NOT IMPROVE YOUR CHANCES OF WINNING.\n\nBy participating in The Midway’s Cash Carnival Sweepstakes (the “Promotion”), each entrant (or his or her parent or legal guardian if the entrant is under the age of majority in his or her state of residence) unconditionally accepts and agrees to comply with and abide by these Official Rules and the decisions of Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC (“Sponsor”), which are final and binding in all respects. Sponsor is responsible for the collection and selection entries and the Promotion’s overall administration. Entrants should look solely to Sponsor with any questions, comments or problems related to the Promotion.\n\n1. ELIGIBILITY: The Midway’s Cash Carnival Prize (the “Promotion”) is open only to legal residents of the 50 United States and the District of Columbia who are 18 years of age or older. Entrants under the legal age of majority in their state of residence should get permission to enter the Promotion from their parent or guardian. Employees of Sponsor and its parent companies, affiliates, subsidiaries, and related companies, and agencies and immediate families (defined as parents, children, siblings and spouse and their respective spouses, regardless of where they reside) and those living in the same household, whether or not related, are not eligible to enter or win. Void in all U.S. territories and possessions and overseas military installations and where prohibited or restricted by law\n\n2. TIMING: The Promotion begins May 16, 2012 at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Daylight Time (“PDT”) and ends on November 6, 2012 at 11:59 p.m. PDT (the “Promotion Period”).  During the Promotion Period, each week is defined as follows:\ni. Week 1: 5:00 a.m. PDT May 16, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT May 22, 2012\nii. Week 2: 12:00 a.m. PDT May 23, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT May 29, 2012\niii.  Week 3: 12:00 a.m. PDT May 30, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 5, 2012 \niv. Week 4: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 6, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 12, 2012 \nv. Week 5: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 13, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 19, 2012 \nvi. Week 6: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 20, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 26, 2012 \nvii. Week 7: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 27, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 3, 2012 \nviii. Week 8: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 4, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 10, 2012 \nix. Week 9: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 11, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 17, 2012 \nx. Week 10: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 18, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 24, 2012 \nxi. Week 11: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 25, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 31, 2012 \nxii. Week 12: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 1, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 7, 2012 \nxiii. Week 13: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 8, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 14, 2012 \nxiv. Week 14: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 15, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 21, 2012 \nxv. Week 15: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 22, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 28, 2012 \nxvi. Week 16: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 29, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 4, 2012 \nxvii. Week 17: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 5, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 11, 2012 \nxviii. Week 18: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 12, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 18, 2012 \nxix. Week 19: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 19, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 25, 2012 \nxx. Week 20: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 26, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 2, 2012 \nxxi. Week 21: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 3, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 9, 2012 \nxxii. Week 22: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 10, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 16, 2012 \nxxiii. Week 23: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 17, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 23, 2012 \nxxiv. Week 24: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 24, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 30, 2012 \nxxv. Week 25: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 31, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT November 6, 2012 \n\n3. HOW TO ENTER:  \ni. Enter through PlayStation®Home:\n1) During the Promotion Period, log into your PlayStation®Network account and launch PlayStation®Home application.\n2) Make your way to the Midway section of PlayStation®Home.\n3) Play any of the games located in the Midway section. To play any of the games located in the Midway, you will need a ticket. You can purchase 50 tickets for $0.99.  Free-play games do not count as an entry into the Promotion.\n4) For Week 1 through Week 25’s drawings, one ticket will count as one entry into the Promotion for that week.  You must play one of the games in Midway to enter that week’s drawing.  You may play any of the Midway games multiple times to submit multiple entries.  There is no limit on the number of entries that you can submit.\n5) To be entered into the Grand Prize drawing, you will get one entry for every one entry entered into the Promotion from Week 1 through Week 25’s drawings.  For example, if you have one entry in Week One and one entry in Week Two, you will get two entries into the Grand Prize drawing.  If your entry is chosen as a winning entry during one of the weekly drawings, that winning entry will be considered an eligible entry for the Grand Prize drawing.\n6) You may play any of the Midway games multiple times to submit multiple entries.  There is no limit on the number of entries you can submit.\n7) The Sponsor will randomly draw a winner for each week.\nii. Enter by Mail:\n1) During the Promotion Period, handwrite your name, email address, and indicate which week’s promotion drawing you would like to be entered into on a postage paid postcard via US Postal Service mail to The Midway’s Cash Carnival Prize, 530 Los Angeles Avenue #115 Box 218 Moorpark, CA 93021.  \n2) For Week 1 through Week 25’s drawings, one mail in entry will count as one entry into the Promotion for that week.  There is no limit on the number of entries that you can submit.  If your entry is chosen as a winning entry during one of the weekly drawings, that winning entry will be considered an eligible entry for the Grand Prize drawing.\n3) To be qualified in each week’s promotion, mail-in entries must be received between the following dates:\nWeek 01: May 16, 2012 - May 29, 2012\nWeek 02: May 23, 2012 - June 5, 2012\nWeek 03: May 30, 2012 - June 12, 2012\nWeek 04: June 6, 2012 - June 19, 2012\nWeek 05: June 13, 2012 - June 26, 2012\nWeek 06: June 20, 2012 - July 3, 2012\nWeek 07: June 27, 2012 - July 10, 2012\nWeek 08: July 4, 2012 - July 17, 2012\nWeek 09: July 11, 2012 - July 24, 2012\nWeek 10: July 18, 2012 - July 31, 2012\nWeek 11: July 25, 2012 - August 7, 2012\nWeek 12: August 1, 2012 - August 14, 2012\nWeek 13: August 8, 2012 - August 21, 2012\nWeek 14: August 15, 2012 - August 28, 2012\nWeek 15: August 22, 2012 - September 4, 2012\nWeek 16: August 29, 2012 - September 11, 2012\nWeek 17: September 5, 2012 - September 18, 2012\nWeek 18: September 12, 2012 - September 25, 2012\nWeek 19: September 19, 2012 - October 2, 2012\nWeek 20: September 26, 2012 - October 9, 2012\nWeek 21: October 3, 2012 - October 16, 2012\nWeek 22: October 10, 2012 - October 23, 2012\nWeek 23: October 17, 2012 - October 30, 2012\nWeek 24: October 24, 2012 - November 6, 2012\nWeek 25: October 31, 2012 - November 13, 2012\nGrand Prize: May 16, 2012 - November 13, 2012\n4) Sponsor will draw a winner for each week.\n\n4. ENTRY CONDITIONS:  The authorized account holder of the email address used to enter the Promotion is deemed to be the entrant. The “authorized account holder” is the natural person assigned to an email address by an internet access provider, online service provider or other organization responsible for assigning email addresses for the domain associated with the submitted address. Each potential winner may be required to show proof of being the authorized account holder.\n\n5. PRIZES: \nWeek 1: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $2,699.98 Approximate Retail Value (“ARV”))\nWeek 2: 1 Sony - 1000W 5.1-Ch. 3D/Wi-Fi Blu-ray Home Theater System. (BDVE780W / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 3: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver. (DSC-TX55 / $349.99 ARV)\nWeek 4: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory. (SGPT112US-S / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 5: 1 Sony - 3D Wi-Fi Built-In Blu-ray Player. (BDPS780 / $199.98 ARV)\nWeek 6: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $2,699.98 ARV)\nWeek 7: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory. (SGPT112US-S / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 8: 1 Sony - 1000W 5.1-Ch. 3D/Wi-Fi Blu-ray Home Theater System. (BDVE780W / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 9: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver. (DSC-WX9 / $199.98 ARV)\nWeek 10: 1 Sony - Handycam 32GB HD Flash Memory Camcorder – Black. (HDR-PJ710V / $1299.99 ARV)\nWeek 11: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $2,699.98 ARV)\nWeek 12: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory. (SGPT112US-S / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 13: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver. (DSC-WX9 / $199.98 ARV)\nWeek 14: 1 Sony - 10" Widescreen LCD Portable Blu-ray Disc Player. (BDP-SX1000 / $299.99 ARV)\nWeek 15: 1 Sony - 3D Wi-Fi Built-In Blu-ray Player. (BDPS780 / $1,199.98 ARV)\nWeek 16: 1 Sony - Handycam 16GB HD Flash Memory Projection Camcorder and $1,000.00 cash prize. (HDR-PJ260V / $1,649.99 ARV)\nWeek 17: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver and $1,000.00 cash prize. (DSC-WX9 / $1,199.98 ARV)\nWeek 18: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory and $1,000.00 cash prize. (SGPT112US-S / $1,499.98 ARV)\nWeek 19: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs and $1,000.00 cash prize. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $3,699.98 ARV)\nWeek 20: 1 Sony - 10" Widescreen LCD Portable Blu-ray Disc Player and $1,000.00 cash prize. (BDP-SX1000 / $1,299.99 ARV)\nWeek 21: 1 Sony - Handycam 16GB HD Flash Memory Projection Camcorder and $1,000.00 cash prize. (HDR-PJ260V / $1,649.99 ARV)\nWeek 22: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver and $1,000.00 cash prize. (DSC-WX9 / $1,199.98 ARV)\nWeek 23: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory and $1,000.00 cash prize. (SGPT112US-S / $1,499.98 ARV)\nWeek 24: 1 Sony - PlayStation®Vita Wi-Fi Portable Gaming System - Black and $1,000.00 cash prize. (PSV22031 / $1,249.99 ARV)\nWeek 25: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs and $1,000.00 cash prize. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $3,699.98 ARV)\nGrand Prize: $15,000 Cash Prize ($15,000.00 ARV)\n\nPrize fulfillment is based on availability. Please allow 8 to 12 weeks for prize delivery from the time a winner provides delivery information to Sponsor. Taxes on prize, if any, are solely the responsibility of the winner. Winners of a prize valued at $600.00 or more will receive a Federal Tax Form 1099.  We recommend that you consult with your tax advisor if you have further questions.  Sponsor reserves the right to substitute a prize of equal or greater value if a prize is unavailable. Sponsor may disqualify a winner and select an alternate winner if any prize is returned undeliverable. Prizes are non-transferable. Sponsor need not substitute a prize based on the winner’s request.\n\n6. ODDS OF WINNING: The odds of winning depend on the total number of eligible entries received.\n\n7. WINNER SELECTION:  Each Week a winner will be randomly selected by Sponsor from the entries received during that Week.\nWeek 01: Winner chosen on or about May 30, 2012\nWeek 02: Winner chosen on or about June 6, 2012\nWeek 03: Winner chosen on or about June 13, 2012\nWeek 04: Winner chosen on or about June 20, 2012\nWeek 05: Winner chosen on or about June 27, 2012\nWeek 06: Winner chosen on or about July 4, 2012\nWeek 07: Winner chosen on or about July 11, 2012\nWeek 08: Winner chosen on or about July 18, 2012\nWeek 09: Winner chosen on or about July 25, 2012\nWeek 10: Winner chosen on or about August 1, 2012\nWeek 11: Winner chosen on or about August 8, 2012\nWeek 12: Winner chosen on or about August 15, 2012\nWeek 13: Winner chosen on or about August 22, 2012\nWeek 14: Winner chosen on or about August 29, 2012\nWeek 15: Winner chosen on or about September 5, 2012\nWeek 16: Winner chosen on or about September 12, 2012\nWeek 17: Winner chosen on or about September 19, 2012\nWeek 18: Winner chosen on or about September 26, 2012\nWeek 19: Winner chosen on or about October 3, 2012\nWeek 20: Winner chosen on or about October 10, 2012\nWeek 21: Winner chosen on or about October 17, 2012\nWeek 22: Winner chosen on or about October 24, 2012\nWeek 23: Winner chosen on or about October 31, 2012\nWeek 24: Winner chosen on or about November 7, 2012\nWeek 25: Winner chosen on or about November 14, 2012\nGrand Prize: Winner chosen on or about November 21, 2012\n\nPotential winning entrants will be contacted via email.  If a potential winning entrant is determined by Sponsor to be unqualified to participate in this Promotion or does not respond to Sponsor’s correspondence within 72 hours, the potential winning entrant will be disqualified and a new potential winning entrant will be selected by random drawing.\n\n8. REQUIRED DOCUMENTATION:  The potential winning entrant will be required to complete an Affidavit of Eligibility and Release (“Affidavit”) in accordance with the instructions listed in the notification correspondence. Any entrant who fails or refuses to sign and return the required documentation within the time period as specified by Sponsor will be disqualified. If a potential winning entrant is considered a minor in the legal jurisdiction in which the entrant resides, then that entrant’s parent or legal guardian may be required to execute and return the Affidavit. Non-compliance with these Official Rules or failure to return all required documentation by the stated deadline or Sponsor’s inability to contact an entrant (using the contact information provided in his or her registration) within a reasonable time period, as determined in Sponsor’s sole discretion may result in disqualification and the forfeiture of the prize.\n\n9. PUBLICITY: Except where prohibited, participation in the Promotion constitutes entrant’s consent to Sponsor’s and its agent’s use of the entrant’s name, likeness, photograph, voice, opinions, hometown, state, and any other information submitted to Sponsor by entrant for promotional purposes, or on a winner’s list, if applicable, in any media, worldwide, without further payment or compensation.\n\n10. GENERAL CONDITIONS: Potential winning entrants are subject to Sponsor’s verification. Sponsor’s decisions are final and binding in all matters related to the Promotion. Potential winners must comply with the Official Rules, and receipt of prizes is contingent upon fulfilling all requirements. Sponsor is not responsible for technical, hardware or software failures, malfunctions, lost or unavailable network connections or failed, incomplete, garbled or delayed computer transmissions or unforeseen schedule changes that may limit an entrant’s ability to participate in the Promotion, even if caused by Sponsor’s negligence. Entries generated by script, macro or other automated means or with the intent to impair the integrity of the Promotion will be void.  Sponsor has the sole discretion to modify, cancel or suspend this Promotion should viruses, bugs, unauthorized human intervention or other causes beyond Sponsor’s control affect the administration, security or proper play of the Promotion or Sponsor otherwise becomes incapable of running the Promotion as planned. Sponsor is not responsible for changes to entrant’s contact information. Any individual who attempts or otherwise encourages, directly or indirectly, the submission of false entries, as determined by Sponsor, will be disqualified. Sponsor has the sole discretion to disqualify any entrant who tampers with the entry process.  Sponsor has the sole discretion to disqualify entrants who violate these Official Rules, tamper with the operation of the Promotion or engage in any conduct that is deemed detrimental or unfair to Sponsor, the Promotion or any other entrant.  Sponsor has no obligation to return any entry consideration, if applicable, submitted by a disqualified entrant.\n\n11. RELEASE: As a condition of participating in the Promotion, entrants release the Sponsor and its respective affiliates, subsidiaries, parent corporations, advertising and promotional agencies, and all of their officers, directors, shareholders, members, employees, and agents (collectively, the “Promotion Entities”) from liability, for loss, harm, damage, injury, cost or expense whatsoever including property damage, personal injury and death that may occur in connection with, preparation for, travel to, or participation in the Promotion, or possession, acceptance or use of prizes or participation in any Promotion-related activities and claims based on publicity rights, copyright or trademark infringement, defamation or invasion of privacy and merchandise delivery.\n\n12. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY: The Promotion Entities are not responsible for: any incorrect or inaccurate entry information; human errors; technical malfunctions; lost, stolen, mutilated, mis-delivered, postage due, illegible, incomplete or untimely entries that may limit entrant’s ability to participate in the Promotion, even if caused by Sponsor’s negligence; failures, omissions, interruptions, deletions, or defects of any telephone network, computer online system, computer equipment, servers, providers, or software, including any injury or damage to entrant's or any other person's computer relating to participation or inability to participate in the Promotion; inability to access the site or upload information or data; theft, tampering, destruction, or unauthorized access to, or alteration of, entries; data that is processed late or incorrectly or is incomplete or lost due to telephone, computer, or electronic malfunction or traffic congestion on telephone lines or the Internet or any website (including the site) or for any other reason whatsoever; printing or other errors; or any combination thereof. Proof of uploading information or data or entering information at the site is not considered proof of delivery or receipt. Illegible, duplicate and incomplete entries will be disqualified. False, fraudulent, or deceptive entries or acts, as determined by Sponsor, render entrants ineligible, and all associated entries will be void.\n\n13. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION: Information collected in connection with the Promotion will be collected in accordance with Sponsor’s Privacy Policy, available at http://www.us.playstation.com/Support/PrivacyPolicy. By participating in the Promotion, each entrant agrees to the terms of Sponsor’s Privacy Policy.\n\n14. GOVERNING LAW: All issues and questions concerning the construction, validity, interpretation and enforceability of these Official Rules or the rights and obligations of entrants or Sponsor in connection with this Promotion are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California without giving effect to any choice of law or conflict of law rules (whether of the State of California or any other jurisdiction) that would cause the application of any other state’s laws. Entrants hereby submit to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of the Federal and State Courts in San Mateo, California for the purposes of any suit related to the Promotion and waive any claim that they are not subject personally to the jurisdiction of said courts or that any such suit or other proceeding is brought in an inconvenient forum or improper venue.\n\n15. WINNER LIST: To obtain a winner list by mail, send a stamped, self-addressed envelope to “The Midway’s Cash Carnival Sweepstakes” Attn: SCEA PlayStation Home, 919 E. Hillsdale Blvd., Foster City, CA 94404. Sponsor will send requested winner lists within 4-6 weeks after all prizes are awarded. Requests for the winner list must be received by November 20, 2012.\n\n16. SPONSOR: Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC, 919 E. Hillsdale Blvd, Foster City, CA 94404.\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">We are delighted to introduce an exciting sweepstakes opportunity! Every time you use your Green Ticket to play any game in any Midway space or the Hot Zone, you will get a sweepstakes entry! There are 25 fabulous Sony prizes and a pile of money to give away too! Check out the Sweepstakes Prizes Board to see what you can win. Just read the Official Rules and, if you qualify, sign up for the Sweepstakes and start playing for fun and a chance to win real prizes! Once you enter the sweepstakes you can track your entries on the My Sweepstakes Entries Board. Have a ton of fun and good luck!\n\n\nOFFICIAL RULES\nThe following promotion is intended for viewing in the 50 United States and D.C. only and is construed and evaluated according to California law.  Do not enter this Promotion if you are not a legal resident of, and located in, the 50 United States or D.C. at the time of entry.\n\nNO PURCHASE NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN. A PURCHASE DOES NOT IMPROVE YOUR CHANCES OF WINNING.\n\nBy participating in The Midway’s Cash Carnival Sweepstakes (the “Promotion”), each entrant (or his or her parent or legal guardian if the entrant is under the age of majority in his or her state of residence) unconditionally accepts and agrees to comply with and abide by these Official Rules and the decisions of Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC (“Sponsor”), which are final and binding in all respects. Sponsor is responsible for the collection and selection entries and the Promotion’s overall administration. Entrants should look solely to Sponsor with any questions, comments or problems related to the Promotion.\n\n1. ELIGIBILITY: The Midway’s Cash Carnival Prize (the “Promotion”) is open only to legal residents of the 50 United States and the District of Columbia who are 18 years of age or older. Entrants under the legal age of majority in their state of residence should get permission to enter the Promotion from their parent or guardian. Employees of Sponsor and its parent companies, affiliates, subsidiaries, and related companies, and agencies and immediate families (defined as parents, children, siblings and spouse and their respective spouses, regardless of where they reside) and those living in the same household, whether or not related, are not eligible to enter or win. Void in all U.S. territories and possessions and overseas military installations and where prohibited or restricted by law\n\n2. TIMING: The Promotion begins May 16, 2012 at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Daylight Time (“PDT”) and ends on November 6, 2012 at 11:59 p.m. PDT (the “Promotion Period”).  During the Promotion Period, each week is defined as follows:\ni. Week 1: 5:00 a.m. PDT May 16, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT May 22, 2012\nii. Week 2: 12:00 a.m. PDT May 23, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT May 29, 2012\niii.  Week 3: 12:00 a.m. PDT May 30, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 5, 2012 \niv. Week 4: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 6, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 12, 2012 \nv. Week 5: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 13, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 19, 2012 \nvi. Week 6: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 20, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 26, 2012 \nvii. Week 7: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 27, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 3, 2012 \nviii. Week 8: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 4, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 10, 2012 \nix. Week 9: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 11, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 17, 2012 \nx. Week 10: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 18, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 24, 2012 \nxi. Week 11: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 25, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 31, 2012 \nxii. Week 12: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 1, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 7, 2012 \nxiii. Week 13: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 8, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 14, 2012 \nxiv. Week 14: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 15, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 21, 2012 \nxv. Week 15: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 22, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 28, 2012 \nxvi. Week 16: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 29, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 4, 2012 \nxvii. Week 17: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 5, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 11, 2012 \nxviii. Week 18: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 12, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 18, 2012 \nxix. Week 19: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 19, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 25, 2012 \nxx. Week 20: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 26, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 2, 2012 \nxxi. Week 21: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 3, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 9, 2012 \nxxii. Week 22: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 10, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 16, 2012 \nxxiii. Week 23: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 17, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 23, 2012 \nxxiv. Week 24: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 24, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 30, 2012 \nxxv. Week 25: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 31, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT November 6, 2012 \n\n3. HOW TO ENTER:  \ni. Enter through PlayStation®Home:\n1) During the Promotion Period, log into your PlayStation®Network account and launch PlayStation®Home application.\n2) Make your way to the Midway section of PlayStation®Home.\n3) Play any of the games located in the Midway section. To play any of the games located in the Midway, you will need a ticket. You can purchase 50 tickets for $0.99.  Free-play games do not count as an entry into the Promotion.\n4) For Week 1 through Week 25’s drawings, one ticket will count as one entry into the Promotion for that week.  You must play one of the games in Midway to enter that week’s drawing.  You may play any of the Midway games multiple times to submit multiple entries.  There is no limit on the number of entries that you can submit.\n5) To be entered into the Grand Prize drawing, you will get one entry for every one entry entered into the Promotion from Week 1 through Week 25’s drawings.  For example, if you have one entry in Week One and one entry in Week Two, you will get two entries into the Grand Prize drawing.  If your entry is chosen as a winning entry during one of the weekly drawings, that winning entry will be considered an eligible entry for the Grand Prize drawing.\n6) You may play any of the Midway games multiple times to submit multiple entries.  There is no limit on the number of entries you can submit.\n7) The Sponsor will randomly draw a winner for each week.\nii. Enter by Mail:\n1) During the Promotion Period, handwrite your name, email address, and indicate which week’s promotion drawing you would like to be entered into on a postage paid postcard via US Postal Service mail to The Midway’s Cash Carnival Prize, 530 Los Angeles Avenue #115 Box 218 Moorpark, CA 93021.  \n2) For Week 1 through Week 25’s drawings, one mail in entry will count as one entry into the Promotion for that week.  There is no limit on the number of entries that you can submit.  If your entry is chosen as a winning entry during one of the weekly drawings, that winning entry will be considered an eligible entry for the Grand Prize drawing.\n3) To be qualified in each week’s promotion, mail-in entries must be received between the following dates:\nWeek 01: May 16, 2012 - May 29, 2012\nWeek 02: May 23, 2012 - June 5, 2012\nWeek 03: May 30, 2012 - June 12, 2012\nWeek 04: June 6, 2012 - June 19, 2012\nWeek 05: June 13, 2012 - June 26, 2012\nWeek 06: June 20, 2012 - July 3, 2012\nWeek 07: June 27, 2012 - July 10, 2012\nWeek 08: July 4, 2012 - July 17, 2012\nWeek 09: July 11, 2012 - July 24, 2012\nWeek 10: July 18, 2012 - July 31, 2012\nWeek 11: July 25, 2012 - August 7, 2012\nWeek 12: August 1, 2012 - August 14, 2012\nWeek 13: August 8, 2012 - August 21, 2012\nWeek 14: August 15, 2012 - August 28, 2012\nWeek 15: August 22, 2012 - September 4, 2012\nWeek 16: August 29, 2012 - September 11, 2012\nWeek 17: September 5, 2012 - September 18, 2012\nWeek 18: September 12, 2012 - September 25, 2012\nWeek 19: September 19, 2012 - October 2, 2012\nWeek 20: September 26, 2012 - October 9, 2012\nWeek 21: October 3, 2012 - October 16, 2012\nWeek 22: October 10, 2012 - October 23, 2012\nWeek 23: October 17, 2012 - October 30, 2012\nWeek 24: October 24, 2012 - November 6, 2012\nWeek 25: October 31, 2012 - November 13, 2012\nGrand Prize: May 16, 2012 - November 13, 2012\n4) Sponsor will draw a winner for each week.\n\n4. ENTRY CONDITIONS:  The authorized account holder of the email address used to enter the Promotion is deemed to be the entrant. The “authorized account holder” is the natural person assigned to an email address by an internet access provider, online service provider or other organization responsible for assigning email addresses for the domain associated with the submitted address. Each potential winner may be required to show proof of being the authorized account holder.\n\n5. PRIZES: \nWeek 1: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $2,699.98 Approximate Retail Value (“ARV”))\nWeek 2: 1 Sony - 1000W 5.1-Ch. 3D/Wi-Fi Blu-ray Home Theater System. (BDVE780W / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 3: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver. (DSC-TX55 / $349.99 ARV)\nWeek 4: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory. (SGPT112US-S / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 5: 1 Sony - 3D Wi-Fi Built-In Blu-ray Player. (BDPS780 / $199.98 ARV)\nWeek 6: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $2,699.98 ARV)\nWeek 7: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory. (SGPT112US-S / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 8: 1 Sony - 1000W 5.1-Ch. 3D/Wi-Fi Blu-ray Home Theater System. (BDVE780W / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 9: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver. (DSC-WX9 / $199.98 ARV)\nWeek 10: 1 Sony - Handycam 32GB HD Flash Memory Camcorder – Black. (HDR-PJ710V / $1299.99 ARV)\nWeek 11: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $2,699.98 ARV)\nWeek 12: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory. (SGPT112US-S / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 13: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver. (DSC-WX9 / $199.98 ARV)\nWeek 14: 1 Sony - 10" Widescreen LCD Portable Blu-ray Disc Player. (BDP-SX1000 / $299.99 ARV)\nWeek 15: 1 Sony - 3D Wi-Fi Built-In Blu-ray Player. (BDPS780 / $1,199.98 ARV)\nWeek 16: 1 Sony - Handycam 16GB HD Flash Memory Projection Camcorder and $1,000.00 cash prize. (HDR-PJ260V / $1,649.99 ARV)\nWeek 17: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver and $1,000.00 cash prize. (DSC-WX9 / $1,199.98 ARV)\nWeek 18: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory and $1,000.00 cash prize. (SGPT112US-S / $1,499.98 ARV)\nWeek 19: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs and $1,000.00 cash prize. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $3,699.98 ARV)\nWeek 20: 1 Sony - 10" Widescreen LCD Portable Blu-ray Disc Player and $1,000.00 cash prize. (BDP-SX1000 / $1,299.99 ARV)\nWeek 21: 1 Sony - Handycam 16GB HD Flash Memory Projection Camcorder and $1,000.00 cash prize. (HDR-PJ260V / $1,649.99 ARV)\nWeek 22: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver and $1,000.00 cash prize. (DSC-WX9 / $1,199.98 ARV)\nWeek 23: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory and $1,000.00 cash prize. (SGPT112US-S / $1,499.98 ARV)\nWeek 24: 1 Sony - PlayStation®Vita Wi-Fi Portable Gaming System - Black and $1,000.00 cash prize. (PSV22031 / $1,249.99 ARV)\nWeek 25: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs and $1,000.00 cash prize. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $3,699.98 ARV)\nGrand Prize: $15,000 Cash Prize ($15,000.00 ARV)\n\nPrize fulfillment is based on availability. Please allow 8 to 12 weeks for prize delivery from the time a winner provides delivery information to Sponsor. Taxes on prize, if any, are solely the responsibility of the winner. Winners of a prize valued at $600.00 or more will receive a Federal Tax Form 1099.  We recommend that you consult with your tax advisor if you have further questions.  Sponsor reserves the right to substitute a prize of equal or greater value if a prize is unavailable. Sponsor may disqualify a winner and select an alternate winner if any prize is returned undeliverable. Prizes are non-transferable. Sponsor need not substitute a prize based on the winner’s request.\n\n6. ODDS OF WINNING: The odds of winning depend on the total number of eligible entries received.\n\n7. WINNER SELECTION:  Each Week a winner will be randomly selected by Sponsor from the entries received during that Week.\nWeek 01: Winner chosen on or about May 30, 2012\nWeek 02: Winner chosen on or about June 6, 2012\nWeek 03: Winner chosen on or about June 13, 2012\nWeek 04: Winner chosen on or about June 20, 2012\nWeek 05: Winner chosen on or about June 27, 2012\nWeek 06: Winner chosen on or about July 4, 2012\nWeek 07: Winner chosen on or about July 11, 2012\nWeek 08: Winner chosen on or about July 18, 2012\nWeek 09: Winner chosen on or about July 25, 2012\nWeek 10: Winner chosen on or about August 1, 2012\nWeek 11: Winner chosen on or about August 8, 2012\nWeek 12: Winner chosen on or about August 15, 2012\nWeek 13: Winner chosen on or about August 22, 2012\nWeek 14: Winner chosen on or about August 29, 2012\nWeek 15: Winner chosen on or about September 5, 2012\nWeek 16: Winner chosen on or about September 12, 2012\nWeek 17: Winner chosen on or about September 19, 2012\nWeek 18: Winner chosen on or about September 26, 2012\nWeek 19: Winner chosen on or about October 3, 2012\nWeek 20: Winner chosen on or about October 10, 2012\nWeek 21: Winner chosen on or about October 17, 2012\nWeek 22: Winner chosen on or about October 24, 2012\nWeek 23: Winner chosen on or about October 31, 2012\nWeek 24: Winner chosen on or about November 7, 2012\nWeek 25: Winner chosen on or about November 14, 2012\nGrand Prize: Winner chosen on or about November 21, 2012\n\nPotential winning entrants will be contacted via email.  If a potential winning entrant is determined by Sponsor to be unqualified to participate in this Promotion or does not respond to Sponsor’s correspondence within 72 hours, the potential winning entrant will be disqualified and a new potential winning entrant will be selected by random drawing.\n\n8. REQUIRED DOCUMENTATION:  The potential winning entrant will be required to complete an Affidavit of Eligibility and Release (“Affidavit”) in accordance with the instructions listed in the notification correspondence. Any entrant who fails or refuses to sign and return the required documentation within the time period as specified by Sponsor will be disqualified. If a potential winning entrant is considered a minor in the legal jurisdiction in which the entrant resides, then that entrant’s parent or legal guardian may be required to execute and return the Affidavit. Non-compliance with these Official Rules or failure to return all required documentation by the stated deadline or Sponsor’s inability to contact an entrant (using the contact information provided in his or her registration) within a reasonable time period, as determined in Sponsor’s sole discretion may result in disqualification and the forfeiture of the prize.\n\n9. PUBLICITY: Except where prohibited, participation in the Promotion constitutes entrant’s consent to Sponsor’s and its agent’s use of the entrant’s name, likeness, photograph, voice, opinions, hometown, state, and any other information submitted to Sponsor by entrant for promotional purposes, or on a winner’s list, if applicable, in any media, worldwide, without further payment or compensation.\n\n10. GENERAL CONDITIONS: Potential winning entrants are subject to Sponsor’s verification. Sponsor’s decisions are final and binding in all matters related to the Promotion. Potential winners must comply with the Official Rules, and receipt of prizes is contingent upon fulfilling all requirements. Sponsor is not responsible for technical, hardware or software failures, malfunctions, lost or unavailable network connections or failed, incomplete, garbled or delayed computer transmissions or unforeseen schedule changes that may limit an entrant’s ability to participate in the Promotion, even if caused by Sponsor’s negligence. Entries generated by script, macro or other automated means or with the intent to impair the integrity of the Promotion will be void.  Sponsor has the sole discretion to modify, cancel or suspend this Promotion should viruses, bugs, unauthorized human intervention or other causes beyond Sponsor’s control affect the administration, security or proper play of the Promotion or Sponsor otherwise becomes incapable of running the Promotion as planned. Sponsor is not responsible for changes to entrant’s contact information. Any individual who attempts or otherwise encourages, directly or indirectly, the submission of false entries, as determined by Sponsor, will be disqualified. Sponsor has the sole discretion to disqualify any entrant who tampers with the entry process.  Sponsor has the sole discretion to disqualify entrants who violate these Official Rules, tamper with the operation of the Promotion or engage in any conduct that is deemed detrimental or unfair to Sponsor, the Promotion or any other entrant.  Sponsor has no obligation to return any entry consideration, if applicable, submitted by a disqualified entrant.\n\n11. RELEASE: As a condition of participating in the Promotion, entrants release the Sponsor and its respective affiliates, subsidiaries, parent corporations, advertising and promotional agencies, and all of their officers, directors, shareholders, members, employees, and agents (collectively, the “Promotion Entities”) from liability, for loss, harm, damage, injury, cost or expense whatsoever including property damage, personal injury and death that may occur in connection with, preparation for, travel to, or participation in the Promotion, or possession, acceptance or use of prizes or participation in any Promotion-related activities and claims based on publicity rights, copyright or trademark infringement, defamation or invasion of privacy and merchandise delivery.\n\n12. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY: The Promotion Entities are not responsible for: any incorrect or inaccurate entry information; human errors; technical malfunctions; lost, stolen, mutilated, mis-delivered, postage due, illegible, incomplete or untimely entries that may limit entrant’s ability to participate in the Promotion, even if caused by Sponsor’s negligence; failures, omissions, interruptions, deletions, or defects of any telephone network, computer online system, computer equipment, servers, providers, or software, including any injury or damage to entrant's or any other person's computer relating to participation or inability to participate in the Promotion; inability to access the site or upload information or data; theft, tampering, destruction, or unauthorized access to, or alteration of, entries; data that is processed late or incorrectly or is incomplete or lost due to telephone, computer, or electronic malfunction or traffic congestion on telephone lines or the Internet or any website (including the site) or for any other reason whatsoever; printing or other errors; or any combination thereof. Proof of uploading information or data or entering information at the site is not considered proof of delivery or receipt. Illegible, duplicate and incomplete entries will be disqualified. False, fraudulent, or deceptive entries or acts, as determined by Sponsor, render entrants ineligible, and all associated entries will be void.\n\n13. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION: Information collected in connection with the Promotion will be collected in accordance with Sponsor’s Privacy Policy, available at http://www.us.playstation.com/Support/PrivacyPolicy. By participating in the Promotion, each entrant agrees to the terms of Sponsor’s Privacy Policy.\n\n14. GOVERNING LAW: All issues and questions concerning the construction, validity, interpretation and enforceability of these Official Rules or the rights and obligations of entrants or Sponsor in connection with this Promotion are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California without giving effect to any choice of law or conflict of law rules (whether of the State of California or any other jurisdiction) that would cause the application of any other state’s laws. Entrants hereby submit to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of the Federal and State Courts in San Mateo, California for the purposes of any suit related to the Promotion and waive any claim that they are not subject personally to the jurisdiction of said courts or that any such suit or other proceeding is brought in an inconvenient forum or improper venue.\n\n15. WINNER LIST: To obtain a winner list by mail, send a stamped, self-addressed envelope to “The Midway’s Cash Carnival Sweepstakes” Attn: SCEA PlayStation Home, 919 E. Hillsdale Blvd., Foster City, CA 94404. Sponsor will send requested winner lists within 4-6 weeks after all prizes are awarded. Requests for the winner list must be received by November 20, 2012.\n\n16. SPONSOR: Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC, 919 E. Hillsdale Blvd, Foster City, CA 94404.\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">We are delighted to introduce an exciting sweepstakes opportunity! Every time you use your Green Ticket to play any game in any Midway space or the Hot Zone, you will get a sweepstakes entry! There are 25 fabulous Sony prizes and a pile of money to give away too! Check out the Sweepstakes Prizes Board to see what you can win. Just read the Official Rules and, if you qualify, sign up for the Sweepstakes and start playing for fun and a chance to win real prizes! Once you enter the sweepstakes you can track your entries on the My Sweepstakes Entries Board. Have a ton of fun and good luck!\n\n\nOFFICIAL RULES\nThe following promotion is intended for viewing in the 50 United States and D.C. only and is construed and evaluated according to California law.  Do not enter this Promotion if you are not a legal resident of, and located in, the 50 United States or D.C. at the time of entry.\n\nNO PURCHASE NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN. A PURCHASE DOES NOT IMPROVE YOUR CHANCES OF WINNING.\n\nBy participating in The Midway’s Cash Carnival Sweepstakes (the “Promotion”), each entrant (or his or her parent or legal guardian if the entrant is under the age of majority in his or her state of residence) unconditionally accepts and agrees to comply with and abide by these Official Rules and the decisions of Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC (“Sponsor”), which are final and binding in all respects. Sponsor is responsible for the collection and selection entries and the Promotion’s overall administration. Entrants should look solely to Sponsor with any questions, comments or problems related to the Promotion.\n\n1. ELIGIBILITY: The Midway’s Cash Carnival Prize (the “Promotion”) is open only to legal residents of the 50 United States and the District of Columbia who are 18 years of age or older. Entrants under the legal age of majority in their state of residence should get permission to enter the Promotion from their parent or guardian. Employees of Sponsor and its parent companies, affiliates, subsidiaries, and related companies, and agencies and immediate families (defined as parents, children, siblings and spouse and their respective spouses, regardless of where they reside) and those living in the same household, whether or not related, are not eligible to enter or win. Void in all U.S. territories and possessions and overseas military installations and where prohibited or restricted by law\n\n2. TIMING: The Promotion begins May 16, 2012 at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Daylight Time (“PDT”) and ends on November 6, 2012 at 11:59 p.m. PDT (the “Promotion Period”).  During the Promotion Period, each week is defined as follows:\ni. Week 1: 5:00 a.m. PDT May 16, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT May 22, 2012\nii. Week 2: 12:00 a.m. PDT May 23, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT May 29, 2012\niii.  Week 3: 12:00 a.m. PDT May 30, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 5, 2012 \niv. Week 4: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 6, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 12, 2012 \nv. Week 5: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 13, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 19, 2012 \nvi. Week 6: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 20, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 26, 2012 \nvii. Week 7: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 27, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 3, 2012 \nviii. Week 8: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 4, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 10, 2012 \nix. Week 9: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 11, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 17, 2012 \nx. Week 10: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 18, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 24, 2012 \nxi. Week 11: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 25, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 31, 2012 \nxii. Week 12: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 1, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 7, 2012 \nxiii. Week 13: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 8, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 14, 2012 \nxiv. Week 14: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 15, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 21, 2012 \nxv. Week 15: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 22, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 28, 2012 \nxvi. Week 16: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 29, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 4, 2012 \nxvii. Week 17: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 5, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 11, 2012 \nxviii. Week 18: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 12, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 18, 2012 \nxix. Week 19: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 19, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 25, 2012 \nxx. Week 20: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 26, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 2, 2012 \nxxi. Week 21: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 3, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 9, 2012 \nxxii. Week 22: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 10, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 16, 2012 \nxxiii. Week 23: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 17, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 23, 2012 \nxxiv. Week 24: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 24, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 30, 2012 \nxxv. Week 25: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 31, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT November 6, 2012 \n\n3. HOW TO ENTER:  \ni. Enter through PlayStation®Home:\n1) During the Promotion Period, log into your PlayStation®Network account and launch PlayStation®Home application.\n2) Make your way to the Midway section of PlayStation®Home.\n3) Play any of the games located in the Midway section. To play any of the games located in the Midway, you will need a ticket. You can purchase 50 tickets for $0.99.  Free-play games do not count as an entry into the Promotion.\n4) For Week 1 through Week 25’s drawings, one ticket will count as one entry into the Promotion for that week.  You must play one of the games in Midway to enter that week’s drawing.  You may play any of the Midway games multiple times to submit multiple entries.  There is no limit on the number of entries that you can submit.\n5) To be entered into the Grand Prize drawing, you will get one entry for every one entry entered into the Promotion from Week 1 through Week 25’s drawings.  For example, if you have one entry in Week One and one entry in Week Two, you will get two entries into the Grand Prize drawing.  If your entry is chosen as a winning entry during one of the weekly drawings, that winning entry will be considered an eligible entry for the Grand Prize drawing.\n6) You may play any of the Midway games multiple times to submit multiple entries.  There is no limit on the number of entries you can submit.\n7) The Sponsor will randomly draw a winner for each week.\nii. Enter by Mail:\n1) During the Promotion Period, handwrite your name, email address, and indicate which week’s promotion drawing you would like to be entered into on a postage paid postcard via US Postal Service mail to The Midway’s Cash Carnival Prize, 530 Los Angeles Avenue #115 Box 218 Moorpark, CA 93021.  \n2) For Week 1 through Week 25’s drawings, one mail in entry will count as one entry into the Promotion for that week.  There is no limit on the number of entries that you can submit.  If your entry is chosen as a winning entry during one of the weekly drawings, that winning entry will be considered an eligible entry for the Grand Prize drawing.\n3) To be qualified in each week’s promotion, mail-in entries must be received between the following dates:\nWeek 01: May 16, 2012 - May 29, 2012\nWeek 02: May 23, 2012 - June 5, 2012\nWeek 03: May 30, 2012 - June 12, 2012\nWeek 04: June 6, 2012 - June 19, 2012\nWeek 05: June 13, 2012 - June 26, 2012\nWeek 06: June 20, 2012 - July 3, 2012\nWeek 07: June 27, 2012 - July 10, 2012\nWeek 08: July 4, 2012 - July 17, 2012\nWeek 09: July 11, 2012 - July 24, 2012\nWeek 10: July 18, 2012 - July 31, 2012\nWeek 11: July 25, 2012 - August 7, 2012\nWeek 12: August 1, 2012 - August 14, 2012\nWeek 13: August 8, 2012 - August 21, 2012\nWeek 14: August 15, 2012 - August 28, 2012\nWeek 15: August 22, 2012 - September 4, 2012\nWeek 16: August 29, 2012 - September 11, 2012\nWeek 17: September 5, 2012 - September 18, 2012\nWeek 18: September 12, 2012 - September 25, 2012\nWeek 19: September 19, 2012 - October 2, 2012\nWeek 20: September 26, 2012 - October 9, 2012\nWeek 21: October 3, 2012 - October 16, 2012\nWeek 22: October 10, 2012 - October 23, 2012\nWeek 23: October 17, 2012 - October 30, 2012\nWeek 24: October 24, 2012 - November 6, 2012\nWeek 25: October 31, 2012 - November 13, 2012\nGrand Prize: May 16, 2012 - November 13, 2012\n4) Sponsor will draw a winner for each week.\n\n4. ENTRY CONDITIONS:  The authorized account holder of the email address used to enter the Promotion is deemed to be the entrant. The “authorized account holder” is the natural person assigned to an email address by an internet access provider, online service provider or other organization responsible for assigning email addresses for the domain associated with the submitted address. Each potential winner may be required to show proof of being the authorized account holder.\n\n5. PRIZES: \nWeek 1: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $2,699.98 Approximate Retail Value (“ARV”))\nWeek 2: 1 Sony - 1000W 5.1-Ch. 3D/Wi-Fi Blu-ray Home Theater System. (BDVE780W / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 3: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver. (DSC-TX55 / $349.99 ARV)\nWeek 4: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory. (SGPT112US-S / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 5: 1 Sony - 3D Wi-Fi Built-In Blu-ray Player. (BDPS780 / $199.98 ARV)\nWeek 6: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $2,699.98 ARV)\nWeek 7: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory. (SGPT112US-S / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 8: 1 Sony - 1000W 5.1-Ch. 3D/Wi-Fi Blu-ray Home Theater System. (BDVE780W / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 9: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver. (DSC-WX9 / $199.98 ARV)\nWeek 10: 1 Sony - Handycam 32GB HD Flash Memory Camcorder – Black. (HDR-PJ710V / $1299.99 ARV)\nWeek 11: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $2,699.98 ARV)\nWeek 12: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory. (SGPT112US-S / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 13: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver. (DSC-WX9 / $199.98 ARV)\nWeek 14: 1 Sony - 10" Widescreen LCD Portable Blu-ray Disc Player. (BDP-SX1000 / $299.99 ARV)\nWeek 15: 1 Sony - 3D Wi-Fi Built-In Blu-ray Player. (BDPS780 / $1,199.98 ARV)\nWeek 16: 1 Sony - Handycam 16GB HD Flash Memory Projection Camcorder and $1,000.00 cash prize. (HDR-PJ260V / $1,649.99 ARV)\nWeek 17: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver and $1,000.00 cash prize. (DSC-WX9 / $1,199.98 ARV)\nWeek 18: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory and $1,000.00 cash prize. (SGPT112US-S / $1,499.98 ARV)\nWeek 19: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs and $1,000.00 cash prize. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $3,699.98 ARV)\nWeek 20: 1 Sony - 10" Widescreen LCD Portable Blu-ray Disc Player and $1,000.00 cash prize. (BDP-SX1000 / $1,299.99 ARV)\nWeek 21: 1 Sony - Handycam 16GB HD Flash Memory Projection Camcorder and $1,000.00 cash prize. (HDR-PJ260V / $1,649.99 ARV)\nWeek 22: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver and $1,000.00 cash prize. (DSC-WX9 / $1,199.98 ARV)\nWeek 23: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory and $1,000.00 cash prize. (SGPT112US-S / $1,499.98 ARV)\nWeek 24: 1 Sony - PlayStation®Vita Wi-Fi Portable Gaming System - Black and $1,000.00 cash prize. (PSV22031 / $1,249.99 ARV)\nWeek 25: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs and $1,000.00 cash prize. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $3,699.98 ARV)\nGrand Prize: $15,000 Cash Prize ($15,000.00 ARV)\n\nPrize fulfillment is based on availability. Please allow 8 to 12 weeks for prize delivery from the time a winner provides delivery information to Sponsor. Taxes on prize, if any, are solely the responsibility of the winner. Winners of a prize valued at $600.00 or more will receive a Federal Tax Form 1099.  We recommend that you consult with your tax advisor if you have further questions.  Sponsor reserves the right to substitute a prize of equal or greater value if a prize is unavailable. Sponsor may disqualify a winner and select an alternate winner if any prize is returned undeliverable. Prizes are non-transferable. Sponsor need not substitute a prize based on the winner’s request.\n\n6. ODDS OF WINNING: The odds of winning depend on the total number of eligible entries received.\n\n7. WINNER SELECTION:  Each Week a winner will be randomly selected by Sponsor from the entries received during that Week.\nWeek 01: Winner chosen on or about May 30, 2012\nWeek 02: Winner chosen on or about June 6, 2012\nWeek 03: Winner chosen on or about June 13, 2012\nWeek 04: Winner chosen on or about June 20, 2012\nWeek 05: Winner chosen on or about June 27, 2012\nWeek 06: Winner chosen on or about July 4, 2012\nWeek 07: Winner chosen on or about July 11, 2012\nWeek 08: Winner chosen on or about July 18, 2012\nWeek 09: Winner chosen on or about July 25, 2012\nWeek 10: Winner chosen on or about August 1, 2012\nWeek 11: Winner chosen on or about August 8, 2012\nWeek 12: Winner chosen on or about August 15, 2012\nWeek 13: Winner chosen on or about August 22, 2012\nWeek 14: Winner chosen on or about August 29, 2012\nWeek 15: Winner chosen on or about September 5, 2012\nWeek 16: Winner chosen on or about September 12, 2012\nWeek 17: Winner chosen on or about September 19, 2012\nWeek 18: Winner chosen on or about September 26, 2012\nWeek 19: Winner chosen on or about October 3, 2012\nWeek 20: Winner chosen on or about October 10, 2012\nWeek 21: Winner chosen on or about October 17, 2012\nWeek 22: Winner chosen on or about October 24, 2012\nWeek 23: Winner chosen on or about October 31, 2012\nWeek 24: Winner chosen on or about November 7, 2012\nWeek 25: Winner chosen on or about November 14, 2012\nGrand Prize: Winner chosen on or about November 21, 2012\n\nPotential winning entrants will be contacted via email.  If a potential winning entrant is determined by Sponsor to be unqualified to participate in this Promotion or does not respond to Sponsor’s correspondence within 72 hours, the potential winning entrant will be disqualified and a new potential winning entrant will be selected by random drawing.\n\n8. REQUIRED DOCUMENTATION:  The potential winning entrant will be required to complete an Affidavit of Eligibility and Release (“Affidavit”) in accordance with the instructions listed in the notification correspondence. Any entrant who fails or refuses to sign and return the required documentation within the time period as specified by Sponsor will be disqualified. If a potential winning entrant is considered a minor in the legal jurisdiction in which the entrant resides, then that entrant’s parent or legal guardian may be required to execute and return the Affidavit. Non-compliance with these Official Rules or failure to return all required documentation by the stated deadline or Sponsor’s inability to contact an entrant (using the contact information provided in his or her registration) within a reasonable time period, as determined in Sponsor’s sole discretion may result in disqualification and the forfeiture of the prize.\n\n9. PUBLICITY: Except where prohibited, participation in the Promotion constitutes entrant’s consent to Sponsor’s and its agent’s use of the entrant’s name, likeness, photograph, voice, opinions, hometown, state, and any other information submitted to Sponsor by entrant for promotional purposes, or on a winner’s list, if applicable, in any media, worldwide, without further payment or compensation.\n\n10. GENERAL CONDITIONS: Potential winning entrants are subject to Sponsor’s verification. Sponsor’s decisions are final and binding in all matters related to the Promotion. Potential winners must comply with the Official Rules, and receipt of prizes is contingent upon fulfilling all requirements. Sponsor is not responsible for technical, hardware or software failures, malfunctions, lost or unavailable network connections or failed, incomplete, garbled or delayed computer transmissions or unforeseen schedule changes that may limit an entrant’s ability to participate in the Promotion, even if caused by Sponsor’s negligence. Entries generated by script, macro or other automated means or with the intent to impair the integrity of the Promotion will be void.  Sponsor has the sole discretion to modify, cancel or suspend this Promotion should viruses, bugs, unauthorized human intervention or other causes beyond Sponsor’s control affect the administration, security or proper play of the Promotion or Sponsor otherwise becomes incapable of running the Promotion as planned. Sponsor is not responsible for changes to entrant’s contact information. Any individual who attempts or otherwise encourages, directly or indirectly, the submission of false entries, as determined by Sponsor, will be disqualified. Sponsor has the sole discretion to disqualify any entrant who tampers with the entry process.  Sponsor has the sole discretion to disqualify entrants who violate these Official Rules, tamper with the operation of the Promotion or engage in any conduct that is deemed detrimental or unfair to Sponsor, the Promotion or any other entrant.  Sponsor has no obligation to return any entry consideration, if applicable, submitted by a disqualified entrant.\n\n11. RELEASE: As a condition of participating in the Promotion, entrants release the Sponsor and its respective affiliates, subsidiaries, parent corporations, advertising and promotional agencies, and all of their officers, directors, shareholders, members, employees, and agents (collectively, the “Promotion Entities”) from liability, for loss, harm, damage, injury, cost or expense whatsoever including property damage, personal injury and death that may occur in connection with, preparation for, travel to, or participation in the Promotion, or possession, acceptance or use of prizes or participation in any Promotion-related activities and claims based on publicity rights, copyright or trademark infringement, defamation or invasion of privacy and merchandise delivery.\n\n12. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY: The Promotion Entities are not responsible for: any incorrect or inaccurate entry information; human errors; technical malfunctions; lost, stolen, mutilated, mis-delivered, postage due, illegible, incomplete or untimely entries that may limit entrant’s ability to participate in the Promotion, even if caused by Sponsor’s negligence; failures, omissions, interruptions, deletions, or defects of any telephone network, computer online system, computer equipment, servers, providers, or software, including any injury or damage to entrant's or any other person's computer relating to participation or inability to participate in the Promotion; inability to access the site or upload information or data; theft, tampering, destruction, or unauthorized access to, or alteration of, entries; data that is processed late or incorrectly or is incomplete or lost due to telephone, computer, or electronic malfunction or traffic congestion on telephone lines or the Internet or any website (including the site) or for any other reason whatsoever; printing or other errors; or any combination thereof. Proof of uploading information or data or entering information at the site is not considered proof of delivery or receipt. Illegible, duplicate and incomplete entries will be disqualified. False, fraudulent, or deceptive entries or acts, as determined by Sponsor, render entrants ineligible, and all associated entries will be void.\n\n13. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION: Information collected in connection with the Promotion will be collected in accordance with Sponsor’s Privacy Policy, available at http://www.us.playstation.com/Support/PrivacyPolicy. By participating in the Promotion, each entrant agrees to the terms of Sponsor’s Privacy Policy.\n\n14. GOVERNING LAW: All issues and questions concerning the construction, validity, interpretation and enforceability of these Official Rules or the rights and obligations of entrants or Sponsor in connection with this Promotion are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California without giving effect to any choice of law or conflict of law rules (whether of the State of California or any other jurisdiction) that would cause the application of any other state’s laws. Entrants hereby submit to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of the Federal and State Courts in San Mateo, California for the purposes of any suit related to the Promotion and waive any claim that they are not subject personally to the jurisdiction of said courts or that any such suit or other proceeding is brought in an inconvenient forum or improper venue.\n\n15. WINNER LIST: To obtain a winner list by mail, send a stamped, self-addressed envelope to “The Midway’s Cash Carnival Sweepstakes” Attn: SCEA PlayStation Home, 919 E. Hillsdale Blvd., Foster City, CA 94404. Sponsor will send requested winner lists within 4-6 weeks after all prizes are awarded. Requests for the winner list must be received by November 20, 2012.\n\n16. SPONSOR: Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC, 919 E. Hillsdale Blvd, Foster City, CA 94404.\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">We are delighted to introduce an exciting sweepstakes opportunity! Every time you use your Green Ticket to play any game in any Midway space or the Hot Zone, you will get a sweepstakes entry! There are 25 fabulous Sony prizes and a pile of money to give away too! Check out the Sweepstakes Prizes Board to see what you can win. Just read the Official Rules and, if you qualify, sign up for the Sweepstakes and start playing for fun and a chance to win real prizes! Once you enter the sweepstakes you can track your entries on the My Sweepstakes Entries Board. Have a ton of fun and good luck!\n\n\nOFFICIAL RULES\nThe following promotion is intended for viewing in the 50 United States and D.C. only and is construed and evaluated according to California law.  Do not enter this Promotion if you are not a legal resident of, and located in, the 50 United States or D.C. at the time of entry.\n\nNO PURCHASE NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN. A PURCHASE DOES NOT IMPROVE YOUR CHANCES OF WINNING.\n\nBy participating in The Midway’s Cash Carnival Sweepstakes (the “Promotion”), each entrant (or his or her parent or legal guardian if the entrant is under the age of majority in his or her state of residence) unconditionally accepts and agrees to comply with and abide by these Official Rules and the decisions of Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC (“Sponsor”), which are final and binding in all respects. Sponsor is responsible for the collection and selection entries and the Promotion’s overall administration. Entrants should look solely to Sponsor with any questions, comments or problems related to the Promotion.\n\n1. ELIGIBILITY: The Midway’s Cash Carnival Prize (the “Promotion”) is open only to legal residents of the 50 United States and the District of Columbia who are 18 years of age or older. Entrants under the legal age of majority in their state of residence should get permission to enter the Promotion from their parent or guardian. Employees of Sponsor and its parent companies, affiliates, subsidiaries, and related companies, and agencies and immediate families (defined as parents, children, siblings and spouse and their respective spouses, regardless of where they reside) and those living in the same household, whether or not related, are not eligible to enter or win. Void in all U.S. territories and possessions and overseas military installations and where prohibited or restricted by law\n\n2. TIMING: The Promotion begins May 16, 2012 at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Daylight Time (“PDT”) and ends on November 6, 2012 at 11:59 p.m. PDT (the “Promotion Period”).  During the Promotion Period, each week is defined as follows:\ni. Week 1: 5:00 a.m. PDT May 16, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT May 22, 2012\nii. Week 2: 12:00 a.m. PDT May 23, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT May 29, 2012\niii.  Week 3: 12:00 a.m. PDT May 30, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 5, 2012 \niv. Week 4: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 6, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 12, 2012 \nv. Week 5: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 13, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 19, 2012 \nvi. Week 6: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 20, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT June 26, 2012 \nvii. Week 7: 12:00 a.m. PDT June 27, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 3, 2012 \nviii. Week 8: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 4, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 10, 2012 \nix. Week 9: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 11, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 17, 2012 \nx. Week 10: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 18, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 24, 2012 \nxi. Week 11: 12:00 a.m. PDT July 25, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT July 31, 2012 \nxii. Week 12: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 1, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 7, 2012 \nxiii. Week 13: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 8, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 14, 2012 \nxiv. Week 14: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 15, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 21, 2012 \nxv. Week 15: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 22, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT August 28, 2012 \nxvi. Week 16: 12:00 a.m. PDT August 29, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 4, 2012 \nxvii. Week 17: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 5, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 11, 2012 \nxviii. Week 18: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 12, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 18, 2012 \nxix. Week 19: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 19, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT September 25, 2012 \nxx. Week 20: 12:00 a.m. PDT September 26, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 2, 2012 \nxxi. Week 21: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 3, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 9, 2012 \nxxii. Week 22: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 10, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 16, 2012 \nxxiii. Week 23: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 17, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 23, 2012 \nxxiv. Week 24: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 24, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT October 30, 2012 \nxxv. Week 25: 12:00 a.m. PDT October 31, 2012 - 11:59 p.m. PDT November 6, 2012 \n\n3. HOW TO ENTER:  \ni. Enter through PlayStation®Home:\n1) During the Promotion Period, log into your PlayStation®Network account and launch PlayStation®Home application.\n2) Make your way to the Midway section of PlayStation®Home.\n3) Play any of the games located in the Midway section. To play any of the games located in the Midway, you will need a ticket. You can purchase 50 tickets for $0.99.  Free-play games do not count as an entry into the Promotion.\n4) For Week 1 through Week 25’s drawings, one ticket will count as one entry into the Promotion for that week.  You must play one of the games in Midway to enter that week’s drawing.  You may play any of the Midway games multiple times to submit multiple entries.  There is no limit on the number of entries that you can submit.\n5) To be entered into the Grand Prize drawing, you will get one entry for every one entry entered into the Promotion from Week 1 through Week 25’s drawings.  For example, if you have one entry in Week One and one entry in Week Two, you will get two entries into the Grand Prize drawing.  If your entry is chosen as a winning entry during one of the weekly drawings, that winning entry will be considered an eligible entry for the Grand Prize drawing.\n6) You may play any of the Midway games multiple times to submit multiple entries.  There is no limit on the number of entries you can submit.\n7) The Sponsor will randomly draw a winner for each week.\nii. Enter by Mail:\n1) During the Promotion Period, handwrite your name, email address, and indicate which week’s promotion drawing you would like to be entered into on a postage paid postcard via US Postal Service mail to The Midway’s Cash Carnival Prize, 530 Los Angeles Avenue #115 Box 218 Moorpark, CA 93021.  \n2) For Week 1 through Week 25’s drawings, one mail in entry will count as one entry into the Promotion for that week.  There is no limit on the number of entries that you can submit.  If your entry is chosen as a winning entry during one of the weekly drawings, that winning entry will be considered an eligible entry for the Grand Prize drawing.\n3) To be qualified in each week’s promotion, mail-in entries must be received between the following dates:\nWeek 01: May 16, 2012 - May 29, 2012\nWeek 02: May 23, 2012 - June 5, 2012\nWeek 03: May 30, 2012 - June 12, 2012\nWeek 04: June 6, 2012 - June 19, 2012\nWeek 05: June 13, 2012 - June 26, 2012\nWeek 06: June 20, 2012 - July 3, 2012\nWeek 07: June 27, 2012 - July 10, 2012\nWeek 08: July 4, 2012 - July 17, 2012\nWeek 09: July 11, 2012 - July 24, 2012\nWeek 10: July 18, 2012 - July 31, 2012\nWeek 11: July 25, 2012 - August 7, 2012\nWeek 12: August 1, 2012 - August 14, 2012\nWeek 13: August 8, 2012 - August 21, 2012\nWeek 14: August 15, 2012 - August 28, 2012\nWeek 15: August 22, 2012 - September 4, 2012\nWeek 16: August 29, 2012 - September 11, 2012\nWeek 17: September 5, 2012 - September 18, 2012\nWeek 18: September 12, 2012 - September 25, 2012\nWeek 19: September 19, 2012 - October 2, 2012\nWeek 20: September 26, 2012 - October 9, 2012\nWeek 21: October 3, 2012 - October 16, 2012\nWeek 22: October 10, 2012 - October 23, 2012\nWeek 23: October 17, 2012 - October 30, 2012\nWeek 24: October 24, 2012 - November 6, 2012\nWeek 25: October 31, 2012 - November 13, 2012\nGrand Prize: May 16, 2012 - November 13, 2012\n4) Sponsor will draw a winner for each week.\n\n4. ENTRY CONDITIONS:  The authorized account holder of the email address used to enter the Promotion is deemed to be the entrant. The “authorized account holder” is the natural person assigned to an email address by an internet access provider, online service provider or other organization responsible for assigning email addresses for the domain associated with the submitted address. Each potential winner may be required to show proof of being the authorized account holder.\n\n5. PRIZES: \nWeek 1: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $2,699.98 Approximate Retail Value (“ARV”))\nWeek 2: 1 Sony - 1000W 5.1-Ch. 3D/Wi-Fi Blu-ray Home Theater System. (BDVE780W / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 3: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver. (DSC-TX55 / $349.99 ARV)\nWeek 4: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory. (SGPT112US-S / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 5: 1 Sony - 3D Wi-Fi Built-In Blu-ray Player. (BDPS780 / $199.98 ARV)\nWeek 6: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $2,699.98 ARV)\nWeek 7: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory. (SGPT112US-S / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 8: 1 Sony - 1000W 5.1-Ch. 3D/Wi-Fi Blu-ray Home Theater System. (BDVE780W / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 9: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver. (DSC-WX9 / $199.98 ARV)\nWeek 10: 1 Sony - Handycam 32GB HD Flash Memory Camcorder – Black. (HDR-PJ710V / $1299.99 ARV)\nWeek 11: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $2,699.98 ARV)\nWeek 12: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory. (SGPT112US-S / $499.98 ARV)\nWeek 13: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver. (DSC-WX9 / $199.98 ARV)\nWeek 14: 1 Sony - 10" Widescreen LCD Portable Blu-ray Disc Player. (BDP-SX1000 / $299.99 ARV)\nWeek 15: 1 Sony - 3D Wi-Fi Built-In Blu-ray Player. (BDPS780 / $1,199.98 ARV)\nWeek 16: 1 Sony - Handycam 16GB HD Flash Memory Projection Camcorder and $1,000.00 cash prize. (HDR-PJ260V / $1,649.99 ARV)\nWeek 17: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver and $1,000.00 cash prize. (DSC-WX9 / $1,199.98 ARV)\nWeek 18: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory and $1,000.00 cash prize. (SGPT112US-S / $1,499.98 ARV)\nWeek 19: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs and $1,000.00 cash prize. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $3,699.98 ARV)\nWeek 20: 1 Sony - 10" Widescreen LCD Portable Blu-ray Disc Player and $1,000.00 cash prize. (BDP-SX1000 / $1,299.99 ARV)\nWeek 21: 1 Sony - Handycam 16GB HD Flash Memory Projection Camcorder and $1,000.00 cash prize. (HDR-PJ260V / $1,649.99 ARV)\nWeek 22: 1 Sony - Cyber-shot 16.2-Megapixel Digital Camera – Silver and $1,000.00 cash prize. (DSC-WX9 / $1,199.98 ARV)\nWeek 23: 1 Sony - Tablet S with 32GB Memory and $1,000.00 cash prize. (SGPT112US-S / $1,499.98 ARV)\nWeek 24: 1 Sony - PlayStation®Vita Wi-Fi Portable Gaming System - Black and $1,000.00 cash prize. (PSV22031 / $1,249.99 ARV)\nWeek 25: 1 Sony - BRAVIA 55" Class LED 1080p 240Hz 3D HDTV with 1 set of Sony - Battery-Operated 3D Glasses for Sony 3D Flat-Panel HDTVs and $1,000.00 cash prize. (XBR55HX929 &amp; TDGBR250B / $3,699.98 ARV)\nGrand Prize: $15,000 Cash Prize ($15,000.00 ARV)\n\nPrize fulfillment is based on availability. Please allow 8 to 12 weeks for prize delivery from the time a winner provides delivery information to Sponsor. Taxes on prize, if any, are solely the responsibility of the winner. Winners of a prize valued at $600.00 or more will receive a Federal Tax Form 1099.  We recommend that you consult with your tax advisor if you have further questions.  Sponsor reserves the right to substitute a prize of equal or greater value if a prize is unavailable. Sponsor may disqualify a winner and select an alternate winner if any prize is returned undeliverable. Prizes are non-transferable. Sponsor need not substitute a prize based on the winner’s request.\n\n6. ODDS OF WINNING: The odds of winning depend on the total number of eligible entries received.\n\n7. WINNER SELECTION:  Each Week a winner will be randomly selected by Sponsor from the entries received during that Week.\nWeek 01: Winner chosen on or about May 30, 2012\nWeek 02: Winner chosen on or about June 6, 2012\nWeek 03: Winner chosen on or about June 13, 2012\nWeek 04: Winner chosen on or about June 20, 2012\nWeek 05: Winner chosen on or about June 27, 2012\nWeek 06: Winner chosen on or about July 4, 2012\nWeek 07: Winner chosen on or about July 11, 2012\nWeek 08: Winner chosen on or about July 18, 2012\nWeek 09: Winner chosen on or about July 25, 2012\nWeek 10: Winner chosen on or about August 1, 2012\nWeek 11: Winner chosen on or about August 8, 2012\nWeek 12: Winner chosen on or about August 15, 2012\nWeek 13: Winner chosen on or about August 22, 2012\nWeek 14: Winner chosen on or about August 29, 2012\nWeek 15: Winner chosen on or about September 5, 2012\nWeek 16: Winner chosen on or about September 12, 2012\nWeek 17: Winner chosen on or about September 19, 2012\nWeek 18: Winner chosen on or about September 26, 2012\nWeek 19: Winner chosen on or about October 3, 2012\nWeek 20: Winner chosen on or about October 10, 2012\nWeek 21: Winner chosen on or about October 17, 2012\nWeek 22: Winner chosen on or about October 24, 2012\nWeek 23: Winner chosen on or about October 31, 2012\nWeek 24: Winner chosen on or about November 7, 2012\nWeek 25: Winner chosen on or about November 14, 2012\nGrand Prize: Winner chosen on or about November 21, 2012\n\nPotential winning entrants will be contacted via email.  If a potential winning entrant is determined by Sponsor to be unqualified to participate in this Promotion or does not respond to Sponsor’s correspondence within 72 hours, the potential winning entrant will be disqualified and a new potential winning entrant will be selected by random drawing.\n\n8. REQUIRED DOCUMENTATION:  The potential winning entrant will be required to complete an Affidavit of Eligibility and Release (“Affidavit”) in accordance with the instructions listed in the notification correspondence. Any entrant who fails or refuses to sign and return the required documentation within the time period as specified by Sponsor will be disqualified. If a potential winning entrant is considered a minor in the legal jurisdiction in which the entrant resides, then that entrant’s parent or legal guardian may be required to execute and return the Affidavit. Non-compliance with these Official Rules or failure to return all required documentation by the stated deadline or Sponsor’s inability to contact an entrant (using the contact information provided in his or her registration) within a reasonable time period, as determined in Sponsor’s sole discretion may result in disqualification and the forfeiture of the prize.\n\n9. PUBLICITY: Except where prohibited, participation in the Promotion constitutes entrant’s consent to Sponsor’s and its agent’s use of the entrant’s name, likeness, photograph, voice, opinions, hometown, state, and any other information submitted to Sponsor by entrant for promotional purposes, or on a winner’s list, if applicable, in any media, worldwide, without further payment or compensation.\n\n10. GENERAL CONDITIONS: Potential winning entrants are subject to Sponsor’s verification. Sponsor’s decisions are final and binding in all matters related to the Promotion. Potential winners must comply with the Official Rules, and receipt of prizes is contingent upon fulfilling all requirements. Sponsor is not responsible for technical, hardware or software failures, malfunctions, lost or unavailable network connections or failed, incomplete, garbled or delayed computer transmissions or unforeseen schedule changes that may limit an entrant’s ability to participate in the Promotion, even if caused by Sponsor’s negligence. Entries generated by script, macro or other automated means or with the intent to impair the integrity of the Promotion will be void.  Sponsor has the sole discretion to modify, cancel or suspend this Promotion should viruses, bugs, unauthorized human intervention or other causes beyond Sponsor’s control affect the administration, security or proper play of the Promotion or Sponsor otherwise becomes incapable of running the Promotion as planned. Sponsor is not responsible for changes to entrant’s contact information. Any individual who attempts or otherwise encourages, directly or indirectly, the submission of false entries, as determined by Sponsor, will be disqualified. Sponsor has the sole discretion to disqualify any entrant who tampers with the entry process.  Sponsor has the sole discretion to disqualify entrants who violate these Official Rules, tamper with the operation of the Promotion or engage in any conduct that is deemed detrimental or unfair to Sponsor, the Promotion or any other entrant.  Sponsor has no obligation to return any entry consideration, if applicable, submitted by a disqualified entrant.\n\n11. RELEASE: As a condition of participating in the Promotion, entrants release the Sponsor and its respective affiliates, subsidiaries, parent corporations, advertising and promotional agencies, and all of their officers, directors, shareholders, members, employees, and agents (collectively, the “Promotion Entities”) from liability, for loss, harm, damage, injury, cost or expense whatsoever including property damage, personal injury and death that may occur in connection with, preparation for, travel to, or participation in the Promotion, or possession, acceptance or use of prizes or participation in any Promotion-related activities and claims based on publicity rights, copyright or trademark infringement, defamation or invasion of privacy and merchandise delivery.\n\n12. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY: The Promotion Entities are not responsible for: any incorrect or inaccurate entry information; human errors; technical malfunctions; lost, stolen, mutilated, mis-delivered, postage due, illegible, incomplete or untimely entries that may limit entrant’s ability to participate in the Promotion, even if caused by Sponsor’s negligence; failures, omissions, interruptions, deletions, or defects of any telephone network, computer online system, computer equipment, servers, providers, or software, including any injury or damage to entrant's or any other person's computer relating to participation or inability to participate in the Promotion; inability to access the site or upload information or data; theft, tampering, destruction, or unauthorized access to, or alteration of, entries; data that is processed late or incorrectly or is incomplete or lost due to telephone, computer, or electronic malfunction or traffic congestion on telephone lines or the Internet or any website (including the site) or for any other reason whatsoever; printing or other errors; or any combination thereof. Proof of uploading information or data or entering information at the site is not considered proof of delivery or receipt. Illegible, duplicate and incomplete entries will be disqualified. False, fraudulent, or deceptive entries or acts, as determined by Sponsor, render entrants ineligible, and all associated entries will be void.\n\n13. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION: Information collected in connection with the Promotion will be collected in accordance with Sponsor’s Privacy Policy, available at http://www.us.playstation.com/Support/PrivacyPolicy. By participating in the Promotion, each entrant agrees to the terms of Sponsor’s Privacy Policy.\n\n14. GOVERNING LAW: All issues and questions concerning the construction, validity, interpretation and enforceability of these Official Rules or the rights and obligations of entrants or Sponsor in connection with this Promotion are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California without giving effect to any choice of law or conflict of law rules (whether of the State of California or any other jurisdiction) that would cause the application of any other state’s laws. Entrants hereby submit to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of the Federal and State Courts in San Mateo, California for the purposes of any suit related to the Promotion and waive any claim that they are not subject personally to the jurisdiction of said courts or that any such suit or other proceeding is brought in an inconvenient forum or improper venue.\n\n15. WINNER LIST: To obtain a winner list by mail, send a stamped, self-addressed envelope to “The Midway’s Cash Carnival Sweepstakes” Attn: SCEA PlayStation Home, 919 E. Hillsdale Blvd., Foster City, CA 94404. Sponsor will send requested winner lists within 4-6 weeks after all prizes are awarded. Requests for the winner list must be received by November 20, 2012.\n\n16. SPONSOR: Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC, 919 E. Hillsdale Blvd, Foster City, CA 94404.\n</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kScroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFTSTICK][UP][DOWN] Scroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFTSTICK][UP][DOWN] Faites défiler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFTSTICK][UP][DOWN] Blättern Sie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFTSTICK][UP][DOWN] Scorrere</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFTSTICK][UP][DOWN] Desplácese</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[LEFTSTICK][UP][DOWN] スクロール</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[LEFTSTICK][UP][DOWN] 스크롤</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[LEFTSTICK][UP][DOWN] Scroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[LEFTSTICK][UP][DOWN] 滾動</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[LEFTSTICK][UP][DOWN] 滾動</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[LEFTSTICK][UP][DOWN] Scroll</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDecline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE] Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE] Lasciare</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] Dejar de</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE] Decline</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kAccept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Accept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Accept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Accept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Accept</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kQuit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE] Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE] Lasciare</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] Dejar de</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[DECLINE] 終了する</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[DECLINE] 나가기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[DECLINE] 離開</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[DECLINE] 離開</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kInfo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[SQUARE] Hot Zone Info</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[SQUARE] Hot Zone Info</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[SQUARE] Hot Zone Info</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[SQUARE] Hot Zone Info</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kRules</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[SQUARE] Contest Rules</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[SQUARE] Contest Rules</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[SQUARE] Contest Rules</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[SQUARE] Contest Rules</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kConfirmTitle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sweepstakes Confirmation</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sweepstakes Confirmation</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sweepstakes Confirmation</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sweepstakes Confirmation</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kConfirm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">I have read the Official Rules and accept the terms of the Sweepstakes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">I have read the Official Rules and accept the terms of the Sweepstakes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">I have read the Official Rules and accept the terms of the Sweepstakes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">I have read the Official Rules and accept the terms of the Sweepstakes.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kConfirmAccept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Accept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Accept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Accept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Accept</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kConfirmDecline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE] Decline</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kConfirmDecline_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE] Decline</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>