<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Gone To Town Shirt - Light Well Worn (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Chemisier Gone To Town - Usé délavé clair (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Gone To Town Hemd - Leicht ausgebleicht (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Gone To Town Camicia - Effetto usato (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Gone To Town Camisa - Efecto gastado (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Gone To Town is a long sleeve novelty denim button down shirt with a bleached out wash on the pockets and sleeves to create colour clocked effect. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Gone To Town est un nouveau chemisier boutonné en denim à manches longues avec un effet blanchi sur les poches et les manches pour créer une cadence de couleurs. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Gone To Town Jeanshemd hat lange Ärmel und eine durchgehende Knopffleiste vorne und ist an den Brusttaschen und Ärmeln leicht ausgebleicht, was dem Hemd einen attraktiv abgetragenen Look verleiht. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La nuova camicia di jeans a maniche lunghe Gone To Town presenta lavaggio "bleached" con effetto sbiancato sulle tasche e sulle maniche per creare un effetto a blocchi di colore. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La Gone To Town es una nueva camisa de manga larga en tela vaquera y de botones, con un efecto lavado a lejía en bolsillos y mangas para crear un efecto programado en el color. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Gone To Town is a long sleeve novelty denim button down shirt with a bleached out wash on the pockets and sleeves to create color clocked effect. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>