<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Master Higgins Kanji T-shirt - [ゲームは一日一時間] (Men's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">T-shirt Kanji du Maître - [ゲームは一日一時間] (pour homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kanji-T-Shirt von Master Higgins – [ゲームは一日一時間] (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maglietta del Maestro - [ゲームは一日一時間] (da uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta con kanji del maestro - [ゲームは一日一時間] (Hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">高橋名人の漢字Ｔシャツ「ゲームは一日一時間」　男性用</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Master Higgins Kanji T-shirt - [ゲームは一日一時間] (Men's)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Chinese character T-shirt hand written by Master Higgins.\n“ゲームは一日一時間”  means “Game for 1 hour a day”, and those are the famous words of Master Higgins.\nIt always not good to overdo things. Master Higgins said these words in the hope that all kids would have various experiences in their lives as well as playing games. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">T-shirt à caractères chinois écrits à la main par le Maître.\n"ゲームは一日一時間" signifie "Une heure de jeu par jour", l'un des célèbres conseils du Maître. Ce dernier conseille par ailleurs de faire chaque chose avec mesure. Il destine ces mots à tous les enfants, en les invitant à vivre une vie riche d'expériences et de jeu. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Handbeschriebenes T-Shirt mit chinesischen Zeichen von Master Higgins.\n„ゲームは一日一時間“ bedeutet „1 Stunde täglich spielen“. Dies ist der berühmte Rat von Master Higgins.\nEs ist nie gut, die Dinge zu übertreiben. Master Higgins sprach diese Worte aus in der Hoffnung, dass alle Kinder neben Computerspielen noch viele andere Erfahrungen in ihrem Leben machen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maglietta con ideogrammi cinesi dipinti a mano dal Maestro.\n“ゲームは一日一時間” sono celebri parole del Maestro che significano "Gioca per 1 ora al giorno".\nNon è mai un bene esagerare nelle cose. Il Maestro ha pronunciato queste parole nella speranza che tutti i ragazzi abbiano esperienze diverse nella vita, oltre che giocare. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta con caracteres chinos escritos por el maestro.\n“ゲームは一日一時間” significa “Jugar 1 hora al día”, un famoso lema del maestro.\nNo siempre es bueno exagerar. El maestro pronunció estas palabras con la esperanza de que todos los chavales tuviesen otras experiencias en sus vidas además de los videojuegos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">高橋名人直筆の漢字Ｔシャツです！\n「ゲームは一日一時間」とは、言わずと知れた高橋名人の名言です！\n何ごともやりすぎは良くありませんね。ゲームも大事ですが様々な事を経験して欲しいという高橋名人の願いが込められています！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Chinese character T-shirt hand written by Master Higgins.\n“ゲームは一日一時間”  means “Game for 1 hour a day”, and those are the famous words of Master Higgins.\nIt always not good to overdo things. Master Higgins said these words in the hope that all kids would have various experiences in their lives as well as playing games. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>