<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Winter Vacation Villa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Maison de vacances d'hiver</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Winterferienvilla</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Villa vacanze invernali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Villa de vacaciones invernales</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">겨울 휴양지 빌라</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Winter Vacation Villa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">冬季度假屋</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">冬季度假屋</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Winter Vacation Villa</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Experience the frills and chills of this ski chalet winter wonderland overlooked by an icy cascading waterfall and nestled neatly in between a snowy cliff and snow-dressed forest. Complete with its own outdoor jacuzzi, indoor fireplace, and veranda bedroom, this is how the winter holiday was meant to be spent. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Situé au pied d'une cascade d'eau glacée, découvrez ce merveilleux chalet qui fera le bonheur des amateurs de ski. Il est niché entre une falaise enneigée et une forêt recouverte de flocons. Vous y trouverez un jacuzzi d'intérieur, une cheminée et une chambre véranda. Que pourrait-on rêver de mieux pour passer l'hiver ? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erlebe die kühle Faszination dieses wundervollen Winter-Chalets vor dem Hintergrund eines eisigen Wasserfalls und eingerahmt von einer verschneiten Klippe und einem schneebestäubten Wald. Mit einem Außen-Whirlpool, einem Kamin im Haus und dem Verandaschlafzimmer gibt es keinen schöneren Ort für den Winter. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sperimenta le sensazioni elettrizzanti della magia invernale di questo chalet di montagna affacciato su una cascatella ghiacciata e annidato elegantemente tra un dirupo e una foresta innevati. Completo di jacuzzi esterna personale, caminetto interno e stanza da letto fornita di veranda, questo chalet ti offre il modo perfetto di trascorrere l'inverno. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Disfruta de la tranquilidad y del fresquito de este maravilloso chalet para esquiar, con vistas a unas cataratas heladas y asentado entre un acantilado y un bosque cubiertos de nieve. Cuenta con un jacuzzi en el exterior, una chimenea y un dormitorio con una galería: no hay mejor modo de pasar el invierno. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">눈 덮인 숲과 바람을 따라 눈송이가 흩날리는 절벽 사이에 절묘하게 위치한 산장에서, 절벽을 타고 떨어지는 폭포수를 바라보며 겨울 휴양지의 따스함을 그대로 경험해 보십시오. 야외에 위치한 자쿠지와 실내 화로, 베란다가 딸린 침실을 포함하는 이 산장은 바로 겨울 휴가가 어떻게 사용되어야 하는지 여실히 보여줍니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Experience the frills and chills of this ski chalet winter wonderland overlooked by an icy cascading waterfall and nestled neatly in between a snowy cliff and snow-dressed forest. Complete with its own outdoor jacuzzi, indoor fireplace, and veranda bedroom, this is how the winter holiday was meant to be spent. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這間滑雪小木屋位於鋪滿白雪的懸崖和被白雪粉飾的森林，有冰冷的瀑布由高處落下，讓你體驗冰涼的冬日樂園。小木屋設有獨立的室外按摩池、室內壁爐和附有露台的臥室，寒假本來就是應該在這樣的地方度過的。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這間滑雪小木屋位於鋪滿白雪的懸崖和被白雪粉飾的森林，有冰冷的瀑布由高處落下，讓你體驗冰涼的冬日樂園。小木屋設有獨立的室外按摩池、室內壁爐和附有陽台的臥室，寒假本來就是應該在這樣的地方度過的。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Experience the frills and chills of this ski chalet winter wonderland overlooked by an icy cascading waterfall and nestled neatly in between a snowy cliff and snow-dressed forest. Complete with its own outdoor jacuzzi, indoor fireplace, and veranda bedroom, this is how the winter holiday was meant to be spent. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>