<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Novus Prime Concept: The Blade Lotus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Concept de Novus Prime : le Blade Lotus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Novus Prime Konzept: The Blade Lotus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Design Novus Prime: Blade Lotus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Concepto de Novus Prime: Blade Lotus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムのコンセプト：ブレイドロータス</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임 컨셉: 블레이드 로터스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Novus Prime Concept: The Blade Lotus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Novus Prime概念畫：Blade Lotus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Novus Prime概念畫：Blade Lotus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Novus Prime Concept: The Blade Lotus</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. Building and storing a seemingly-endless force of bot fighters, the Blade Lotus continues to produce ships during battle, ultimately overwhelming its foes. Four different turret weapons can be employed to take a direct hand in battle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ornez vos murs de peintures conceptuelles de Novus Prime. Semblant avoir un stock sans fin de droïdes, le Blade Lotus se bat tout en produisant ces unités durant la bataille, allant jusqu'à écraser sous le nombre ses ennemis. Quatre tourelles différentes sont également déployables pour directement prendre part au combat. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schmücke deine Wände mit den Konzeptzeichnungen von Novus Prime. Der Blade Lotus unterstützt den Kampf, indem er eine scheinbar endlose Flut an Bot-Schiffen baut und lagert, welche den Feind schließlich überwältigen. Vier unterschiedliche Raketentürme können eingesetzt werden, um einen direkten Einfluß auf den Kampf zu haben. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Decora le tue pareti con il design della Novus Prime. La Blade Lotus continua a costruire e produrre caccia anche in battaglia, accumulando un rifornimento con cui sopraffare il nemico. Può anche essere direttamente coinvolta in battaglia grazie alle quattro differenti torrette che può utilizzare. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Adorna tus paredes con las pinturas conceptuales de Novus Prime. Construye y almacena una fuerza interminable de robots de combate. Blade Lotus continua produciendo naves durante la batalla, sofocando a sus enemigos. Cuatro diferentes torres de armas pueden ser empleadas para entrar de lleno en batalla. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムのコンセプト絵画を壁に飾ろう。ボット戦闘機を次々と建造し、格納するブレイドロータスは、戦闘中にもどんどん船を送り出し敵を圧倒する。タレットウェポンは4種類を装備、戦闘中にも大活躍。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임의 컨셉화로 벽을 장식합니다. 끝없이 등장하는 봇 전투기를 생산하고 보관하는 블레이드 로터스는 전투 중에도 함선 생산을 멈추지 않아 결국에는 적을 휩쓸고 맙니다. 직접 전투에 대비해 4개의 각기 다른 포가 설치되어 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. Building and storing a seemingly-endless force of bot fighters, the Blade Lotus continues to produce ships during battle, ultimately overwhelming its foes. Four different turret weapons can be employed to take a direct hand in battle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用Novus Prime的概念繪畫裝飾你的牆壁。Blade Lotus能在戰爭中不斷製造太空船，建立及儲存無窮無進的機械戰鬥機團隊，最終壓倒敵人。可安裝四款不同的迴轉砲塔武器，直接在戰爭中大派用場。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用Novus Prime的概念繪畫裝飾你的牆壁。Blade Lotus能在戰爭中不斷製造太空船，建立及儲存無窮無進的機械戰鬥機團隊，最終壓倒敵人。可安裝四款不同的迴轉砲塔武器，直接在戰爭中大派用場。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. Building and storing a seemingly-endless force of bot fighters, the Blade Lotus continues to produce ships during battle, ultimately overwhelming its foes. Four different turret weapons can be employed to take a direct hand in battle. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>