<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Aunt Mildred.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tante Mildred.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tante Mildred.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Zia Mildred.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tía Mildred.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Legend has it that this monster would devour pink elephants by drinking too much seawater and then hallucinating to the point of loosing control. In the mayhem that would ensue, it would fall about uncontrollably, always, by pure chance, falling mouth first on the pink elephants. It’s downfall came from the fact that it suffered from acute vertigo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La légende raconte que ce monstre dévore les éléphants roses lorsqu'il boit trop d'eau de mer. Il est ensuite victime d'hallucinations jusqu'à en perdre tout contrôle. Dans le désordre qui s'ensuit, il tombe de manière incontrôlable et toujours, par pur hasard, la bouche la première sur les éléphants roses. Sa chute est causée par son vertige aigu. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Legende nach fraß dieses Monster rosafarbene Elefanten, indem es zu viel Meerwasser trank und dann durch Halluzinationen völlig die Kontrolle verlor. Im anschließenden Chaos fiel es dann immer wieder unwillkürlich hin, mit dem Maul voran, genau auf die rosafarbenen Elefanten. Sein Ende fand es aufgrund seiner extremen Höhenangst. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Secondo la leggenda, questo mostro divora elefanti rosa bevendo troppa acqua salata e in seguito ha allucinazioni tali da perdere il controllo. Nella follia che ne segue, si dice che si metta a ridere a crepapelle, provocando le crepe sempre sulla pelle degli elefanti rosa. Pare che il suo impero sia caduto perché soffriva di vertigini. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Según la leyenda, este monstruo devoraba elefantes rosas porque al beber demasiada agua marina, después alucinaba hasta el punto de perder el control. En el caos que se sucedía, siempre caía de boca, por pura casualidad, encima de los elefantes rosas. La causa de su declive fue que sufría de vértigo agudo. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>