<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Junkmobile 2-piece Bundle (White)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le  Junkmobile ensemble 2 pièces (Blanc)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Junkmobile zweiteiliges Set (Weiß)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Junkmobile , set di due pezzi (Bianco)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Conjunto de 2 Piezas  Junkmobile (Blanco)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Junkmobile 2-piece Bundle (White) </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LMO - The Junkmobile Car (White)\n
	 
The Junk Guy has no shame when he pedals his way around Home. He takes pride knowing his eco-friendly Junkmobile burns calories, not fossil fuels.  Join the Junk Guy movement – go pedal power and save planet Home!  Toggle full-forward for maximum boost speed! \n

Active Item - The Junkmobile Sofa with Radio (White)\n

With this purchase, you’ll also receive a matching Junkmobile sofa! Modeled after the car version, it can be placed in any of your private spaces for all of your friends to enjoy (non-Locomotion). Sit on the hood, behind the wheel or just play the radio. \n

This bundle sale contains the following items:\n
 
- LMO - The Junkmobile Car (White) (The LMO car does not include a radio)\n
- Active Item  - The Junkmobile Sofa with Radio (White) (Not a Locomotion)\n

*LMO (Locomotion) is a portable item.
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">LMO – La voiture Junkmobile (Blanc)\n
    
Le Junk Guy n’a aucune honte quand il pédale dans son quartier, il est très fier de montrer que son Junkmobile est bon  pour l’environnement en brulant ses calories et n’utilisant aucun combustible fossile – Rejoignez le mouvement du  Junk Guy – vive l’énergie à pédale et sauvons la planète. Basculer plein avant pour une vitesse maximale de suralimentation! \n
 
(Elément Interactif) Le canapé  Junkmobile avec Radio (Blanc)\n
 
Avec cet achat, vous recevrez également un canapé assorti Junkmobile! A l’image de la version voiture, il peut être placé à l’endroit que vous souhaitez pour que tous vos amis puissent l’apprécier (non- Locomotion). Asseyez-vous sur le capot, devant le volant ou écoutez seulement la radio. \n
 
Cet ensemble contient les éléments suivants:\n

- LMO – La Voiture Junkmobile (Blanc) (la voiture n’inclut pas la radio)\n  
- Elément Interactif - Le Canapé Junkmobile avec radio (Blanc) (non Locomotion)\n

*LMO (Locomotion) est un élément transportable.
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LMO - Der Junkmobile Wagen (Weiß)\n
    
Der Junk Guy schämt sich nicht, durch das Haus zu fahren, und er ist stolz darauf, dass sein umweltfreundiger Wagen nur Kalorien verbrennt und keine fossilen Brennstoffe.  Schließe dich der Junk Guy bewegung  – verbrauche Pedalen-Kraft und rette den Planeten. Fahren Sie ganz nach vorn für maximalen Schub Geschwindigkeit! \n

(Aktiver Artikel) Das Junkmobile Sofa mit Radio (Weiß)\n

Bei diesem Kaufpreis, Sie werden auch ein passendes Junkmobile Sofa erhalten! Nach der Wagen-Version modelliert, es kann für die Vergnügung ihrer Freunde in jedem privaten Raum gestellt werden (keine-Locomotion). Sitze auf der Motorhaube, hinter dem Lenkrad oder ganz einfach Radio hören. \n

Dieses Bündel enthält folgende Artikel:\n

- LMO - Der Junkmobile Wagen (Weiß) (der Wagen enthält kein Radio)\n
- Activer Artikel  - Das weiche Junkmobile Sofa mit Radio (Weiß) (keine Locomotion)\n

*LMO (Locomotion) ist ein tragbarer Artikel.
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">LMO - L'auto Junkmobile (Bianco)\n
    
Il Junk Guy non si vergogna quando pedala dentro Casa, è fiero del fatto che la sua Junkmobile ecologica bruci calorie e non comustibili fossili.  Unisciti all'iniziativa del Junk Guy – usa il potere dei pedali e salva il pianeta Casa. Alterna pieno in avanti per la velocità massima di spinta! \n

(Articolo attivo) Il Sofà Junkmobile dotato di Radio (Bianco)\n

Con questo acquisto, riceverai un sofà Junkmobile correlato! Modellato come la versione della macchina, può essere collocato in qualsiasi punto dei luoghi casalinghi per il divertimento dei tuoi amici (non-Locomotion). Siediti sulla capote, dietro al volante oppure ascolta semplicemente la radio. \n

Questo insieme include i seguenti articoli:\n

- LMO – la macchina Junkmobile (Bianco) (la macchina non include la radio)\n
- Articolo Attivo  - Il Sofà Junkmobile morbido con la Radio (Bianco) (non un Locomotion)\n

*LMO (Locomotion) è un oggetto portatile.
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LMO - El coche Junkmobile (Blanco)\n
    
El  Junk Guy no siente vergüenza cuando pedalea alrededor de su casa, el se enorgullece sabiendo que su  Junkmobile  ecológico quema calorías, no combustibles fósiles.  Únete al movimiento  Junk Guy  – muévete con el poder del pedaleo y salva nuestro planeta Hogar. Cambia completamente hacia adelante para la velocidad de carga máxima! \n
 
(Artículo Interactivo) El Sofá  Junkmobile con Radio (Blanco)\n

Con esta compra, tu también recibirás el correspondiente sofá Junkmobile. Inspirado en el modelo del coche, puede ser colocado en cualquiera de tus espacios privados para disfrute de todos tus amigos (no conducible). Siéntate en el capó, detrás del volante o simplemente escucha la radio. \n

Este paquete a la venta contiene los siguientes elementos:\n

- LMO - El coche Junkmobile (Blanco) (el coche no incluye radio)\n
- Artículo Interactivo  - El Sofá  Junkmobile con Radio (Blanco) (no conducible)\n

*LMO (Conducible) es un artículo portátil.
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LMO - The Junkmobile Car (White)\n
	 
The Junk Guy has no shame when he pedals his way around Home. He takes pride knowing his eco-friendly Junkmobile burns calories, not fossil fuels.  Join the Junk Guy movement – go pedal power and save planet Home! Toggle full-forward for maximum boost speed! \n

Active Item - The Junkmobile Sofa with Radio (White)\n

With this purchase, you’ll also receive a matching Junkmobile sofa! Modeled after the car version, it can be placed in any of your private spaces for all of your friends to enjoy (non-Locomotion). Sit on the hood, behind the wheel or just play the radio. \n

This bundle sale contains the following items:\n
 
- LMO - The Junkmobile Car (White) (The LMO car does not include a radio)\n
- Active Item  - The Junkmobile Sofa with Radio (White) (Not a Locomotion)\n

*LMO (Locomotion) is a portable item.
[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>