<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Wakamatsu and Senryo Ikebana 2-piece Set</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de 2 pièces d'Ikebana de Wakamatsu et de Senryo</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">2-teiliges Set von Wakamatsu- und Senryo-Ikebana</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set 2 ikebana con wakamatsu e senryo</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos artículos ikebana de wakamatsu y senryo</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">若松と仙蓼（せんりょう）の生け花２点セット</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">Wakamatsu and Senryo Ikebana 2-piece Set</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Wakamatsu and Senryo Ikebana 2-piece Set</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">Wakamatsu and Senryo Ikebana 2-piece Set</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">Wakamatsu and Senryo Ikebana 2-piece Set</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Wakamatsu and Senryo Ikebana 2-piece Set</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 2-piece set that includes wakamatsu and senryo arranged in bamboo and ceramic vases.\nThis set includes the following items for private lounge customization:\n\n- Wakamatsu and Senryo Arranged in Bamboo (Ornaments)\n- Wakamatsu and Senryo Arranged in Ceramic (Ornaments)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category in "Private Lounge Customization".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 2 pièces incluant des wakamatsu et senryo arrangés dans des vases en bambou et en céramique.\nCe set inclut les objets suivants, pour personnaliser votre espace personnel :\n\n- Wakamatsu et Senryo arrangés dans un bambou (Décoration)\n- Wakamatsu et Senryo arrangés dans une céramique (Décoration)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective dans "Personnalisation de l'espace privé".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 2-teiliges Set, das Wakamatsu- und Senryo-Blumenarrangements in einer Bambusvase und einer Keramikvase enthält.\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände zur Bearbeitung des persönlichen Raumes.\n\n- Bambusvase mit Wakamatsu- und Senryo-Blumenarrangement (Verzierungen)\n- Keramikvase mit Wakamatsu- und Senryo-Blumenarrangement (Verzierungen)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie in "Bearbeitung des persönlichen Raumes" hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set composto da 2 elementi comprendente delle piante di wakamatsu e senryo disposte in un vaso di bambù e in un vaso di ceramica.\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti per la personalizzazione della stanza privata.\n\n- Vaso di bambù con composizione di wakamatsu e senryo (Decorazioni)\n- Vaso di ceramica con composizione di wakamatsu e senryo (Decorazioni)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettiva categoria in "Personalizzazione stanza privata".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos artículos que incluye arreglos de wakamatsu y senryo en jarrones de bambú y cerámica.\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos para la personalizar la sala.\n\n- Arreglo de wakamatsu y senryo en recipiente de bambú (Adornos)\n- Arreglo de wakamatsu y senryo en recipiente de cerámica (Adornos)\n\n* Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría en "Personalización de la sala privada".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">若松と仙蓼（せんりょう）の、竹の器に生けたものと陶器に生けたものの２点セット。\n
本セットには、プライベートラウンジのカスタマイズ用の下記アイテムが含まれています。\n
\n
・竹の器に生けた若松と仙蓼（せんりょう）/装飾品\n
・陶器に生けた若松と仙蓼（せんりょう）/装飾品\n
\n
※購入すると、「プライベートラウンジのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">A 2-piece set that includes wakamatsu and senryo arranged in bamboo and ceramic vases.\nThis set includes the following items for private lounge customization:\n\n- Wakamatsu and Senryo Arranged in Bamboo (Ornaments)\n- Wakamatsu and Senryo Arranged in Ceramic (Ornaments)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category in "Private Lounge Customization".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 2-piece set that includes wakamatsu and senryo arranged in bamboo and ceramic vases.\nThis set includes the following items for private lounge customization:\n\n- Wakamatsu and Senryo Arranged in Bamboo (Ornaments)\n- Wakamatsu and Senryo Arranged in Ceramic (Ornaments)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category in "Private Lounge Customization".[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
