<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">DC Universe™ Online Mask: Inspired by SCARECROW</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Masque DC Universe™ Online : inspiré par SCARECROW</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">DC Universe™ Online: Maske (nach Vorbild von SCARECROW)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maschera DC Universe™ Online: ispirata a SCARECROW</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Máscara de DC Universe™ Online: inspirada en SCARECROW</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">DC Universe™ Online Mask: Inspired by SCARECROW</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Step into the DC Universe™ and create your own super hero or archvillain, harness unique superpowers and join thousands of other players online. Battle alongside legendary characters in the iconic settings of METROPOLIS, GOTHAM CITY and beyond in compelling storylines as you fight to save – or rule – the universe.  

DC Universe™ Online – The Next Legend Is You!™ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plongez dans DC Universe™ et créez votre propre super-héros ou super-vilain doté de super-pouvoirs uniques. Rejoignez des milliers d'autres joueurs en ligne. Vous pourrez combattre aux côtés de personnages légendaires dans des lieux aussi mythiques que METROPOLIS, GOTHAM CITY et bien d'autres. Découvrez des scénarios captivants et battez-vous pour sauver l'univers... ou l'asservir.

DC Universe™ Online – La nouvelle légende, c'est VOUS !™[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Betritt das DC Universe™ und erschaffe deinen eigenen Superhelden oder Erzfeind, nutze einzigartige Superkräfte und werde Teil einer Online-Community mit Tausenden von Spielern. Kämpfe Seite an Seite mit legendären Charakteren u. a. an den berühmten Schauplätzen METROPOLIS und GOTHAM CITY. In dieser fesselnden Story musst du das Universum retten oder beherrschen.

DC Universe™ Online – Die nächste Legende bist DU!™[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Entra in DC Universe™ e crea il tuo supereroe o il tuo supercriminale, sfoggia superpoteri unici e unisciti a migliaia di altri giocatori online. Lotta in storie avvincenti al fianco di personaggi leggendari in ambienti mitici come METROPOLIS e GOTHAM CITY, mentre combatti per salvare, o dominare, l'universo.  

DC Universe™ Online – La Prossima Leggenda sei Tu!™ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Entra en el DC Universe™ y crea tu propio superhéroe o archivillano, haz uso de superpoderes únicos y únete a cientos de jugadores online. Lucha en las filas de los legendarios personajes en los icónicos escenarios de METROPOLIS y GOTHAM CITY, entre otros, disfrutando de un argumento trepidante mientras peleas por salvar -o dominar- el universo.

DC Universe™ Online: ¡La próxima leyenda eres TÚ!™[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Step into the DC Universe™ and create your own super hero or archvillain, harness unique superpowers and join thousands of other players online. Battle alongside legendary characters in the iconic settings of METROPOLIS, GOTHAM CITY and beyond in compelling storylines as you fight to save – or rule – the universe.  

DC Universe™ Online – The Next Legend Is You!™ [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>