<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Find out more about LYNX Attract</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En savoir plus sur AXE Anarchy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weitere Informationen über "AXE Anarchy"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maggiori info su AXE Anarchy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Descubre más cosas sobre AXE Anarchy</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Find out more about LYNX Attract [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En savoir plus sur AXE Anarchy [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weitere Informationen über "AXE Anarchy" [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maggiori info su AXE Anarchy [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Descubre más cosas sobre AXE Anarchy [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">InfoText</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LYNX ATTRACT
\n\n
KNOW WHAT ‘FOUGERE’ SMELLS LIKE? NO? WE’RE NOT SURPRISED – THE ONLY PEOPLE AT LYNX WHO DO ARE THE BIGGEST BRAINS IN OUR NEW FRAGRANCE DEPARTMENT. AND THEY ASSURE US IT’S JUST ABOUT AS UNIQUELY STYLISH AS FRAGRANCES GET.
\n\n
FUSING FRUITY FRESHNESS WITH LYNX’S ESSENTIAL WOODY SENSUALITY, ATTRACT TAKES US INTO SOME VERY EXCITING NEW PLACES. AND IT’S SURE TO DO THE SAME FOR YOU.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">AXE ANARCHY
\n\n
CONNAISSEZ-VOUS L'ODEUR DE LA FOUGÈRE ? NON ? CELA NE NOUS SURPREND PAS. LES SEULES PERSONNES CHEZ AXE QUI LA CONNAISSENT SONT LES MEILLEURS ÉLÉMENTS DE NOTRE NOUVEAU DÉPARTEMENT PARFUM. ET ILS NOUS ASSURENT QUE C'EST LE TOP EN MATIÈRE DE SENTEURS À LA MODE.
\n\n
ASSOCIANT UNE FRAÎCHEUR FRUITÉE À LA SENSUALITÉ BOISÉE DE AXE, ANARCHY NOUS EMPORTE DANS DE NOUVEAUX ENDROITS HALLUCINANTS. ET IL EN SERA FORCÉMENT DE MÊME POUR VOUS.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"AXE ANARCHY"
\n\n
WEISST DU, WIE "FOUGÈRE" RIECHT? NEIN? DAS ÜBERRASCHT UNS NICHT. AUCH BEI "AXE" WISSEN DAS NUR DIE HELLSTEN KÖPFE UNSERER DÜFTE-ABTEILUNG, UND SIE VERSICHERN UNS: ES IST SO EINZIGARTIG STILVOLL, WIE EIN DUFT NUR SEIN KANN.
\n\n
"ANARCHY" VERBINDET FRUCHTIGE FRISCHE MIT DER TYPISCHEN, HOLZIGEN SINNLICHKEIT VON "AXE" UND ERÖFFNET UNS DAMIT AUFREGENDE NEUE WEGE. UND FÜR DICH WIRD ES DAS GLEICHE TUN.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">AXE ANARCHY
\n\n
HAI MAI SENTITO PARLARE DELLA FRAGRANZA "FOUGERE"? NO? LA COSA NON CI SORPRENDE. LE UNICHE PERSONE CHE DA AXE LA CONOSCONO, SONO LE GRANDI MENTI CHE LAVORANO NEL NOSTRO REPARTO PROFUMI, E CHE CI ASSICURANO CHE ABBIA LO STILE INCONFONDIBILE DELLE MIGLIORI FRAGRANZE.
\n\n
FONDENDO LA FRESCHEZZA DELLA FRUTTA ALLA SENSUALITÀ LEGNOSA ESSENZIALE DI AXE, LA LINEA ANARCHY CI FA SCOPRIRE NUOVI LUOGHI ELETTRIZZANTI. E SICURAMENTE AVRÀ LO STESSO EFFETTO SU DI TE.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">AXE ANARCHY
\n\n
¿SABES A QUÉ HUELE EL «FOUGÈRE»? ¿NO? NO ES EXTRAÑO: LAS ÚNICAS PERSONAS DE AXE QUE LO SABEN SON LOS MEJORES CEREBROS DE NUESTRO NUEVO DEPARTAMENTO DE FRAGANCIAS. Y NOS ASEGURAN QUE TIENE EL ESTILO ÚNICO DE LAS MEJORES FRAGANCIAS.
\n\n
CON UNA FUSIÓN DE FRESCURA FRUTAL Y DE LA SENSUALIDAD AMADERADA DE AXE, ANARCHY NOS TRASLADA A LUGARES NUEVOS Y EXCITANTES. Y SEGURO QUE HARÁ LO MISMO CONTIGO.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Quit_Legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CIRCLE] Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CIRCLE] Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CIRCLE] Beenden</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CIRCLE] Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CIRCLE] Salir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>