<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Azure Retro Flyers Value Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack Économique Retro Flyers Azurs</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Azurblaue Retroflieger Vorteilspaket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Retro Flyers azzurro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de Valor Voladores Retro Azul Celeste</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アジュール・レトロフライヤー・バリューパック</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Azure Retro Flyers Value Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Azure Retro Flyers Value Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Get three Retro Flyers for the price of two with the Azure Retro Flyers Value Pack! Includes the Azure Mysterious UFO, Azure Daredevil Biplane, and Azure Supersonic Jetpack. Access your Retro Flyers for a major speed boost when moving at full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Obtenez trois Retro Flyers pour le prix de deux avec le Pack Économique Retro Flyers Azur ! Inclut l'OVNI Mystérieux Azur, le Biplan Casse-cou Azur et le Jetpack Supersonique Azur. Accédez à vos Retro Flyers pour obtenir un boost de vitesse majeur quand vous vous déplacez à la vitesse maximale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hole dir drei Retroflieger zum Preis von zwei mit dem azurblauen Retroflieger Vorteilspaket! Enthält das azurblaue mysteriöse UFO, den azurblauen Daredevil-Doppeldecker und den azurblauen Überschall-Jetpack. Verwende deine Retroflieger für einen beachtlichen Geschwindigkeitsschub bei voller Geschwindigkeit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ottieni tre Retro Flyers al prezzo di due con il Pacchetto Retro Flyers azzurro! Questo pacchetto comprende Retro Flyers UFO misterioso azzurro, Biplano incursore azzurro e Jetpack supersonico azzurro. Utilizza i Retro Flyers per aumentare di molto la tua velocità quando corri al massimo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Obtén tres Voladores Retro por el precio de dos con el Paquete de Valor Voladores Retro Azul Celeste! Incluye los Voladores Retro OVNI Misterioso Azul Celeste, Biplano Temerario Azul Celeste y Jetpack Supersónico Azul Celeste. Accede tus Voladores Retro para incrementar tu velocidad cuando vayas a máxima velocidad. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アジュール・レトロフライヤー・バリューパック2個分の値段でレトロフライヤー3個をゲットしよう！アジュール・ミステリアスＵＦＯ、アジュール・デアデビル・バイプレーン、アジュールスーパーソニック・ジェットパックが含まれます。フルスピードでの走行時に、超スピードを出すためにレトロフライヤーにアクセスしよう。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Get three Retro Flyers for the price of two with the Azure Retro Flyers Value Pack! Includes the Azure Mysterious UFO, Azure Daredevil Biplane, and Azure Supersonic Jetpack. Access your Retro Flyers for a major speed boost when moving at full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Get three Retro Flyers for the price of two with the Azure Retro Flyers Value Pack! Includes the Azure Mysterious UFO, Azure Daredevil Biplane, and Azure Supersonic Jetpack. Access your Retro Flyers for a major speed boost when moving at full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>