<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object" default_language="en-GB">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fragment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fragmento</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Frammento</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">破片</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fragment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fragment</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fragment description. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Descripción del fragmento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Descrizione frammento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">破片の説明 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Description du fragment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fragment-Beschreibung. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kFinished</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have collected all of the available fragments today!  More will be available to collect tomorrow.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Ya has recogido todos los fragmentos disponibles hoy! Podrás recoger más mañana.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai raccolto tutti i frammenti disponibili per oggi! Domani ce ne saranno altri da collezionare.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">今日ある破片をすべて集めました！　明日からもっと集められるよ！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tu as trouvé tous les fragments disponibles aujourd'hui ! D'autres t'attendront demain.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast alle heute zur Verfügung stehenden Fragmente eingesammelt! Morgen kannst du weitersammeln.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kSuccess</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Congratulations you have found a new fragment! You can view it in your book.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Enhorabuena! Has encontrado un fragmento nuevo. Puedes verlo en el libro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Congratulazioni, hai trovato un nuovo frammento! Puoi vederlo nel tuo libro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">新しい破片を見つけたね、おめでとう！　この破片は、ノートで確認できるよ。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Félicitations, tu as trouvé un nouveau fragment ! Tu peux le voir dans ton livre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Herzlichen Glückwunsch, du hast ein neues Fragment gefunden! Du kannst es in deinem Übungsbuch ansehen.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kFailure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bad luck, no fragment this time. Try again later.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mala suerte. Esta vez no hay fragmentos. Inténtalo de nuevo más tarde.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Che sfortuna, niente frammenti stavolta. Riprova più tardi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">残念！　今回は、破片がありませんでした。後でまた試してみて！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pas de chance, aucun fragment cette fois-ci. Reviens plus tard.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schade, diesmal gab es kein Fragment. Versuche es später noch einmal.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kClose</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Close</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] Cerrar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE] Schließen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Fermer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE] Chiudi</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kFinishedChapter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have collected all of the available fragments for this chapter now!  More will be available when you unlock the next chapter.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Ya has recogido todos los fragmentos disponibles para este capítulo! Al desbloquear el siguiente capítulo habrá más disponibles.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast alle für dieses Kapitel zur Verfügung stehenden Fragmente eingesammelt! Wenn du das nächste Kapitel freischaltest, werden mehr verfügbar sein.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tu as trouvé tous les fragments disponibles pour ce chapitre ! D'autres t'attendront lorsque tu auras débloqué le chapitre suivant.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai raccolto tutti i frammenti disponibili per questo capitolo al momento! Ce ne saranno altri disponibili quando sbloccherai il capitolo successivo.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
