<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">About Survival Bomber</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">A propos de Bomber Survie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über Überlebens-Bomber</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Informazioni su Survival Bomber</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acerca de Bomber Supervivencia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">サバイバルボンバー説明</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">About Survival Bomber</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">What is Survival Bomber?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Qu'est-ce que Bomber Survie ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Was ist Überlebens-Bomber?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cos'è Survival Bomber?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Qué es Bomber Supervivencia?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">サバイバルボンバーとは</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">What is Survival Bomber?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Starting Out</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Démarrer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Einführung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Iniziare</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Inicio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゲームの始め方</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Starting Out</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Objective</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Objectif</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ziel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Obiettivo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Objetivo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゲームの目的</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Objective</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rules (1)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Règles (1)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Regeln (1)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Regole (1)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Reglas (1)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ルール(１)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rules (1)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rules (2)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Règles (2)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Regeln (2)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Regole (2)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Reglas (2)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ルール(２)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rules (2)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ranking</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Classement</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rangliste</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Graduatoria</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Clasificación</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">段位認定</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ranking</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Score and Level</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Score et niveau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Punktzahl und Level</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Punteggio e livello</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Puntuación y nivel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スコアとレベル</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Score and Level</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tips</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Astuces</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tipps</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Consigli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Consejos</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゲームのヒント</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Tips</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">About Survival Bomber (1/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">A propos de Bomber Survie (1/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über Überlebens-Bomber (1/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Informazioni su Survival Bomber (1/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acerca de Bomber Supervivencia (1/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">サバイバルボンバー説明(1/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">About Survival Bomber (1/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">About Survival Bomber (2/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">A propos de Bomber Survie (2/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über Überlebens-Bomber (2/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Informazioni su Survival Bomber (2/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acerca de Bomber Supervivencia (2/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">サバイバルボンバー説明(2/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">About Survival Bomber (2/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">About Survival Bomber (3/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">A propos de Bomber Survie (3/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über Überlebens-Bomber (3/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Informazioni su Survival Bomber (3/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acerca de Bomber Supervivencia (3/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">サバイバルボンバー説明(3/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">About Survival Bomber (3/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">About Survival Bomber (4/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">A propos de Bomber Survie (4/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über Überlebens-Bomber (4/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Informazioni su Survival Bomber (4/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acerca de Bomber Supervivencia (4/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">サバイバルボンバー説明(4/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">About Survival Bomber (4/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">About Survival Bomber (5/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">A propos de Bomber Survie (5/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über Überlebens-Bomber (5/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Informazioni su Survival Bomber (5/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acerca de Bomber Supervivencia (5/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">サバイバルボンバー説明(5/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">About Survival Bomber (5/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">About Survival Bomber (6/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">A propos de Bomber Survie (6/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über Überlebens-Bomber (6/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Informazioni su Survival Bomber (6/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acerca de Bomber Supervivencia (6/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">サバイバルボンバー説明(6/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">About Survival Bomber (6/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">About Survival Bomber (7/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">A propos de Bomber Survie (7/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über Überlebens-Bomber (7/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Informazioni su Survival Bomber (7/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acerca de Bomber Supervivencia (7/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">サバイバルボンバー説明(7/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">About Survival Bomber (7/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">About Survival Bomber (8/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">A propos de Bomber Survie (8/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über Überlebens-Bomber (8/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Informazioni su Survival Bomber (8/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acerca de Bomber Supervivencia (8/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">サバイバルボンバー説明(8/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">About Survival Bomber (8/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Survival Bomber requires memory, decisions, teamwork, and a little luck!\nSee how long you can survive and aim to become a Bomber Master!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Dans Bomber Survie, tu dois faire travailler ta mémoire, faire des choix, travailler en équipe et avoir de la chance !\nSurvis le plus longtemps possible afin de devenir un maître Bomber !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Für Überlebens-Bomber sind Erinnerungsvermögen, Entscheidungen, Teamwork und etwas Glück nötig!\nFinde heraus, wie lange du überleben kannst und versuche, ein Bomber-Meister zu werden!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per giocare a Survival Bomber servono memoria, capacità decisionale, lavoro di squadra e un po' di fortuna!\nSopravvivi il più a lungo possibile per diventare un Bomber Master!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bomber Supervivencia requiere memoria, decisiones, trabajo en equipo y, ¡algo de suerte!\nIntenta convertirte en un Maestro Bomber. ¡A ver cuánto puedes sobrevivir!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「サバイバルボンバー」は記憶力と判断力、団結力さらに運も求められるゲームです。\nあなたのサバイバル能力を発揮し、「ボンバー名人」を目指しましょう！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Survival Bomber requires memory, decisions, teamwork, and a little luck!\nSee how long you can survive and aim to become a Bomber Master!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Talk to any of the 4 Bombermen floating around this floor. The rules are the same for each, so select whichever stage you like.\n\nEach stage can be played by up to 8 players at once. You can join games already in progress.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Adresse-toi à l'un des 4 Bombermans qui se trouvent sur ce plateau. Les règles sont les mêmes, alors choisis n'importe quel niveau.\n\nChaque niveau peut être joué avec jusqu'à 8 joueurs simultanément. Tu peux rejoindre les parties en cours.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sprich mit irgendeinem der 4 Bombermans, die auf dieser Etage herumschweben. Jede Stufe hat dieselben Regeln, also suche dir irgendeine aus.\n\nJede Stufe kann von bis zu 8 Spielern gleichzeitig gespielt werden. Du kannst Spielen beitreten, die bereits angefangen haben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Parla con uno qualunque dei 4 Bomberman che fluttuano su questo piano. Le regole sono sempre le stesse, quindi scegli quello che ti piace di più.\n\nPossono partecipare fino a 8 giocatori insieme per ogni livello. Puoi unirti a partite già in corso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Habla con cualquiera de los 4 Bombermans de esta planta. Las reglas son siempre las mismas, así que selecciona el escenario que quieras.\n\nEn cada escenario pueden jugar hasta 8 jugadores a la vez. Puedes unirte a partidas en curso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このフロアの外周に浮かぶ、４体のボンバーマンの誰かに話しかけてください。どのボンバーマンでもルールは同じですので、好きなステージを選びましょう。\n\n１つのステージで１～８人のプレイヤーが同時にプレイできます。ゲームの途中から参加することもできます。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Talk to any of the 4 Bombermen floating around this floor. The rules are the same for each, so select whichever stage you like.\n\nEach stage can be played by up to 8 players at once. You can join games already in progress.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Collect the keys within the time limit without getting hit by a bomb blast.\nCollect all 3 keys to advance to the next level. Each key is worth points that will be added to your score.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Récupère les clés dans le temps imparti sans être touché par une explosion.\nRécupère 3 clés pour accéder au niveau suivant. Chaque clé vaut des points qui seront ajoutés à ton score.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sammle die Schlüssel innerhalb des Zeitlimits, ohne von einer Bombenexplosion getroffen zu werden.\nSammle alle 3 Schlüssel, um zum nächsten Level zu gelangen. Für jeden Schlüssel erhältst du Punkte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Raccogli le chiavi entro il tempo limite senza essere colpito da un'esplosione. \nRaccogli 3 chiavi per proseguire al livello successivo. Ogni chiave vale punti che saranno aggiunti al tuo punteggio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Recoge las llaves dentro del tiempo establecido sin que te alcance la explosión de ninguna bomba.\nRecoge las 3 llaves para pasar al siguiente nivel. Cada llave vale varios puntos, que se sumarán a tu puntuación.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">時間内に「カギ」を集め、爆風が当たらない場所に移動するゲームです。\nステージに配置された３つのカギを集めれば、次のレベルに進むことが出来ます。集めたカギに応じてスコアが加算されます。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Collect the keys within the time limit without getting hit by a bomb blast.\nCollect all 3 keys to advance to the next level. Each key is worth points that will be added to your score.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Keys and bombs are placed around the stage. You can start moving after the start signal is given.\n\nThe fuse on the top shows how long until the bomb goes off and the Bomberman Icons on the lower-left show how many tries you have left.\n\nKeys are shown separately to each player. If another player gets a key, it will not disappear from your stage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les clés et les bombes sont disposées sur le niveau. Tu peux te déplacer après le signal de départ.\n\nLa mèche indique dans combien de temps la bombe va exploser et les icônes Bomberman en bas à gauche représentent le nombre d'essais restants.\n\nLes clés s'affichent séparément pour chaque joueur. Si un autre joueur obtient une clé, elle ne disparaîtra pas de ton niveau.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Auf der Stufe sind Schlüssel und Bomben verteilt. Du kannst dich bewegen, sobald das Startsignal gegeben wurde.\n\nDie Zündschnur oben zeigt an, wie viel Zeit bleibt, bis die Bombe explodiert. Die Bomberman-Symbole unten links zeigen an, wie viele Versuche dir noch bleiben.\n\nSchlüssel werden für jeden Spieler separat angezeigt. Wenn ein anderer Spieler einen Schlüssel einsammelt, verschwindet dieser nicht aus deiner Stufe.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le chiavi e le bombe sono sparse per il livello. Puoi iniziare a muoverti dopo il segnale di partenza.\n\nLa miccia in alto segnala quanto tempo manca all'esplosione e le Icone Bomberman in basso a sinistra indicano quanti tentativi hai a disposizione.\n\nLe chiavi sono mostrate separatamente per ogni giocatore. Se un altro giocatore prende una chiave, non sparirà dal tuo livello.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">En el escenario hay llaves y bombas. Cuando se dé la señal de inicio, podrás empezar a moverte.\n\nLa mecha de la parte superior indica cuándo explotará la bomba y los iconos de Bomberman en la parte inferior izquierda, cuántos intentos te quedan.\n\nCada jugador ve sus propias llaves. Si otro jugador consigue una llave, no desaparecerá de tu escenario.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">最初にカギと爆弾がステージに設置されます。スタートの合図で動けるようになります。\n\n画面上の導火線は「爆弾が爆発するまでの時間」を、左下のボンバーマンアイコンは「チャレンジ回数」を示します。\n\nカギはゲームに参加しているプレイヤーそれぞれに見えており、他の人がカギを獲得しても自分のカギは無くなりません。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Keys and bombs are placed around the stage. You can start moving after the start signal is given.\n\nThe fuse on the top shows how long until the bomb goes off and the Bomberman Icons on the lower-left show how many tries you have left.\n\nKeys are shown separately to each player. If another player gets a key, it will not disappear from your stage.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bombs explode 3 seconds after the fuse runs out. Their blast is 5 spaces wide and if you get hit by one, you'll lose 1 try.\n\nCollect all 3 keys to advance to the next level. If there is a key that none of the participating players have gotten, all players will lose 1 try and go back a level.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les bombes explosent 3 secondes après la combustion de la mèche. La déflagration touche 5 cases et si tu es touché, tu perds 1 essai.\n\nRécupère 3 clés pour accéder au niveau suivant. Si aucun des joueurs n'a obtenu une clé, ils perdent tous 1 essai et reculent d'un niveau.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bomben explodieren 3 Sekunden nach Abbrennen der Zündschnur. Die Explosion umfasst 5 Felder und wenn du von ihr getroffen wirst, verlierst du 1 Versuch.\n\nSammle alle 3 Schlüssel, um zum nächsten Level zu gelangen. Wurde ein Schlüssel von keinem der Teilnehmer eingesammelt, verlieren alle Spieler 1 Versuch und gehen ein Level zurück.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le bombe esplodono 3 secondi dopo la fine della miccia. L'esplosione è grande 5 spazi e, se vieni colpito, perdi 1 tentativo.\n\nRaccogli tutte e 3 le chiavi per proseguire al livello successivo. Se c'è una chiave che nessuno dei giocatori ha raccolto, tutti perderanno 1 tentativo e torneranno indietro di un livello.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las bombas explotan 3 segundos después de acabarse la mecha. Su explosión se extiende 5 casillas. Si te alcanza una, perderás 1 intento.\n\nRecoge las 3 llaves para pasar al siguiente nivel. Si hay una llave que ningún jugador ha conseguido, perderéis todos 1 intento y retrocederéis 1 nivel.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">画面上の導火線が無くなると、３秒後に爆弾が一斉に爆発します。爆風は５マス先まで届き、当たるとチャレンジ回数が１回分減ってしまいます。\n\nカギが３つ揃っていれば次のレベルへ進めます。参加者の誰も取っていないカギがある場合は、全員のチャレンジ回数が１減って、少し前のレベルに戻されてしまいます。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Bombs explode 3 seconds after the fuse runs out. Their blast is 5 spaces wide and if you get hit by one, you'll lose 1 try.\n\nCollect all 3 keys to advance to the next level. If there is a key that none of the participating players have gotten, all players will lose 1 try and go back a level.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Once you run out of tries, it's game over.\nThe players are ranked according to their score and receive rewards.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si tu n'as plus d'essais, la partie est terminée.\nLe classement des joueurs dépend du score et ils obtiennent des récompenses.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sobald du keine Versuche mehr hast, ist das Spiel vorbei.\nDie Ränge der Spieler werden anhand ihrer Punktzahlen ermittelt und die Spieler erhalten Belohnungen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una volta esauriti i tentativi, il gioco è finito.\nI giocatori ricevono dei premi in funzione della classifica. Quest'ultima viene stilata in base al punteggio dei giocatori.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuando te quedes sin intentos, se acabó el juego.\nLos jugadores se clasifican según su puntuación y reciben premios.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">チャレンジ回数が０になるとゲームオーバーとなります。\n獲得スコアに応じて段位が発表され、リワードアイテムがもらえることもあります。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Once you run out of tries, it's game over.\nThe players are ranked according to their score and receive rewards.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The higher the level, the harder the game will get, but the points you receive will also increase. You'll receive 1 extra try at 10,000, 20,000, 40,000, 80,000 points...and so on.\n\nAt Level 30 the game goes into "Survival Time". Other players cannot join and it's super hard, but you can earn a lot of points!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plus le niveau est élevé et plus la partie sera difficile, mais les points obtenus seront plus importants. Tu obtiens un essai supplémentaire à 10 000, 20 000, 40 000, 80 000 points, etc.\n\nAu niveau 30, le jeu entre en mode Survie. Les autres joueurs ne peuvent rejoindre la partie. C'est très difficile mais tu gagnes un max de points !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Je höher der Level, desto schwieriger wird das Spiel, doch erhöht sich auch die Anzahl an Punkten. Du erhältst 1 Extraversuch bei 10.000, 20.000, 40.000, 80.000 Punkten und so weiter.\n\nBei Level 30 geht das Spiel in „Überlebenszeit“ über. Andere Spieler können nicht beitreten und es ist superschwer, doch kannst du eine Menge Punkte verdienen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Più alto il livello, più difficile diventa il gioco, ma si riceveranno anche più punti. Riceverai 1 tentativo extra a 10.000, 20.000, 40.000, 80.000 punti e così via.\n\nA livello 30 il gioco entra in modalità "Survival Time". Non si potrà unire nessun altro giocatore e le cose si faranno difficili, ma si possono ottenere molti punti in più!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuanto más alto sea el nivel, más difícil se pondrá el juego, pero también recibirás más puntos. Por ejemplo, recibirás 1 intento extra cuando alcances 10.000 puntos, 20.000, 40.000, 80.000, etc.\n\nEn el nivel 30, el juego pasa a "Modo Supervivencia". Ya no se pueden unir más jugadores y es muy difícil, ¡pero puedes ganar un montón de puntos!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">レベルが上がると、難易度も高くなりますが、獲得できるスコアも増えていきます。また、獲得したスコアが、10000点、20000点、40000点、80000点…を超えるとチャレンジ回数が１回増えます。\n\nさらに、レベル３０になると途中参加不能となる「サバイバルモード」になります。もちろんスコアも難易度も最高！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The higher the level, the harder the game will get, but the points you receive will also increase. You'll receive 1 extra try at 10,000, 20,000, 40,000, 80,000 points...and so on.\n\nAt Level 30 the game goes into "Survival Time". Other players cannot join and it's super hard, but you can earn a lot of points!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">*Once the first bombs fall into place, figure out the path to the keys. You'll also want to find a safe area for the end.\n\n*If you collect all 3 keys then get hit by a bomb blast, you'll lose 1 try but still clear the level. If you get hit before you collect the keys, you'll lose 2 tries, so be careful!\n\n*When playing with several players, you can have each player be in charge of getting the key nearest them. Spreading out is crucial to reaching the higher levels.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">*Lorsque les premières bombes sont lancées, fraie-toi un chemin jusqu'aux clés. Trouve un endroit sûr pour la fin.\n\n*Si tu es touché par une bombe après avoir récupéré les 3 clés, tu perds un essai mais termines le niveau. Si tu es touché avant d'avoir obtenu les clés, tu perds 2 essais, alors sois prudent !\n\n*Sur une partie à plusieurs joueurs, tu peux assigner à chacun de prendre la clé la plus proche. Le déploiement est essentiel pour accéder aux niveaux supérieurs.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">*Finde den Weg zu den Schlüsseln, sobald die ersten Bomben platziert sind. Du solltest dir auch einen sicheren Ort für den Schluss suchen.\n\n*Wenn du alle 3 Schlüssel gesammelt hast und dann von einer Bombenexplosion erwischt wirst, verlierst du 1 Versuch, schließt das Level jedoch ab. Wirst du erwischt, bevor du die Schlüssel gesammelt hast, verlierst du 2 Versuche, also sei vorsichtig!\n\n*Wenn du mit mehreren Spielern spielst, kann jeder von euch den Schlüssel einsammeln, der ihm am nächsten ist. Um die höheren Level zu erreichen, solltet ihr euch unbedingt aufteilen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">*Quando le prime bombe saranno in posizione, calcola il percorso verso le chiavi. Dovrai anche cercare una zona sicura per la fine.\n\n*Se raccogli tutte e 3 le chiavi e poi vieni colpito da un'esplosione, perderai 1 tentativo, ma potrai comunque terminare il livello. Se vieni colpito prima di aver raccolto le chiavi, perderai 2 tentativi, quindi fai attenzione!\n\n*Quando si gioca in tanti, si può assegnare ad ogni giocatore il compito di raccogliere la chiave a lui più vicina. Sparpagliarsi è fondamentale per raggiungere i livelli più alti.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">*Cuando aparezcan las primeras bombas, piensa cómo llegar a las llaves. También deberías encontrar una zona segura para el final.\n\n*Si recoges las 3 llaves y te alcanza la explosión de una bomba, perderás 1 intento pero superarás el nivel. Si te alcanza una explosión antes de recoger las llaves, perderás 2 intentos, ¡así que ten cuidado!\n\n*Cuando juegues con varios jugadores, puedes pedir a cada uno que consiga la llave que tenga más cerca. Es fundamental que os separéis para alcanzar los niveles superiores.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">・最初の爆弾が降ってくるときに、カギを取るコースを覚えることが重要です。最後に隠れる安全地帯も覚えておきましょう。\n\n・爆風に当たってもカギを３つ揃えればクリアになります(チャレンジ回数は１回減ります)。爆風に当たり、カギも揃っていない場合はチャレンジ回数が２回減ることになりますのでご注意ください。\n\n・多人数プレイでは、遠くのカギはその近くのプレイヤーに任せ、自分は近くのカギだけ取るなど、協力が可能です。なるべく同じ場所に集まらないのが高レベルに進むコツです。\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">*Once the first bombs fall into place, figure out the path to the keys. You'll also want to find a safe area for the end.\n\n*If you collect all 3 keys then get hit by a bomb blast, you'll lose 1 try but still clear the level. If you get hit before you collect the keys, you'll lose 2 tries, so be careful!\n\n*When playing with several players, you can have each player be in charge of getting the key nearest them. Spreading out is crucial to reaching the higher levels.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFT] [RIGHT] Switch page [CIRCLE] Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFT] [RIGHT] Tourner la page [CIRCLE] Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFT] [RIGHT] Seite wechseln [CIRCLE] Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFT] [RIGHT] Cambia pagina [CIRCLE] Abbandona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFT] [RIGHT] Cambiar de página [CIRCLE] Salir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[LEFT] [RIGHT]ページ切り替え [CIRCLE]終了</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[LEFT] [RIGHT] Switch page [CIRCLE] Quit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>