<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Neo, design Alban Gilles, Ligne Roset, 2003. Suitable for both contemporary and traditional interiors. Successful thanks to its simple and geometric design. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Neo, design Alban Gilles, Ligne Roset, 2003. Parfait pour les intérieurs modernes ou classiques. Très apprécié grâce à son design simple et géométrique. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Neo, Design von Alban Gilles, Ligne Roset, 2003. Für zeitgenössische wie traditionelle Einrichtungen gleichfalls geeignet. Überzeugt durch das schlichte und geometrische Design.\n\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Neo, design di Alban Gilles, Ligne Roset, 2003. Adatto a interni in stile sia moderno che classico. Deve il successo alla sua linea semplice e geometrica.\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Neo, diseño de Alban Gilles, Ligne Roset, 2003. Apto para interiores contemporáneos y tradicionales. Su éxito reside en la simplicidad de su diseño geométrico. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Neo：2003年のリーン・ロゼ製品。デザイン担当はアルバン・ジル。伝統的なインテリアにもモダンなインテリアにもマッチする。その秘密は、シンプルで左右対称のデザインにある。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Neo, Alban Gilles, Ligne Roset 디자인, 2003년. 현대적이고 전통적인\n인테리어 모두에 어울리는 디자인입니다. 간결하고 기하학적인 디자인을 통해 디자인의 혁신을\n이룩하였습니다.\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Neo, design Alban Gilles, Ligne Roset, 2003. Suitable for both contemporary\nand traditional interiors. Successful thanks to its simple and geometric\ndesign. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Neo：Alban Gilles 設計，Ligne Roset，2003 年。 完美融入現代\n與傳統風格室內裝潢， 新舊兼容的極簡與幾何\n設計。\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Neo：Alban Gilles 設計，Ligne Roset，2003 年。 完美融入現代\n與傳統風格室內裝潢， 新舊兼容的極簡與幾何\n設計。\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Neo, design Alban Gilles, Ligne Roset, 2003. Suitable for both contemporary\nand traditional interiors. Successful thanks to its simple and geometric\ndesign. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Neo Armchair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fauteuil Neo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sessel "Neo"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Poltrona Neo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sillón Neo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ネオ・アームチェア</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">네오 안락의자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Neo Armchair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Neo 扶手椅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Neo 扶手椅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Neo Armchair</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>