<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tuscan Villa Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Villa toscane clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Toskanische Villa: Clubhaus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sede del club Villa toscana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sede del club Villa toscana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Tuscan Villa Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">투스칸 빌라 클럽하우스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Tuscan Villa Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">托斯卡納別墅聯盟俱樂部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">托斯卡納別墅聯盟俱樂部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Tuscan Villa Clubhouse</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Enjoy a day in the countryside at your elaborate Tuscan Villa. This two-room lodging has a swanky living room connected to an outdoor porch and patio. To make things better, we’ve added an indoor swimming pool in the very next room. This is the perfect place to lay out and get to know your guests better. The Tuscan Villa space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Profitez d'une journée à la campagne à votre élaborée Villa toscane. Ce gîte de deux chambres a une salle de séjour chic connecté à un porche et terrasse extérieure. Pour rendre les choses meilleures, nous avons ajouté une piscine intérieure dans la pièce suivante. C'est l'endroit idéal pour exposer et faire connaissance avec vos invités de mieux. Le Villa toscane clubhouse est un espace où chacun est invité à se joindre. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Genieße in deiner feinen toskanischen Villa die Landluft. Diese Zweizimmer-Unterkunft bietet ein schickes Wohnzimmer mit Veranda und Terrasse. Und obendrauf haben wir direkt im nächsten Raum ein Schwimmbad eingebaut. Das ist der perfekte Ort, um sich hinzulegen und seine Gäste besser kennenzulernen. Die toskanische Villa ist ein Clubhaus, in dem jeder Gast willkommen ist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Goditi un giorno in campagna nella tua ricercata Villa toscana. Questa sistemazione bilocale offre un elegante soggiorno connesso all'esterno con un portico e una terrazza. Come se non bastasse, abbiamo aggiunto una piscina interna nella stanza accanto. È il luogo perfetto dove rilassarsi e conoscere meglio i propri ospiti. La Villa toscana è una sede del club dove chiunque è il benvenuto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Disfruta de un día en el campo en tu propia Villa toscana. Este alojamiento de dos habitaciones tiene un ostentoso salón conectado a un porche y a un patio exterior. Y por si no fuera suficiente, hemos añadido una piscina cubierta en la habitación contigua. Es el lugar perfecto para descansar y conocer mejor a tus invitados. El espacio Villa toscana es una sede del club a la que todos están invitados. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Enjoy a day in the countryside at your elaborate Tuscan Villa. This two-room lodging has a swanky living room connected to an outdoor porch and patio. To make things better, we’ve added an indoor swimming pool in the very next room. This is the perfect place to lay out and get to know your guests better. The Tuscan Villa space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">여러분의 화려한 투스칸 빌라에서 시골 풍경을 즐기세요. 두 개의 방을 가진 이 빌라는 호화로운 거실과 연결된 야외 현관과 테라스도 있습니다. 그리고 더 큰 만족감을 위해 바로 옆방에 실내 수영장도 만들었습니다. 여기야말로 편히 쉬면서 손님들과 친해질 수 있는 최적의 장소입니다. 투스칸 빌라 스페이스는 누구나 환영받는 클럽하우스입니다. *주의: 클럽하우스에 입장하려면 먼저 클럽을 구매해야 합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Enjoy a day in the countryside at your elaborate Tuscan Villa. This two-room lodging has a swanky living room connected to an outdoor porch and patio. To make things better, we’ve added an indoor swimming pool in the very next room. This is the perfect place to lay out and get to know your guests better. The Tuscan Villa space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. *Please note, in order to access the Tuscan Villa Clubhouse you will need to have purchased the Club Slot.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在奢華的托斯卡納別墅內享受一日的郊遊時光。這座兩房的別墅擁有時髦的客廳，連接室外的門廊及中庭，而隔壁的房間還加建了室內游泳池。這是最佳的地方讓你跟賓客交流。和大家一起在托斯卡納別墅聯盟俱樂部內相聚吧。※請注意，要使用托斯卡納別墅聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在奢華的托斯卡納別墅內享受一日的郊遊時光。這座兩房的別墅擁有時髦的客廳，連接室外的門廊及中庭，而隔壁的房間還加建了室內游泳池。這是最佳的地方讓你跟賓客交流。和大家一起在托斯卡納別墅聯盟俱樂部內相聚吧。※請注意，要使用托斯卡納別墅聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Enjoy a day in the countryside at your elaborate Tuscan Villa. This two-room lodging has a swanky living room connected to an outdoor porch and patio. To make things better, we’ve added an indoor swimming pool in the very next room. This is the perfect place to lay out and get to know your guests better. The Tuscan Villa space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>