<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="it-IT" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Adam Android</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'Androïde Adam</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Adam-Android</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'Androide Adamo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El androide Adán</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Adam Android</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The battle is on! Join the Android Army to deter the imminent alien invasion. This ultra resistant avatar is the weapon you need to send those aliens back to where they came!  Sure, they can float, but nobody can do the robot like you! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Autrefois gardiens de PlayStation®Home, les personnages Adam et Ève sont devenus conscients de leur personne et dirigent maintenant d’une main de fer !  Qui nous sauvera de la domination oppressive des Androïdes ? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Schlacht ist im Gange! Schließe dich der Android Army an, um die bevorstehende Alien-Invasion zu verhindern. Diese ultra-widerstandsfähige Avatar ist die Waffe, die du benötigst, um die Außerirdischen dorthin zu schicken, woher sie kamen! Klar, sie können schweben, aber keiner spielt den Roboter so wie du! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La battaglia è cominciata! Unisciti all'Esercito Androide  per impedire l'imminente invasione aliena. Questo avatar super resistente è ciò che ti serve per rimandare quegli alieni da dove sono venuti!  Certo, sanno volare, ma nessuno sa fare il robot come te! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡La lucha ha comenzado! Únete al Ejército Androide para detener la inminente invasión alienígena. ¡Este avatar ultra resistente es el arma que necesitas para mandar a esos alienígenas al lugar de donde proceden!  Vale, ellos flotan, ¡pero nadie hace el robot como tú! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Once the former guardians of PlayStation®Home, the Eve and Adam models have become self-aware and now rule with an iron fist! Who will save us from the oppressive Android Rule? [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>