<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Nis_Dots_No020</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Personnage 2D: Almaz</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドットオブジェ　勇者？ただのヘタレ？　アルマース</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">도트 오브제 용사? 그냥 어설픔? 알마스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Almaz: Hero or Coward?" Sprite Statue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">像素雕像 是勇者？還是懦夫？ ALMAZ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">像素雕像 是勇者？還是懦夫？ ALMAZ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">2D Character Objects: Almaz</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nis_dot_No020</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Untitled</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La statuette d'un personnage que tu peux mettre dans ta chambre pour décorer.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">彼の名は、アルマース・フォン・アルマディン・アダマント。そんな立派な名を持つ彼は、愛しの姫様を守るため、魔王城に乗り込んだ。しかし、マッドな悪魔にとっ捕まって、“勇者”の称号を奪われてしまう。いやいや、しかし、実は“勇者”の称号は、とりあえず名乗っていただけだった。本当は小さな国の単なる近衛兵！？魔王の息子に称号を奪われるばかりか、部下にされてしまいました。彼の運命や、いかに・・・？「姫様を守る為ならばこれくらい！…どうしてこうなっちゃったんだろう。。。」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">그의 이름은 알마스 폰 알마딘 아다만트. 그런 훌륭한 이름을 가진 그는, 사랑하는 공주님을 지키기 위해, 마왕성에 들어갔다. 그러나, 미친 마왕에게 붙잡혀 "용사"의 칭호를 빼앗겨 버린다. 이런이런, 그런데, "용사"의 칭호는 스스로 밝힌 것일 뿐, 사실은 작은 나라의 근위병!? 마왕의 아들에게 호칭을 빼앗기자마자 부하가 되어 버렸습니다. 그의 운명은, 어떻게… ?「공주님을 구하기 위해서라면 이 정도 쯤이야!…왜 이렇게 되어 버린 걸까...」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">His full name is "Almaz von Almandine Adamant," and he dared to venture into the Overlord's Castle to protect the princess he loves. But once there, he was captured by a mad demon, and stripped of his "Hero" title.  But he was never really a "Hero", it was only a nickname of sorts. In reality, he was just a simple guardsman from a small country. Not only was his title stripped by the Overlord's son, but he was made into one of his servants! Could this be his ultimate fate? "If it's for the safety of the princess, I can bear it... But, why did it have to happen like this...?"  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">他的名字是 Almaz von Almadine Adamant。有著這麼帥氣的名字，為了保護心愛的公主，進入了魔王城，但是卻被瘋狂的惡魔輕易的抓住，就連“勇者”的稱號也被搶走。其實“勇者”這個稱謂也只是掛名而己。本來他也只是一個小國的小兵！？不但被魔王的兒子搶走稱號，更莫名奇妙的成為他的部下。Almaz的命運到底如何？「我只是為了保護公主而已，為什麼會變成這樣呢…。」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">他的名字是 Almaz von Almadine Adamant。有著這麼帥氣的名字，為了保護心愛的公主，進入了魔王城，但是卻被瘋狂的惡魔輕易的抓住，就連“勇者”的稱號也被搶走。其實“勇者”這個稱謂也只是掛名而己。本來他也只是一個小國的小兵！？不但被魔王的兒子搶走稱號，更莫名奇妙的成為他的部下。Almaz的命運到底如何？「我只是為了保護公主而已，為什麼會變成這樣呢…。」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A small character statue that you can place to decorate your own room.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>