<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">S.V.E.R. Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaise S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">S.V.E.R.-Stuhl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sedia S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Silla de S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">椅子 セイバー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">S.V.E.R. 의자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SVER Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">SVER 椅子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">SVER 椅子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">SVER Chair</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Only S.V.E.R. can provide chairs that are not only surprisingly comfortable, but can also be used a close-combat weapons in a pinch ... as this one obviously has. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Seul S.V.E.R. est capable de proposer des chaises étonnamment confortables et susceptibles de se transformer en armes en un clin d'œil. À l'image de celle-ci. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nur S.V.E.R. versteht es, einen Stuhl zu entwickeln, der nicht nur überraschend komfortabel ist, sondern zur Not auch als Nahkampfwaffe eingesetzt werden kann – wie es bei diesem Exemplar offensichtlich bereits der Fall war. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Solo la S.V.E.R. riesce ad offrire delle sedie comodissime utilizzabili anche come armi d'emergenza nel combattimento ravvicinato. Questa sedia ha sicuramente svolto in pieno la sua funzione. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Solo S.V.E.R. podría vender sillas que además de ser cómodas pueden utilizarse como arma en combates cuerpo a cuerpo. Esta la han usado unas cuantas veces. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">あらゆる状況に備え、近接戦時の武器として使えるこの椅子は、意外に座り心地が良い。セイバーらしい発想だ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">오직 S.V.E.R. 만이 편안하면서도 위기의 순간에 백병전 무기로 사용할 수 있는 의자를 만들 수 있습니다. 물론 이 의자도 마찬가지입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Only SVER can provide chairs that are not only surprisingly comfortable, but can also be used as close-combat weapons in a pinch. As this one obviously has. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這款意想不到地舒適，而且可以在必要時用作近身戰武器的椅子，只有SVER可以提供。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這款意想不到地舒適，而且可以在必要時用作近身戰武器的椅子，只有SVER可以提供。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Only SVER can provide chairs that are not only surprisingly comfortable, but can also be used as close-combat weapons in a pinch. As this one obviously has. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>