<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">METAL GEAR SOLID: PEACE WALKER Battle Armour Snake</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">METAL GEAR SOLID: PEACE WALKER Tenue de combat Snake</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">METAL GEAR SOLID: PEACE WALKER Kampfanzug Snake</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">METAL GEAR SOLID: PEACE WALKER Armatura Battaglia Snake</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">METAL GEAR SOLID: PEACE WALKER uniforme de combate Snake</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">メタルギアソリッド: ピースウォーカー  バトルアーマースネーク</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">METAL GEAR SOLID: PEACE WALKER 배틀 아머 스네이크 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">METAL GEAR SOLID: PEACE WALKER Battle Armor Snake (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「METAL GEAR SOLID: PEACE WALKER」的Snake戰鬥盔甲（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「METAL GEAR SOLID: PEACE WALKER 」的Snake戰鬥盔甲（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">METAL GEAR SOLID: PEACE WALKER Battle Armor Snake</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Former member of the CIA Special Forces Unit, “Fox.” An expert in combat and stealth infiltration, Snake is a legendary hero who once rescued the world from the brink of all-out nuclear war. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ancien membre de l'unité des forces spéciales de la CIA, « Fox ». Un expert en combat et infiltration furtive, Snake est un héros légendaire qui a sauvé le monde de justesse d'une guerre nucléaire totale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Früheres Mitglied der CIA-Spezialeinheit "Fox". Als ein Experte für Kampf und Schleichinfiltration ist Snake ein legendärer Held, der einst die Welt vor dem Ausbruch eines totalen, nuklearen Krieges bewahrte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ex membro dell'unità di Forze Special della CIA, "Fox." Un esperto in combattimento e infiltrazione furtiva, Snake è l'eroe leggendario che salvò una volta il mondo sull'orlo di una guerra totale nucleare. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Antiguo miembro de la Unidad de Fuerzas Especiales de la CIA, "Fox". Experto en combate e infiltración furtiva, Snake es un héroe legendario que salvó al mundo de una guerra nuclear mundial que estaba a punto de estallar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">CIA（中央情報局）のスカウトにより秘匿工作員であった上、世界をメタルギアの脅威から救った伝説の英雄 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">전직 CIA 특수요원 "폭스"입니다. 대인격투와 잠입 전문가이며, 스네이크는 핵 전면전의 위기로부터 세계를 구한 전설적인 영웅입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Former member of the CIA Special Forces Unit, “Fox.” An expert in combat and stealth infiltration, Snake is a legendary hero who once rescued the world from the brink of all-out nuclear war. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">傳奇英雄Snake，中央情報局“Fox.”特種部隊前成員，格鬥和潛行突破專家；曾經力挽狂瀾，拯救全世界免於陷入核武大戰。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">傳奇英雄Snake，中央情報局“Fox.”特種部隊前成員，格鬥和潛行突破專家；曾經力挽狂瀾，拯救全世界免於陷入核武大戰。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Former member of the CIA Special Forces Unit, “Fox.” An expert in combat and stealth infiltration, Snake is a legendary hero who once rescued the world from the brink of all-out nuclear war. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>