<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Torpedo Jane Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Torpedo Jane Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Torpedo Jane Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Torpedo Jane Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Torpedo Jane Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup02_RedHeadUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup02_RedHeadUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup02_RedHeadUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup02_RedHeadUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup02_RedHeadUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Torpedo Jane Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dive, dive, dive!  This pin-up girl will deep-six your heart in an instant, so stay on red alert!  This full character costume sports a sexy retro uniform, brunette tresses, nautical tats along with custom walk, run and pin-up pose animations, you'll earn your stripes with this one![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plonge, plonge, plonge! Cette Pin-up nana va faire balancer ton cœur en un instant, alors, sois en alerte rouge! Ce costume à part entière affiche un uniforme retro sexy, tresses brunes, tatouages nautiques en plus d'une marche personnalisée, course et pose animées de pin-up, tu vas gagner ton respect avec celle-là! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tauchen, tauchen, tauchen! Dieses Pin-Up Girl kann dein Herz sofort über Bord werfen - sei also auf der Hut! Dieses komplette Charakterkostüm kommt mit sexy Retro-Uniform, braunen Locken und Animationen für Pin-Up Posen, mit denen du deine Streifen verdienen wirst!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nuota, nuota, nuota!  Questa bimba pin-up catturerá il tuo cuore in un'istante, qundi fai attenzione!  Questo costume completo ha un uniforme sexy retro, trecce marroni, insegne nautiche con animazioni di camminata particolare, corsa e pose da pin-up, con questa qui sicuramente guadagnerai le tue insegne![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nada, nada, nada!  Esta niña pin-up cautivará tu corazón en un instante, asi que debes estar alerta!  Este disfraz completo del personaje lleva un sexy uniforme retro, trenzas morenas, motivos nauticos así como también animaciones de caminata especial, corrida y poses de pin-up, seguro te ganarás tus menciones con ella! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup02_RedHeadUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup02_RedHeadUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup02_RedHeadUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup02_RedHeadUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup02_RedHeadUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dive, dive, dive!  This pin-up girl will deep-six your heart in an instant, so stay on red alert!  This full character costume sports a sexy retro uniform, brunette tresses, nautical tats along with custom walk, run and pin-up pose animations, you'll earn your stripes with this one![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>