<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bramblenook Farm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bramblenook Farm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bramblenook Farm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bramblenook Farm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bramblenook Farm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Bramblenook Farm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Bramblenook Farm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Bramblenook Farm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Bramblenook Farm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Bramblenook Farm</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Relax and get back to nature in this charming country farm. In this space you can raise plants and animals to improve your farming skills. As you gain experience, you will be able to plant new crops and raise new animals. Chop wood and level your woodworking skills to create furnishings for yourself or to gift to a guest. Place crafted furniture items in Bramblenook Farm for no furniture cost! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Détendez-vous et profitez de la nature dans cette ferme de charme. Dans cet espace, vous pouvez cultiver des plantes et élever des animaux pour améliorer vos compétences en agriculture. Avec l’expérience, vous parviendrez à planter de nouvelles cultures et à élever de nouveaux animaux. Couper du bois et améliorer vos compétences en menuiserie pour créer des meubles pour vous-même ou en faire cadeau à un invité. Installer vos meubles artisanaux à Bramblenook Farm pour ne pas payer de meubles ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Entspannen Sie sich und kehren Sie zurück zur Natur auf dieser bezaubernden Country Farm. In diesem Raum können Sie Pflanzen und Tiere (auf)ziehen, um ihre landwirtschaftlichen Kenntnisse aufzubessern.  Sobald Sie Erfahrung gewonnen haben, sind Sie imstande, neue Ernten zu pflanzen und neue Tiere aufzuziehen. Spalten Sie Holz und machen Sie Fortschritte in Ihrem Geschick der Holzbearbeitung, um selber Möbel zu entwerfen oder einen Gast zu beschenken. Stellen Sie handgearbeitete Möbelstücke in der Bramblenook Farm auf ohne Möbelkosten! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Rilassatevi a contatto con la natura in questa deliziosa fattoria di campagna. In questo spazio è possibile coltivare le piante e allevare gli animali per migliorare le proprie abilità agricole. Man mano che fate esperienza, sarete in grado di piantare nuove colture e allevare nuovi animali. Tagliare la legna e migliorare le vostre capacità di lavorare il legno per creare mobili per voi stessi o da donare a un ospite. Posizionare gli elementi di arredo creati nella Bramblenook Farm senza costi di mobilia! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Relájate y disfruta de la naturaleza en esta encantadora granja rural. En este espacio puedes hacer crecer plantas y animales para mejorar tus técnicas agrícolas. A medida que adquieras experiencia, serás capaz de plantar nuevos cultivos y criar animales nuevos. Cortar madera y aumentar de nivel tus habilidades para trabajar la madera para crear mobiliario para el hogar y hacer un regalo a un invitado. ¡Colocar los muebles hechos a mano en Bramblenook Farm, para no tener que gastar en mobiliario! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Relax and get back to nature in this charming country farm. In this space you can raise plants and animals to improve your farming skills. As you gain experience, you will be able to plant new crops and raise new animals. Chop wood and level your woodworking skills to create furnishings for yourself or to gift to a guest. Place crafted furniture items in Bramblenook Farm for no furniture cost! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Relax and get back to nature in this charming country farm. In this space you can raise plants and animals to improve your farming skills. As you gain experience, you will be able to plant new crops and raise new animals. Chop wood and level your woodworking skills to create furnishings for yourself or to gift to a guest. Place crafted furniture items in Bramblenook Farm for no furniture cost! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Relax and get back to nature in this charming country farm. In this space you can raise plants and animals to improve your farming skills. As you gain experience, you will be able to plant new crops and raise new animals. Chop wood and level your woodworking skills to create furnishings for yourself or to gift to a guest. Place crafted furniture items in Bramblenook Farm for no furniture cost! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Relax and get back to nature in this charming country farm. In this space you can raise plants and animals to improve your farming skills. As you gain experience, you will be able to plant new crops and raise new animals. Chop wood and level your woodworking skills to create furnishings for yourself or to gift to a guest. Place crafted furniture items in Bramblenook Farm for no furniture cost! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Relax and get back to nature in this charming country farm. In this space you can raise plants and animals to improve your farming skills. As you gain experience, you will be able to plant new crops and raise new animals. Chop wood and level your woodworking skills to create furnishings for yourself or to gift to a guest. Place crafted furniture items in Bramblenook Farm for no furniture cost! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>