<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Snow Globe Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">le globe de neige appartement</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schneekugel Wohnung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">globo di neve appartamento</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">globo de la nieve apartamento</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Snow Globe Apartment</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ever shook a snow globe and gazed inside wanting to be a part of that magical, miniature world?  Now this can be a virtual reality with our Snow Globe Apartment, set on a table inside The Jam Jar, the outside world is visible and giant!  Live the magic and feel the snow because after all….. There’s Snow Place like PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avez-vous déjà retourné une boule à neige et regardé les flocons tomber tout en imaginant faire partie de ce monde miniature et magique? Ce rêve peut devenir réalité en ligne grâce à l’appartement Boule à neige. Placé sur une table dans l’appartement Jam Jar, le monde extérieur y est bien visible et paraît gigantesque!  Vivez la magie de la neige hivernale….. Il n’existe rien de plus beau sur PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hast du jemals eine Schneekugel geschüttelt, ins Innere geblickt und wolltest Teil dieser magischen Miniaturwelt sein? Jetzt kann dies eine virtuelle Realität werden mit unserem Schneekugel-Apartment. Auf einem Tisch im Jam Jar-Apartment platziert, ist die Welt außerhalb sichtbar und riesig!  Lebe die Magie und fühle den Schnee, denn trotz allem ..... Zu Hause ist es so schön wie PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai mai guardato dentro una sfera di neve e desiderato far parte di quel magico mondo in miniatura? Ora questo desiderio può diventare realtà nel mondo virtuale con il nostro Appartamento Sfera di neve. Su un tavolo nell'appartamento Jam Jar il mondo esterno è visibile e sembra gigantesco! Vivi la magia e senti la neve che cade, perché, in fondo, non c'è nulla come essere a casa, sotto la neve con PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Alguna vez has agitado un globo de nieve y has deseado formar parte de ese mundo mágico en miniatura? Pues eso ya es una realidad virtual con nuestro apartamento Globo de Nieve. Ponlo sobre una mesa dentro del apartamento Jam Jar, ¡y verás que el mundo exterior es gigantesco!  ¡Vive la magia y la nieve desde el calor de PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ever shook a snow globe and gazed inside wanting to be a part of that magical, miniature world?  Now this can be a virtual reality with our Snow Globe Apartment, set on a table inside The Jam Jar, the outside world is visible and giant!  Live the magic and feel the snow because after all….. There’s Snow Place like PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>