<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Atticus Guitar (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guitare Atticus (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Atticus-gitarre (Frau)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chitarra Atticus (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guitarra de Atticus (Mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Atticus ギター(女性用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Atticus 기타 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Atticus Guitar (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Atticus - 結他（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Atticus - 吉他（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Atticus Guitar (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Slide this Atticus guitar over your shoulder and walk off into 
the sunset like a true rock star. Admirers will flock behind 
you as they bask in your glory. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Saisissez cette guitare Atticus et marchez au crépuscule comme une vraie rockstar. Vos admirateurs vous suivront et se baigneront dans votre gloire.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lass diese Atticus-gitarre über deine schulter gleiten und gehe wie ein echter rockstar in den sonnenuntergang. um dich werden sich bewunderer scharen, um in deinem ruhm zu baden.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Impugna questa chitarra Atticus e sfila al tramonto, proprio come una vera stella del rock. Gli ammiratori si accalcheranno dietro di te e si bagneranno nella tua gloria.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuélgate esta guitarra de Atticus al hombro y camina hacia la puesta de sol como una auténtica estrella del rock. Los admiradores te perseguirán y se deleitarán con tu gloria.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">夕暮れ時にこのAtticusのギターを肩に歩けば、あなたはもう真のロックスター。夕日を浴びたあなたの後ろにはその崇拝者が集まるでしょう。by Atticus [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 Atticus 기타를 어깨에 메고 진정한 록스타처럼 저녁 노을을 향해 걸어가세요. 팬들이 당신의 매력에 황홀해하며 당신 뒤로 무리지어 따라갈 것입니다.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Slide this Atticus guitar over your shoulder and walk off into 
the sunset like a true rock star. Admirers will flock behind 
you as they bask in your glory. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">將本款Atticus結他背在肩膀上，漫步在夕陽下，頗有搖滾明星的風範。無數崇拜者將蜂擁而至，因為他們在您的榮耀中感到溫暖。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">將本款Atticus吉他背在肩膀上，漫步在夕陽下，頗有搖滾明星的風範。無數崇拜者將蜂擁而至，因為他們在您的榮耀中感到溫暖。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Slide this Atticus guitar over your shoulder and walk off into 
the sunset like a true rock star. Admirers will flock behind 
you as they bask in your glory. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>