<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">S.V.E.R. T-Shirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">T-shirt SVER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">S.V.E.R.-T-Shirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maglietta S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta de S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Tシャツ セイバー（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">S.V.E.R. 티셔츠</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SVER T-Shirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">SVER T恤</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">SVER T恤</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">SVER T-Shirt</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">S.V.E.R. refuses to micromanage its soldier's lifestyle, as represented by this bold and unorthodox fitted t-shirt. Make a statement. Wear this S.V.E.R. 'Tee'. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">SVER se refuse à s'immiscer dans la vie de ses soldats, comme le montre ce t-shirt peu conventionnel. Affichez vos opinions. Portez ce t-shirt SVER. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">S.V.E.R. verzichtet darauf, ins Mikromanagement eines Soldatenlebens einzugreifen, was dieses freche, unorthodoxe T-Shirt beweist. Machen Sie ein Statement! Tragen Sie dieses S.V.E.R.-T-Shirt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La S.V.E.R. rifiuta di scrutinare e controllare lo stile di vita dei suoi soldati, come si può notare in questa maglietta aderente dal disegno sfrontato e anticonformista. Esprimete il vostro credo indossando questa maglietta S.V.E.R. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">S.V.E.R. se niega a controlar al milímetro el estilo de vida de sus soldados, tal y como demuestra esta llamativa y original camiseta ajustada. Si quieres causar sensación, cómprate esta camiseta de S.V.E.R. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">マイクロマネージしないセイバーらしい、斬新で派手なフィットTシャツ。みんなで主張しよう。セイバーのTシャツを購入しよう。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">S.V.E.R.는 함께 싸우는 전우들의 생활을 통제하지 않습니다. 강한 무늬가 들어간 이 티셔츠를 입으면, 역시 S.V.E.R.만의 강한 자신감이 솟아 오릅니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SVER refuses to micromanage its soldier's lifestyle, as represented by this bold and unorthodox fitted t-shirt. Make a statement. Wear this SVER Tee. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">SVER不願從頭到腳的管制軍人的生活模式，其觀點已在這款大膽而非一般的貼身T恤中表露無遺。穿起這款 SVER T恤，來表明自己的立場吧。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">SVER不願從頭到腳的管制軍人的生活模式，其觀點已在這款大膽而非一般的貼身T恤中表露無遺。穿起這款 SVER T恤，來表明自己的立場吧。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">SVER refuses to micromanage its soldier's lifestyle, as represented by this bold and unorthodox fitted t-shirt. Make a statement. Wear this SVER Tee. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>