<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Xero Pro 2MM Long Sleeve Spring Suit - Orange (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Combi-short Xero Pro 2MM à manches longues - Orange (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Xero Pro 2MM Langärmeliger Frühlingstaucheranzug - Orange (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Xero Pro 2MM Muta a maniche lunghe - Arancione (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Shorty de manga larga Xero Pro 2MM - Naranja (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Created for high performance pursuits, this advanced design features the optimum blend of thermal retention, resiliency and durability. Special features include a chest zip entry for easy ins and outs, as well as impact welded seams that offer water-tight durability. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Créé pour des aventures extrêmes, ce combi-short au design ultra-moderne offre à la fois une rétention thermique optimale et une résistance et une durabilité parfaites. Avec des détails très pratiques comme une fermeture éclair sur l'avant ou des coutures renforcées pour une meilleure étanchéité. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Taucheranzug für Hochleistungssportler schlechthin! Das fortschrittliche Design bietet eine optimale Mischung aus Wärmerückhalt, Elastizität und Haltbarkeit. Zu besonderen Details zählen der Reißverschluss auf der Vorderseite für bequemes An- und Ablegen und geschweißte, wasserundurchlässige Nähte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Creato per le massime prestazioni, questo design avanzato offre una combinazione perfetta di ritenzione termica, resistenza e durata. Tra le caratteristiche speciali vi sono l'apertura con zip sul petto per la massima vestibilità, oltre alle cuciture termosaldate antiurto che offrono la massima durata di impermeabilizzazione. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta prenda de diseño avanzado está creada para actividades de gran rendimiento y cuenta con una mezcla de máxima calidad para el mantenimiento térmico, resistencia y una mayor duración. Tiene detalles especiales como una abertura de cremallera en el pecho para ponérselo y quitárselo con facilidad, costuras soldadas contra impactos que ofrecen resistencia al agua. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>