<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">PlayStation®Home Mansion - Garage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">PlayStation®Home Mansion - Garage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">PlayStation®Home-Villa: Garage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Villa PlayStation®Home - Garage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mansión de PlayStation®Home: garaje</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">PlayStation®Home 맨션 - 차고</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">PlayStation®Home Mansion - Garage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">PlayStation®Home豪華別墅－車庫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">PlayStation®Home豪華別墅－車庫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">PlayStation®Home Mansion - Garage</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A mansion isn’t a really a mansion without an expensive place to keep your rides. That’s why we created an over-sized four-door garage to accompany the Playstation®Home Mansion. Your showroom comes equipped with overhead lights to help show off your prized trophies. There is more to this fancy showroom that meets the eye; can you find the missing pieces? As an added bonus, each section of the Playstation®Home Mansion includes up to 5 unique gold rewards for you and your guests. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un manoir digne de ce nom se doit d'avoir un endroit luxueux pour garer vos bolides. C'est pourquoi nous avons créé un immense garage à quatre portes pour accompagner le manoir PlayStation®Home. Cette salle d'exposition est équipée de plafonniers qui mettront en valeur vos précieux trophées. Mais ce garage de star est encore plus génial qu'il n'y paraît : pourrez-vous retrouver les pièces manquantes ? En prime, dans chaque partie du manoir PlayStation®Home se cachent 5 récompenses en or uniques pour vous et vos invités. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine Villa ist keine echte Villa ohne einen teuren Aufbewahrungsort für Ihre Fahrzeuge. Deshalb haben wir eine übergroße, viertürige Garage als Teil Ihrer Playstation®Home-Villa entworfen. Ihr Präsentationsraum ist mit Oberlichtern ausgestattet, um Ihre begehrten Trophäen im richtigen Licht erstrahlen zu lassen. Doch dieser elegante Ausstellungsraum bietet mehr, als mit bloßem Auge zu erkennen ist: Werden Sie fündig? Als zusätzlichen Bonus bietet jeder Bereich der Playstation®Home-Villa bis zu 5 einzigartige Goldbelohnungen für Sie und Ihre Freunde. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una magione che si rispetti non può non avere una lussuosa tana per i tuoi bolidi. Ecco perché, a impreziosire ulteriormente la villa PlayStation®Home, abbiamo creato un enorme garage con quattro ingressi. Più che un garage, è un vero e proprio showroom con punti luce sul soffitto per evidenziare al massimo i tuoi preziosi trofei. Ma in questa splendida sala c'è molto più di quanto sembri: riuscirai a trovare gli elementi mancanti? Come se non bastasse, ogni sezione della villa PlayStation®Home contiene fino a 5 esclusive ricompense in oro per te e i tuoi ospiti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Toda mansión que se precie necesita un gran espacio en el que guardar la colección de vehículos. Por eso hemos creado un inmenso garaje de cuatro puertas, como complemento de la mansión de PlayStation®Home. La zona de exhibición incluye una iluminación especial que realza tus preciados trofeos. Sin embargo, no todo está a la vista. ¿Podrás encontrar lo que falta? Además, cada sección de la mansión de PlayStation®Home incluye hasta cinco premios únicos de oro para ti y tus invitados. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">값비싼 차를 보관할 수 있는 차고 없이는 맨션이라는 이름으로 불릴 자격이 없습니다. 그래서 저희가 PlayStation®Home 맨션에는 네 개의 거대한 문이 달린 차고를 함께 드립니다. 당신의 보물을 제대로 전시 하도록 이 쇼룸에는 천장 조명이 있습니다. 사실 이 멋진 쇼룸에는 숨겨진 비밀이 있습니다; 찾아낼 수 있겠습니까? 또한 추가 보너스로는 PlayStation®Home 맨션을 방문하는 친구들에게 최대 4개의 황금 리워드를 각기 선물할 수 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A mansion isn’t really a mansion without an expensive place to keep your rides. That’s why we created an over-sized four-door garage to accompany the PlayStation®Home Mansion. Your showroom comes equipped with overhead lights to help showoff your prized trophies. There is more to this fancy showroom that meets the eye; can you find the missing pieces? As an added bonus, each section of the PlayStation®Home Mansion includes up to 4 unique gold rewards for you and your guests. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">沒有奢華的地方來收藏你的座駕，就說不上是大宅，所以我們準備了一座巨型的四門車庫。展示室裝有高射燈來展示你珍貴的獎盃，這個別緻的展示室還不只如此，你能找到欠缺什麼嗎？PlayStation®Home豪華別墅還包括最多4份額外黃金獎品道具給你和你的賓客。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">沒有奢華的地方來收藏你的座駕，就說不上是大宅，所以我們準備了一座巨型的四門車庫。展示室裝有高射燈來展示你珍貴的獎盃，這個別緻的展示室還不只如此，你能找到欠缺什麼嗎？PlayStation®Home豪華別墅還包括最多4份額外黃金獎品道具給你和你的賓客。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A mansion isn’t really a mansion without an expensive place to keep your rides. That’s why we created an over-sized four-door garage to accompany the PlayStation®Home Mansion. Your showroom comes equipped with overhead lights to help showoff your prized trophies. There is more to this fancy showroom that meets the eye; can you find the missing pieces? As an added bonus, each section of the PlayStation®Home Mansion includes up to 5 unique gold rewards for you and your guests. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>