<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Drey Slim Fit Leather Jacket - Black</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Veste en cuir à coupe serrée Drey - Noir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drey enge Lederjacke - Schwarz</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Giacca di pelle Drey aderente - Nero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chaqueta de piel de corte entallado Drey - Negra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">【Drey】スリムフィット レザージャケット（ブラック・男性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"드레이"의 몸에 딱 붙는 가죽 재킷 - 검은색 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Drey Slim Fit Leather Jacket - Black (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Drey緊身皮夾克：黑 （男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Drey緊身皮夾克：黑 （男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Drey Slim Fit Leather Jacket - Black</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Vintage leather expertly crafted into an ultra-modern slim fit jacket. Teamed with an open-necked shirt, this iconic jacket is an ideal wardrobe staple for any fashion forward gentleman. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le cuir vintage magnifiquement travaillé sur une veste coupe serrée ultra-moderne. Accompagnée d'une chemise à col ouvert, cette veste symbolique est un élément de base pour toute garde robe de gentleman concerné par la mode. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drey hat Vintage-Leder kunstvoll zu einer ultramodernen, eng anliegenden Lederjacke verarbeitet. Kombiniert mit einem Hemd mit weitem Kragen ist diese ikonische Jacke perfekt für jeden modebewussten Mann. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Giacca di pelle vintage realizzata da mani esperte con un taglio aderente ultra moderno. Abbinata a una camicia con colletto sbottonato, questa giacca iconica è un capo ideale per ogni uomo alla moda. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chaqueta de piel vieja, de corte entallado súper moderna confeccionada por manos expertas. A juego con una camisa desabrochada en el cuello, esta icónica chaqueta no puede faltar en el armario de los más vanguardistas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ヴィンテージレザーで加工してあるウルトラモダンなスリムフィットジャケット。オープンネックシャツと組み合わせてワイルドなジェントルマンを演出してみては？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">빈티지 가죽으로 정교하게 만든 울트라 모던 스타일의 몸에 딱 붙는 재킷. 앞이 열린 셔츠와 어울리는 이 멋진 재킷은 뛰어난 패션 감각의 신사에게 완벽하게 어울립니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Vintage leather expertly crafted into an ultra-modern slim fit jacket. Teamed with an open-necked shirt, this iconic jacket is an ideal wardrobe staple for any fashion forward gentleman. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">仿舊色澤皮革，經師傅精心剪裁，做成超具現代感的緊身夾克。這件傳統風格的夾克只要搭配開領上衣，就是前衛男士的必備外出服。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">仿舊色澤皮革，經師傅精心剪裁，做成超具現代感的緊身夾克。這件傳統風格的夾克只要搭配開領上衣，就是前衛男士的必備外出服。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Vintage leather expertly crafted into an ultra-modern slim fit jacket. Teamed with an open-necked shirt, this iconic jacket is an ideal wardrobe staple for any fashion forward gentleman. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>