<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Bulldog" Mk 2 Reinforced Body Armour</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Protection corps renforcée Mk 2 "Bulldog"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verstärkte Panzerung „Bulldog“ Mk 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Armatura rinforzata Mk 2 "Bulldog" per il busto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Blindaje reforzado Mk 2 "Bulldog"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">強化ファイバーMkIIボディー装甲"ブルドッグ"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">방탄복 MK2 - "불독"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Bulldog" Mk 2 Reinforced Body Armour</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「Bulldog」MK 2強化防彈衣</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「Bulldog」MK 2強化防彈衣</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Bulldog" Mk 2 Reinforced Body Armor</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Relying heavily on proven battle technology, Valor believes that "if it ain't broke, don't fix it". Durable and functional, Valor's no-nonsense gear is comfortable and quiet for those long missions behind enemy lines. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">S'appuyant largement sur une technologie éprouvée, Valor pense que "tant que ça marche, pas besoin de réparer". Résistant et fonctionnel, l'équipement épuré de Valor est confortable et discret, idéal pour les longues missions derrière les lignes ennemies. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Valor vertraut in erster Linie auf bewährte Kriegstechnologien nach dem Motto: „Wenn es nicht kaputt ist, muss es auch nicht ersetzt werden". Die Ausrüstung von Valor verzichtet auf alles Überflüssige und ist ausdauernd, funktional und weist zugleich einen hohen Komfort und minimierte Lärmwerte auf, was sie für Missionen auf feindlichem Territorium ideal macht. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Confidando nel fatto che la tecnologia collaudata in battaglia è sempre la migliore, la Valor crede che, se una cosa non si è ancora rotta, non va cambiata. Durevole e funzionale senza ghiribizzi, l'attrezzatura della Valor è comoda e silenziosa, adatta alle lunghe missioni dietro le linee nemiche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los operativos de Valor hacen uso principalmente de la tecnología ya probada en combate y creen firmemente en que si algo funciona bien, para qué cambiarlo. Resistente y funcional, el práctico equipo de Valor es cómodo y silencioso, perfecto para largas misiones entre líneas enemigas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">戦場で実績のある技術しか採用しないベイラーは、「壊れていないなら直すな」という信念を持っている。耐久力があり機能的なベイラーのギアは、実用重視で敵陣深く潜入しても快適かつ信頼できるギアに仕上がっている。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이미 전장에서 효능이 입증된 기술을 사용하여, '고장나지 않았다면 고치지 말라'는 격언을 실천하는 Valor의 장비입니다. 내구성과 기능에는 의심의 여지가 없습니다. 적진 뒤에서 오랜 시간 임무를 수행할 때에도 완벽한 착용감을 선사합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Relying heavily on proven battle technology, Valor believes that "if it ain't broke, don't fix it". Durable and functional, Valor's no-nonsense gear is comfortable and quiet for those long missions behind enemy lines. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Valor非常倚重具備實績的戰鬥科技 ，相信「未壞掉就別修理」這個道理。耐用與功能齊全。Valor實事求是的裝備，使用上舒適而寧靜，適用於深入敵方戰線的長期任務。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Valor非常倚重具備實績的戰鬥科技 ，相信「未壞掉就別修理」這個道理。耐用與功能齊全。Valor實事求是的裝備，使用上舒適而寧靜，適用於深入敵方戰線的長期任務。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Relying heavily on proven battle technology, Valor believes that "if it ain't broke, don't fix it". Durable and functional, Valor's no-nonsense gear is comfortable and quiet for those long missions behind enemy lines. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>