<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A social gathering spot from the early 20th Century that has somehow weathered decades of storms and conflict. Sully's is a rustic lounge and watering hole set deep in the tropics.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un lieu de réunion de socialisation du début du 20e siècle qui a été témoin de décennies de tempêtes et de conflits. Le bar de Sully est une aire de repos rustique situé au coeur des tropiques.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein sozialer Treffpunkt aus dem frühen 20. Jahrhundert, der irgendwie die konfliktreichen und stürmischen Jahrzehnte überstand. Sullys Bar ist eine rustikale Kneipe und eine tief in den Tropen gelegene Oase.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Luogo di ritrovo e incontro risalente ai primi del Novecento sopravvissuto a decenni di conflitti e intemperie, il Bar Sully è una taverna in stile rustico situata nel cuore dei tropici.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un punto de reunión social de principios del siglo XX que de algún modo ha sobrevivido décadas de tormentas y conflictos. Sully es una sala y bar en mitad de los trópicos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">20세기 초에 지어진 것으로 보이는 술집. 수십 년에 걸친 폭풍우와 전투에도 견뎌왔다. 설리의 술집은 정글 깊이 숨겨진 라운지이며, 목마른 자들을 위한 우물이다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A social gathering spot from the early 20th Century that has somehow weathered decades of storms and conflict. Sully's is a rustic lounge and watering hole set deep in the tropics.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sully’s Bar經歷了數十年的風吹雨打和戰亂，是一個位於熱帶樹林深處、充滿純樸情調和20世紀風情的酒吧，成為大家喝酒聊天的聚腳處。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sully’s Bar經歷了數十年的風吹雨打和戰亂，是一個位於熱帶樹林深處、充滿純樸情調和20世紀風情的酒吧，成為大家喝酒聊天的聚腳處。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A social gathering spot from the early 20th Century that has somehow weathered decades of storms and conflict. Sully's is a rustic lounge and watering hole set deep in the tropics.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Uncharted™: Sully's Bar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Uncharted™: Bar de Sully</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Uncharted™: Sullys Bar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Uncharted™: Bar Sully</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Uncharted™: Bar de Sully</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Uncharted™: 설리의 술집</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Uncharted™: Sully's Bar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Uncharted™: Sully's Bar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Uncharted™: Sully's Bar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Uncharted™: Sully's Bar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>