<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Xi: Continuum - Axiom Agent Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Xi: Continuum - Pack Agent Axiom</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Xi: Continuum - Axiom-Agenten-Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Xi: Continuum - Pacchetto agente Axiom</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Xi: Continuum, paquete agente de la Axiom</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This awesome bundle provides you with complete access to the greatest adventure in PlayStation®Home. Xi: Continuum, the sequel to Xi, is an adventure game featuring over 30 missions with hidden rewards, an evolving story, as well as exclusive videos and websites. \n\n

This bundle comes with the evolving 'Vertigo' apartment (with additional areas that unlock as you play through the game), the flying robotic Aeropal companion, the Xoff Cola Machine teleporter, 10 combat associates to fight with in single and multiplayer battles, and 5 buffs to  temporarily boost the power of your combat associates. This bundle includes: \n\n
* Access to the Xi: Continuum adventure game, including the Xi: Continuum Public Space. \n
* Xi: Continuum - Vertigo Apartment \n
* Xi: Continuum - Aeropal Companion \n
* Xi: Continuum - Xoff Cola Machine \n
* 10 random associates and 5 consumable buffs for use within the Xi: Continuum Combat Game. \n\n

※Upon purchase, all items will be added to their corresponding categories. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce super pack vous fournit un accès complet à la plus fantastique des aventures dans le PlayStation®Home. Xi: Continuum, la suite de Xi, est un jeu d'aventure de plus de 30 missions avec des récompenses cachées, une histoire qui évolue et des vidéos et sites web exclusifs. \n\n

Ce pack contient l'appartement « Vertige » en évolution (avec des zones supplémentaires à déverrouiller tout au long du jeu), Aeropal, le robot volant qui vous accompagne, 10 associés de combat pour des batailles en mode un joueur ou multijoueur, et 5 puissances pour augmenter temporairement la puissance de vos associés. Ce pack inclut : \n\n
* Accès au jeu d'aventure Xi: Continuum, y compris à l'Espace public de Xi: Continuum. \n
* Xi: Continuum - Appartement Vertige \n
* Xi: Continuum - Machine Xoff Cola \n
* Xi:Continuum - Compagnon Aeropal \n
* 10 associés aléatoires et 5 puissances consommables à utiliser dans le jeu de combat Xi: Continuum \n\n

※Après l'achat, chaque objet sera ajouté à la catégorie qui lui correspond. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Wahnsinns-Bundle bietet dir den kompletten Zugang zum größten Abenteuer auf PlayStation®Home. Xi: Continuum, die Fortsetzung zu Xi, ist ein Adventurespiel mit über 30 Missionen samt verborgener Belohnungen, einer sich weiterentwickelnden Geschichte sowie exklusiven Videos und Webseiten. \n\n

Dieses Bundle kommt mit dem sich vergrößernden Apartment 'Vertigo' (mit zusätzlichen Bereichen, die im Laufe des Spiels freigeschaltet werden), dem fliegenden robotischen Aeropal-Begleiter, 10 Kampfgefährten zur Unterstützung in Einzel- und Mehrspielerkämpfen sowie 5 Buffs, die deinen Gefährten vorübergehend mehr Power verleihen. Dieses Bundle beinhaltet: \n\n
* Zugang zum Xi: Continuum Adventurespiel, inklusive dem Xi: Continuum Öffentlichen Raum \n
* Xi: Continuum - Vertigo-Apartment \n
* Xi: Continuum - Aeropal-Begleiter \n
* Xi: Continuum - Xoff-Cola-Automat \n
* 10 zufällige Gefährten und 5 Einmal-Buffs für das Xi: Continuum Combat Game. \n\n

※ Nach dem Kauf stehen diese Gegenstände in den entsprechenden Kategorien zur Verfügung. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa favolosa raccolta offre accesso completo alla più grande avventura su PlayStation®Home. Xi: Continuum, il sequel di Xi, è un gioco di avventura che propone oltre 30 missioni con ricompense nascoste, una trama avvincente, video e siti web esclusivi. \n\n

Questa raccolta include l'appartamento vertiginoso (con zone aggiuntive che si sbloccano nel corso del gioco), il robottino volante Aeropal, 10 complici di combattimento per battaglie in singolo e multigiocatore, e 5 potenziamenti per aumentare momentaneamente la potenza dei tuoi complici in battaglia. Include: \n\n
* Accesso al gioco d'avventura Xi: Continuum, compreso lo spazio pubblico Xi: Continuum. \n
* Xi: Continuum - Appartamento vertiginoso \n
* Xi: Continuum - Compagno Aeropal \n
* Xi: Continuum - Distributore di Xoff Cola \n
* 10 complici a caso e 5 potenziamenti per la modalità di combattimento di Xi: Continuum. \n\n

※Con l'acquisto, tutti gli oggetti saranno aggiunti alle categorie corrispondenti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este increíble paquete te ofrece un acceso completo a la mayor aventura de PlayStation®Home. Xi: Continuum, la secuela de Xi, es un juego de aventuras cuya historia se va desarrollando. Cuenta con más de 30 misiones, recompensas ocultas, vídeos y sitios web exclusivos. \n\n

Este paquete viene con el apartamento "Vértigo" (que va evolucionando, con zonas adicionales que se desbloquean a medida que juegas), el compañero robótico volador Aeropal, 10 socios de combate para luchar en batallas individuales y multijugador, además de 5 mejoras para aumentar de forma temporal la potencia de tus socios de combate. Incluye: \n\n
* Acceso al juego de aventuras Xi: Continuum, con el espacio público de Xi: Continuum incluido. \n
* Xi: Continuum, apartamento Vértigo \n
* Xi: Continuum, socio Aeropal \n
* Xi: Continuum, máquina de Xoff Cola \n
* 10 socios aleatorios y 5 mejoras consumibles para el juego de combate de Xi: Continuum. \n\n

※Estas cartas solo se pueden usar en el Juego de Combate de Xi: Continuum. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>