<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Jade Daredevil Biplane</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Biplan Casse-cou Jade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jadegrüner Daredevil-Doppeldecker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Biplano da stunt giada</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Biplano Temerario Jade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LMO-デアデビル・バイプレーン （ジェイド）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Jade Daredevil Biplane</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Jade Daredevil Biplane</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blast off into the past and boost your speed to 150% with Retro Flyers! Your speed boost will automatically engage when moving at full running speed. Retro Flyers can be accessed from your personal inventory. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Faites un bond dans le passé et boostez votre vitesse jusqu'à 150% avec les Retro Flyers ! Votre boost de vitesse se déclenchera automatiquement quand vous vous déplacerez à la vitesse maximale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Starte durch zurück in die Vergangenheit und verbessere deine Geschwindigkeit auf 150% mit den Retrofliegern!  Dein Geschwindigkeitsschub setzt automatisch ein, wenn du dich mit voller Geschwindigkeit bewegst. Die Retroflieger sind über das persönliche Inventar abrufbar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fiondati nel passato e aumenta la tua velocità fino al 150% con i Retro Flyers! La tua velocità aumenterà automaticamente quando corri al massimo. Puoi accedere ai Retro Flyers dal tuo inventario personale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Despega hacia el pasado e incrementa tu velocidad al 150% con los Voladores Retro! El incremento de tu velocidad entrará en marcha automáticamente cuando vayas a máxima velocidad. Los Voladores Retro pueden ser accedidos desde el inventario personal. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">過去に飛んでレトロフライヤーでスピードを150%までブーストさせよう！フルスピードでの走行時は自動的にスピードはブーストします。レトロフライヤーはパーソナルインベントリからアクセスできます。\n移動速度アップ：◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆\nLMO（ロコモーション）はポータブルアイテムです。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Blast off into the past and boost your speed to 150% with Retro Flyers! Your speed boost will automatically engage when moving at full running speed. Retro Flyers can be accessed from your personal inventory. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blast off into the past and boost your speed to 150% with Retro Flyers! Your speed boost will automatically engage when moving at full running speed. Retro Flyers can be accessed from your personal inventory. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>