<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sky Fishing Lure Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot d'appâts pour pêche du ciel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sky Fishing-Köderpaket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto esca Pesca del cielo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de cebo de pesca espacial</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スカイフィッシングルアセット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">스카이 피싱 미끼 세트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sky Fishing Lure Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">空中釣魚魚餌組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">空中釣魚魚餌組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sky Fishing Lure Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Get this bundle of fantastic lures for the Aurora Sky Fishing game so you can hone in on specific catches . This set includes:\n\n
* The Tasty Snapper \n
* The Magnetico \n
* Genie in a Bottle \n\n

※ Upon purchase, these items will not appear in your inventory. These items are upgrades that will increase your chances of catching specific items in the Aurora Sky Fishing game.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Acquérez ce superbe lot d'appâts qui vous permettra d'attraper plus facilement certaines prises dans le jeu de pêche d'Aurora Sky. Ce lot comprend :\n\n
* Le Délicieux vorace  \n
* Le magnético \n
* Génie dans une bouteille \n\n

※ À l'achat, ces objets n'apparaîtront pas dans votre inventaire. Il s'agit d'améliorations qui faciliteront grandement votre partie de pêche d'Aurora Sky.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hole dir dieses Paket mit fantastischen Ködern für das Aurora Sky Fishing, damit du spezifische Fische anlocken kannst. In diesem Set enthalten:\n\n
* Der schmackhafte Schnapper \n
* Der Magnetiko \n
* Flaschengeist \n\n

※ Diese Gegenstände werden nach dem Kauf nicht in deinem Inventar erscheinen. Diese Gegenstände sind Upgrades, mit denen Aurora Sky Fishing viel leichter wird.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ottieni queste fantastiche esche per il gioco Pesca del cielo di Aurora e potrai concentrarti su prede specifiche. Il set include:\n\n
*Il Dentice gustoso \n
*Il Magnetico \n
*Genio della lampada \n\n

※ Dopo l'acquisto, questi oggetti non appariranno nel tuo inventario. Questi oggetti sono potenziamenti che renderanno il gioco Pesca del cielo di Aurora molto più semplice.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Consigue este paquete de magníficos cebos para el juego de pesca espacial de Aurora, ideal para atrapar ciertas presas. Incluye:\n\n
* El pargo delicioso\n
* El Magnético\n
* Genio en una botella\n\n 

※ Una vez que lo hayas comprado, los artículos no se mostrarán en el inventario. Estos artículos son mejoras que aumentarán las posibilidades de conseguir ciertas presas en el juego de pesca espacial de Aurora.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラ スカイフィッシングゲームで使える素敵なルア。特殊なアイテムを釣り上げられるかも。\n\n
* テースティースナッパー \n
* マグネーティコ \n
* ビンの中の精霊 \n\n

※ これらのアイテムは購入後も所持品に表示されません。アイテムは オーロラ スカイフィッシングゲームで特定アイテムを釣り上げる確率を高めるアップグレードです。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">오로라 스카이 피싱 게임을 위한 이 환상적인 미끼 번들을 얻고 특정 어획물에 사용하세요. 이 세트는 다음을 포함합니다:\n\n
●맛있는 스내퍼 \n
●마그네티코 \n
●병 속의 지니 \n\n
구입을 하면 이 아이템들은 당신의 인벤토리에 나타나지 않을 것입니다. 이들 아이템들은 오로라 스카이 피싱 게임에서 특정 아이템을 잡을 확률을 높여주는 업그레이드입니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Get this bundle of fantastic lures for the Aurora Sky Fishing game so you can hone in on specific catches . This set includes:\n\n
* The Tasty Snapper \n
* The Magnetico \n
* Genie in a Bottle \n\n

※ Upon purchase, these items will not appear in your inventory. These items are upgrades that will increase your chances of catching specific items in the Aurora Sky Fishing game.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">為極光空中釣魚遊戲購買這套神奇的魚餌，以便您能夠釣到特定的魚。本組合包包括：\n\n
●美味鯛魚\n
●磁鐵\n
●瓶中精靈\n\n
※在購買後，您的道具欄並不會顯示這些物品。這些物品屬升級道具，增加您在極光空中釣魚遊戲中獲得特定物品的機率。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">為極光空中釣魚遊戲購買這套神奇的魚餌，以便您能夠釣到特定的魚。本組合包包括：\n\n
●美味鯛魚\n
●磁鐵\n
●瓶中精靈\n\n
※在購買後，您的道具欄並不會顯示這些物品。這些物品屬升級道具，增加您在極光空中釣魚遊戲中獲得特定物品的機率。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Get this bundle of fantastic lures for the Aurora Sky Fishing game so you can hone in on specific catches . This set includes:\n\n
* The Tasty Snapper \n
* The Magnetico \n
* Genie in a Bottle \n\n

※ Upon purchase, these items will not appear in your inventory. These items are upgrades that will increase your chances of catching specific items in the Aurora Sky Fishing game.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>