<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Novus Prime Tech Goggles with Enemy Scanner (female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lunettes Novus Prime Tech avec Scanner d'ennemi (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Novus Prime Tech-Brille mit Feindradar (weibliche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Visore ad alta tecnologia Novus Prime con Scanner Nemici (per donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Gafas Tech Novus Prime con Escáner Enemigo (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">エネミースキャナーつきノーバス・プライムテックゴーグル（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">에너미 스캐너와 노부스 프라임 테크 고글 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Novus Prime Tech Goggles with Enemy Scanner (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Novus Prime技術護目鏡和敵人掃描器(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Novus Prime技術護目鏡和敵人掃描器(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Novus Prime Tech Goggles with Enemy Scanner (female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Expose the weaknesses of your foes with the Novus Prime Tech Goggles!  This lightweight eyewear piece allows its wearer to scan enemy vessels in Novus Prime space combat game.  Once scanned, all damage dealt to the target is doubled, allowing you and your allies to exterminate with ease. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Exposez les faiblesses de vos ennemis avec les lunettes Novus Prime Tech! Ce dispositif léger de vision permet à son porteur de numériser les navires ennemis dans le jeu de combat spatial Novus Prime. Une fois numérisés, tous les dégâts infligés à la cible sont doublés, vous permettant à vous et vos alliés de les exterminer en toute facilité. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Decke mit dieser Novus Prime Tech-Brille die Schwächen deiner Feinde auf! Diese leichtgewichtige Sehhilfe erlaut es seinem Träger während der Weltraumschlacht um Novus Prime feindliche Schiffe zu scannen. Sobald ein Ziel gescannt wurde, wird jeglicher zugefügter Schaden verdoppelt, was es dir und deinen Allierten erleichtert, Feinde auszuschalten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Visualizza le debolezze dei tuoi nemici con il Visore ad alta tecnologia Novus Prime! Chi indossa questo visore superleggero può analizzare le unità nemiche nei dintorni della Novus Prime. A scansione terminata, ogni danno inferto al nemico viene duplicato, permettendo a te ed ai tuoi alleati di procedere con facilità nell'eliminazione delle truppe nemiche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Expone la debilidad de tus enemigos con las Gafas Tech Novus Prime! Esta pieza de gafas ligeras permiten a su portador escanear los buques enemigos en el juego de combate espacial Novus Prime. Una vez escaneados, todo el daño hecho al blanco es doblegado, permitiendo a ti y tus aliados exterminar con facilidad. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス･プライムテックゴーグルで敵の弱点を暴きだそう！この軽量アイウェアは、ミニゲーム「ノーバス･プライム」で着用者に敵船のスキャンを可能にする。一度スキャンするとターゲットのダメージは2倍になり、君と君の味方は容易く敵を一掃できるようになる。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임 테크 고글로 적의 약점을 찾아내 보십시오! 이 가벼운 고글을 쓰면 노부스 프라임 스페이스 컴뱃 게임에서 적의 함선을 스캔할 수 있습니다. 한번 스캔하고 나면, 당신과 당신의 협력자의 공격이 2배로 강해져, 적을 쉽게 제거할 수 있습니다 . [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Expose the weaknesses of your foes with the Novus Prime Tech Goggles!  This lightweight eyewear piece allows its wearer to scan enemy vessels in Novus Prime space combat game.  Once scanned, all damage dealt to the target is doubled, allowing you and your allies to exterminate with ease. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Novus Prime的護目鏡能夠讓你在Novus Prime太空作戰模式中輕鬆掃描出敵人的艦隊。一但被掃描到，對目標的所有損傷將增加一倍，讓你以及你的盟友能夠輕鬆消滅敵人。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Novus Prime的護目鏡能夠讓你在Novus Prime太空作戰模式中輕鬆掃描出敵人的艦隊。一但被掃描到，對目標的所有損傷將增加一倍，讓你以及你的盟友能夠輕鬆消滅敵人。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Expose the weaknesses of your foes with the Novus Prime Tech Goggles!  This lightweight eyewear piece allows its wearer to scan enemy vessels in Novus Prime space combat game.  Once scanned, all damage dealt to the target is doubled, allowing you and your allies to exterminate with ease. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>