<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Diamond and Pearl Drop Earring (Left Ear)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Boucle d'oreille diamant et perle (oreille gauche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ohrring mit Diamanten und Perlen (Linkes Ohr)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Orecchino di diamanti e perle (Orecchio sinistro)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pendiente de diamante y perla (oreja izquierda)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">다이아몬드와 진주 귀걸이 (왼쪽 귀)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Diamond and Pearl Drop Earring (Left Ear)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">鑽石和珍珠耳環 (左耳/女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">鑽石和珍珠耳環 (左耳/女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Diamond and Pearl Drop Earring (Left Ear)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Diamonds (and pearls) are a girl's best friend. Iridescent freshwater pearls suspended beneath delicate diamonds set in white gold. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les diamants (et les perles) sont les meilleurs amis des filles. Perles irisées d'eau douce suspendues sous de délicats diamants sertis dans de l'or blanc. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diamanten (und Perlen) sind die besten Freunde einer Frau. Schimmernde Süßwasserperlen unter erlesenen, weißgoldgefassten Diamanten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I diamanti (e le perle) sono i migliori amici di ogni ragazza. Perle di fiume iridescenti pendenti da una montatura di diamanti e oro bianco. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los diamantes (y las perlas) son los mejores amigos de las chicas. Perlas auténticas iridiscentes suspendidas tras unos diamantes delicados en un marco de oro blanco. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">다이아몬드(그리고 진주)는 항상 아가씨들의 사랑을 받죠. 백금으로 세팅한 섬세한 다이아몬드 아래 매달린 무지갯빛의 민물 진주. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Diamonds (and pearls) are a girl's best friend. Iridescent freshwater pearls suspended beneath delicate diamonds set in white gold. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">鑽石（和珍珠）是姑娘們最好的朋友。鑲鑽的白金底座下懸掛著五彩的淡水珍珠。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">鑽石（和珍珠）是姑娘們最好的朋友。鑲鑽的白金底座下懸掛著五彩的淡水珍珠。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Diamonds (and pearls) are a girl's best friend. Iridescent freshwater pearls suspended beneath delicate diamonds set in white gold. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>