<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Piñata</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Piñata</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Piñata</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pignatta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Piñata</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Piñata [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Piñata [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Piñata [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pignatta [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Piñata [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PinataTalk1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Birthday Piñata will give people, who are generous with Birthday Gifts, a special reward!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La Piñata anniversaire réserve une récompense spéciale aux personnes généreuses en cadeaux d'anniversaire !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Geburtstags-Piñata hat eine besondere Belohnung für alle, die großzügige Geburtstagsgeschenke machen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Pignatta di Compleanno dà un premio speciale alle persone generose con i Regali di Compleanno!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡La Piñata de Cumpleaños recompensará con un premio especial a las personas que sean generosas en Regalos de cumpleaños !</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PinataTalk2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Maybe you should try gifting some Birthday Soda or Birthday Cake to your friends?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Peut-être devriez-vous offrir quelques sodas ou gâteaux d'anniversaire à vos amis ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vielleicht sollten Sie Ihren Freunden zum Geburtstag eine Limonade oder einen Geburtstagskuchen schenken!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Magari dovresti provare a regalare un po' di Bibite di Compleanno o di Torta di Compleanno ai tuoi amici?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Quizás deberías regalar algún refresco de cumpleaños o pastel de cumpleaños a tus amigos.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PinataTalk3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Congratulations! You've shared gifts with the community and here's a special reward.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Félicitations ! Vous avez partagé des cadeaux avec la communauté et une récompense spéciale vous est réservée.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Herzlichen Glückwunsch! Sie haben der Gemeinschaft etliche Geschenke gemacht und erhalten dafür eine besondere Belohnung.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Congratulazioni! Hai scambiato regali con la comunità e ti meriti un premio speciale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Enhorabuena! Has compartido regalos con la comunidad y aquí tienes un premio especial.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PinataTalk4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You've already had a gift from the Piñata!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez déjà reçu un cadeau du Piñata !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben bereits ein Geschenk aus der Piñata erhalten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai già ricevuto un regalo dalla Pignatta!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Ya has conseguido un regalo de la Piñata!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sortie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beenden</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salida</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>