<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nebulon Containment Trunk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Malle imperméable au Nébulon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nebulon Eindämmungscontainer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fusto di contenimento nebule</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tanque de contención Nebulon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ネブロンコンテナタンク</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">네뷸론 컨테이너 탱크</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Nebulon Containment Trunk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Nebulon封鎖箱</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Nebulon封鎖箱</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Nebulon Containment Trunk</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">These efficient stackable containers are ideal for storing Nebulon within approved facilities.   Even though these units are often brought into crew  quarters for use as coffee tables, the Novus Prime Safety Commission officially recommends against such use. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ces conteneurs empilables sont très pratiques pour stocker du Nebulon dans des endroits non autorisés.  Bien souvent entreposés dans les quartiers de l'équipage pour servir comme table basse, la Commission de Sécurite de Novus Prime déconseille officiellement un tel usage de ce matériel . [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese sehr effizienten und stapelbaren Container sind ideal zur  Aufbewahrung von Nebulon innerhalb zugelassener Anlagen.  Auch wenn diese Einheiten häufig in die Mannschaftsräume  gebracht  und als Kaffeetische verwendet werden, so hat sich die Novus Prime Sicherheitsabteilung offiziell gegen eine solche Nutzung ausgesprochen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questi efficienti contenitori impilabili sono l'ideale per immagazinare nebule all'interno degli impianti specializzati. Anche se queste unità vengono spesso portate negli alloggi dell'equipaggio per essere usate come tavolini, la Commissione di Sicurezza della Novous Prime si è ufficialmente dichiarata contro questo loro utilizzo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estos eficientes contenedores que pueden apilarse son  ideales para almacenar Nebulon dentro de instalaciones  aprobadas. A pesar que estas unidades son generalmente  usadas por el equipo de los cuarteles como mesas para  tomar café, la Comisión de Seguridad de Novus Prime oficialmente está en contra de este uso. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このコンテナは認可を受けた施設内にてネブロンを保存するのに最適。乗組員たちは宿舎にコーヒーテーブルとしてこのコンテナを持ち込んでいることがあるが、ノーバス・プライム安全委員会は正式にこのような使い方をおすすめしない。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 컨테이너는 인가를 받은 시설내에서 네뷸론을 보존하기위해 적합함. 승무원들이 숙사에 커피테이블 용도로 이 컨테이너를 사용하는 경우가 있으나, 노부스·프라임 안전위원회는 정식으로 이러한 사용방법을 권장하지 않음. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">These efficient stackable containers are ideal for storing Nebulon within approved facilities.  Even though these units are often brought into crew quarters for use as coffee tables, the Novus Prime Safety Commission officially recommends against such use. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這些高效能的容器是在經過批准的設施內存放Nebulon的理想道具。儘管工作人員經常帶進宿舍當作咖啡桌使用，不過Novus Prime安全委員會正式建議避免這種使用方式。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這些高效能的容器是在經過批准的設施內存放Nebulon的理想道具。儘管工作人員經常帶進宿舍當作咖啡桌使用，不過Novus Prime安全委員會正式建議避免這種使用方式。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">These efficient stackable containers are ideal for storing Nebulon within approved facilities.  Even though these units are often brought into crew quarters for use as coffee tables, the Novus Prime Safety Commission officially recommends against such use. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>