<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Crystal Seashores Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cristal bords de mer bundle de meubles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kristallküste: Möbelset</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto arredamento Spiagge cristalline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de muebles Orillas de cristal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Crystal Seashores Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">수정 해안 번들</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Crystal Seashores Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">水晶海岸組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">水晶海岸組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Crystal Seashores Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Capturing that deep-rooted summer home atmosphere, the Crystal Seashores furniture bundle is a great seasonal set made for any time of the year. Bundle includes a console, coffee table, couch, chair and lamp. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Capturer cette atmosphère profondément enracinés chez l'été, le faisceau de meubles Cristal bords de mer est un ensemble très saisonnière fait pour n'importe quel moment de l'année. L'ensemble comprend un tableau console, table basse, canapé, chaise et lampe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Kristallküste-Möbelset fängt die intensive Sommerhausatmosphäre ein und ist ein wunderbares Saisonpaket fürs ganze Jahr. Im Paket enthalten sind ein Konsolentisch, ein Couchtisch, eine Couch, ein Sessel und eine Lampe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dalla profonda atmosfera di residenza estiva, il Pacchetto arredamento Spiagge cristalline è una grande raccolta stagionale fatta per qualsiasi periodo dell'anno. Il pacchetto include un tavolo console, un tavolino da caffè, un divano, una sedia e una lampada. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El conjunto de muebles Orillas de cristal captura esa atmósfera de casa veraniega arraigada y es un paquete de temporada genial creado para todo el año. El paquete incluye: una mesilla, una mesa de café, un sofá, una silla y una lámpara. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Capturing that deep-rooted summer home atmosphere, the Crystal Seashores furniture bundle is a great seasonal set made for any time of the year. Bundle includes a console, coffee table, couch, chair and lamp. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">여름 별장 느낌을 확실히 살린 수정 해안 가구 번들은, 계절과 상관없이 언제나 어울리는 세트입니다.\n 이 번들은 다음이 포함됩니다.\n\n   ●수정 해안 콘솔 테이블\n ●수정 해안 커피 테이블\n ●수정 해안 소파\n ●수정 해안 의자\n ●수정 해안 램프\n\n  *구매 후 각 아이템은 해당 카테고리에 추가됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Capturing that deep-rooted summer home atmosphere, the Crystal Seashores furniture bundle is a great seasonal set made for any time of the year.\n This bundle includes the following items.\n\n  ・Crystal Seashores Console Table\n ・Crystal Seashores Coffee Table\n ・Crystal Seashores Couch\n ・Crystal Seashores Chair\n ・Crystal Seashores Lamp\n\n  *When purchased, each item is added to its respective category. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">水晶海岸組合包完全捕捉了夏日度假屋的氣氛，適合全年任何時候使用。\n 本組合包包括以下道具：\n\n  ●水晶海岸桌子\n ●水晶海岸咖啡桌\n ●水晶海岸長沙發\n ●水晶海岸椅子\n ●水晶海岸檯燈\n\n  ※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別內。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">水晶海岸組合包完全捕捉了夏日度假屋的氣氛，適合全年任何時候使用。\n 本組合包包括以下道具：\n\n  ●水晶海岸桌子\n ●水晶海岸咖啡桌\n ●水晶海岸長沙發\n ●水晶海岸椅子\n ●水晶海岸檯燈\n\n  ※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別內。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Capturing that deep-rooted summer home atmosphere, the Crystal Seashores furniture bundle is a great seasonal set made for any time of the year. Bundle includes a console, coffee table, couch, chair and lamp. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>