<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Li'l Reaper</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">P'ite faucheuse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kleiner Sensenmann</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il piccolo mietitore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pequeña Muerte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">リトル リーパー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">꼬마 리퍼</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Li'l Reaper</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">小小鐮刀手</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">小小鐮刀手</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Li'l Reaper</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This remorseless, unforgiving, bringer of death wants to drag you into the abyss from whence it came! But until then, why not show him to all your friends because lets face it, it exudes cool. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce convoyeur de mort sans remords et sans pitié veut vous entraîner dans l'abysse d'où il vient ! Mais entre-temps, pourquoi ne pas le montrer à tous vos amis, parce qu'il faut bien le dire, c'est trop la classe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser erbarmungslose und unerbittliches Todesbringer will dich in den Abgrund ziehen, aus dem er gekommen ist! Aber bis dahin solltest du ihn deinen Freunden zeigen, denn seien wir ehrlich: Er ist cooler als cool. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lo spietato e inesorabile portatore di morte desidera trascinarti negli abissi da cui proviene! Ma prima potresti mostrarlo agli amici perché, ammettiamolo, è proprio forte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Esta despiadada e implacable Muerte quiere llevarte al abismo de donde vino! Hasta entonces, ¿por qué no se la enseñas a tus amigos? Hay que reconocer que es superguay. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">一見するとちょっとコワオモテ。でも、彼はとてもクールなので見せびらかしてもいいのでは？[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">가차없고 무자비한 죽음의 전달자가 심연으로 당신을 끌어들이려 합니다! 하지만 그날이 올 때까지, 그를 당신의 친구들에게 보여주는 것을 어떻습니까? 사실 정말 멋지잖아요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This remorseless, unforgiving, bringer of death wants to drag you into the abyss from whence it came! But until then, why not show him to all your friends because lets face it, it exudes cool. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這個無情、無義的死神召喚者想把你拖入深淵！但是在此之前，為什麼不讓你的朋友都看看它呢。讓我們面對它，它還有點酷。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這個無情、無義的死神召喚者想把你拖入深淵！但是在此之前，為什麼不讓你的朋友都看看它呢。讓我們面對它，它還有點酷。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This remorseless, unforgiving, bringer of death wants to drag you into the abyss from whence it came! But until then, why not show him to all your friends because lets face it, it exudes cool. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>