<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Khul Mercali Primeval Bow</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Arc primitif Khul Mercali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Khul-Mercali-Urzeitbogen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Arco primordiale di Khul Mercali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Arco primigenio de Khul Mercali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Khul Mercali Primeval Bow</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Striking at targets from distance, such is the way of a Mercian Ranger. \n\nUsed in the dark corners of the primeval jungles. The hunter becomes the prey.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La frappe à distance est l'apanage du ranger mercian.\n\nPour une utilisation dans les sombres recoins des jungles primitives, où le chasseur devient la proie.\n\nDÉBLOQUE DES ARTICLES DU JEU MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS – N'OFFRE PAS DE COMPOSANTS D'AVATAR POUR UN USAGE GÉNÉRAL SUR PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBLE POUR LES UTILISATEURS DU JAPON ET DE L'ASIE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Kampfstil des Mercia-Waldläufers zeichnet sich durch Angriffe aus der Ferne aus. \n\nWird in den finstersten Tiefen des Dschungels eingesetzt. Der Jäger wird zum Gejagten.\n\nZUM FREISCHALTEN VON GEGENSTÄNDEN IN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS - NICHT ZUM ERHALT VON AVATAR-KOMPONENTEN ZUR ALLGEMEINEN NUTZUNG AUF PLAYSTATION®HOME. NICHT VERFÜGBAR FÜR BENUTZER IN JAPAN UND ASIEN [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Colpendo i bersagli dalla distanza, così combatte un ranger Mercian. \n\nUsato negli angoli oscuri delle giungla primordiali. Il cacciatore diventa la preda.\n\nSBLOCCA OGGETTI ALL'INTERNO DEL GIOCO MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS. NON REGALA COMPONENTI PER AVATAR PER USO GENERICO CON PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBILE PER GLI UTENTI IN ASIA E GIAPPONE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Golpear a los objetivos desde la distancia, así actúan los exploradores de Mercia. \n\nSe utiliza en los recodos oscuros de las junglas primigenias. El cazador se convierte en la presa.\n\nDESBLOQUEARÁ ELEMENTOS EN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS GAME. NO REGALARÁ COMPONENTES DE AVATAR PARA EL USO GENERAL EN CASA DE PLAYSTATION. NO DISPONIBLE PARA LOS USUARIOS DE JAPÓN Y ASIA. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Striking at targets from distance, such is the way of a Mercian Ranger. \n\nUsed in the dark corners of the primeval jungles. The hunter becomes the prey.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>