<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This personal space is your very own tropical island inhabited by LocoRoco™ characters. The tropical retreat is full of exciting activities. Collect berries that fall from the trees, and communicate with islanders to expand the facilities. Enjoy the Swing, Slide, Jukebox, and games for two players! And the more time you spend on Loco Island, the more vibrant and exciting the paradise becomes! Treat yourself to this fun-filled personal space![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cet espace personnel, habité par des personnages de LocoRoco™, c'est ton île tropicale ! Les activités alléchantes sont légion sur cette île fantastique. Ramasse les noix qui tombent des arbres et communique avec les insulaires pour développer les installations. Amuse-toi avec la balançoire, le toboggan, le juke-box et tous les jeux pour deux ! Et plus tu passes de temps sur Île Loco, plus ce paradis devient animé et passionnant ! Fais-toi plaisir dans cet espace personnel ultra-fun ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit diesem persönlichen Apartment hast du deine eigene Tropeninsel, die von LocoRoco™-Charakteren bevölkert ist. Dieses tropische Paradies bietet dir zahlreiche aufregende Aktivitäten. Sammle Nüsse ein, die von den Bäumen fallen. Sprich mit den Inselbewohnern, um deine Gebäude zu erweitern. Hab Spaß mit Schaukel, Rutsche, Jukebox und Spielen für zwei Spieler! Und je mehr Zeit du auf der Loco-Insel verbringst, desto lebendiger und aufregender wird dein Garten Eden! Verwöhne dich selbst und schenke dir dieses tolle persönliche Apartment![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo spazio personale è un'isola tropicale tutta tua, abitata dai simpatici LocoRoco™. Il rifugio tropicale è ricco di attività entusiasmanti. Colleziona i frutti che cadono dagli alberi e comunica con gli isolani per ampliare gli edifici. Divertiti con l'altalena, lo scivolo, il juke-box e giochi per due giocatori! Più tempo passi su Loco Island, più questo paradiso diventa vibrante e rigoglioso! Goditi questo ricchissimo spazio personale![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este espacio personal es tu propia isla tropical habitada por los personajes de LocoRoco™. El retiro tropical está a rebosar de actividades emocionantes. Recoge las nueces que caen de los árboles y comunícate con los isleños para ampliar las instalaciones. ¡Disfrutar con el columpio, el tobogán, el tocadiscos y los juegos para dos jugadores! ¡Y cuanto más tiempo pases en la Loco Isla, más vibrante y divertido será el paraíso! ¡Disfruta en este espacio personal repleto de diversión![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Loco Island</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Île Loco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Loco-Insel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Loco Island</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Loco Isla</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>