<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Washed Out Tee - Dark Blue (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - T-shirt Washed Out - Bleu foncé (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Washed Out T-Shirt - Dunkelblau (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Washed Out  T-shirt - Blu Scuro (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Washed Out Camiseta - Azul oscuro (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our regular fit Washed Out pocket tee will be one of your new favorites. Treated with a crystal wash, the rich colouring you see will stay that way without a trace of fading or shrinking. And you can be sure the art screen will stay pristine. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Notre T-shirt à poche coupe régulière Washed Out sera l'un de vos nouveaux favoris. Délavé avec la technique Crystal wash, la coloration riche que vous voyez durera, sans s'estomper ni rétrécir. Et vous pouvez être sûr que l'imprimé artistique restera immaculé. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unser Washed Out T-Shirt mit normaler Passform und Brusttasche wird unter Garantie Ihr neues Lieblings-T-Shirt! Das kristallgewaschene Baumwollhemd behält seine Form und lebhafte Farbe völlig unverändert auch nach vielen Wäschen bei, also kein Schrumpfen, Verwaschen oder Ausbleichen! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La T-shirt Washed Out con taglio regolare e taschino diventerà una delle tue preferite. Trattata con lavaggio ai cristalli, la ricca colorazione rimarrà invariata, senza scolorire o ritirarsi. Puoi star sicuro che la serigrafia rimarrà intatta. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nuestra camiseta Washed Out, de corte clásico y con bolsillos, se convertirá en una de tus favoritas. Tratada con una técnica especial de lavado, los vivos colores que ves permanecerán así, sin riesgo de que destiña o encoja. Y ten por seguro que el estampado permanecerá totalmente nítido. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Our regular fit Washed Out pocket tee will be one of your new favorites. Treated with a crystal wash, the rich coloring you see will stay that way without a trace of fading or shrinking. And you can be sure the art screen will stay pristine. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>