<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Yukata Bottom (Shishimai, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bas de Yukata (Shishimai, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Yukata-Unterteil (Shishimai, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Yukata parte inferiore (Shishimai, D)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Parte inferior de Yukata (Shishimai, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">浴衣・下（女性・獅子舞）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">유카타 하의(여성, 사자 춤)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Yukata Bottom (Women/Lion dance)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">日式浴衣 下 (女用／獅子舞）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">日式浴衣 下 (女用／獅子舞）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Yukata Bottom (Shishimai, F)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A single-layer kimono dyed a light pink, with a shishimai (lion dance) motif featured on the hem. This is only the bottom half, below the obi belt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un kimono composé d'une seule couche teint en rose clair et orné de motifs de shishimai (danse du lion). C'est seulement le bas, au-dessous de la ceinture obi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein einfacher, hellrosa eingefärbter Kimono aus Baumwolle mit einem Shishimai-Motiv (Löwentanz) auf dem Saum. Dies ist nur die untere Hälfte, die sich unterhalb des Obigürtels befindet.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un kimono leggero tinto in rosa pallido e decorato con uno Shishimai (leone cinese danzante). Solo la parte inferiore, dalla cintola (obi) in giù.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un kimono de algodón de una sola capa teñido de color rosa claro con un motivo shishimai (baile de león) en el dobladillo. Esto solo es la parte inferior, por debajo del cinturón obi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">淡いピンク色に染めた浴衣の裾に、獅子頭（ししがしら）が描かれている、ひとえの着物。帯から下の半身。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">희미한 분홍색에 물들인 유카타의 옷자락에 사자의 탈이 그려진 전통 복장. 허리띠 아래의 하의.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">An unlined kimono bottom with light pink dyed hemming and a lion head drawn on it.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在染成淺粉紅色的下擺印上獅子頭的一重和服。腰帶之下的下半身部份。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在染成淺粉紅色的下擺印上獅子頭的一重和服。腰帶之下的下半身部份。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A single-layer kimono dyed a light pink, with a shishimai (lion dance) motif featured on the hem. This is only the bottom half, below the obi belt.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>