<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">DataBot Jr.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">InfoDroïde Jr.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">DataBot Jr.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">DataBot Jr.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">DataBot Junior</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">データボットJr</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">데이터봇 주니어</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">DataBot Jr.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">小數據機械人</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">小數據機械人</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">DataBot Jr.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This highly-portable companion bot hovers over all terrain, following diligently as your faithful pal. It also fits into most overhead storage compartments. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce compagnon droïde ultra-portable peut se déplacer sur tous types de terrains. Tel un ami fidèle, il vous suivra partout où vous allez. Il pourra également être placé dans les compartiments de stockage supérieurs. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser enorm transportable Gefährte schwebt über sämtliche Untergründe und folgt Dir eifrig als treuer Kamerad. Er passt auch in die meisten Gepäckablagen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo robot ultra-leggero si muove su ogni tipo di terreno e ti seguirà diligentemente come un compagno fedele. Date le ridotte dimensioni può poi essere riposto nel portaoggetti del velivolo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este robot portátil planea sobre el terreno, siguiéndote con diligencia como un fiel compañero. También cabe en la mayoría de compartimentos de almacenamiento superiores. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この携帯式相棒ボットはあらゆる地形を移動でき、忠実な仲間としてどこまでも付いて来る。収納スペースにすんなりおさまるスグレモノ。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">매우 휴대성이 뛰어난 동료 로봇으로, 어떤 지형이라도 날아서 지나갈 수 있는 믿음직한 친구입니다. 대부분의 화물 칸에 알맞게 들어갑니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This highly-portable companion bot hovers over all terrain, following diligently as your faithful pal. It also fits into most overhead storage compartments. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這個非常便於攜帶的同伴機械人能在所有地面上盤旋，忠實的跟隨你，亦能放進大部分的上部儲物櫃。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這個非常便於攜帶的同伴機械人能在所有地面上盤旋，忠實的跟隨你，亦能放進大部分的上部儲物櫃。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This highly-portable companion bot hovers over all terrain, following diligently as your faithful pal. It also fits into most overhead storage compartments. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>