<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Sneaky Peaks Dress - Sweet Plum (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Robe Sneaky Peaks Prune (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Sneaky Peaks Kleid - Pflaumenblau (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Sneaky Peaks Vestito - Prugna Dolce (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Sneaky Peaks Vestido - Ciruela dulce (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Sneaky Peaks dress puts every fashionable detail out on display with multi tiers, tonal floral embroidery, and lacy surprises. What's more, a die cut embroidery creates a fabulous finish for the hem. The length hits above the knee. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La robe Sneaky Peaks met en valeur chaque détail à la mode avec ses niveaux multiples, son motif floral brodé et ses surprises en dentelle. En outre, une broderie matricée crée une finition fabuleuse pour l'ourlet. Elle tombe au-dessus du genou. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Sneaky Peaks Stufenkleid mit seinen farblich abgestimmten Blumenstickereien und überraschenden Spitzenverzierungen lässt kein modisches Detail ungenutzt. Ein besonderer Augenfang ist die wunderschöne Stanzstickerei am Saum. Überknielänge. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il vestito Sneaky Peaks mette in mostra ogni dettaglio trendy con vari strati di tessuto, ricami floreali tono su tono e dettagli in pizzo. In più, il ricamo sull'orlo inferiore crea una rifinitura favolosa. La lunghezza è sopra il ginocchio. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El vestido Sneaky Peaks despliega hasta el más mínimo detalle de elegancia con multicapas, bordado tonal de flores y encajes sorprendentes. Y lo que es más,  un volante de puntilla ofrece un acabado fabuloso al bajo. Llega hasta por encima de la rodilla. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>