<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Red Lightspeeder</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lightspeeder rouge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rote Lightspeeder</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lightspeeder rosso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lightspeeder rojo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Red Lightspeeder</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Red Lightspeeder</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Explore through PlayStation®Home in style, riding this slick animated motorcylce! The pulsating neon glows cycle through all different colours as well as varying in intensity. Zooming around, you'll hear the futuristic sound of your turbo engine, and a streak of light will stretch from your tail lights! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Explorez PlayStation®Home avec style, aux commandes de cette moto futuriste! Les lumières néon changent de couleur et varient en intensité. En accélérant, vous entendrez le son du turbo, et une trainée lumineuse s'étirera de vos phares arrières!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Entdecken Sie über PlayStation®Home in modernem Stil: fahren Sie dieses futuristische animierte Motorräder! Die pulsierende Neoneffekten durchlaufen alle Farben.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esplora PlayStation®Home con stile, con questa moto futuristica! Le luci al neon cambiano colore.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Explora PlayStation®Home con estilo, con esta moto futurista. Las luces de neón cambian de color.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Explore through PlayStation®Home in style, riding this slick animated motorcylce! The pulsating neon glows cycle through all different colors as well as varying in intensity. Zooming around, you'll hear the futuristic sound of your turbo engine, and a streak of light will stretch from your tail lights![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Explore through PlayStation®Home in style, riding this slick animated motorcylce! The pulsating neon glows cycle through all different colors as well as varying in intensity. Zooming around, you'll hear the futuristic sound of your turbo engine, and a streak of light will stretch from your tail lights![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>