<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Skimmer Assault Drone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Drone de combat des sables</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fliegende Angriffsdrohne</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Drone d'assalto Skimmer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Robot volador de asalto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スキマーアサルトドローン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">스키머 어설트 무인전투기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Skimmer Assault Drone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">水上攻擊機</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">水上攻擊機</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Skimmer Assault Drone</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">High speed and powerful front weaponry make this a dangerous opponent. Try to get behind it in the heat of battle and exploit its weak armour. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sa grande vitesse et ses puissantes armes de front font de lui un dangereux adversaire. Tentez de vous placer derrière lui en plein combat et exploitez la faiblesse de son armure. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hohe Geschwindigkeit und schlagkräftige Frontwaffen machen es zu einem gefährlichen Gegner. Versuche, in der Hitze des Gefechts hinter das Fahrzeug zu gelangen und seine schwache Panzerung auszunutzen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un avversario pericoloso, veloce e con un potente armamento frontale. Prova ad aggirarlo in battaglia per attaccare la debole corazza posteriore. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Su gran velocidad y su potente armamento frontal lo convierten en un adversario peligroso. Intenta acercarte por detrás en el fervor de la batalla y destruir su delicada armadura. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">高スピードで強力な前線用敵機。かなり危険で手ごわいので、後方に回り弱点を突くのだ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">빠른 속도와 강력한 전면 무기를 자랑하는 위험한 적입니다. 전투 중에는 비교적 얇은 후미의 장갑을 노려 보십시오. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">High speed and powerful front weaponry make this a dangerous opponent. Try to get behind it in the heat of battle and exploit its weak armour. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">速度快，威力強的前端武器使之成為一個危險的對手。嘗試在激戰中繞到它身後，爆破它的裝甲薄弱部分。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">速度快，威力強的前端武器使之成為一個危險的對手。嘗試在激戰中繞到它身後，爆破它的裝甲薄弱部分。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">High speed and powerful front weaponry make this a dangerous opponent. Try to get behind it in the heat of battle and exploit its weak armor. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>