<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rocket Boots (Male and Female) Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble de bottes fusées (homme et femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Raketenstiefel-Bundle (Herren und Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ensemble de bottes fusées (homme et femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de botas espaciales (masculinas y femeninas)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rocket Boots (Male and Female) Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rock these stylish robotic boots from the MiniBots game. BONUS: unlocks the Rocket Boot gadget for use in  MiniBots: Battlebox and in MiniBots multiplayer. Death from above! (Bundle includes both male and female versions.) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Faites chauffer ces bottes robotiques très chic du jeu MiniBots. BONUS : déverrouille le gadget Botte fusée utilisable dans MiniBots : Battlebox et dans MiniBots multijoueur. La mort viendra du ciel ! (L'ensemble inclut les versions homme et femme.) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Welt liegt Ihnen zu Füßen – mit diesen eleganten Roboterstiefeln aus dem MiniBots-Spiel. BONUS: Schaltet das Raketenstiefel-Gadget für die Anwendung in MiniBots: Battlebox frei und MiniBots-Multiplayer-Modus frei.. Der Tod kommt von oben! (Das Bundle enthält sowohl die Herren- als auch die Damenstiefel.)  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scopri questi eleganti stivali robotizzati per MiniBot. BONUS: sblocca il gadget Stivali razzo per usarlo in MiniBots: Battlebox e modalità multigiocatore di MiniBots.. Morte dall'alto! (Il pacchetto include modelli sia da uomo che da donna.) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Presume con tus estilosas botas espaciales del juego MiniBots. BONUS:  libera el dispositivo Bota espacial para utilizarlo en MiniBots: Battlebox y el modo varios jugadores de MiniBots. ¡Muerte desde arriba! (El paquete incluye versiones tanto masculina como femenina). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rock these stylish robotic boots from the MiniBots game. BONUS: unlocks the Rocket Boot gadget for use in  MiniBots: Battlebox and in MiniBots multiplayer. Death from above! (Bundle includes both male and female versions.) [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>