<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Milton the Lockwood Lion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Milton le lion de Lockwood</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Milton der Lockwood-Löwe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Milton il leone di Lockwood</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Milton el león de Lockwood</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Lockwoodライオン　ミルトン君</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Lockwood 마스코트 - 밀튼</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Milton the Lockwood Lion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Lockwood獅隊：米爾頓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Lockwood獅隊：米爾頓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Milton the Lockwood Lion</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Every great sports team needs a great mascot and Milton is the one who's always there for the Lockwood Lions, cheering them on. He'd be only too happy to give you some moral support too. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaque équipe de sport a besoin d'une super mascotte et Milton est celle qui est toujours là pour encourager les Lions de Lockwood. Il serait heureux de vous apporter un peu de soutien moral. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jedes gute Team braucht ein gutes Maskottchen und Milton ist derjenige, der immer für die Lockwood Lions da ist und sie anfeuert. Er würde nur zu gern auch dich unterstützen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ogni grande squadra, qualunque sia lo sport, ha una mascotte e Milton è sempre lì per supportare i Lockwood Lions. Sarebbe felicissimo di dare anche a te un po' di supporto morale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cualquier equipo de deportes que se precie necesita tener una buena mascota y Milton siempre está ahí para los Lockwood Lions, animándoles sin parar. Le encantaría que tú también le dieras un poco de apoyo moral. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">全てのスポーツチームにマスコットキャラは必須です。Lockwoodライオンにはいつもミルトン君が付いています！彼は皆さんをサポートするのが大好き！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">모든 뛰어난 스포츠 팀에는 그에 걸맞는 마스코트가 필요합니다. 밀튼은 언제나 Lockwood를 위해 대기 중이며, 필요할 때마다 격려를 아끼지 않습니다. 당신을 위해서도 열심히 응원해 줄 겁니다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Every great sports team needs a great mascot and Milton is the one who's always there for the Lockwood Lions, cheering them on. He'd be only too happy to give you some moral support too. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">每個偉大的球隊都要有偉大的吉祥物。米爾頓總是不離不棄，為Lockwood獅隊加油到底。他也一定願意給你道義上的支持。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">每個偉大的球隊都要有偉大的吉祥物。米爾頓總是不離不棄，為Lockwood獅隊加油到底。他也一定願意給你道義上的支持。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Every great sports team needs a great mascot and Milton is the one who's always there for the Lockwood Lions, cheering them on. He'd be only too happy to give you some moral support too. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>