<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Khul Mercali Primeval Blade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Épée primitive Khul Mercali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Khul-Mercali-Urzeitklinge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Spada primordiale di Khul Mercali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Espada primigenia de Khul Mercali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Khul Mercali Primeval Blade</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Built for close-quarters combat style of a Mercian Fighter.\n\nThe ancient weapon  of the  warriors of the primeval jungles where great beasts leap through the trees and ancient lizards slither through the undergrowth.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Conçu pour le style de combat rapproché du guerrier mercian.\n\nL'ancienne arme des guerriers issus des jungles primitives où les grands fauves bondissaient entre les arbres et où les anciens lézards se faufilaient dans les broussailles.\n\nDÉBLOQUE DES ARTICLES DU JEU MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS – N'OFFRE PAS DE COMPOSANTS D'AVATAR POUR UN USAGE GÉNÉRAL SUR PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBLE POUR LES UTILISATEURS DU JAPON ET DE L'ASIE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Speziell auf den Nahkampf-Stil der Mercia-Kämpfer ausgelegt.\n\nDie klassische Waffe der Krieger aus den Dschungeln der Urzeit, wo riesige Monster in den Bäumen und urzeitliche Echsen im Dickicht lauern.\n\nZUM FREISCHALTEN VON GEGENSTÄNDEN IN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS - NICHT ZUM ERHALT VON AVATAR-KOMPONENTEN ZUR ALLGEMEINEN NUTZUNG AUF PLAYSTATION®HOME. NICHT VERFÜGBAR FÜR BENUTZER IN JAPAN UND ASIEN [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Perfetta per il combattimento corpo a corpo del guerriero Mercian.\n\nL'antica arma dei guerrieri delle giungle primordiali dove grandi bestie balzano tra gli alberi e antichi rettili strisciano nel sottobosco.\n\nSBLOCCA OGGETTI ALL'INTERNO DEL GIOCO MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS. NON REGALA COMPONENTI PER AVATAR PER USO GENERICO CON PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBILE PER GLI UTENTI IN ASIA E GIAPPONE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Creada para el estilo de combate cuerpo a cuerpo de un luchador de Mercia.\n\nLa antigua arma de los guerreros de las junglas primigenias donde enormes bestias saltan por los árboles y antiguos lagartos se deslizan por entre la maleza.\n\nDESBLOQUEARÁ ELEMENTOS EN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS GAME. NO REGALARÁ COMPONENTES DE AVATAR PARA EL USO GENERAL EN CASA DE PLAYSTATION. NO DISPONIBLE PARA LOS USUARIOS DE JAPÓN Y ASIA. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Built for close-quarters combat style of a Mercian Fighter.\n\nThe ancient weapon  of the  warriors of the primeval jungles where great beasts leap through the trees and ancient lizards slither through the undergrowth.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>