<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Paintball Gun and Gloves - Green (for Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pistolet et gants de paintball - Vert (pour Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Paintball-Kanone und -Handschuhe – Grün (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pistola e guanti da paintball - verde (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pistola y guantes de paintball; verde (para hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">페인트볼 건과 장갑 - 녹색 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Paintball Gun and Gloves - Green (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">漆彈槍與手套：綠（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">漆彈槍與手套：綠（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Paintball Gun and Gloves - Green (for Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If you send this to your friends, you have to warn them. The paintballs are flying, run, RUUUUUNNNNNNNN!!!! \n\n Created by Double Time – Play to Win, Play Double Time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si vous envoyez cela à vos amis, vous devez les avertir. Les boules de peintures fusent, courrez, COURREEEEZ !!! \n\n Créé par Double Time – Jouez pour Gagner, Jouez avec Double Time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn du deinen Freunden das sendest, musst du sie warnen. Die Paintballs fliegen, lauft weg, LAAAAAUUUUUUUUFT!!!! \n\n Entwickelt von Double Time – Spiele auf Sieg, Setze auf Double Time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se le invii ai tuo amici, non dimenticare di avvertirli. Attento alle paintball, corri, COOORRRIIIII!!!\n\n Una creazione Double Time – Gioca per vincere, gioca con Double Time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Antes de enviarle este regalo a tus amigos, adviérteles para que no acaben pringados en pintura.\n\n Un producto de Double Time, equipamiento para divertirte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 아이템을 보낼 때는 먼저 경고를 해 주십시오. 페인트볼이 날아 다니니까, 피하라구요.\n\n  Double Time 제작 - 승리를 위한 플레이, 플레이 Double Time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">If you send this to your friends, you have to warn them. The paintballs are flying, run, RUUUUUNNNNNNNN!!!! \n\n Created by Double Time – Play to Win, Play Double Time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">送這個給朋友時別忘了警告他們。漆彈可是用飛的，快跑啊！\n\n
Double Time榮譽出品：勝利精品，就在Double Time。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">送這個給朋友時別忘了警告他們。漆彈可是用飛的，快跑啊！\n\n
Double Time榮譽出品：勝利精品，就在Double Time。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">If you send this to your friends, you have to warn them. The paintballs are flying, run, RUUUUUNNNNNNNN!!!! \n\n Created by Double Time – Play to Win, Play Double Time. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>