<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nightlife Lounge Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Salon vie nocturne clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nightlife-Lounge: Clubhaus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sede del club Locale notturno</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sede del club Sala nocturna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Nightlife Lounge Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">밤의 생활 라운지 클럽하우스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Nightlife Lounge Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">夜生活休息室聯盟俱樂部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">夜生活休息室聯盟俱樂部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Nightlife Lounge Clubhouse</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Spend a night out on the town in your very own Nightlife Lounge. Inside, you can wine and dine your guests as they walk down the fashion runway inside. Get cozy and have a drink in the lounge area.  Are you ready to party?  The Nightlife Lounge is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Passez une nuit sur la ville dans votre Salon vie nocturne très propre. A l'intérieur, vous pouvez vin et dîner à vos invités comme ils marchent sur la piste de la mode à l'intérieur. Vous confortablement et prendre un verre dans le salon. Puis passer le reste de la nuit sur la piste de danse éclairée poing de pompage pour le DJ au deuxième étage. Êtes-vous prêt à faire la fête? Le Salon vie nocturne est un club où tout le monde est invité à se joindre. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verbringe mit deiner eigenen Nightlife-Lounge einen Abend in der Stadt. Drinnen kannst du deine Gäste zum Essen einladen, während sie über den Laufsteg laufen. Mach es dir gemütlich und trinke etwas in der Lounge. Kann die Party losgehen? Die Nightlife-Lounge ist ein Clubhaus, in dem jeder Gast willkommen ist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Passa una notte in giro per la città nel tuo personale Locale notturno. Al suo interno puoi viziare per bene i tuoi ospiti mentre camminano per la passerella. Mettiti comodo e prendi una bevanda nella sala centrale. Sei pronto per la festa? Il Locale notturno è una sede del club dove chiunque è il benvenuto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pasa una noche en la ciudad, en tu propia sala nocturna. Dentro puedes servir vino y la cena a tus invitados cuando atraviesen la pasarela de moda. Ponte cómodo y tómate algo de beber en la zona de relax. ¿Listo para ir de fiesta? La Sala nocturna es una sede del club a la que todos están invitados. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Spend a night out on the town in your very own Nightlife Lounge. Inside, you can wine and dine your guests as they walk down the fashion runway inside. Get cozy and have a drink in the lounge area. Then spend the rest of the night on the lighted dance floor fist pumping to the DJ on the second floor. Are you ready to party? The Nightlife Lounge is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">여러분 소유의 밤의 생활 라운지에서 하룻 밤을 맘껏 즐겨보세요. 안에는 손님들이 런웨이에서 자신의 패션을 자랑하는 동안, 실컷 먹고 마실 수 있습니다. 안락한 장소를 찾아서 뭐라도 한잔 드세요. 파티에 참석할 준비가 되셨나요? 밤의 생활 라운지는 모두가 환영받는 클럽하우스입니다. ※주의: 클럽하우스에 입장하려면 먼저 클럽을 구매해야 합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Spend a night out on the town in your very own Nightlife Lounge. Inside, you can wine and dine your guests as they walk down the fashion runway inside. Get cozy and have a drink in the lounge area.  Are you ready to party?  The Nightlife Lounge is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. ※Please note, in order to access the clubhouse you will need to have purchased the Club Slot. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在屬於你的夜生活休息室裡享受城中一夜。在這裡，你可以邀請賓客沿著時裝跑道走進休息室，享受美酒佳餚，並在休息區舉杯放鬆。準備好開派對沒有？夜生活休息室是一個歡迎任何人加入的聯盟俱樂部。※請注意，要使用聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在屬於你的夜生活休息室裡享受城中一夜。在這裡，你可以邀請賓客沿著時裝跑道走進休息室，享受美酒佳餚，並在休息區舉杯放鬆。準備好開派對沒有？夜生活休息室是一個歡迎任何人加入的聯盟俱樂部。※請注意，要使用聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Spend a night out on the town in your very own Nightlife Lounge. Inside, you can wine and dine your guests as they walk down the fashion runway inside. Get cozy and have a drink in the lounge area. Then spend the rest of the night on the lighted dance floor fist pumping to the DJ on the second floor. Are you ready to party? The Nightlife Lounge is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>