<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Bar Key</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La clé du bar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Barschlüssel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La chiave del bar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La llave del bar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">バーのカギ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">바의 열쇠</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Bar Key</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">酒吧鑰匙</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">酒吧鑰匙</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Bar Key</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Purchase this key to unlock the Bar area in Darla's Den (the free personal space you get when entering The Midway).  This includes access to the original arcade game Trigger Happy In-A-Box and your very own free-to-play Bell Ringer! The price of this item is reduced If you already own Trigger Happy In-A-Box. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Achetez cette clé pour ouvrir l'espace bar dans Darla's Den (l'espace personnel gratuit que vous obtenez en accédant à The Midway). Sont aussi inclus le jeu d'arcade original Trigger Happy In-A-Box et votre Bell Ringer rien qu'à vous ! Si vous possédez déjà Trigger Happy In-A-Box, vous bénéficierez d'une remise sur cet article. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kaufen Sie diesen Schlüssel, um den Barbereich in Darla's Den (dem kostenlosen persönlichen Apartment, das Sie erhalten, wenn Sie "The Midway" betreten) aufzuschließen. Enthält außerdem das ursprüngliche Arkade-Spiel "Trigger Happy In-A-Box" und Ihren eigenen kostenlosen Hau-den-Lukas! Besitzer von Trigger Happy In-A-Box erhalten diesen Artikel zum Sonderpreis. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Compra questa chiave per aprire lo spazio del bar nel Darla's Den (lo spazio libero personale quando si entra in Midway). Questo include l'accesso al gioco Trigger Happy In-A-Box ed il tuo Bell Ringer gratuito! Questo oggetto costa meno se hai già Trigger Happy In-A-Box. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Compra esta llave para desbloquear la zona del bar en Darla´s Den (el espacio personal gratuito que obtienes al entrar en The Midway). ¡Esto incluye el acceso al juego de arcade original Trigger Happy In-A-Box y tu propia versión gratuita de Bell Ringer! Este artículo tiene precio reducido si ya tienes Trigger Happy In-A-Box. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ダーラの部屋（アメリカン・カーニバルに入場すると手に入るパーソナルスペース）の中にあるバーで仕切られたエリアに入ることが出来るようになるカギです。\nバーで仕切られたエリアには、「Trigger Happy」アーケード版筐体と、「Bell Ringer」の無料版を楽しむことができます。\nすでに、「Trigger Happy」アーケード版筐体を所有している場合は、値引き価格で購入することができます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 열쇠를 구입하시면 달라의 보금자리에 있는 바를 해제할 수 있습니다. 달라의 보금자리는 The Midway에 입장하면 무료로 얻을 수 있는 퍼스널 스페이스입니다. 오리지널 아케이드 게임인 상자 속의 트리거 해피를 플레이할 수 있으며, 벨 울리기 게임 또한 무료로 제공됩니다. 이미 상자 속의 트리거 해피 게임을 소유하고 있다면 해당 아이템의 가격이 할인됩니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Purchase this key to unlock the Bar area in Darla's Den (the free personal space you get when entering The Midway).  This includes access to the original arcade game Trigger Happy In-A-Box and your very own free-to-play Bell Ringer! The price of this item is reduced If you already own Trigger Happy In-A-Box. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">購買此鑰匙可解放「達拉之家」的酒吧區域 (「達拉之家」是進入Midway時獲得的免費個人空間)。 您可以在這玩到原創大型機台遊戲「箱型版歡樂神槍手」，以及免費玩到您個人的「敲鐘人」！若您已經擁有「箱型版歡樂神槍手」，此商品價格便會下降。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">購買此鑰匙可解放「達拉之家」的酒吧區域 (「達拉之家」是進入Midway時獲得的免費個人空間)。 您可以在這玩到原創大型機台遊戲「箱型版歡樂神槍手」，以及免費玩到您個人的「敲鐘人」！若您已經擁有「箱型版歡樂神槍手」，此商品價格便會下降。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Purchase this key to unlock the Bar area in Darla's Den (the free personal space you get when entering The Midway).  This includes access to the original arcade game Trigger Happy In-A-Box and your very own free-to-play Bell Ringer! The price of this item is reduced If you already own Trigger Happy In-A-Box. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>