<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Paradise at Sea Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Paradis sur mer appartement</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Meeresparadies: Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Appartamento Paradiso al mare</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apartamento Paraíso en el mar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Paradise at Sea Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">바다의 파라다이스 아파트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Paradise at Sea Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">海上樂園公寓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">海上樂園公寓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Paradise at Sea Apartment</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Explore the seven seas in style aboard the grandiose Paradise at Sea Apartment. With both a pool and hot tub located at the bow of the ship, you’ll never tire of the soft summer rays giving you that perfect tan. Better yet, grab a drink at the bar inside and enjoy the day from the comfort of your own window side booth. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Découvrez les sept mers dans un style à bord du grandioses en Paradis sur mer clubhouse. Avec une piscine et un jacuzzi situé à la proue du navire, vous ne vous lasserez jamais de l'été, les rayons mous qui vous donne un bronzage parfait. Mieux encore, prenez un verre au bar à l'intérieur et profiter de la journée dans le confort de votre stand fenêtre de côté. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erforsche die sieben Weltmeere an Bord des grandiosen Meeresparadies-Apartments mit Stil. Ein Swimmingpool und ein Whirlpool am Bug des Schiffs sorgen dafür, dass du nie genug von der sanften Sommersonne bekommst, die dir zur perfekten Bräune verhilft. Es wird noch besser: Du kannst drinnen an der Bar etwas trinken und den Tag in deiner eigenen Kabine mit Fenster genießen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esplora i sette mari con stile a bordo della grandiosa Sede del club Paradiso al mare. Con una piscina e una vasca idromassaggio a prua, non sarai mai stanco dei leggeri raggi solari estivi che perfezioneranno la tua abbronzatura. Ancora meglio, prendi una bevanda al bar che c'è dentro, e goditi la giornata dall'oblò della tua confortevole camera. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Explora los siete mares con estilo a bordo del grandioso apartamento Paraíso en el mar. Con piscina y bañera de hidromasaje en la proa del barco, nunca te cansarás de los rayos veraniegos del sol proporcionándote un bronceado perfecto. Y lo que es mejor, podrás tomar una bebida en el bar interior y disfrutar del día en tu mesa con ventana al lado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Explore the seven seas in style aboard the grandiose Paradise at Sea Apartment. With both a pool and hot tub located at the bow of the ship, you’ll never tire of the soft summer rays giving you that perfect tan. Better yet, grab a drink at the bar inside and enjoy the day from the comfort of your own window side booth. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">웅장한 바다의 파라다이스에 탑승하고 7대양을 우아하게 탐험하세요. 뱃머리에 수영장과 욕조까지 완비한 이 선박에서는, 여러분께 완벽한 태닝을 제공하는 따듯한 여름 태양이 지겹지 않습니다. 그리고 여러분은 실내 바에서 음료를 준비하고, 창가 쪽 부스에서 즐길 수도 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Explore the seven seas in style aboard the grandiose Paradise at Sea Apartment. With both a pool and hot tub located at the bow of the ship, you’ll never tire of the soft summer rays giving you that perfect tan. Better yet, grab a drink at the bar inside and enjoy the day from the comfort of your own window side booth. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在壯觀的海上樂園裡進行海洋探險。船頭設有泳池及熱水浴池，讓你盡情在柔和的夏日陽光下曬一身漂亮的古銅色。更棒的是在室內酒吧喝一杯，在你的窗邊特別座享受美好時光。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在壯觀的海上樂園裡進行海洋探險。船頭設有泳池及熱水浴池，讓你盡情在柔和的夏日陽光下曬一身漂亮的古銅色。更棒的是在室內酒吧喝一杯，在你的窗邊特別座享受美好時光。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Explore the seven seas in style aboard the grandiose Paradise at Sea Apartment. With both a pool and hot tub located at the bow of the ship, you’ll never tire of the soft summer rays giving you that perfect tan. Better yet, grab a drink at the bar inside and enjoy the day from the comfort of your own window side booth. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>