<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Nis_Dots_No029</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Personnage 2D: Celestial Host</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドットオブジェ　絶対なる善　天使兵</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">도트 오브제 절대선 천사병</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Absolute Justice Celestial Host" Sprite Statue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">像素雕像　絕對的善　天使兵</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">像素雕像　絕對的善　天使兵</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">2D Character Objects: Celestial Host</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nis_dot_No029</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Untitled</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La statuette d'un personnage que tu peux mettre dans ta chambre pour décorer.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">天界と天使を守護、そして天使の絶対的な善を迷うことなく貫き通す天の兵士がドットオブジェで降臨。天使の中でも戦闘に秀でた者しか天使兵にはなれない。見た目の柔和さとは異なり、天界に逆らう者はすべて排除するという信念の元に行動をする。一概に感情の起伏が乏しいとされるのは戦いに身を投じた代償なのか―。神々しさを称える静穏なドットオブジェ。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A small character statue that you can place to decorate your own room.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">천계와 천사를 수호, 그리고 천사들의 절대적인 선을 행하는 하늘의 병사가 도트 오브제로 강림. 천사들 중에서도 전투에 뛰어난 사람만이 천사병으로 선발된다. 외형의 온화함과는 달리, 천계에 거역하는 자는 모두 처단한다는 신념을 바탕으로 행동. 감정이 메말라다는 말을 듣는 것도 싸움에 몸을 던졌기 때문인가... 신들의 평온을 위한 도트 오브제.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Celestial Host sprite statue finally arrives on PlayStation®Home! Celestial Hosts are the guardians of the celestial world and they embody all that is righteous. Only the toughest fighters among Celestia can become Celestial Hosts. Despite their gentle appearance, they show no mercy on the battlefield. This sprite statue illustrates the divine serenity of a fighter who devotes himself to defending the celestial world. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">守護天界與天使，並會毫不猶豫貫徹天使主張的「絕對的善」信念的天界士兵化身為像素雕像降臨了。在天使當中，也必須是特別擅長戰鬥的才能成為天使兵。雖然天使兵看似溫和，但卻以排除所有違抗天界的人、事、物為信念行動。缺乏所有情緒起伏，也許是他們投身於戰鬥中所付出的代價吧。這是一尊在沉靜中散發出神性氣質的像素雕像。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">守護天界與天使，並會毫不猶豫貫徹天使主張的「絕對的善」信念的天界士兵化身為像素雕像降臨了。在天使當中，也必須是特別擅長戰鬥的才能成為天使兵。雖然天使兵看似溫和，但卻以排除所有違抗天界的人、事、物為信念行動。缺乏所有情緒起伏，也許是他們投身於戰鬥中所付出的代價吧。這是一尊在沉靜中散發出神性氣質的像素雕像。[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>