<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Lion House Furniture Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Lion Maison paquet de meubles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Löwenhaus Möbel-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Casa Leone pacchetto mobili</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Casa León paquete de muebles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ライオンハウス家具を詰める</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">라이온 하우스 가구를 싸</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Lion House Furniture Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">包狮子屋家具</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">包狮子屋家具</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Lion House Furniture Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A loyal banner-man of House Raleigh should own all of the finely crafted furniture pertaining to that house. It's basic respect. Or you just like the color palette! Includes House Raleigh Throne, House Raleigh Ottoman, House Raleigh Circular Coffee Table, House Raleigh Rectangular Coffee Table, House Raleigh Grand Vase, House Raleigh Daybed, House Raleigh King Bed, House Raleigh Grand Chair, House Raleigh Chair, House Raleigh Loveseat, House Raleigh Grand Dining Chair, House Raleigh Dining Chair, House Raleigh Wardrobe, and House Raleigh Shield.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un fidèle porte-bannière de la Maison de Raleigh doit posséder tous les meubles de belle facture se rapportant à cette maison. C'est le respect fondamental. Ou vous aimez tout simplement la palette de couleurs! Maison Raleigh Trône, Maison Raleigh pouf, Maison Raleigh table à café circulaire, Maison Raleigh table à café rectangulaire, Maison Raleigh grande vase, Maison Raleigh Méridienne, Maison Raleigh roi lit, Maison Raleigh chaise grande, Maison Raleigh chaise, Maison Raleigh petit canapé, Maison Raleigh chaise dinante, Grand
Maison Raleigh chaise dinante, Maison Raleigh Armoire, et Maison Raleigh Bouclier.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein treuer Bannerträger des House of Raleigh müssen alle Möbel, schön gemacht im Zusammenhang mit diesem Haus. Dies ist der grundlegende Respekt. Liebe oder einfach nur die Farbe! Haus Raleigh Thron, Haus Raleigh Ottomane, Haus Raleigh kreisförmigen Couchtisch, Haus Raleigh rechteckiger Couchtisch, Haus Raleigh große Vase, Haus Raleigh Schlafcouch, Haus Raleigh Königs Bett, Haus Raleigh großartigen Stuhl, Haus Raleigh Stuhl, Haus Raleigh kleines Sofa, Haus Raleigh großen Speisesaal Stuhl, Haus Raleigh Speisesaal Stuhl, Haus Raleigh Schrank, und Haus Raleigh Wappenschild.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un fedele alfiere della casa di Raleigh deve avere tutti i mobili, ben fatto appartenenti a questa casa. Questo è il rispetto fondamentale. O semplicemente ama il colore! Casa Raleigh Trono, Casa Raleigh pouf, Casa Raleigh circolare tavolino, Casa Raleigh tavolino rettangolare, Casa Raleigh grande vaso, Casa Raleigh divanoletto, Casa Raleigh letto del re, Casa Raleigh grande sedia, Casa Raleigh sedia, Casa Raleigh piccolo divano, Casa Raleigh gran pranzo sedia, Casa Raleigh pranzo sedia, Casa Raleigh armadio, e Casa Raleigh scudo.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un fiel estandarte de la Cámara de Raleigh debe tener todos los muebles, muy bien hecho concernientes a esta casa. Este es el aspecto fundamental. O me encanta el color! Casa Raleigh Trono, Casa Raleigh otomana, Casa Raleigh mesa de café circular, Casa Raleigh mesa de café rectangular, Casa Raleigh de gran jarrón, Casa Raleigh sofá cama, Casa Raleigh la cama del rey, Casa Raleigh gran silla, Casa Raleigh silla, Casa Raleigh pequeño sofá, Casa Raleigh gran silla de comedor, Casa Raleigh silla de comedor, Casa Raleigh armario, y Casa Raleigh escudo.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ハウスローリーの忠実なバナー男はその家に関連する精巧な家具のすべてを所有する必要があります。これは、基本的な敬意です。または、カラーパレットを単に好きです！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">하우스 롤리의 충성도 배너 - 사람이 그 집에 관련된 잘게 만들어진 가구를 모두 소유해야합니다. 그것은 기본 예의입니다. 또는 색상 팔레트를 똑같아![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A loyal banner-man of House Raleigh should own all of the finely crafted furniture pertaining to that house. It's basic respect. Or you just like the color palette! Includes House Raleigh Throne, House Raleigh Ottoman, House Raleigh Circular Coffee Table, House Raleigh Rectangular Coffee Table, House Raleigh Grand Vase, House Raleigh Daybed, House Raleigh King Bed, House Raleigh Grand Chair, House Raleigh Chair, House Raleigh Loveseat, House Raleigh Grand Dining Chair, House Raleigh Dining Chair, House Raleigh Wardrobe, and House Raleigh Shield.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">一位忠诚的旗帜内务罗利人应该拥有的所有有关那家精心制作的家具。这是基本的尊重。或者你只是想调色板！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">一位忠诚的旗帜内务罗利人应该拥有的所有有关那家精心制作的家具。这是基本的尊重。或者你只是想调色板！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A loyal banner-man of House Raleigh should own all of the finely crafted furniture pertaining to that house. It's basic respect. Or you just like the color palette! Includes House Raleigh Throne, House Raleigh Ottoman, House Raleigh Circular Coffee Table, House Raleigh Rectangular Coffee Table, House Raleigh Grand Vase, House Raleigh Daybed, House Raleigh King Bed, House Raleigh Grand Chair, House Raleigh Chair, House Raleigh Loveseat, House Raleigh Grand Dining Chair, House Raleigh Dining Chair, House Raleigh Wardrobe, and House Raleigh Shield.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>