<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Tree peony ikebana 2-piece set</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de 2 pièces d'ikebana de pivoines</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">2-teiliges Set von Pfingsrosen-Ikebana</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set 2 ikebana con peonie</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos artículos de ikebana de peonías</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ボタンの生け花２点セット</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Tree peony ikebana 2-piece set</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 2-piece set that includes peonies arranged in bamboo and ceramic vases.\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Bamboo vase with peony arrangement (Decoration)\n- Ceramic vase with peony arrangement (Decoration)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 2 pièces qui inclut des pivoines arrangées dans des vases en bambou et en céramique.\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Vase de bambou avec un arrangement de pivoines (décoration)\n- Vase en céramique avec un arrangement de pivoines (décoration)\n\n* Après achat, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 2-teiliges Set, das Pfingstrosen-Blumenarrangements in einer Bambusvase und einer Keramikvase enthält.\nDieses Set enthält die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Bambusvase mit Pfingstrosen-Blumenarrangement (Dekoration)\n- Keramikvase mit Pfingstrosen-Blumenarrangement (Dekoration)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set composto da 2 elementi comprendente delle peonie disposte in un vaso di bambù e in un vaso di ceramica.\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Vaso di bambù con composizione di peonie (decorazione)\n- Vaso di ceramica con composizione di peonie (decorazione)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettiva categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos artículos que incluye arreglos de peonías en jarrones de bambú y cerámica.\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Jarrón de bambú con un arreglo de peonías (adorno)\n- Jarrón de cerámica con un arreglo de peonías (adorno)\n\n*Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ボタンの花の、竹の器に生けたものと陶器に生けたものの２点セット。\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・竹の器に生けたボタン/装飾品\n・陶器に生けたボタン/装飾品\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 2-piece set that includes peonies arranged in bamboo and ceramic vases.\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Bamboo vase with peony arrangement (Decoration)\n- Ceramic vase with peony arrangement (Decoration)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
