<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">WipEout® Modes Hologram Viewer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">WipEout® Modes Hologram Viewer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Afficheur holographique de modes de WipEout®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Holografischer WipEout®-Modus-Betrachter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Visualizzatore ologramma delle modalità di WipEout®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Visor holográfico de modos de WipEout®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">WipEout® 게임 모드 홀로그램 뷰어</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">WipEout® Modes Hologram Viewer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">WipEout®模式瀏覽器</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">WipEout®模式瀏覽器</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SINGLE_RACE_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Single Race: the core of all WipEout® HD competitions, the single race sees 8 teams battle it out over a single location, with or without weapons, for the glory of taking first place and the coveted gold medal.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Course unique : l'essence de toute compétition de WipEout® HD. En Course unique, 8 écuries s'affrontent sur un lieu unique, avec ou sans armes, pour récolter les honneurs de la victoire et remporter la médaille d'or.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Einzelrennen: Das Herz jedes „WipEout® HD"-Wettbewerbs. Im Einzelrennen treten acht Teams an einem einzigen Standort gegeneinander an, um den Ruhm des Sieges und eine Goldmedaille zu erringen – mit oder ohne Waffen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gara singola: anima di tutte le competizioni di WipEout® HD, la Gara singola vede 8 scuderie darsi battaglia su di un singolo tracciato, con o senza armi, per la gloria del primo posto e l'agognata medaglia d'oro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Carrera individual: esta es la base de todas las competiciones de WipEout® HD: una carrera en la que se enfrentan ocho equipos en un mismo circuito, con armas o sin ellas, y con el único objetivo de obtener el primer puesto y conseguir la ansiada medalla de oro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">シングルレース：WipEout® HD の核となるレースです。アイテムを「使用する／しない」に関係なく、全８チームがゴールドメダルの栄冠を求めてしのぎを削り合います。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">싱글 레이스: WipEout® HD 레이싱의 기본을 이루는 모드입니다. 8개의 팀이 하나의 트랙에서 경쟁을 펼치며, 일등에게 수여되는 금메달을 위해 달립니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Single Race: the core of all WipEout® HD competitions, the single race sees 8 teams battle it out over a single location, with or without weapons, for the glory of taking first place and the coveted gold medal.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Single Race(單人競賽)：所有「WipEout® HD」比賽的主要模式，在此模式中是由8個小隊在同一個賽道上競爭第一名的榮耀以及大家盼望的金牌，在此可以設定使用武器或不使用武器。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Single Race(單人競賽)：所有「WipEout® HD」比賽的主要模式，在此模式中是由8個小隊在同一個賽道上競爭第一名的榮耀以及大家盼望的金牌，在此可以設定使用武器或不使用武器。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Single Race: the core of all WipEout® HD competitions, the single race sees 8 teams battle it out over a single location, with or without weapons, for the glory of taking first place and the coveted gold medal.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TOURNAMENT_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tournament: this multiple-race competition awards points after each race based on finishing position. If your tally is high enough at the end of the tournament, then you've rightfully earned your gold medal.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tournoi : Une série de courses uniques à l'issue desquelles des points sont attribués en fonction de votre position. Si la somme de vos points est suffisamment élevée, vous remporterez peut-être la médaille d'or.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Turnier: In diesem Wettbewerb über mehrere Rennen erhält man je nach Platzierung eine bestimmte Punktzahl. Warst du am Ende des Wettbewerbs stark genug, hast du dir deine Goldmedaille redlich verdient.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Torneo: competizione multievento che conferisce punti alla fine di ogni gara sulla base del piazzamento ottenuto. Se al termine del torneo il tuo punteggio è sufficientemente elevato, ti verrà assegnata la medaglia d'oro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Torneo: esta competición consta de varias carreras en las que ganarás puntos según la posición que obtengas en cada carrera. Si consigues suficientes puntos al final del torneo, podrás hacerte con la medalla de oro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">トーナメント：複数のレースを連戦して合計ポイントを競い合います。前のレースの順位が次のレースのスタート位置となります。トーナメントでのゴールドメダルの味は格別です。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">토너먼트: 다수의 레이스로 구성된 토너먼트는 각 레이스의 종료 후 점수를 부여합니다. 토너먼트 종료 시점에서 가장 높은 점수를 받았다면 금메달의 주인이 됩니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Tournament: this multiple-race competition awards points after each race based on finishing position. If your tally is high enough at the end of the tournament, then you've rightfully earned your gold medal.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Tournament(錦標賽)：這個由多場競賽所構成的比賽會在每一場比賽結束時以名次決定獲得的分數。如果您的成績在錦標賽結束時夠高，那您就可以獲得屬於您的金牌。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Tournament(錦標賽)：這個由多場競賽所構成的比賽會在每一場比賽結束時以名次決定獲得的分數。如果您的成績在錦標賽結束時夠高，那您就可以獲得屬於您的金牌。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Tournament: this multiple-race competition awards points after each race based on finishing position. If your tally is high enough at the end of the tournament, then you've rightfully earned your gold medal.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TIME_TRIAL_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Time Trial: this classic solo event pits racers against the clock, where the approach to every corner is paramount, and where each application of the airbrakes must be timed to perfection if victory is to be achieved.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Contre-la-montre : cette épreuve de vitesse classique pour un seul joueur implique une excellente maîtrise du circuit et des aérofreins pour espérer remporter la victoire.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeitrennen: In diesem Klassiker kämpfen die Spieler gegen die Uhr. Jede Kurve ist von Bedeutung, und der Einsatz der Luftbremsen muss perfekt getimt sein, um am Ende erfolgreich zu sein.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prova a tempo: classico evento in solitaria contro il cronometro. Per ottenere la vittoria è decisivo l'approccio a ogni curva come pure la scelta di tempo di ciascun ricorso agli aerofreni.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Contrarreloj: en esta clásica prueba individual lucharás contra el tiempo. Aquí, cada curva es vital y debes controlar a la perfección los frenos aerodinámicos para conseguir la victoria.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">タイムトライアル：時計相手のクラシックなレースイベントです。全てのコーナーでエアブレーキを完璧に使いこなし、自分に勝利しましょう。全ラップタイムの合計がスコアになります。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">기록 경쟁: 클래식 솔로 모드입니다. 승리를 하려면 모든 턴과 브레이크에 완벽한 정확성을 기해야 합니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Time Trial: this classic solo event pits racers against the clock, where the approach to every corner is paramount, and where each application of the airbrakes must be timed to perfection if victory is to be achieved.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Time Trial(競時賽)：這個經典的單人模式是要讓駕駛員對抗時間。如果您想達到勝利，每一個轉彎都要非常卓越，每一次噴射煞車也都要適時並完美地施展才行。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Time Trial(競時賽)：這個經典的單人模式是要讓駕駛員對抗時間。如果您想達到勝利，每一個轉彎都要非常卓越，每一次噴射煞車也都要適時並完美地施展才行。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Time Trial: this classic solo event pits racers against the clock, where the approach to every corner is paramount, and where each application of the airbrakes must be timed to perfection if victory is to be achieved.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SPEED_LAP_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Speed Lap: the logical extension of Time Trial, the Speed Lap event gives players 7 laps in which to record an exceptional lap time. Strategic use of the free turbo pickups is essential.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tour rapide : suite logique du Contre-la-montre, l'épreuve du Tour rapide laisse au joueur 7 tours pour réaliser un temps au tour exceptionnel. L'utilisation stratégique des turbos gratuits est cruciale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schnelle Runde: Die logische Erweiterung des Zeitrennens. Die Spieler müssen innerhalb von sieben Runden eine herausragende Rundenzeit fahren. Es wird empfohlen, die kostenlosen Turbo-Extras strategisch einzusetzen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Giro veloce: evoluzione naturale della Prova a tempo, gli eventi Giro veloce concedono al giocatore 7 giri per registrare un tempo sul giro eccezionale. L'uso strategico del potenziamento turbo è fondamentale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Velocidad de vuelta: la prueba de Velocidad de vuelta, una extensión lógica de la Contrarreloj, consta de 7 vueltas en las que los jugadores deben lograr un tiempo excepcional. El uso estratégico de los objetos de turbo gratuitos es esencial.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スピードラップ：全７ラップのうち、最速ラップのみがスコアとして記録されます。ラップごとに与えられるターボを上手に使いましょう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">스피드 랩: 스피드 랩 모드에서 플레이어들은 7번의 랩 중 가장 빠른 랩 타임을 기록해야 합니다. 트랙에서 주어지는 터보 픽업을 잘 활용해야 합니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Speed Lap: the logical extension of Time Trial, the Speed Lap event gives players 7 laps in which to record an exceptional lap time. Strategic use of the free turbo pickups is essential.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Speed Lap(單圈競速賽)：這是從競時賽衍生出來的模式，這個賽事活動會讓玩者奔馳7圈並記錄其中最優秀的單圈時間。有效地使用自動追加功能道具是不可或缺的關鍵。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Speed Lap(單圈競速賽)：這是從競時賽衍生出來的模式，這個賽事活動會讓玩者奔馳7圈並記錄其中最優秀的單圈時間。有效地使用自動追加功能道具是不可或缺的關鍵。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Speed Lap: the logical extension of Time Trial, the Speed Lap event gives players 7 laps in which to record an exceptional lap time. Strategic use of the free turbo pickups is essential.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ZONE_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Zone: the fan-favourite event returns to test the nerve of anyone looking for the ultimate speed-rush. Acceleration is automatic and the top speed increases after every 10 second zone. Your destruction is assured, but for how long can your navigation skills delay the inevitable?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Zone : l'épreuve préférée des fans est de retour pour mettre vos nerfs à l'épreuve dans une épreuve de vitesse ultime. Le vaisseau accélère automatiquement et la vitesse augmente à chaque tranche de dix secondes appelée zone. La destruction de votre vaisseau est inévitable, mais combien de temps pourrez-vous tenir grâce à vos compétences de pilote ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zone: Ein bei den Spielern äußerst beliebtes Rennen kehrt zurück und stellt die Nerven all jener auf die Probe, die nach dem ultimativen Geschwindigkeitsrausch suchen. Man wird automatisch schneller, und die Höchstgeschwindigkeit steigt mit jeder 10-Sekunden-Zone. Deine Zerstörung ist gewiss, doch wie lange kannst du das Unvermeidbare hinauszögern?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Zona: l'evento più amato dagli appassionati torna a mettere alla prova i nervi di chiunque sia alla ricerca del test di velocità assoluto. L'accelerazione è automatica e la velocità di punta aumenta ogni 10 secondi (zona). La distruzione è assicurata, ma quanto saprai ritardare l'inevitabile?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Zona: la prueba favorita de todos los aficionados vuelve para desafiar a cualquiera que esté buscando sensaciones fuertes. La aceleración es automática y la velocidad máxima aumenta tras cada zona de diez segundos. La destrucción total está garantizada, pero, ¿cuánto tiempo conseguirás retrasarla gracias a tu habilidad?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゾーン：ファンがこよなく愛する究極の体感スピードレース。クラフトは自動的に加速し、最高速度は 10秒ごとに増していきます。レースはクラフトが大破するまで続きます。あなたの真の操縦スキルが問われるモードです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">존: 팬들이 선호하는 모드입니다. 스피드를 찾는 플레이어를 만족시키기에 충분합니다. 가속은 자동적으로 이루어지며, 최고 속력 또한 매 10초마다 증가합니다. 충돌을 피할수는 없지만 얼마나 오래 달릴 수 있을까요?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Zone: the fan-favourite event returns to test the nerve of anyone looking for the ultimate speed-rush. Acceleration is automatic and the top speed increases after every 10 second zone. Your destruction is assured, but for how long can your navigation skills delay the inevitable?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Zone(區域)：深受本遊戲迷喜愛的賽事活動再度復活，要來測試大家對無限奔馳的緊張程度。油門加速會自動進行，而每經過一個10秒區域後最高速度便會增加。機體遭受破壞是一定的，但問題是在於您的操縱技術能將這無法避免的破壞拖延多久？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Zone(區域)：深受本遊戲迷喜愛的賽事活動再度復活，要來測試大家對無限奔馳的緊張程度。油門加速會自動進行，而每經過一個10秒區域後最高速度便會增加。機體遭受破壞是一定的，但問題是在於您的操縱技術能將這無法避免的破壞拖延多久？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Zone: the fan-favourite event returns to test the nerve of anyone looking for the ultimate speed-rush. Acceleration is automatic and the top speed increases after every 10 second zone. Your destruction is assured, but for how long can your navigation skills delay the inevitable?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ZONE_BATTLE_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Zone Battle: Be the first to reach the zone target.  Like Zone Mode, acceleration is automatic and ever-increasing, gradually moving you up through the zone levels towards the target.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Combat zone : soyez le premier à entrer dans la zone cible.  Comme en mode Zone, la vitesse augmente automatiquement, vous entraînant de plus en plus rapidement de zone en zone, jusqu'à la cible.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zonenkampf: Erreiche als Erster das Zonenziel. Wie im Zonenmodus steigt die Geschwindigkeit automatisch immer weiter an und du näherst dich durch die Zonen deinem Ziel.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Battaglia a zone: raggiungi per primo l'Obiettivo zona. Come nella modalità Zona, l'accelerazione è automatica e aumenta costantemente, facendoti progredire attraverso i Livelli zona verso l'obiettivo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Combate de zona: sé el primero en llegar al objetivo de la zona. Como en el modo Zona, la aceleración es automática y creciente y va haciéndote subir gradualmente por los niveles de la zona hasta el objetivo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">존 배틀: 존의 목표 지점에 가장 먼저 도달해야 합니다. 존 모드처럼 가속은 자동으로 이루어지며, 목표 지점에 차츰 가까워지게 됩니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Zone Battle: Be the first to reach the zone target.  Like Zone Mode, acceleration is automatic and ever-increasing, gradually moving you up through the zone levels towards the target.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Zone Battle(區域戰鬥)：成為第一個到達區域目標的玩者吧。跟Zone Mode(區域模式)一樣，油門會自動加速，漸漸增加速度讓您到達區域目標等級。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Zone Battle(區域戰鬥)：成為第一個到達區域目標的玩者吧。跟Zone Mode(區域模式)一樣，油門會自動加速，漸漸增加速度讓您到達區域目標等級。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ELIMINATOR_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Eliminator: An old favourite returns. Forget finishing in first place, use the full arsenal of WipEout® HD weaponry to attack the other racers and be first to reach the target score.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Eliminator : le retour d'un mode populaire. N'essayez plus de finir en première position, utilisez l'arsenal complet WipEout® HD pour attaquer les autres concurrents et être le premier à atteindre le score cible.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eliminator: Ein alter Favorit kehrt zurück. Statt dich auf den ersten Platz zu konzentrieren, verwende das gesamte Arsenal an „WipEout® HD"-Waffen, um die anderen Schiffe anzugreifen und als Erster die Zielpunktzahl zu erreichen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Eliminatore: ritorna un vecchio classico. Lascia stare il primo posto, l'Eliminatore premia l'aggressività repressa! Usa tutto l'arsenale di armi di WipEout® HD 
per attaccare gli altri piloti e raggiungere il punteggio obiettivo per primo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Eliminador: vuelve un viejo favorito. Olvídate de llegar en primer lugar: utiliza todo el arsenal de WipEout® HD para atacar a los otros pilotos y ser el primero en alcanzar la puntuación objetivo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">제거: 클래식 히트입니다. 가장 먼저 결승선에 들어오는 것은 이제 중요하지 않습니다. WipEout® HD 무기를 사용하여 다른 경쟁자들을 제거함으로서 목표 점수를 채워야 승자가 될 수 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Eliminator: An old favourite returns. Forget finishing in first place, use the full arsenal of WipEout® HD weaponry to attack the other racers and be first to reach the target score.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Eliminator(淘汰)：一個大家喜愛的模式回來了。暫時忘記第一名的金牌，Eliminator(淘汰)模式讓您盡情享受攻擊樂趣！使用所有WipEout® HD中的武器攻擊其他競爭對手，並設法首先達到目標分數 。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Eliminator(淘汰)：一個大家喜愛的模式回來了。暫時忘記第一名的金牌，Eliminator(淘汰)模式讓您盡情享受攻擊樂趣！使用所有WipEout® HD中的武器攻擊其他競爭對手，並設法首先達到目標分數 。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">DETONATOR_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Detonator: Blast your way through as many of the 14 stages as you can to achieve as high a score as possible.  Like Zone mode, acceleration is automatic and ever-increasing.  Score points for destroying mines and bombs that are strewn along the track.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Detonator : frayez-vous un chemin à travers le plus possible des 14 niveaux disponibles pour obtenir le score le plus élevé possible.  Comme en mode Zone, la vitesse augmente automatiquement. Marquez des points en détruisant les mines et les bombes disséminées sur la piste.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Detonator: Schieße deine Bahn durch so viele der 14 Stufen wie möglich um möglichst viele Punkte zu erzielen. Wie im Zonenmodus steigt die Geschwindigkeit automatisch immer weiter an. Erziele durch das Zerstören der auf der Strecke verteilten Minen und Bomben Punkte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Detonatore: fatti strada a suon di esplosioni affrontando il maggior numero di tappe: ce ne sono 14. Tenta di raggiungere il punteggio più alto. Come nella modalità Zona, l'accelerazione è automatica e aumenta costantemente. Guadagna punti distruggendo le mine e le bombe disseminate lungo il tracciato.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Detonador: ábrete paso por el mayor número de fases de las 14 que hay para obtener la puntuación más alta posible. Como en el modo Zona, la aceleración es automática y creciente. Consigue puntos por destruir las minas y las bombas diseminadas por la pista.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">폭발: 14개의 트랙을 자유롭게 드나들며 가장 높은 점수를 획득하십시오. 가속은 자동이며 계속 빨라집니다! 지뢰와 폭탄을 스스로 터뜨리면서 점수를 쌓게 됩니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Detonator: Blast your way through as many of the 14 stages as you can to achieve as high a score as possible.  Like Zone mode, acceleration is automatic and ever-increasing.  Score points for destroying mines and bombs that are strewn along the track.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Detonator(破壞)：在多達14個的關卡中攻擊您的賽道並盡可能地達到高分。跟Zone Mode(區域模式)一樣，油門會自動加速並漸漸增加速度。破壞賽道上的地雷與炸彈，便能增加您的分數。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Detonator(破壞)：在多達14個的關卡中攻擊您的賽道並盡可能地達到高分。跟Zone Mode(區域模式)一樣，油門會自動加速並漸漸增加速度。破壞賽道上的地雷與炸彈，便能增加您的分數。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CYCLE_CONTROLS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFT][RIGHT] CYCLE MODELS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFT][RIGHT] PARCOURIR LES MODÈLES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFT][RIGHT] MODELLE DURCHBLÄTTERN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFT][RIGHT] VISUALIZZA MODELLI</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFT][RIGHT] CAMBIAR DE MODELO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[LEFT][RIGHT] 모델 변경</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[LEFT][RIGHT] CYCLE MODELS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[LEFT][RIGHT] 瀏覽模型</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[LEFT][RIGHT] 瀏覽模型</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ROTATE_CONTROLS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFTSTICK] ROTATE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFTSTICK] PIVOTER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFTSTICK] DREHEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFTSTICK] RUOTA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFTSTICK] ROTAR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[LEFTSTICK] 회전</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[LEFTSTICK] ROTATE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[LEFTSTICK] 回轉</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[LEFTSTICK] 回轉</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RESET_CONTROLS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[TRIANGLE] RESET</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[TRIANGLE] RÉINITIALISER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[TRIANGLE] ZURÜCKSETZEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[TRIANGLE] RIPRISTINA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[TRIANGLE] REINICIAR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[TRIANGLE] 리셋</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[TRIANGLE] RESET</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[TRIANGLE] 重置</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[TRIANGLE] 重置</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">EXIT_CONTROLS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CIRCLE] EXIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CIRCLE] QUITTER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CIRCLE] BEENDEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CIRCLE] ESCI</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CIRCLE] SALIR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[CIRCLE] 나가기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[CIRCLE] EXIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[CIRCLE] 離開</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[CIRCLE] 離開</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>