<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cherry Bomb Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cherry Bomb Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Cherry Bomb Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cherry Bomb Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cherry Bomb Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Cherry</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Cherry</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Cherry</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Cherry</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Cherry</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cherry Bomb Pin-up Girl</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cha-cha-cha Cherry Bomb! This hot retro pin-up babe is a full character costume, sporting a sexy cherry on black swim suit, long black tresses and covered in sizzling tats!  With custom walk, run and pin-up pose animations, she's da' bomb![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cha-cha-cha Cherry Bomb! Cette sexy retro  pin-up minette est un costume à part entière , affichant un maillot de bain sexy, cerise sur fond noir, de longues tresses noires et couverte de superbes tatouages! Avec marche personnalisée, course et pose animées, Elle est "Canon"! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Cha-cha-cha Cherry Bomb! Dieses heiße Pin-Up Girl kommt als komplettes Charakterkostüm, mit einer sexy Kirsche auf einem schwarzen Badeanzug, langen schwarzen Locken und bedeckt mit super heißen Tätowierungen! Mit benutzerdefiniertem Animationen für Gang, Lauf- und Pin-Up Posen ist sie eine Bombe! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cha-cha-cha Cherry Bomb! Questa bambola sexy pin-up é un costume completo del personaggio, portando un costume da bagno ciliegia sexy, lunghe trecce nere e coperte di lustrini scintillanti!  Con camminata particolare, animazioni per la corsa e pose da  pin-up, é una bomba! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cha-cha-cha Cherry Bomb! Esta guapa muñeca retro pin-up es un disfraz completo del personaje, lleva un traje de baño sexy color cereza sobre fondo negro, largas trenzas negras y esta cubierta en motivos brillantes! Con animaciones de caminata, corrida y de poses pin-up, es una bomba! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Cherry [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Cherry [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Cherry [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Cherry [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Cherry [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cha-cha-cha Cherry Bomb! This hot retro pin-up babe is a full character costume, sporting a sexy cherry on black swim suit, long black tresses and covered in sizzling tats!  With custom walk, run and pin-up pose animations, she's da' bomb![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>