<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kCompanionName1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Forsaken Planet – Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Forsaken Planet - Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Forsaken Planet – Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Forsaken Planet – Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Forsaken Planet – Zombi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Forsaken Planet – Zombie</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Forsaken Planet – Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Forsaken Planet - Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Forsaken Planet – Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Forsaken Planet – Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Forsaken Planet – Zombi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Forsaken Planet – Zombie</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Travel PlayStation®Home with this companion from Forsaken Planet, a LOOT™ Entertainment videogame for tablets and smart phones! When you purchase one of our Forsaken Planet companions (one time purchase only), you unlock a character hat* for use in the Forsaken Planet game. This exclusive hat can only be unlocked in PlayStation®Home. To retrieve your reward, create or access your LOOT™ Entertainment account at the log-in station located at the Forsaken Planet globe logo in the LOOT Space Station Hub. Looking for even sweeter Forsaken Planet deals and in-game rewards? Check out the Forsaken Planet Bundles in the LOOT™ Store! (*Character hat unlocks specialized gameplay perks within the Forsaken Planet videogame!) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Parcourez PlayStation®Home avec ce compagnon de Forsaken Planet, un jeu vidéo de LOOT™ Entertainment pour tablettes et téléphones intelligents !  En achetant un de nos compagnons Forsaken Planet (seulement un achat), vous gagnez un chapeau de personnage*  à utiliser dans le jeu Forsaken Planet. Ce chapeau exclusif ne peut être gagné que dans PlayStation®Home.  Pour collecter votre récompense, créez ou accédez à votre compte  LOOT™ Entertainment à la station de connexion située dans le logo globe de Forsaken Planet sur la plateforme de la station spatiale LOOT. Vous cherchez des affaires Forsaken Planet encore plus intéressantes et des récompenses dans le jeu ? Allez voir les Lots Forsaken Planet dans la Boutique LOOT™  !  (*Le chapeau de personnage permet d'obtenir certains avantages spécifiques de jouabilité dans le jeu vidéo Forsaken Planet !) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bereise PlayStation®Home mit diesem Begleiter aus Forsaken Planet, einem LOOT™ Entertainment Videospiel für Tablets und Smartphones! Wenn du einen unserer Forsaken Planet-Begleiter erwirbst (nur einmaliger Kauf), schaltest du einen Hut für deine Spielfigur* im Spiel Forsaken Planet frei. Dieser exklusive Hut kann nur in PlayStation®Home freigeschaltet werden. Um deine Belohnung zu erhalten, erstelle oder öffne dein LOOT™ Entertainment Konto mit dem GRATIS Forsaken Planet – Globe Logo (Active), es ist erhältlich im LOOT™ Store. Möchtest du noch bessere Deals Forsaken Planet und Spielgegenstände abgreifen? Schau dir die Forsaken Planet-Bundles im LOOT™ Store an! (*Dieser Spielgegenstand schaltet besondere Gameplay-Vorteile im Videospiel Forsaken Planet frei!) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esplora PlayStation®Home con questo compagno di viaggi di Forsaken Planet, un videogioco di LOOT™ Entertainment per tablet e smartphone! Con l'acquisto dei nostri compagni Forsaken Planet (acquisto unico), sblocchi un cappello* da utilizzare nel gioco Forsaken Planet. Questo cappello esclusivo può essere sbloccato solo in PlayStation®Home. Per recuperare il tuo premio, crea o accedi all'account LOOT™ Entertainment con il LOGO Globe (Active) GRATUITO di Forsaken Planet disponibile nel LOOT™ Store. Cerchi altre offerte e altri premi Forsaken Planet? Dai un'occhiata ai Pacchetti Forsaken Planet nel LOOT™ Store! (*Il cappello sblocca elementi di gioco particolari all'interno del videogioco Forsaken Planet!) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Viaja en PlayStation®Home con tu compañero Forsaken Planet, un videojuego de LOOT™ Entertainment para tabletas y smartphones! Cuando compres uno de nuestros compañeros Forsaken Planet (una compra única), desbloquearás un sombrero de personaje* que podrás utilizar en el juego Forsaken Planet. Este exclusivo sombrero solo se puede desbloquear en PlayStation®Home. Para conseguir tu premio, crea o accede a tu cuenta de LOOT™ Entertainment con el logotipo del planeta GRATUITO de Forsaken Planet (Activo) disponible en la tienda LOOT™. ¿Quieres ofertas y premios aún más jugosos de Forsaken Planet? ¡No te pierdas los lotes de Forsaken Planet en la tienda LOOT™! (*El sombrero del personaje desbloquea extras especiales para el videojuego de Forsaken Planet) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Travel PlayStation®Home with this companion from Forsaken Planet, a LOOT™ Entertainment videogame for tablets and smart phones! When you purchase one of our Forsaken Planet companions (one time purchase only), you unlock a character hat* for use in the Forsaken Planet game. This exclusive hat can only be unlocked in PlayStation®Home. To retrieve your reward, create or access your LOOT™ Entertainment account at the log-in station located at the Forsaken Planet globe logo in the LOOT Space Station Hub. Looking for even sweeter Forsaken Planet deals and in-game rewards? Check out the Forsaken Planet Bundles in the LOOT™ Store! (*Character hat unlocks specialized gameplay perks within the Forsaken Planet videogame!) [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>