<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bomberman Costume - Set of full body parts (Black/Ladies')</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tenue Bomberman - Tous les éléments de corps (noir/pour femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bomberman-Kostüm – Kompletter Körper-Satz (Schwarz/Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vestito di Bomberman - Set corpo completo (nero/da donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de Bomberman. Conjunto de cuerpo completo (Negro/Mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ボンバーマン着ぐるみ　全身セット (黒・女性)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Bomberman Costume - Set of full body parts (Black/Ladies')</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Full set of the Bomberman (Black Bomber) Costume.\nThis set contains the following customsable avatar parts:\n\n-Bomberman Costume - Normal face (Black/Ladies')\n(Head part)\n-Bomberman Costume - Body (Black/Ladies') (Set: Top, Bottom, Shoes)\n-Bomberman Costume - Arm (Ladies') (Arm part)\n\n*When you purchase this set, the items will be added to the "Customise Avatar" categories they belong to. Please note that Bomberman Costume - Body (Black/Ladies') is a set which includes a top, bottom, and shoes. Since it is treated as a single item, each part cannot be used separately by category.\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tenue complète de Bomberman (Bomber noir).\nCet ensemble comprend les éléments personnalisables suivants :\n\n- Tenue Bomberman - Visage normal (noir/pour femme)\n(élément tête)\n- Tenue Bomberman - Corps (noir/pour femme) (ensemble haut, bas, chaussures)\n- Tenue Bomberman - Bras (femme) (bras)\n\n* Pour l'achat de cet ensemble, les éléments seront ajoutés à leurs catégories "Personnalisation d'avatar" respectives. Attention : la Tenue Bomberman - Corps (noir/pour femme) est considérée comme un ensemble dont les éléments (haut, bas et chaussures) ne peuvent être utilisés séparément par catégorie.\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vollständiger Bomberman-Kostümsatz (Schwarzer Bomber).\nDieser Satz enthält folgende anpassbare Avatar-Teile:\n\n- Bomberman-Kostüm – Normales Gesicht (Schwarz/Damen)\n(Kopfteil)\n- Bomberman-Kostüm – Körper (Schwarz/Damen) (Satz: Oberteil, Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Bomberman-Kostüm – Arm (Damen) (Armteil)\n\n*Wenn du diesen Satz kaufst, werden die Artikel zu den entsprechenden Kategorien der Option „Avatar anpassen“ hinzugefügt. Bitte beachte, dass der Satz „Bomberman-Kostüm – Körper (Schwarz/Damen)“ ein Oberteil, ein Unterteil und Schuhe enthält. Da der Satz als Einheit behandelt wird, kann er nicht separat nach Kategorie verwendet werden.\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set completo del vestito di Bomberman (Bomber Nero).\nQuesto set contiene le seguenti parti personalizzabili per il tuo avatar:\n\n- Vestito di Bomberman - Faccia normale (nero/da donna)\n(Testa)\n- Vestito di Bomberman - Corpo (nero/da donna) (set: alto, basso, scarpe)\n- Vestito di Bomberman - Braccio (da donna) (braccia)\n\n*Quando acquisti questo set, gli oggetti verranno aggiunti alla categoria "Personalizza Avatar" alla quale appartengono. Il Vestito di Bomberman - Corpo (nero/da donna) è un set che include la parte alta, quella bassa e le scarpe. È considerato un oggetto unico, quindi non si possono usare separatamente le diverse parti.\n[#Legal]\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de Bomberman completo (Bombero Negro).\nEste conjunto contiene los siguientes elementos personalizables para tu avatar:\n\n-Vestido de Bomberman. Cara normal (Negro/Mujer)\n(Cabeza)\n-Vestido de Bomberman. Cuerpo (Negro/Mujer) (Conjunto: camiseta, pantalón, zapatos)\n-Traje de Bomberman. Brazo (Mujer) (Brazo)\n\n*Cuando compres este conjunto, los objetos se añadirán a las categorías correspondientes de "Personalizar avatar". Ten en cuenta que el traje de Bomberman (Cuerpo) (Negro/Mujer) es un conjunto que incluye camiseta, pantalón y zapatos. Puesto que se considera un único objeto, no se pueden utilizar las partes separadamente por categoría.\n[#Legal]\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ボンバーマン着ぐるみセットの黒ボンバージョン。\n本セットには、アバターカスタマイズ用の下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・ボンバーマン着ぐるみ　ノーマル顔　(黒・女性) (頭カテゴリー)\n・ボンバーマン着ぐるみ　ボディー (黒・女性) (組み合わせ・トップス・ボトムス・靴)\n・ボンバーマン着ぐるみ　ボンバーハンド (女性) (手カテゴリー)\n\n※購入すると、「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。ボンバーマン着ぐるみ　ボディー (黒・女性)はトップス・ボトムス・靴をまとめて一つのアイテムとしております。カテゴリ毎のアイテムを単体で使用することはできませんのでご注意ください。\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Full set of the Bomberman (Black Bomber) Costume.\nThis set contains the following customizable avatar parts:\n\n-Bomberman Costume - Normal face (Black/Ladies')\n(Head part)\n-Bomberman Costume - Body (Black/Ladies') (Set: Top, Bottom, Shoes)\n-Bomberman Costume - Arm (Ladies') (Arm part)\n\n*When you purchase this set, the items will be added to the "Customize Avatar" categories they belong to. Please note that Bomberman Costume - Body (Black/Ladies') is a set which includes a top, bottom, and shoes. Since it is treated as a single item, each part cannot be used separately by category.\n[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>