<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">‘Chris’ the Bodyguard</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Chris" le garde du corps</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Leibwächter "Chris"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chris la guardia del corpo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chris, el guardaespaldas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ボディーガードのクリス</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">보디가드 '크리스'</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">‘Chris’ the Bodyguard</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">保鏢克里斯</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">保鏢克里斯</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">‘Chris’ the Bodyguard</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Can’t afford a real security team? Then Chris the bodyguard is perfect for making sure your guests stay well behaved, even if he is just a cardboard cut out. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pas les moyens de vous offrir une vraie équipe de sécurité ? Chris le garde du corps s'assurera de la bonne conduite des invités, même s'il ne s'agit que d'une silhouette en carton.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kannst du dir kein echtes Sicherheits-Team leisten? Dann wird Chris der Leibwächter dafür sorgen, dass deine Gäste brav bleiben, auch wenn er nur aus einem Karton ausgeschnitten ist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non puoi permetterti una squadra di buttafuori? Allora la guardia del corpo Chris ti servirà per far sì che i tuoi ospiti siano al sicuro, anche se è solo un ritaglio in cartoncino. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Los equipos de seguridad son demasiado caros? Chris, el guardaespaldas, es perfecto para que tus invitados se porten bien, aunque solo sea un troquelado de cartón. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">セキュリティ ガードを何人も雇うのは大変！そんな時はこのクリスをどうぞ。彼がいればゲストもきっとハメを外し過ぎないはず。実は段ボール製なんですけどね。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">진짜 경호팀은 비싸서 고용할 수 없습니까? 오려낸 판지일 뿐이지만 보디가드 크리스가 당신의 손님들이 얌전히 있도록 도와드릴 것입니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Can’t afford a real security team? Then Chris the bodyguard is perfect for making sure your guests stay well behaved, even if he is just a cardboard cut out. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">聘請不起一支真正的保安團隊？那麼，保鏢克里斯十分適合確保您的來賓安分守己，即使他僅是一塊紙板剪切像。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">聘請不起一支真正的保安團隊？那麼，保鏢克里斯十分適合確保您的來賓安分守己，即使他僅是一塊紙板剪切像。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Can’t afford a real security team? Then Chris the bodyguard is perfect for making sure your guests stay well behaved, even if he is just a cardboard cut out. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>