<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Egyptian Throne</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Egyptienne Trône</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">ägyptischen Thron</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Egiziano Trono</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Trono de Egipto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Egyptian Throne</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Escape the hectic life of desert royalty in this 5-star authentic Egyptian throne.  This stunning piece of furniture is imported directly to you from a virtual pyramid in Egypt.  Don't accept cheap ripoffs, they Sphinx.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Échapper à la vie trépidante de la royauté dans cette impressionnante, trône égyptien authentique. Cette pièce étonnante de meubles sont importés directement de vous à partir d'une pyramide virtuelle en Egypte. Ne pas accepter les arnaques bon marché, ils Sphinx.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Entfliehen Sie dem hektischen Leben in der Wüste Lizenzgebühren in diesem 5-Sterne-authentischen ägyptischen Thron. Dieses beeindruckende Möbelstück wird Ihnen direkt von einer virtuellen Pyramide in Ägypten importiert. Akzeptieren Sie keine billigen Gaunereien, sie Sphinx.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sfuggire alla vita frenetica della regalità deserto in questo trono a 5 stelle autentico egiziano. Questa sbalorditiva di mobili viene importato direttamente a voi da una piramide virtuale in Egitto. Non accettare imbrogli a buon mercato, si Sfinge.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Escapar de la agitada vida de la realeza del desierto en este trono egipcio de 5 estrellas, auténticos. Esta impresionante pieza de mobiliario es importado directamente a usted de una pirámide virtual en Egipto. No acepte estafas económicas, que la Esfinge.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Escape the hectic life of desert royalty in this 5-star authentic Egyptian throne.  This stunning piece of furniture is imported directly to you from a virtual pyramid in Egypt.  Don't accept cheap ripoffs, they Sphinx.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>