<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stan the Salesman Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Baluchon de Stan the Salesman</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stan, der Verkäufer- Komplettpaket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Stan il Venditore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de Stan the Salesman</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Stan the Salesman Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is the complete look of a used ship salesman. You’re obviously an educated person who wants to make an educated decision. I can tell you are a real no-frills kind of buyer. You seem to have a rugged Nordic quality to you! It’s the definition of affordable quality! Just how much were you looking to spend today? It doesn’t matter if you’ve had credit problems in the past. Who am I to judge, right? Includes Stan's Suit Jacket, Pants, Shoes, and Hat. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Voici tout l'attirail d'un vendeur de bateaux d'occasion. Vous êtes certainement une personne avertie qui veut prendre des décisions réfléchies. Je vois bien que vous n'êtes pas le genre d'acheteur à céder au superflu. Vous avez ce côté rude des Nordiques ! C'est ce qui caractérise la qualité à bon prix ! Combien vouliez-vous dépenser aujourd'hui ? Vos problèmes de crédit font partie du passé. Qui suis-je pour juger, n'est-ce pas ? Comprend la veste, le pantalon, les chaussures et le chapeau de Stan. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das ist der komplette Look eines Verkäufers für gebrauchte Schiffe. Du bist offensichtlich eine gebildete Person, die eine intelligente Entscheidung trifft. Ich sehe ganz klar, dass du kein Spontankäufer bist. Dir haftet eine gewisse nordische Kühle an! Das hier ist der Inbegriff erschwinglicher Qualität! Es kommt nur darauf an, wie viel du heute ausgeben kannst. Ob du in der Vergangenheit Geldprobleme hattest, interessiert hier nicht. Darüber kann ich mir ja kein Urteil erlauben. Beinhaltet Stans Jackett, Hose und Hut. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo è il look completo di un venditore di navi usate. Tu sei certamente una persona colta che vuole prendere una decisione colta.  Immagino che tu sia un compratore che va al dunque. Sembra che tu possegga la qualità del duro nordico! È una qualità abbordabile! Quanto pensavi di spendere oggi? Non importa se hai avuto problemi di credito in passato. Chi sono io per giudicare, giusto? Include Giacca completo, pantaloni, Scarpe e Cappello di Stan. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este es el look completo de un vendedor de barcos usados. Obviamente eres una persona inteligente que quiere tomar una decisión inteligente. Ya veo que eres la clase de comprador que se deja de tonterías. ¡Pareces tener un estilo Nórdico duro! ¡Es la definición de calidad asequible! ¿Cuánto pensabas gastarte hoy? No importa si has tenido problemas financieros en el pasado. ¿Quién soy yo para juzgarte? Incluye la chaqueta de traje, los pantalones, los zapatos y el sombrero de Stan. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This is the complete look of a used ship salesman. You’re obviously an educated person who wants to make an educated decision. I can tell you are a real no-frills kind of buyer. You seem to have a rugged Nordic quality to you! It’s the definition of affordable quality! Just how much were you looking to spend today? It doesn’t matter if you’ve had credit problems in the past. Who am I to judge, right? [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>