<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">S.V.E.R. Wolf Skin Rug</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tapis peau de loup S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">S.V.E.R.-Wolfsfellteppich</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tappeto S.V.E.R. in pelle di lupo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Alfombra de piel de lobo de S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">狼の毛皮絨毯 セイバー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">S.V.E.R. 늑대가죽 양탄자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SVER Wolf Skin Rug</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">SVER狼皮地毯</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">SVER狼皮地毯</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">SVER Wolf Skin Rug</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This S.V.E.R. wolfskin rug comes from the harsh winters of Grozny and adding this rug to your apartment makes you one of the pack. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce tapis en peau de loup S.V.E.R. a connu les rudes hivers de Grozny. Intégrez la meute en l'installant chez vous. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der S.V.E.R.-Wolfsfellteppich hat den weiten Weg von den harten Wintern Grosnys zurückgelegt, damit Sie Ihr Apartment damit ausstatten und so Teil des Rudels werden können. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il tappeto in pelle di lupo della S.V.E.R. ci giunge dagli inverni gelidi di Grozny, se lo userete nella vostra abitazione diventerete parte del branco. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta alfombra de piel de lobo de S.V.E.R. ha sido creada en los duros inviernos de Grozny. Únete a la manada y coloca esta alfombra en tu apartamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">グロズヌイの厳しい寒さに最適なセイバー製狼の毛皮絨毯。部屋に置いて群れの一員になれ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">S.V.E.R.가 위치한 그로즈니 지역의 설원을 배회하는 늑대의 가죽입니다. 자신의 아파트에 이 양탄자를 깔면, 무리의 일원이 되는 겁니다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This SVER wolfskin rug comes from the harsh winters of Grozny, and adding this rug to your apartment makes you one of the pack. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這款SVER狼皮地毯由格羅茲尼的寒冬而來。把這款地毯放進你的住處，令你成為狼群之一。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這款SVER狼皮地毯由格羅茲尼的寒冬而來。把這款地毯放進你的住處，令你成為狼群之一。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This SVER Wolf Skin rug comes from the harsh winters of Grozny, and adding this rug to your apartment makes you one of the pack. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>