<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Doctor Who - Silurian Costume with mask</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Doctor Who - Costume Silurian avec masque</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Doctor Who – Silurian-Kostüm mit Maske</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Doctor Who - Costume di Silurian con maschera</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Doctor Who - Traje con máscara Silurian</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Doctor Who - Silurian Costume with mask</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Doctor Who - Silurian Costume with mask</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Earth's first intelligent inhabitants, cold-blood reptilians with a lifespan of over three centuries who developed a civilisation at least 300 million years before human beings evolved  and a distinct dislike of the apes who took over their planet. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Premiers habitants intelligents de la Terre, reptiles à sang froid avec une durée de vie de plus de trois siècles, qui ont développé une civilisation au moins 300 millions d'années avant que les êtres humains évoluent et qui ont une nette aversion pour les singes qui se sont emparés de leur planète. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die ersten intelligenten Bewohner der Erde, kaltblütige Reptilien mit einer Lebenserwartung von über drei Jahrhunderten, die vor mindestens 300 Millionen Jahren, lange bevor sich menschliche Wesen entwickelten, eine Zivilisation  gründeten. Sie hegen einen starken Abscheu vor den Affen, die später ihren Planeten übernommen haben. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Primi abitanti intelligenti della Terra, sono rettili a sangue freddo esistenti da più di tre secoli che svilupparono una civiltà almeno 300 milioni di anni prima dell'evoluzione degli esseri umani e con una chiara antipatia per le scimmie che hanno occupato il loro pianeta. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los primeros habitantes inteligentes de la Tierra fueron unos reptiles de sangre fría que podían llegar a vivir más de tres siglos. Desarrollaron una civilización al menos 300 millones de años antes de que los seres humanos evolucionaran, y una clara aversión a los simios que dominaron su planeta. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Earth's first intelligent inhabitants, cold-blood reptilians with a lifespan of over three centuries who developed a civilisation at least 300 million years before human beings evolved  and a distinct dislike of the apes who took over their planet. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Earth's first intelligent inhabitants, cold-blood reptilians with a lifespan of over three centuries who developed a civilisation at least 300 million years before human beings evolved  and a distinct dislike of the apes who took over their planet. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>