<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cogs Silver Level Prize</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Récompense du rang Argent de Cogs</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Cogs Silber-Rang-Wandschmuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Opera d’arte “Silver Rank” di Cogs</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Obra de arte del nivel Plata de Cogs</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* SinglePlayerAward</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">코그 실버 등급 상품</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Cogs Silver Level Prize</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">齒輪白銀等級獎賞</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">齒輪白銀等級獎賞</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cogs Silver Level Prize</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Congratulations! You've reached Silver rank in Cogs by achieving a score of over 8400!  To commemorate the occasion, here is a solo play themed piece of art for your apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Félicitations ! Vous avez atteint le rang Argent dans Cogs en réalisant un score supérieur à 8 400 points ! Pour célébrer cela, voici un objet d'art sur le thème du jeu solo pour votre appartement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Herzlichen Glückwunsch! Mit einer Punktzahl von 8400 hast du bei Cogs den Silber-Rang erreicht! Um diesen Erfolg zu würdigen, übergeben wir dir hiermit ein im Einzelspieler-Stil gehaltenes Kunstwerk für dein Appartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Congratulazioni! Hai raggiunto il livello d’Argento in Cogs, ottenendo un punteggio pari ad almeno 8.400 punti! Per celebrare questo evento ti vogliamo regalare un’opera d’arte che rappresenta un giocatore singolo: un piccolo pensiero per il tuo appartamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Enhorabuena, has alcanzado el nivel Plata en Cogs al lograr una puntuación superior a 8.400 puntos! Para celebrarlo, aquí tienes una obra de arte del tema de un único jugador para tu apartamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">축하합니다, 8400점 이상의 점수를 기록하여 코그에서 실버 등급을 획득했습니다! 당신의 실력을 기념하기 위하여 솔로 플레이를 테마로 삼은 멋진 장식물을 증정합니다. 아파트를 장식하세요! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Congratulations! You've reached Silver rank in Cogs by achieving a score of over 8400!  To commemorate the occasion, here is a solo play themed piece of art for your apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">恭喜您在「齒輪王」遊戲得分稱過8400分並獲得白銀等級！為了紀念這一刻，我們特別獻上這個以單人遊玩模式為主題的壁飾，供您裝飾個人空間。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">恭喜您在「齒輪王」遊戲得分稱過8400分並獲得白銀等級！為了紀念這一刻，我們特別獻上這個以單人遊玩模式為主題的壁飾，供您裝飾個人空間。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Congratulations! You've reached Silver rank in Cogs by achieving a score of over 8400!  To commemorate the occasion, here is a solo play themed piece of art for your apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>