<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Nis_Dots_No014</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Personnage 2D: Taro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドットオブジェ　気弱で緊張感ゼロの皮肉屋　タロー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">도트 오브제 심약하고 긴장감 제로인 투덜이 타로</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Taro: The Timid Cynic" Sprite Statue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">像素雕像 懦弱沒有緊張感的挖苦專家TARO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">像素雕像 懦弱沒有緊張感的挖苦專家TARO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">2D Character Objects: Taro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nis_Dots_No014</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Untitled</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La statuette d'un personnage que tu peux mettre dans ta chambre pour décorer.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アデルの弟・ハナコの兄であるタロー。見た目からも疑いのないように、諸事情で牛タイプの悪魔としてこの世に生を受ける。常にまゆが下がっており気弱な性格ではあるが、カルシウムを摂取しているおかげか、ちょっとした皮肉やマイペースさは骨太。おそろしいほどのんびりした口調は緊張感が皆無。「健康牛乳・元気牛乳・至高の牛乳」を常に所持している様子。やっぱ牛乳です。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">아델의 남동생이자 하나코의 오빠, 타로. 생김새부터도 의심의 여지가 없듯, 여러 가지 사정에 의해 소 타입의 악마로 이 세상에 태어난다. 언제나 눈썹이 쳐져 있고 기가 약한 성격이지만, 칼슘을 섭취하고 있는 덕에 조금은 살도 찌고 마이페이스도 강해졌다. 무서울 정도로 느긋한 말투는 긴장감 전무.「건강 우유・원기 우유・최고의 우유」를 항상 소지하고 있는 상태. 특수 기술은 우유를 사용한 공격입니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Taro is the middle child in a family of three siblings, with his older brother Adell and younger sister Hanako. For reasons unknown, he came into the world as a cow-like demon. Taro is a timid creature, but perhaps due to his large intake of calcium, he is known to be a big-boned cynic, doing things at his own pace. Taro is entirely too laid-back, talking in a comfortably slow tone, always carrying "Milk, Strawberry Milk and Chocolate Milk", with milk-based attacks as his specialty. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Taro是Adell的弟弟，Hanako的哥哥。無庸置疑，從第一眼見到他就可確定他是個牛型的悪魔。常常表現出懦弱的個性、可能是因為鈣質攝取充足，不但愛譏諷而且我行我素，令人不敢領教的慢郎中般說話方式。不管隨時都帶著「健康牛奶、元氣牛奶、最高級牛奶」。還是牛奶好。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Taro是Adell的弟弟，Hanako的哥哥。無庸置疑，從第一眼見到他就可確定他是個牛型的悪魔。常常表現出懦弱的個性、可能是因為鈣質攝取充足，不但愛譏諷而且我行我素，令人不敢領教的慢郎中般說話方式。不管隨時都帶著「健康牛奶、元氣牛奶、最高級牛奶」。還是牛奶好。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A small character statue that you can place to decorate your own room.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>