<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Large Outdoor Comet Rocket - Gold</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Grosse Fusée Comète d’Extérieur - Or</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Große Komet-Feuerwerksrakete - Gold</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Razzo grande con cometa da esterni - Oro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cohete Cometa grande para exterior - Dorado</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アウトドア・コメットロケット花火　ゴールド</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">대형 옥외용 혜성 로켓 - 골드</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Large Outdoor Comet Rocket - Gold</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">大型彗星沖天炮：金光</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">大型彗星沖天炮：金光</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Large Outdoor Comet Rocket - Gold</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Impress your guests or just satisfy your creative pyrotechnic desires with these animated fireworks. Place several together to produce a breathtaking spectacle. Only suitable for outdoor use. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Impressionnez vos invités ou comblez vos propres désirs de création pyrotechnique à l'aide de ces feux d'artifices animés. Placez-en plusieurs simultanément pour un spectacle à couper le souffle. Utilisation extérieure uniquement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beeindrucke deine Gäste oder erfülle dir einfach deine pyrotechnischen Träume mit diesem animierten Feuerwerk. Zünde mehrere gleichzeitig für ein atemberaubendes Spektakel. Nur für den Einsatz im Freien. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lascia i tuoi ospiti a bocca aperta o soddisfa i tuoi desideri creativi pirotecnici con questi fuochi animati. Se ne usi più insieme, l'effetto sarà spettacolare. Adatto solo per gli esterni. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Impresiona a tus invitados o simplemente satisface tus deseos pirotécnicos creativos con estos fuegos artificiales animados. Tira varios juntos para crear un espectáculo de infarto. Solo para uso exterior. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゲストを楽しませるか自分ひとりで楽しむのに最適。いくつか一緒にセットしてそのスペクタルをお楽しみください。注：屋外用 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">에니메이션 불꽃놀이로 여러분의 손님들에게 감동을 주거나 아니면 본인의 창조적인 불꽃놀이 욕구를 만족시켜 보세요. 여러 개를 함께 놓으면 숨막히는 장관을 연출합니다. 옥외에서만 사용 가능. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Impress your guests or just satisfy your creative pyrotechnic desires with these animated fireworks. Place several together to produce a breathtaking spectacle. Only suitable for outdoor use. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這些動態煙火保證讓賓客讚不絕口，或是滿足你的煙火創作慾望。多支連發，就能打造令人驚嘆的表演。只適合戶外使用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這些動態煙火保證讓賓客讚不絕口，或是滿足你的煙火創作慾望。多支連發，就能打造令人驚嘆的表演。只適合戶外使用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Impress your guests or just satisfy your creative pyrotechnic desires with these animated fireworks. Place several together to produce a breathtaking spectacle. Only suitable for outdoor use. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>