<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Glittering Sands Secluded Retreat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sables Scintillants du Havre de Paix</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Abgeschiedener Rückzugsort am Funkelstrand</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ritiro Isolato delle Sabbie Scintillanti</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Refugio solitario de arenas brillantes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ふたりだけの熱い砂浜</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Glittering Sands Secluded Retreat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Glittering Sands Secluded Retreat</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Spend your holiday on a luxurious private beach. 
The clear blue sea, the white sandy beach, and the cottage on the ocean are all yours. 
With a friend, or with that special someone. Your holiday has just begun. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Passez vos vacances sur une plage privée somptueuse. 
La mer bleue et limpide, la plage de sable blanc et le chalet sur l’océan sont à vous.
Avec un(e) ami(e), ou la personne que vous aimez. Vos vacances ne font que commencer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verbringe deine Ferien an einem luxuriösen Privatstrand 
Das kristallklare Wasser, der weiße Sandstrand und das Ferienhaus am Meer, all dies gehört dir.  
Mit einem Freund oder dieser einen besonderen Person. Deine Ferien haben gerade erst begonnen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Passa le tue vacanze in una lussuosa spiaggia privata. 
Il mare cristallino, la spiaggia di sabbia bianchissima e la casetta sull'oceano sono tutti tuoi. 
Con un amico, o con una persona speciale. La tua vacanza è appena iniziata. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pasa tus vacaciones en una lujosa playa privada. 
El mar cristalino, la playa de arena blanca y la casa en el océano te pertencen... 
Con un amigo, o con ese alguien especial. Tus vacaciones acaban de comenzar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">バカンスは、贅沢なプライベートビーチで。\n透き通った青い海も、広い砂浜も、海上のコテージも、全てあなたのもの。\n仲間と、恋人と。あなたのバカンスは始まったばかりです。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Spend your holiday on a luxurious private beach. 
The clear blue sea, the white sandy beach, and the cottage on the ocean are all yours. 
With a friend, or with that special someone. Your holiday has just begun. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Spend your holiday on a luxurious private beach. 
The clear blue sea, the white sandy beach, and the cottage on the ocean are all yours. 
With a friend, or with that special someone. Your holiday has just begun. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>