<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">*Not Localised* </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">*Not Localised* </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ghostbusters™ Fan Pack: Ornaments</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack pour fans de S.O.S. Fantômes™: Ornements</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ghostbusters™ Fan Pack: Ornamente</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cofanetto per i fan di Ghostbusters™: Ornamenti</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Adornos: Pack de juguetes de Cazafantasmas™.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴーストバスターズ™ ファンパック（オーナメント）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ghostbusters™ Fan Pack: Ornaments</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Ghostbusters™ Limited Edition Toy Pack: ORNAMENTS includes a coffee table sized Stay Puft Marshmallow Man  Figurine, Ghost Slimer Figurine, Ecto-1 Miniature Model, Ghost Trap Decorative Toy &amp; PKE Meter Decorative Toy PLUS the "I Got Slimed" green shirt, the Stay Puft Happy black tee and the Blue Ecto-1 tee (all in Male AND Female). No Ghostbusters collection is complete unless you have the greatest Ghostbusters items now available for PlayStation®Home. Get this special offer today.  It will only be available for a limited time! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce Pack de jouets S.O.S. Fantômes™ édition limitée : ORNEMENTS comprend une Figurine Bibendum Marshmallow de la taille d'une table basse, une Figurine du fantôme Bouffe-tout, un Modèle réduit de l'Ecto-1, un Jouet décoratif du piège à fantômes &amp; un Jouet décoratif Ectomètre PLUS un T-shirt vert "Je me suis fait engluer", un T-shirt noir Bibendum Marshmallow "Heureux" et un T-shirt bleu Ecto-1 (un jeu de T-shirts pour homme ET un pour femme). Aucune collection S.O.S. Fantômes n'est complète sans ces fantastiques objets S.O.S. Fantômes disponibles pour PlayStation®Home. Profitez dès aujourd'hui de cette offre spéciale. Elle n'est valable que pour une période limitée ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese limitierte Auflage des Ghostbusters™-Spielzeug-Pack: ORNAMENTE enthält eine Statuette eines Stay Puft Marschmallow-Mannes in Tischhöhe, eine Geister-Slimer-Statuette, eine Ecto-1-Mini-Modell, eine Spielzeug-Geisterfalle &amp; PKE-Messer UND das grüne “I Got Slimed“-T-Shirt, das schwarze Stay-Puft-T-Shirt und das blaue Ecto-1-T-Shirt (jeweils für Männer und Frauen). Keine Ghostbusters-Sammlung ist vollständig ohne die jetzt erhältlichen Ghostbusters-Artikel für  PlayStation®Home. Heute im Angebot. Nur begrenzt erhältlich! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo cofanetto Ghostbusters™ in edizione limitata: ORNAMENTI include un tavolino da caffè della grandezza della statuetta di Stay Puft, l'omino di marshmallow, la statuetta del fantasma Slimer, il modellino della Ecto-1, la trappola per fantasmi giocattolo e il rilevatore di ectoplasmi giocattolo INOLTRE la T-shirt verde "Mi ha ricoperto di bava", la T-shirt nera di Stay Puft "Felice" e la T-shirt blu Ecto-1 (tutte da uomo E da donna). Una collezione Ghostbusters non è completa senza i favolosi oggetti Ghostbusters adesso disponibili per PlayStation®Home. Non lasciarti sfuggire questa offerta speciale. Sarà disponibile solo per un periodo di tempo limitato! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta edición limitada del pack de juguetes de Cazafantasmas™ incluye una mesita para la figura del hombre de malvavisco, una estatuilla de Slimer, una maqueta en miniatura Eco-1, un juguete cazafantasmas decorativo y un juguete contador PKE, además de la camiseta verde de "Me han babeado", la camiseta negra de "Estoy feliz" y la camiseta azul Ecto-1 (masculinas y femeninas). Ninguna colección de cazafantasmas está completa sin los mejores objetos de los Cazafantasmas que PlayStation®Home pone a tu disposición. Consigue esta oferta especial hoy mismo. ¡Solo estará disponible un tiempo limitado!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴーストバスターズ™ ファンパック（オーナメント）\n　本セットには、以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n
\n
「ゴーストバスターズ™ マシュマロマン　フィギュア」（装飾品）\n
「ゴーストバスターズ™ スライマー　フィギュア」（装飾品）\n
「ゴーストバスターズ™ ECTO-1　模型」（装飾品）\n
「ゴースト･トラップと霊探知機のトイ」（装飾品）\n
「男性用 『ベトベトだ！』Ｔシャツ（緑）」（トップス）\n
「男性用 『笑顔のマシュマロマン』Ｔシャツ（黒）」（トップス）\n
「男性用 『ECTO-1』Tシャツ（青）」（トップス）\n
「女性用 『ベトベトだ！』Ｔシャツ（緑）」（トップス）\n
「女性用 『笑顔のマシュマロマン』Ｔシャツ（黒）」（トップス）\n
「女性用 『ECTO-1』Tシャツ（青）」（トップス）\n
\n
※購入すると、「アバターのカスタマイズ」、「パーソナルスペースのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This Ghostbusters™ Limited Edition Toy Pack: ORNAMENTS includes a coffee table sized Stay Puft Marshmallow Man  Figurine, Ghost Slimer Figurine, Ecto-1 Miniature Model, Ghost Trap Decorative Toy &amp; PKE Meter Decorative Toy PLUS the "I Got Slimed" green shirt, the Stay Puft Happy black tee and the Blue Ecto-1 tee (all in Male AND Female). No Ghostbusters collection is complete unless you have the greatest Ghostbusters items now available for PlayStation®Home. Get this special offer today.  It will only be available for a limited time! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>