<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Slingback Wedges - Coral</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaussures Compensées à Bride - Corail</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Slingback Wedges - Koralle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sandali con zeppa e cinturino sul calcagno - Corallo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuñas con tira: Coral</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スリングバックシューズ－珊瑚（女性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">슬링백 웻지 - 산호 스타일 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Slingback Wedges - Coral (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">繫帶楔型鞋：珊瑚 (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">繫帶楔型鞋：珊瑚 (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Slingback Wedges - Coral</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A  little bit sandal for casual combos, a little bit espadrille for days at the beach and a little bit slingback for more formal events - one pair of shoes CAN do it all! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Des sandales pour les ensembles décontractés, des espadrilles pour les balades à la plage et des chaussures à bride pour les soirées habillées : comme quoi une seule paire de chaussures PEUT tout faire ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein bisschen Sandale für lässige Outfits, ein bisschen Espadrille für den Strand und ein bisschen Slingback für vornehme Outfits - ein Paar Schuhe, das wirklich ALLES kann! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un po' sandalo per le occasioni informali, un po' espadrille per le giornate in spiaggia e il cinturino è un tocco perfetto per gli eventi più formali; un paio di scarpe adatto per qualunque occasione! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una sandalia para conjuntos informales, un poco de alpargata para los días de playa y una tira para los eventos más formales; ¡un par de zapatos que PUEDEN servir para todo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">カジュアルな日にはこちらのサンダルで出かけてみてはいかがですか？フォーマルな展開になろうとこの靴ならどちらのシチュエーションにも対応しています。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">캐주얼한 콤보에는 살짝 샌들 스타일로, 해변가에서는 에스파드리유 스타일로, 그리고 더 격식을 차리는 자리에서는 슬링백 스타일로 - 구두 한 켤레로 모든 것을 해결할 수 있답니다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A  little bit sandal for casual combos, a little bit espadrille for days at the beach and a little bit slingback for more formal events - one pair of shoes CAN do it all! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">來點涼鞋的休閒風，加上平底鞋設計適合沙灘漫步，再搭配繫帶鞋感覺讓你出席正式場合，一雙鞋子多種功能！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">來點涼鞋的休閒風，加上平底鞋設計適合沙灘漫步，再搭配繫帶鞋感覺讓你出席正式場合，一雙鞋子多種功能！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A  little bit sandal for casual combos, a little bit espadrille for days at the beach and a little bit slingback for more formal events - one pair of shoes CAN do it all! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>