<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dusty - The Golden Brimstone Dancer Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Dusty - Le Danseuse Brimstone Or Ensemble</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dusty - El Bailarín Azufre de Oro Paquete</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dusty - The Golden Brimstone Dancer Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You are gonna dig Dusty; she's worth her weight in gold.  24 carat and built like Fort Knox.  When she dances, you'll agree that Dusty's commodities should be held in the U. S. Federal Reserve. Put this full sized…"active object" in your personal space and show her miniature version around Home as a dancing companion. Also comes with Gold Dance Platform![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tu vas creuser Dusty, elle vaut son pesant d'or. 24 carats et construit comme Fort Knox. Quand elle danse, vous serez d'accord que les produits Dusty's devrait être tenue à la Réserve fédérale américaine.  Mettez cette pleine grandeur... "objet actif" dans votre espace personnel et montrez sa version miniature autour de Home comme un compagnon de danse. Vient aussi avec Plate-forme de Danse Or! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Usted se va a excavar polvoriento; ella vale su peso en oro. De 24 quilates y construida como Fort Knox. Cuando baila, que estará de acuerdo que los productos de Dusty se celebre en los EE.UU. la Reserva Federal.  Añadir este tamaño completo ... "objeto activo" en su espacio personal y mostrar su versión en miniatura alrededor de Home como un compañero de baile. También viene con Oro Plataforma de Baile![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You are gonna dig Dusty; she's worth her weight in gold.  24 carat and built like Fort Knox.  When she dances, you'll agree that Dusty's commodities should be held in the U. S. Federal Reserve. Put this full sized…"active object" in your personal space and show her miniature version around Home as a dancing companion. Also comes with Gold Dance Platform![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>