<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Vortex DX Hover Engine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Réacteur de suspension Vortex DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vortex DX - Hover-Triebwerk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Motore Hover Vortex DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Motor de planeador Vortex DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Vortex DX ホバーエンジン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Vortex DX 호버 엔진</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Vortex DX Hover Engine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Vortex DX 漂浮引擎</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Vortex DX 漂浮引擎</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Vortex DX Hover Engine</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Hover Engine benefits from increased blade size and less weight to produce a more stable craft that will cope better with the occasional crash. A dip in the craft's turning capabilities will be pronounced. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce Moteur de Suspension comporte des pales de plus grande taille et un poids inférieur afin de vous offrir un engin plus stable qui pourra mieux supporter les accidents occasionnels. Votre rayon de braquage s'en trouvera néanmoins amputé. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Hover-Triebwerk verfügt über größere Rotorblätter und ein geringeres Gewicht, was zu einer verbesserten Stabilität bei Kollisionen führt. Allerdings wird dein Gleiter ein schlechteres Kurvenverhalten aufweisen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo motore a propulsione verticale beneficia di una maggiore ampiezza delle eliche e di un peso minore. In questo modo garantisce maggiore stabilità, utile specialmente in caso di collisione. La minore capacità di sterzata è evidente. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este motor de planeador se beneficia de una hoja mayor y de un peso menor para ofrecer una nave más estable que soportará mejor los impactos ocasionales. Se producirá una reducción del ángulo de giro de la nave. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このホヴァリングエンジンはブレードのサイズを増大させ重量を減らした事によってより、たまのクラッシュに立ち向かう安定したマシンを生み出します。マシンのターン性能を体感してみてください。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블레이드 크기를 늘이고 중량은 줄여 보다 안정적인 기동이 가능해진 이 호버 엔진은 가끔 발생하는 충돌사태에 더 잘 대처할 것입니다. 크래프트의 회전력이 눈에 띄게 떨어지는 것은 감안해야 합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This Hover Engine benefits from increased blade size and less weight to produce a more stable craft that will cope better with the occasional crash. A dip in the craft's turning capabilities will be pronounced. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這台漂浮引擎的葉片更大，重量更輕，使得機身更穩定，偶爾碰撞時也更容易操控。機身過彎能力降低的情形非常明顯。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這台漂浮引擎的葉片更大，重量更輕，使得機身更穩定，偶爾碰撞時也更容易操控。機身過彎能力降低的情形非常明顯。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This Hover Engine benefits from increased blade size and less weight to produce a more stable craft that will cope better with the occasional crash. A dip in the craft's turning capabilities will be pronounced. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>