<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Bitter Sweet Tank Top - Black (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Débardeur Bitter Sweet - Noir (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Bitter Sweet Tanktop - Schwarz (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Bitter Sweet Canottiera - Nero (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Bitter Sweet Camiseta sin mangas - Negro (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bad Billys is back. Originally launched in 1987, our street skate sub label helped launch a counter culture movement that shaped a generation. Fast forward to present day, we've resurrected Bad Billys to its former glory and added progressive elements for groundbreaking designs steeped in modern street style. The slim fit Bitter Sweet tank is made from a premium 30 singles cotton and features a softhand skull screen centered by a Bad Billys woven label. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Bad Billys est de retour. Lancé pour la première fois en 1987, notre sous-label de street skate a participé à l'avènement d'un mouvement de contre-culture qui a modelé une génération. Retour à nos jours, nous avons rendu au Bad Billys sa gloire d'antan et ajouté quelques éléments novateurs pour créer des designs avant-gardistes ancrés dans le style urbain moderne. Le débardeur Bitter Sweet moulant est fabriqué en coton de fils simples titrant 30 décitex et comporte un crâne sérigraphié doux au toucher centré dans une étiquette Bad Billys tissée. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bad Billys ist wieder da. Die ursprünglich 1987 lancierte Skateboarder-Marke hat dazu beigetragen, eine Gegenkulturbewegung zu definieren, die sich auf eine ganze Generation auswirkte. Nun haben wir Bad Billys zu neuem Leben erweckt und bahnbrechende Elemente hinzugefügt, die der glorreichen Marke einen aktuell modischen Street-Look verleihen. Das Bitter Sweet Tanktop aus hochwertiger 30 Single Baumwolle ist eng geschnitten und trägt vorne den Aufdruck eines Totenschädels zusammen mit einem Bad Billys Stoffetikett. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bad Billys è tornato. Originariamente lanciata nel 1987, la nostra etichetta affiliata di abbigliamento urban ha contribuito a lanciare una controcultura che ha dato forma a una generazione. Tornando ai giorni nostri, abbiamo riportato Bad Billys alla sua antica gloria e abbiamo aggiunto elementi progressivi per un design rivoluzionario immerso nel moderno stile urbano. La canottiera Bitter Sweet dal taglio aderente è realizzata in cotone spesso di alta qualità e presenta una stampa serigrafica morbida al tatto con al centro un'etichetta in tessuto di Bad Billys. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bad Billys ha vuelto. Lanzado originalmente 1987, nuestra sub-marca de "skate" callejero contribuyó al auge de un movimiento contracultural que marcó a toda una generación. En un salto temporal hasta hoy, hemos revivido a los Bad Billys y su gloria de antaño y añadido algún elemento actual para lograr unos rompedores diseños con un acentuado estilo callejero moderno. La camiseta de corte ajustado Bitter Sweet está hecha a partir de algodón de alta calidad y presenta un recuadro de calaveras trazadas a mano con la etiqueta de Bad Billys en el centro. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>