<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Check Shirt Bundle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack chemises à carreaux (pour Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Karohemd-Paket (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Camicie a scacchi (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de camisas de cuadros (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">격자무늬 셔츠 번들 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Plaid Shirt Bundle (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">格子襯衣服裝組(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">格子襯衣服裝組(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Plaid Shirt Bundle (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You’ll be a knockout in any of these three great looking shirts. Bundle includes a Check Red Shirt and Tattoo, Check Black Shirt and Tattoo and a Check Blue Shirt and Tattoo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ces trois superbes chemises à carreaux vous iront à merveille. Le pack comprend une chemise rouge et un tatouage, une chemise noire et un tatouage et une chemise bleue et un tatouage. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese drei toll aussehenden Hemden werden dich umhauen. Im Paket enthalten sind ein rotes Karohemd und Tattoo, ein schwarzes Karohemd und Tattoo sowie ein blaues Karohemd und Tattoo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tre fantastiche camicie per essere sempre al top del look. Il pacchetto include tre tatuaggi e tre camicie a scacchi (rossa, nera e blu). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con estas tres magníficas camisas partirás la pana. El conjunto incluye una camisa de cuadros roja y tatuaje, una camisa de cuadros negra y tatuaje, y una camisa de cuadros azul y tatuaje. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">어디서든 돋보이는 멋진 셔츠를 입고 거리를 활보하세요. 이 번들은 붉은 격자무늬 셔츠와 문신, 검은 격자무늬 셔츠와 문신, 그리고 푸른 격자무늬 셔츠와 문신을 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">You’ll be a knockout in any of these three great looking shirts. Bundle includes a Plaid Red Shirt and Tattoo, Plaid Black Shirt and Tattoo and a Plaid Blue Shirt and Tattoo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">穿上這三件漂亮的襯衣，你將艷壓全場。服裝組包括紅格子襯衣和紋身、黑格子襯衣和紋身，以及藍格子襯衣和紋身。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">穿上這三件漂亮的襯衣，你將艷壓全場。服裝組包括紅格子襯衣和紋身、黑格子襯衣和紋身，以及藍格子襯衣和紋身。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You’ll be a knockout in any of these three great looking shirts. Bundle includes a Plaid Red Shirt and Tattoo, Plaid Black Shirt and Tattoo and a Plaid Blue Shirt and Tattoo. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>