<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Brimstone Dancer Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Souffre Danseuse Ensemble</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zitronenfalter Tänzerin Bündel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Zolfo Ballerino Raccolta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Azufre Bailarina Paquete</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Brimstone Dancer Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Bundle includes 3 Brimstone Dancers, 3 Companions and 3 animated dance platforms! Brigitte, Layla and Lilith will tantalize you with their wicked ways. These ladies are as dangerous as they are beautiful.  Put these full sized…"active objects" in your personal space and show the miniature versions around Home as dancing companions.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette ensemble comprend 3 Souffre Danseuses, 3 Compagnons, et  3 plates-formes de danse animée! Brigitte, Layla et Lilith vont vous émoustiller avec ses mauvaises voies. Ces dames sont aussi dangereuses que belles. Mettez ces pleine grandeur... "objets actifs" dans votre espace personnel et montrer ceux versions miniatures autour de Home comme des compagnons de danse. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses bündel enthält 3 Zitronenfalter Tänzer, 3 Gefährten und 3 lebhaften Tanz-Plattformen! Brigitte, Layla und Lilith wird sie mit ihren bösen wegen quälen. Diese damen sind so gefährlich wie sie schön sind. Legen sie diese in voller größe ... "aktive objekte" in Ihrem persönlichen bereich und zeigen die miniaturausgaben um Home wie tanzen gefährten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo pacchetto comprende 3 Ballerini Brimstone, 3 Compagni e 3 le piattaforme danza animata! Brigitte, Layla e Lilith vi stuzzicherà con le sue vie malvagie. Queste signore sono tanto pericolosi quanto sono belle. Mettere queste dimensioni complete ... "oggetti attivi" nel tuo spazio personale e mostrare le versioni in miniatura in giro per Home come danza compagni. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este paquete incluye tres Bailarines Azufre, tres Compañeros y tres plataformas de baile animada! Brigitte, Layla y Lilith le tentarán con sus malos caminos. Estas mujeres son tan peligrosos como hermosos. Ponga estos en tamaño completo ... "objetos activos" en su espacio personal y mostrar el resultado de las versiones en miniatura alrededor de Home como el baile compañeros.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This Bundle includes 3 Brimstone Dancers, 3 Companions and 3 animated dance platforms! Brigitte, Layla and Lilith will tantalize you with their wicked ways. These ladies are as dangerous as they are beautiful.  Put these full sized…"active objects" in your personal space and show the miniature versions around Home as dancing companions.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>