<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Togo, design Michel Ducaroy, Ligne Roset, 1971. Iconic piece from the 70's, first of Ligne Roset's all foam seating range which has been enduringly popular. Suitable in any fabric and leather of the collection. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Togo, design Michel Ducaroy, Ligne Roset, 1971. Icône des années 1970 et premier modèle de la gamme de sièges tout en mousse de Ligne Roset : son succès ne s’est pas démenti. Disponible dans tous les tissus et cuirs de la collection.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Togo, Design von Michel Ducaroy, Ligne Roset, 1971. Ein Kultmöbelstück der 70er, das erste Element der Schaumstoff-Sitzmöbelserie von Ligne Roset, erfreut sich anhaltender Beliebtheit. Passend in allen Textil- und Lederbezügen der Kollektion.\n\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Togo, design di Michel Ducaroy, Ligne Roset, 1971. Modello anni '70, primo della gamma Ligne Roset di imbottiti in poliuretano espanso che riscuote sempre molto successo. Disponibile in qualsiasi tipo di tessuto e pelle della collezione [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Togo, diseño de Michel Ducaroy, Ligne Roset, 1971. Mueble icónico de los 70, primera pieza de la gama de asientos de gomaespuma de Ligne Roset que ha gozado siempre de gran popularidad. Combinable con cualquier tela y cuero de la colección.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Togo：1971年発表のリーン・ロゼ製品。デザイナーはミシェル・デュキャロワ。70年代を象徴するようなデザインであり、以来ずっと人気を保ってきたリーン・ロゼのすべての(ウレタン)フォーム系の腰掛け類の原型となったもの。あらゆる布地やレザーともマッチする。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Togo, Michel Ducaroy, Ligne Roset의 디자인, 1971년. 1970년대를 대표하는\n착석 부분이 모두 발포체로 구성된 Ligne Roset의 첫 번째 작품,\n지속적인 대중의 사랑을 받고 있으며 콜렉션의 모든 직물 및 가죽에 어울립니다.\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Togo, design Michel Ducaroy, Ligne Roset, 1971. Iconic piece from the 70's,\nfirst of Ligne Roset's all foam seating range which has been enduringly\npopular. Suitable in any fabric and leather of the collection. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Togo：Michel Ducaroy 設計，Ligne Roset，1971 年。 70 年代的經典代表作，\nLigne Roset 全泡棉座椅系列的首件作品，已成為歷久不衰\n的傳世之寵。 本系列適合各式布料及皮料材質。\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Togo：Michel Ducaroy 設計，Ligne Roset，1971 年。 70 年代的經典代表作，\nLigne Roset 全泡棉座椅系列的首件作品，已成為歷久不衰\n的傳世之寵。 本系列適合各式布料及皮料材質。\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Togo, design Michel Ducaroy, Ligne Roset, 1971. Iconic piece from the 70's,\nfirst of Ligne Roset's all foam seating range which has been enduringly\npopular. Suitable in any fabric and leather of the collection. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Togo 2 Seater Sofa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Petit canapé Togo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zweisitzersofa "Togo"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Divano Togo a 2 posti</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sofá Togo 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">トゴ・2人掛けソファ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">토고 2인용 소파</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Togo 2 Seater Sofa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Togo 雙人沙發</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Togo 雙人沙發</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Togo 2 Seater Sofa</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>