<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mercia Hulking Turtle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tortue géante de Mercia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mercia-Riesenschildkröte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tartaruga gigante di Mercia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tortuga pesada de Mercia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mercia Hulking Turtle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hulking Turtles are an ancient and dying race that wish to make Mercia their homeland, ridding the world of its current inhabitants first. Immune to many magics, these ancient behemoths must be approached with caution. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les tortues géantes sont une ancienne race en voie d'extinction qui aimerait s'établir à Mercia, en débarrassant d'abord le monde de ses habitants. Insensibles à de nombreux sortilèges, ces monstres anciens doivent être approchés avec prudence. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Riesenschildkröten gehören einer uralten, aussterbenden Rasse an, und wollen sich in Mercia ansiedeln. Dazu müssen sie allerdings die derzeitigen Bewohner erst ausrotten. Sie sind immun gegen viele Zauber, weshalb man sich diesen alten Riesen vorsichtig nähern muss. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le tartarughe giganti sono una razza antica e in estinzione che desidera stabilirsi in Mercia, prima eliminando tutti gli altri abitanti. Immune a molti incantesimi, questo antico colosso deve essere avvicinato con cautela. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las tortugas pesadas son una antigua raza en extinción que desean hacer de Mercia su hogar, no sin antes librar al mundo de sus habitantes actuales. Inmunes a gran parte de la magia, hay que acercarse a estos antiguos colosos con cautela. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hulking Turtles are an ancient and dying race that wish to make Mercia their homeland, ridding the world of its current inhabitants first. Immune to many magics, these ancient behemoths must be approached with caution. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>