<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Apple Table &amp; Chairs Set</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble table et chaises pomme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tisch und Stühle aus Äpfeln</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set di tavolo e sedie mela</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de mesa y sillas de manzana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Apple Table &amp; Chairs Set</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A set including a super cute table and chairs made of apples.
\n
\nThis set includes the following items for customizing your personal space.
\nApple Table (Tables)
\nApple Chair (Chairs)
\n
\n*Each item will be added to their relevant wardrobe and furniture category. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble table et chaises vraiment mignonnes en pomme.\n\nCe service comprend les éléments de personnalisation de l'espace personnel suivants :\nTable pomme (Tables)\nChaise pomme (Chaises)\n\n*Chaque objet sera ajouté à la catégorie garde-robe ou mobilier correspondante. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein richtig hübscher Tisch mit Stühlen aus Äpfeln.\n\nDas Set enthält folgende Objekte, mit denen du dich ausstatten kannst.\nApfel-Tisch (Tische)\nApfel-Stuhl (Stühle)\n\n*Jedes Objekt wird der entsprechenden Kleiderschrank- und Möbel-Kategorie hinzugefügt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un set che include un tavolo e delle sedie fatte di mele.\n\nQuesto set include i seguenti elementi per la personalizzazione del tuo spazio personale.\nTavolo mela (tavoli)\nSedia mela (sedie)\n\n*Ogni oggetto verrà aggiunto alla rispettiva categoria all'interno del guardaroba e dei mobili. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un conjunto que incluye una mesa y sillas súper originales hechas con manzanas.\n\nEl conjunto incluye los siguientes elementos para personalizar tu espacio personal.\nMesa de manzana (mesas)\nSillas de manzana (sillas)\n\n*Cada objeto se añadirá a la categoría de vestuario o mobiliario correspondiente. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A set including a super cute table and chairs made of apples.
\n
\nThis set includes the following items for customizing your personal space.
\nApple Table (Tables)
\nApple Chair (Chairs)
\n
\n*Each item will be added to their relevant wardrobe and furniture category. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>