<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Velocity Racer Green - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Velocity Racer Vert - Motif de peinture pour véhicule Sodium2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Velocity Racer Green - Sodium2-Gleiterlackierung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Veicolo da gara Verde - Sodium2 schema di verniciatura veicolo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Velocity Racer Verde; Diseño de pintura de vehículo de Sodium2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ベロシティー・レーサー　グリーン - Sodium2車体ペイントデザイン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Velocity Racer Green - Sodium2 레이서 도색</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Velocity Racer Green - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Velocity Racer Green - Sodium2飛船油漆色系</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Velocity Racer Green - Sodium2飛船油漆色系</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Velocity Racer Green - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Show your true colours with this official Project Velocity paint scheme. Emblazoned with the preferred colour-scheme of the Velocity Racing leagues this paint-job goes perfectly with the official Project Velocity Racer's Outfit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Montrez vos véritables couleurs avec le thème Project Velocity officiel. Décoré avec le thème de couleur préféré des ligues de Velocity Racing, cette peinture s'accorde à merveille avec la Tenue Project Velocity Racer officielle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bekenne Farbe mit dieser offiziellen Project Velocity-Lackierung. Diese Lackierung ist der Favorit der Velocity-Rennligen und passt perfekt zum offiziellen Outfit der Project Velocity-Piloten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esprimi la tua vera personalità con questo schema di verniciatura ufficiale Project Velocity. Decorato con lo schema preferito dei circuiti Velocity Racing, questo schema si sposa a meraviglia con l'equipaggiamento ufficiale dei veicoli da gara Project Velocity. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Demuestra quién eres con este diseño de pintura oficial de Project Velocity. Esmaltado con la combinación de colores preferida de las ligas Velocity Racing, este trabajo de pintura combina perfectamente con el traje de piloto oficial de Project Velocity. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この公式プロジェクト・べロシティー塗装デザインで自分を際立たせろ！べロシティー・レーシングリーグの公式カラーで飾られたこの塗装は、公式べロシティー・レーサースーツに合うこと間違いなし。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 공식 프로젝트 벨로시티 페인트의 배합을 이용해서 자신만의 색상을 뽐내세요. 벨로시티 레이싱 리그에서 엄선한 색상인 이들 페인트를 칠해서 공식 프로젝트 벨로시티 레이서의 복장을 완벽하게 꾸미세요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Show your true colors with this official Project Velocity paint scheme. Emblazoned with the preferred color-scheme of the Velocity Racing leagues this paint-job goes perfectly with the official Project Velocity Racer's Outfit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Project Velocity官方烤漆款式，秀出你的豪邁本色。這種塗裝繪有「Velocity Racing」聯盟的烤漆款式，和官方版的Project Velocity賽車服最速配。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Project Velocity官方烤漆款式，秀出你的豪邁本色。這種塗裝繪有「Velocity Racing」聯盟的烤漆款式，和官方版的Project Velocity賽車服最速配。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Show your true colors with this official Project Velocity paint scheme. Emblazoned with the preferred color-scheme of the Velocity Racing leagues this paint-job goes perfectly with the official Project Velocity Racer's Outfit. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>