<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Tanabata Starry Sky Bikini Set (Black &amp; Orange, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set bikini et paréo ciel étoilé Tanabata (noir et orange, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Set: Tanabata-Bikini, Sternenhimmel (schwarz &amp; orange, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set bikini Tanabata con stelle (nero e arancione, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego del bikini cielo estrellado de Tanabata (negro y naranja, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">七夕の星空ビキニセット（ブラック＆オレンジ・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Tanabata Starry Sky Bikini Set (Black &amp; Orange, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">2-piece set of a bikini and a bracelet with a Tanabata starry sky design.\nDefensive Strength: (None)~★\nMagic Power: ★~★★★\nSexiness: (None)~★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Tanabata Starry Sky Wrap-around Skirt Bikini (Black, Women) (Outfits)\n- Tanabata Star Bracelet (Orange, Women) (Hands)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 2 pièces contenant un bikini et un bracelet avec un design de ciel étoilé Tanabata.\nDéfense : (Sans)~★\nPouvoir magique : ★~★★★\nSex-appeal : (Sans)~★★★\nCe set contient les objets suivants :\n\n- Bikini et paréo ciel étoilé Tanabata (noir, femme) (Tenues)\n- Bracelet étoilé Tanabata (orange, femme) (Mains)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 2-teiliges Set, das einen Bikini und ein Armband mit Sternenhimmelmotiv zu Tanabata enthält.\nVerteidigung: (keine)~★\nMagie: ★~★★★\nSexappeal: (None)~★★★\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Tanabata-Bikini mit Wickelrock, Sternenhimmel (schwarz, für Frauen) (Outfits)\n- Tanabata-Sternenarmband (orange, für Frauen) (Hände)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set formato da 2 elementi comprendente un bikini e un braccialetto, entrambi decorati con un motivo decorato con un motivo raffigurante il cielo stellato tipico del Tanabata.\nDifesa: (nulla)~★\nPotere magico: ★~★★★\nSensualità: (nulla)~★★★\nQuesto set comprende i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Bikini Tanabata con stelle e pareo (nero, da donna) (aspetti)\n- Braccialetto Tanabata con stella (arancione, da donna) (mani)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, gli oggetti elencati verranno aggiunti nella loro categoria specifica.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos artículos que incluye bikini y brazalete decorados con el cielo estrellado de Tanabata.\nDefensa: (ninguna)~★\nPoder mágico: ★~★★★\nSensualidad: (ninguna)~★★★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Bikini cielo estrellado de Tanabata con pareo (negro, mujer) (trajes)\n- Brazalete estrella de Tanabata (naranja, mujer) (manos)\n\n* Al adquirir este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su categoría correspondiente.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">七夕の星空をイメージしたビキニとブレスレットの２点セット。\n防御力：　（なし）～★\n魔力：　★～★★★\nセクシー度：　（なし）～★★★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・七夕の星空ビキニパレオ（ブラック・女性）/組み合わせ\n・七夕の星ブレスレット（オレンジ・女性）/手\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">2-piece set of a bikini and a bracelet with a Tanabata starry sky design.\nDefensive Strength: (None)~★\nMagic Power: ★~★★★\nSexiness: (None)~★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Tanabata Starry Sky Wrap-around Skirt Bikini (Black, Women) (Outfits)\n- Tanabata Star Bracelet (Orange, Women) (Hands)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
