<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mercia Beetle Pupa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pupe de scarabée de Mercia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mercia-Käferpuppe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pupa di coleottero di Mercia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Crisálida de escarabajo de Mercia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mercia Beetle Pupa</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Beetle Pupa dwell in the dungeons of Mercia, feeding off fallen warriors. Slowly digesting them by breaking them down with venomous ooze until the body, weapons and armour are wholly consumed, the Pupa evolves into one of the deadly Beetles of the Mercian Dungeons. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le pupe de scarabée rôde dans les donjons de Mercia, se nourrissant des guerriers tombés au combat. Ils les digèrent lentement en les rongeant au moyen de leur venin, jusqu'à ce que les corps, les armes et les armures soient entièrement dévorés. Le pupe devient ensuite un des scarabées mortels des donjons mercians. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Käferpuppen leben in den Kerkern Mercias und ernähren sich von gefallenen Kriegern. Sie verdauen ihr Essen vor, indem sie es mit einem giftigen Sekret zersetzen, um dann die Leiche samt Waffen und Rüstung zu verschlingen. Die Puppe verwandelt sich schließlich in einen der tödlichen Käfer der Kerker Mercias. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La pupa di coleottero vive nei dungeon di Mercia e si nutre dei guerrieri caduti. Li digerisce lentamente disgregandoli con un liquido velenoso fino a che corpo, armi e armatura sono completamente consumati. La pupa si trasforma in un coleotteri letale che vive nei dungeon di Mercia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La crisálida de escarabajo mora en las mazmorras de Mercia y se alimenta de guerreros caídos. Los digiere lentamente desmembrándolos con una baba venenosa hasta que el cuerpo, las armas y la armadura se consumen completamente, la crisálida se convierte en uno de los mortales escarabajos de las mazmorras de Mercia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Beetle Pupa dwell in the dungeons of Mercia, feeding off fallen warriors. Slowly digesting them by breaking them down with venomous ooze until the body, weapons and armor are wholly consumed, the Pupa evolves into one of the deadly Beetles of the Mercian Dungeons. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>