<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Fossil Collection Plate Set (for Trilobite)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de Plateaux pour collection de fossiles (pour des Trilobites)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Fossiliensammelplatte-Set (für Trilobiten)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set di tavole per la collezione di fossili (per trilobite)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de placas de colección de fósiles (para tribolites)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">化石収集プレートセット（三葉虫用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">화석 수집 플레이트 세트 (삼엽충용)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Fossil Collection Plate Set (for Trilobite)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">化石收集盤組合包（用於三葉蟲）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">化石收集盤組合包（用於三葉蟲）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Fossil Collection Plate Set (for Trilobites)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A two plate set perfectly suited to mounting and displaying Trilobit fossils. \nThis set contains the following items.\n\n・Antiquated Fossil Collection Plate (for Trilobite) (Ornaments)\n・Brand-new Fossil Collection Plate (for Trilobite) (Ornaments)\n\n*When purchased, each item is added to the appropriate category.  [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de 2 plateaux de collection parfaits pour présenter des fossiles de trilobites.\nCe set comprend les articles suivants:\n\nPlateau de collection de fossile à l’ancienne (décoration)\nPlateau de collection de fossile neuf (décoration)\n\n*Après l’achat chaque article sera ajouté dans la catégorie adéquate[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Set, bestehend aus zwei Sammelplatten, die perfekt für Aufbewahrung und Ausstellung von Trilobiten-Fossilien geeignet sind.\n Dieses Set enthält folgende Gegenstände.\n\nAltmodische Fossiliensammelplatte(Dekoration)\nBrandneue Fossiliensammelplatte(Dekoration)\n\n*Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand in entsprechender Kategorie hinzugefügt. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set di due tavole da collezione perfettamente adatte a conservare ed a mettere in mostra fossili di trilobite.\nQuesto set include i seguenti oggetti.\n\nVecchia lastra per la collezione di fossili (ornamento)\nTavola di ultima generazione per la collezione di fossili (ornamento)\n\n*Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce\nsopra elencata nella specifica categoria.  [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de colección de dos placas perfecto para tener en exhibición los fósiles de un tribolite.\nEste juego incluye los siguientes objetos.\n\nPlaca antigua de colección de fósiles (adorno)\nPlaca nueva de colección de fósiles (adorno)\n\n*Después de la compra, cada objeto será agregado a la categoría a la que aplica.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">三葉虫の化石をピッタリ収めて飾ることが出来る収集プレートの2枚セット。\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・古めかしい化石収集プレート（三葉虫用）（装飾品）\n・真新しい化石収集プレート（三葉虫用）（装飾品）\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">삼엽충의 화석을 딱 맞게 넣어 장식할 수 있는 수집 플레이트 2개 세트. \n본 세트에는 하기 아이템이 포함되어 있습니다.\n\n●고풍스러운 화석 수집 플레이트(삼엽충용) （장식품）\n●새 화석 수집 플레이트(삼엽충용) （장식품）\n\n※구입하면 해당 카테고리에 각 아이템이 추가됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">A two plate set perfectly suited to mounting and displaying Trilobit fossils. \nThis set contains the following items.\n\n・Antiquated Fossil Collection Plate (for Trilobite) (Ornaments)\n・Brand-new Fossil Collection Plate (for Trilobite) (Ornaments)\n\n*When purchased, each item is added to the appropriate category.  [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">適合用來收納和裝飾三葉蟲化石的收集盤2件組合包。\n本組合包包括下列物品。\n\n●古舊的化石收集盤（用於三葉蟲）（裝飾品）\n●全新的化石收集盤（用於三葉蟲）（裝飾品）\n\n※購買後，各物品被添加到相應類別中。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">適合用來收納和裝飾三葉蟲化石的收集盤2件組合包。\n本組合包包括下列物品。\n\n●古舊的化石收集盤（用於三葉蟲）（裝飾品）\n●全新的化石收集盤（用於三葉蟲）（裝飾品）\n\n※購買後，各物品被添加到相應類別中。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A two plate set perfectly suited to mounting and displaying Trilobit fossils. \nThis set contains the following items.\n\n・Antiquated Fossil Collection Plate (for Trilobite) (Ornaments)\n・Brand-new Fossil Collection Plate (for Trilobite) (Ornaments)\n\n*When purchased, each item is added to the appropriate category.  [#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
