<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Flying Doomnut of Sprinkles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Donut volant aspergeur des ténèbres</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fliegender Doomnut der Streusel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ciambella volante del giudizio di Sprinkles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Donut volante con virutas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">空飛ぶスプリンクルドーナツ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">하늘을 나는 스프링클 둠너트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Flying Doomnut of Sprinkles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">附糖衣的飛行甜甜圈</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">附糖衣的飛行甜甜圈</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Flying Doomnut of Sprinkles</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Flying Doomnut of Sprinkles will whiz around your apartment spreading fear to onlookers. This was won from playing the OMG Trap-O-Matic in Aurora. You can win another version of this item by playing Collect-O-Rama in Aurora. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le donut volant aspergeur des ténèbres tourbillonnera autour de votre appartement en effrayant tout le monde. Cet objet a été gagné dans le jeu Trap-O-Matic d’Aurora. Vous pouvez gagner une autre version de cet objet en jouant à Collect-O-rama dans Aurora. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Fliegender Doomnut der Streusel wird durch deine Wohnung schwirren und Zuschauern Angst einjagen. Das wurde beim Spielen von OMG Trap-O-Matic in Aurora gewonnen. Wenn du Collect-O-Rama in Aurora spielst, kannst du eine andere Version dieses Gegenstands gewinnen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La ciambella volante del giudizio di Sprinkles volerà nel tuo appartamento seminando paura tra i visitatori. Questo oggetto è stato vinto dopo aver giocato a Trap-O-Matic in Aurora. Puoi vincere un'altra versione di questo oggetto giocando a Collezione in Aurora. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El anillo volante con virutas flotará por tu apartamento atemorizando a los espectadores. Conseguido al jugar a la Tramp-a-mática en Aurora. Si juegas al Colecci-o-nador de Aurora, podrás conseguir otra versión de este artículo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">空飛ぶスプリンクルドーナツはアパートメントの周辺を飛び回り、周囲の人を震え上がらせます。オーロラのトラップ大作戦で獲得したもの。オーロラのコレクト・オ・ラマをプレイして本アイテムの別バージョンも獲得できます。\n\nこのアイテムは、アニメーションや機能が追加されているアドバンスド家具です。\nこの種類のアイテムは配置できる数に制限があります。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">하늘을 나는 스프링클 둠너트는 구경꾼들에게 공포를 퍼뜨리면서 당신의 아파트 주변을 날아다닐 것입니다. 이것은 Aurora에서 트랩-오-마틱을 플레이하면서 얻을 수 있습니다. Aurora에서 컬렉트-오-라마를 플레이하면서 이 아이템의 다른 버전을 얻을 수도 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Flying Doomnut of Sprinkles will whiz around your apartment spreading fear to onlookers. This was won from playing the OMG Trap-O-Matic in Aurora. You can win another version of this item by playing Collect-O-Rama in Aurora. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">附糖衣的飛行甜甜圈將在您的公寓四周來回飛行，向旁觀者散佈恐怖。這是在極光群島中遊玩「超級陷阱」所獲得的。您可透過在極光群島中遊玩「Collect-O-Rama」獲得本道具的其他版本。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">附糖衣的飛行甜甜圈將在您的公寓四周來回飛行，向旁觀者散佈恐怖。這是在極光群島中遊玩「超級陷阱」所獲得的。您可透過在極光群島中遊玩「Collect-O-Rama」獲得本道具的其他版本。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Flying Doomnut of Sprinkles will whiz around your apartment spreading fear to onlookers. This was won from playing the OMG Trap-O-Matic in Aurora. You can win another version of this item by playing Collect-O-Rama in Aurora. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>