<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Pirate Chainsword</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tronçépée pirate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Piraten-Kettenschwert</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Spada pirata a catena</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Espada sierra pirata</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">パイレーツ・チェーンソード（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">해적 체인소드 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Pirate Chainsword (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">海盜鎖鏈劍(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">海盜鎖鏈劍(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Pirate Chainsword</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Pirate Chainsword is a one-handed melee weapon confiscated during a raid on a space pirate stronghold. These "blades" were auctioned off to raise Nebulon for the Novus Prime space station, and no guarantees are made regarding their function and safety. Use at your own risk! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La Tronçépée pirate est une arme de mélée à une main, confisquée lors d'un raid aérien sur une forteresse spatiale pirate.  Ces "épées" ont étées vendues aux enchères afin d'augmenter le Nebulon de la navette spatiale Novus Prime, rien n'est garanti quant à leur sécurité ou à leur fonctionnalité.  Utilisez-les à vos risques et périls ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Piraten-Kettenschwert ist eine Einhand-Nahkampfwaffe, die während einer Razzia in einer Piratenhochburg konfisziert wurde. Diese "Klingen" wurden versteigert, um Nebulon zur Novus Prime Raumstation zu machen. Es wird keine Gewährleistung für ihre Funktionstüchtigkeit oder Sicherheit gegeben. Benutzung auf eigene Gefahr! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Spada pirata a catena è un'arma da mischia da utilizzare con una sola mano confiscata durante un raid in un bastione pirata nello spazio. Queste "spade" furono messe all'asta per aumentare i Nebulon per la stazione spaziale Novus Prime, per cui non ci sono garanzie riguardo le loro funzioni e la loro sicurezza. Usale a tuo rischio e pericolo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La espada sierra pirata es arma de lucha para una mano, confiscada durante una redada en un bastión de piratas espaciales. Estas "cuchillas" fueron subastadas para elevar el Nebulon para la estación espacial de Novus Prime, no damos garantía sobre su funcionamiento y seguridad. ¡Úsala bajo tu propio riesgo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">パイレーツ・チェーンソードは宇宙海賊の本拠地を攻撃した際に押収した、片手用近接武器である。この「刃」はノーバス・プライム宇宙ステーション用のネブロンを増加させるため、競売にかけられた。機能や安全性については保証できかねます。使用は自己責任で！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">해적 체인소드는 우주 해적 본거지 급습 과정에서 압수한 근접무기입니다. 이 무기는 노부스 프라임 우주 정거장 건설을 위한 재정 마련을 위해 경매되었으며, 기능성과 사용상 안전에 대한 어떠한 보증도 없습니다. 주의하십시오. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Pirate Chainsword is a one-handed melee weapon confiscated during a raid on a space pirate stronghold. These "blades" were auctioned off to raise Nebulon for the Novus Prime space station, and no guarantees are made regarding their function and safety. Use at your own risk! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這把從海盜藏身的據點沒收而來的海盜鎖鏈劍，很適合單手接近戰使用。為了提升Novus Prime太空站的Nebulon，這些「刀鋒」被拍賣出售。但是，對於這些武器的功能和安全性不能提供任何保證。你自己親自冒險嘗試看看吧！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這把從海盜藏身的據點沒收而來的海盜鎖鏈劍，很適合單手接近戰使用。為了提升Novus Prime太空站的Nebulon，這些「刀鋒」被拍賣出售。但是，對於這些武器的功能和安全性不能提供任何保證。你自己親自冒險嘗試看看吧！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Pirate Chainsword is a one-handed melee weapon confiscated during a raid on a space pirate stronghold. These "blades" were auctioned off to raise Nebulon for the Novus Prime space station, and no guarantees are made regarding their function and safety. Use at your own risk! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>