<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Anime Furniture Value Pack #2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack complet mobilier "Anime #2"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Anime-Möbel-Paket 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto arredamento anime 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack 2 de mobiliario Anime</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Anime Furniture Value Pack #2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">애니메이션 가구 할인팩 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Anime Furniture Value Pack #2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">動漫風家具超值組合包2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">動漫風家具超值組合包2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Anime Furniture Value Pack #2</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A matching outfit is so last decade. It's all about matching furniture! Includes 10 items: Chair With Cables, Chair With Display, Futuristic Couch, Futuristic Desk Lamp, Futuristic Jukebox, Futuristic Speaker, Green Crate, Holo-Display Table, Mini White Mech Suit, and Oval Glass Table. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La tenue assortie, c'est has been. Le top dans le futur, ce sont les meubles assortis ! Comprend 10 éléments : un fauteuil avec câbles, un fauteuil avec écran, un canapé futuriste, une lampe de bureau futuriste, un juke-box futuriste, une enceinte futuriste, une caisse verte, une table holographique, un mini-mécha blanc et une table en verre ovale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein perfekt abgestimmtes Outfit ist so was von out. Jetzt stimmt man Möbel perfekt ab! Enthält 10 Teile: Sessel mit Kabeln, Sessel mit Display, futuristische Couch, futuristische Tischlampe, futuristische Musikanlage, futuristischen Lautsprecher, grüne Kiste, Tisch mit Holo-Display, weißen Minimech und ovalen Glastisch. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un completo abbinato fa tanto scorso decennio. È l'arredamento che va abbinato! Include 10 oggetti: poltrona con cavi, poltrona con display, divano futuristico, lampada da scrivania futuristica, juke-box futuristico, altoparlante futuristico, cassa verde, tavolo olografico, mini armatura mech bianca e tavolo ovale in vetro. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjuntar la ropa está pasado de moda. ¡El secreto está en conjuntar los muebles! Incluye 10 objetos: silla con cables, silla con pantalla, sofá futurista, lámpara de mesa futurista, gramola futurista, altavoz futurista, caja verde, panel holográfico, minitraje blanco y mesa de cristal ovalada. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">A matching outfit is so last decade. It's all about matching furniture! Includes 10 items: Chair With Cables, Chair With Display, Futuristic Couch, Futuristic Desk Lamp, Futuristic Jukebox, Futuristic Speaker, Green Crate, Holo-Display Table, Mini White Mech Suit, and Oval Glass Table. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">복장을 통일하는 건 유치해 보일 수 있지만, 가구의 통일은 멋쟁이의 기본입니다. 아래의 10가지 아이템을 포함합니다: 케이블 의자, 디스플레이 의자, 미래형 소파, 미래형 탁상 램프, 미래형 주크박스, 미래형 스피커, 녹색 상자, 홀로-디스플레이 탁자, 미니 화이트 메크 수트, 그리고 타원형 유리 탁자.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A matching outfit is so last decade. It's all about matching furniture! Includes 10 items: Chair With Cables, Chair With Display, Futuristic Couch, Futuristic Desk Lamp, Futuristic Jukebox, Futuristic Speaker, Green Crate, Holo-Display Table, Mini White Mech Suit, and Oval Glass Table. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">相配的服裝已經過時了，現在相配的家具才是潮流！包括十款道具：椅子連電線 、椅子連螢幕、未來世界沙發、未來世界桌燈、未來世界自動點唱機、未來世界擴音器、綠色木箱、螢幕顯示桌、迷你白色機械戰士及橢圓型玻璃桌。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">相配的服裝已經過時了，現在相配的家具才是潮流！包括十款道具：椅子連電線 、椅子連螢幕、未來世界沙發、未來世界桌燈、未來世界自動點唱機、未來世界擴音器、綠色木箱、螢幕顯示桌、迷你白色機械戰士及橢圓型玻璃桌。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A matching outfit is so last decade. It's all about matching furniture! Includes 10 items: Chair With Cables, Chair With Display, Futuristic Couch, Futuristic Desk Lamp, Futuristic Jukebox, Futuristic Speaker, Green Crate, Holo-Display Table, Mini White Mech Suit, and Oval Glass Table. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>