<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LOOT™ Industries Office Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot Bureaux Industriels LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LOOT™-Industries-Office-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Ufficio LOOT™ Industries</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack de oficina de LOOT™ Industries</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LOOT™ Industries Office Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">With the LOOT™ Industries Office Bundle you get the cubicle walls, desk, desk chair, computer, Mini-fridge, phone, printer, Photo Frame, Flower Vase, Red Stapler, Water cooler, waste paper basket, reception chair and two reception desks! Exclusive to this Bundle you’ll get the Photo Copier. Feel free to sit on it. Now you can work from home in HOME. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avec le Lot Bureaux Industriels LOOT™ vous avez les cloisons de bureau, le bureau, le siège de bureau, l'ordinateur, le mini frigo, le téléphone, l'imprimante, le cadre photo, le vase de fleurs, l'agrafeuse rouge, le distributeur d'eau, la poubelle, la chaise de l'accueil et deux bureaux d'accueil ! Vous avez aussi la photocopieuse en exclusivité dans ce lot. N'hésitez pas à vous asseoir dessus. Maintenant vous pouvez travailler à la maison dans HOME. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit dem LOOT™ Industries Office-Paket erhältst du Bürostellwände, Tisch, Stuhl, Computer, Mini-Kühlschrank, Telefon, Drucker, Bilderrahmen, Blumenvase,  den Roten Hefter, Wasserspender, Papierkorb, Empfangsstuhl und zwei Empfangstische! Und exklusiv in diesem Paket ist der Kopierer. Du darfst auch darauf sitzen. Jetzt kannst du dich auch au der Arbeit daheim fühlen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nel Pacchetto Ufficio LOOT™ Industries troverai l'occorrente per montare il cubicolo, scrivania, sedia da ufficio, computer, mini-frigo, telefono, stampante, cornice, vaso, graffettatrice rossa, dispenser acqua, cestino, sedia reception e due scrivanie reception! Inoltre, in esclusiva per te, una bella fotocopiatrice. Puoi anche sedertici sopra. Da ora potrai lavorare da casa, a CASA! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Este pack de oficina de LOOT™ Industries incluye mamparas de cubículo, mesa, silla de oficina, ordenador, mininevera, teléfono, impresora, marco de fotos, jarrón de flores, grapadora roja, fuente de agua, papelera, silla de recepción y dos mesas de recepción! Este pack incluye, en exclusiva, una fotocopiadora. Siéntate encima si quieres. Y ahora, ya puedes trabajar en CASA desde casa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">With the LOOT™ Industries Office Bundle you get the cubicle walls, desk, desk chair, computer, Mini-fridge, phone, printer, Photo Frame, Flower Vase, Red Stapler, Water cooler, waste paper basket, reception chair and two reception desks! Exclusive to this Bundle you’ll get the Photo Copier. Feel free to sit on it. Now you can work from home in HOME. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>