<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Personal Gaming Machines Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Machines de Jeux Personnelles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Persönliches Casino Videorecorder Set</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Macchina da Gioco personale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Máquinas de juego personales</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Personal Gaming Machines Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Personal Gaming Machines Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Personal Gaming Machines Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Personal Gaming Machines Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Personal Gaming Machines Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Personal Gaming Machines Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ever wanted your very own video poker, video blackjack, or slot machine in your personal space? Well now you can have all three in this bundle. Place these active items into your own space and you and your friends can enjoy unlimited plays of your favorite casino games! You will be the talk of the town and everyone will be wanting to visit your space with these machines installed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avez-vous toujours voulu avoir votre propre vidéo poker, vidéo blackjack, ou machine à sous dans votre espace personnel ? Maintenant vous pouvez les avoir tous les trois dans ce lot. Placez ces objets actifs dans votre propre espace pour que vous et vos amis pouvez vous amuser indéfiniment avec vos jeux de casino favoris ! Grâce à ces machines installées chez vous, tout le monde parlera de vous et voudra vous rendre visite. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wollten Sie schon immer Ihr eigenes Poker Video und  Blackjack Video besitzen oder einen Spielautomaten in Ihrer Wohnung haben? Jetzt können Sie  alle drei in einem Gesamtpaket erhalten. Installieren Sie die aktiven Spiele in Ihrer Wohnung, damit Sie und Ihre Freunde unbegrenzten Spaß mit Ihren beliebtesten Casino-Spielen erleben! Sie werden garantiert zum Stadtgespräch werden, und jeder wird Sie unbedingt besuchen wollen, um sich diese Maschinen anzuschauen.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai mai voluto un tuo video poker, video blackjack o slot machine nel tuo spazio personale? Bene, ora potrai averle tutte e tre in questo pacchetto. Posizionate questi oggetti attivi nel vostro appartamento cosicché tu e i tuoi amici potrete divertirvi illimitatamente giocando al vostro gioco preferito del casinò! Sarete sulla bocca di tutti in città e chiunque aspetterà di visitare il vostro appartamento, con quelle macchine installate. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Siempre has querido tu propia tragaperras o máquina de póker o blackjack en tu espacio personal? Bueno ahora puedes tener las tres en este pack. Coloca estos objetos activos en tu espacio personal y tu y tus amigos podréis disfrutar ilimitadamente de vuestros juegos de casino favoritos. Estarás en boca de todos y todo el mundo querrá venir a tu espacio a catar estas máquinas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Personal Gaming Machines Bundle Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Personal Gaming Machines Bundle Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Personal Gaming Machines Bundle Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Personal Gaming Machines Bundle Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Personal Gaming Machines Bundle Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ever wanted your very own video poker, video blackjack, or slot machine in your personal space? Well now you can have all three in this bundle. Place these active items into your own space and you and your friends can enjoy unlimited plays of your favorite casino games! You will be the talk of the town and everyone will be wanting to visit your space with these machines installed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>