<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dead Rising 2 Chuck Trousers &amp; Shoes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pantalon et Chaussures de Chuck Dead Rising 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dead Rising 2 - Chucks Hose und Schuhe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dead Rising 2 Scarpe e pantaloni di Chuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pantalones y zapatos de Chuck de Dead Rising 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_LegsFeet_Chuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_LegsFeet_Chuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Male01_LegsFeet_Chuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_LegsFeet_Chuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_LegsFeet_Chuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dead Rising 2 Chuck Trousers &amp; Shoes</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The zombie outbreak has hit Fortune City! Increase your chances of survival by wearing the Trousers and Shoes of former Motocross champion and new protagonist of Dead Rising 2, Chuck Greene. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'épidémie de zombies a frappé Fortune City ! Augmentez vos chances de survie en portant le Pantalon et les Chaussures de l'ancien champion de motocross et nouveau protagoniste de Dead Rising 2, Chuck Greene. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Zombieseuche hat Fortune City erreicht! Verbessere deine Überlebenschancen mit der Hose und den Schuhen des ehemaligen Motocross-Champions und Protagonisten aus Dead Rising 2, Chuck Greene. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gli zombie hanno invaso Fortune City! Aumenta le tue chance di sopravvivenza indossando le scarpe e i pantaloni di Chuck, ex campione di motocross, nonché inedito protagonista di Dead Rising 2. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡La oleada de zombies ha llegado a Fortune City! Aumenta tus probabilidades de supervivencia poniéndote los pantalones y los zapatos del antiguo campeón de motocross y nuevo protagonista de Dead Rising 2, Chuck Greene. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_LegsFeet_Chuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_LegsFeet_Chuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Male01_LegsFeet_Chuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_LegsFeet_Chuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_LegsFeet_Chuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The zombie outbreak has hit Fortune City! Increase your chances of survival by wearing the Trousers and Shoes of former Motocross champion and new protagonist of Dead Rising 2, Chuck Greene. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>