<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Paris Classical Office Set</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bureau classique Paris</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Klassisches Pariser Büro-Set</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto parigino ufficio classico</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto parisino de oficina clásica</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Paris Classical Office Set</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">파리의 클래식 사무실 세트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Paris Classical Office Set</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">巴黎古典辦公室組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">巴黎古典辦公室組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">0</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It's the classical office set.  Includes a Desk, Chair, Office Lamp, Blotter, Letter Opener, Spy Pocket Watch, and various letters/postcards.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Voici un pack classique pour votre bureau. Comprend un bureau, un fauteuil, une lampe de bureau, un sous-main, un coupe-papier, une montre à gousset d'espion et une série de lettres et cartes postales.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das klassische Büro-Set! Enthält Schreibtisch, Stuhl, Bürolampe, Schreibunterlage, Brieföffner, Spion-Taschenuhr sowie verschiedene Briefe und Postkarten.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ecco il pacchetto ufficio classico. Include scrivania, sedia, lampada da ufficio, sottomano, tagliacarte, orologio spia da tasca e varie lettere/cartoline. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El conjunto de oficina clásica. Incluye escritorio, lámpara de oficina, secante, abrecartas, reloj espía de bolsillo y varias cartas y postales.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">It's the classical office set.  Includes the Classical Desk, Chair, Office Lamp, Blotter, Letter Opener, Spy Pocket Watch, and various letters/postcards.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">클래식 사무실 세트입니다. 책상, 의자, 사무실 램프, 지압대, 편지 개봉기, 스파이 회중시계, 그리고 각종 편지지와 엽서를 포함합니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">It's the classical office set.  Includes the Classical Desk, Chair, Office Lamp, Blotter, Letter Opener, Spy Pocket Watch, and various letters/postcards.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這款古典辦公室組合包，包括古典書桌、古典椅、古典辦公室燈、古典吸墨紙板、古典開信刀、古典間諜陀錶以及古典信件/明信片。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這款古典辦公室組合包，包括古典書桌、古典椅、古典辦公室燈、古典吸墨紙板、古典開信刀、古典間諜陀錶以及古典信件/明信片。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">0 [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>