<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cabin Boy in Trout Trouble!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Life on the open seas is grand! Well, maybe not for our Cabin Boy. Help our hero in this adventure get through the day! Catch the fish Lil’ Dickie throws to him, keep Lil’ Missus from burning under the hot sun and whatever you do, watch out for Chairman Meow!! Get to level 30 and win a free Cabin boy shirt: Lil’ Dickie for the boys, Lil’ Missus for the girls! For you hardcore gamers out there, accumulate 12,000 points over time to win the Golden Trout Trophy! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La vie en pleine mer est grandiose ! Enfin, peut-être pas pour notre Cabin Boy. Aidez notre héros à tenir la journée dans cette aventure ! Attrapez le poisson Lil'Dickie qui lui est lancé, empêchez Lil'Missus de brûler au soleil et quoi que vous fassiez, prenez garde à Président Miaou !! Allez au niveau 30 et gagnez une chemise Cabin Boy gratuite : Lil's Dickie pour les garçons, Lil's Missus pour les filles ! Et pour vous joueurs inconditionnels, accumulez avec le temps 12 000 points pour gagner le Trophée Truite Dorée! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Leben auf dem offenen Meer ist toll! Nun ja, vielleicht nicht für unseren Cabin Boy. Hilf unserem Helden in diesem Abenteuer, es durch den Tag zu schaffen! Fang den Fisch, den Lil' Dickie ihm zuwirft, verhindere, dass Lil' Missus in der heißen Sonne verbrennt, und was du auch tust, pass auf den Vorsitzenden Miau auf!! Erreiche Level 30 und gewinne ein kostenloses Cabin-Boy-T-Shirt: Lil' Dickie für die Jungs, Lil' Missus für die Mädchen! Und für euch Hardcore-Gamer da draußen, sammelt 12.000 Punkte an, um die Trophäe der Goldenen Forelle zu gewinnen! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La vita in mare aperto è fantastica! Be', forse non per il nostro Cabin Boy. Aiuta il nostro eroe in questa avventura del giorno! Cattura i pesci che gli lancia Lil' Dickie, stai attento che Lil' Missus non si scotti al sole e, qualsiasi cosa tu faccia, attento a Chairman Meow!! Raggiungi il livello 30 e vinci una maglia Cabin Boy: Lil' Dickie da uomo, Lil' Missus da donna! E voi, giocatori più appassionati, accumulate 12.000 punti per vincere il Trofeo Trota Dorata! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡La vida en alta mar es grandiosa! Bueno, tal vez no para nuestro Cabin Boy. ¡Ayuda a nuestro héroe a superar esta aventura! ¡Atrapa los peces que Lil’ Dickie le arroja, evita que Lil’ Missus se queme al sol, y hagas lo que hagas, ten cuidado con Presidente Miau! Consigue llegar al nivel 30 y gana una camiseta Cabin Boy gratuita: ¡Lil’ Dickie para los chicos y Lil’ Missus para las chicas! ¡Para los jugadores más duros, acumula 12.000 puntos para ganar el Trofeo de la Trucha Dorada! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Life on the open seas is grand! Well, maybe not for our Cabin Boy. Help our hero in this adventure get through the day! Catch the fish Lil’ Bastard throws to him, keep Lil’ Missus from burning under the hot sun and whatever you do, watch out for Chairman Meow!! Get to level 30 and win a free Cabin boy shirt: Lil’ Bastard for the boys, Lil’ Missus for the girls! For you hardcore gamers out there, accumulate 12,000 points over time to win the Golden Trout Trophy! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>