<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Creek Falls</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Creek Falls</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Creek Falls</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Creek Falls</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Creek Falls</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Creek Falls</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">폭포수 골짜기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Creek Falls</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">小溪瀑布別墅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">小溪瀑布別墅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Creek Falls</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hidden deep within the forest, Creek Falls sits neatly atop a stunning waterfall. The home is built like a modern day studio with a living room, bedroom, and kitchen space all packed into one large open space. You can even hang out with friends in your outdoor patio and breathe in the soft chilly wind of the autumn air. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Caché au plus profond de la forêt, Creek Falls est idéalement situé au sommet d'une superbe cascade. La propriété est un loft moderne avec salon, chambre et cuisine, le tout en open space. Elle offre également un patio en plein air pour vous relaxer avec vos amis tout en respirant l'air frais de l'automne à pleins poumons. Récompensez vos clients avec un élément Arbre d'automne animé, exclusif à Creek Falls espace personnel. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Creek Falls thront tief im Wald versteckt über einem atemberaubenden Wasserfall. Das Zuhause ist wie ein modernes Studio aufgebaut, mit Wohn-, Schlaf- und Küchenbereich in einem einzigen, großen, offenen Raum. Du kannst dich sogar mit Freunden auf deiner Außenveranda treffen und die sanfte, kühle Brise der Herbstluft einatmen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nascosta per bene all'interno della foresta, Creek Falls giace esattamente in cima a una cascata favolosa. La casa è costruita come un monolocale moderno in un grande spazio all'aperto, e divisa tra il soggiorno, la camera da letto e la cucina. Puoi anche passare del tempo con gli amici nella tuo patio all'aperto e respirare la fresca aria autunnale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Oculta en lo profundo del bosque, Creek Falls se posa sobre una espectacular cascada. La casa está diseñada como un estudio moderno, con dormitorio, cuarto de estar y zona de cocina en un solo espacio amplio y abierto. Además, puedes reunirte con los amigos en el patio exterior y respirar la fresca brisa del otoño. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Hidden deep within the forest, Creek Falls sits at the bed of a stunning waterfall. The home is built like a modern day studio with a living room and bedroom packed into one large open space. You can even hang out with friends in your outdoor patio and breathe in the soft chilly wind of the autumn air. Reward yourself and your friends with an exclusive Animated Autumn Tree furniture items, only available in Creek Falls. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">숲 속 깊은 곳에 숨겨진 폭포수 골짜기 위의 아늑한 휴양지입니다. 현대적인 스튜디오 아파트의 구조로 설계되었으며, 거실, 침실, 그리고 부엌이 모두 포함되어 있습니다. 야외의 정원에서 친구들과 시간을 보내면서 조금은 쌀쌀한 가을 바람을 가슴 깊숙히 만끽하십시오. 손님들에게는 오직 폭포수 골짜기 퍼스널 스페이스에서만 구할 수 있는 움직이는 가을 나무를 선물로 줄 수 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Hidden deep within the forest, Creek Falls sits at the bed of a stunning waterfall. The home is built like a modern day studio with a living room and bedroom packed into one large open space. You can even hang out with friends in your outdoor patio and breathe in the soft chilly wind of the autumn air. Reward yourself and your friends with an exclusive Animated Autumn Tree furniture items, only available in Creek Falls. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">小溪瀑布位於森林深處一個壯觀的瀑布上。房子附有客廳、睡房及廚房，充滿空間感，彷彿一間現代風格的工作室。您還可在室外中庭和好友相聚，呼吸微冷的秋日空氣。獨家的小溪瀑布-動態秋天樹獎品道具只在小溪瀑布別墅內才可獲得，用來送給自己和好友吧。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">小溪瀑布位於森林深處一個壯觀的瀑布上。房子附有客廳、睡房及廚房，充滿空間感，彷彿一間現代風格的工作室。您還可在室外中庭和好友相聚，呼吸微冷的秋日空氣。獨家的小溪瀑布-動態秋天樹獎品道具只在小溪瀑布別墅內才可獲得，用來送給自己和好友吧。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hidden deep within the forest, Creek Falls sits at the bed of a stunning waterfall. The home is built like a modern day studio with a living room and bedroom packed into one large open space. You can even hang out with friends in your outdoor patio and breathe in the soft chilly wind of the autumn air. Reward yourself and your friends with an exclusive Animated Autumn Tree furniture items, only available in Creek Falls. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>