<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack Petit Aquarium</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete Acuario pequeño </LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kleines Aquarium Bündel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Acquario Piccolo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Small Aquarium Bundle Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Small Aquarium Bundle Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
<PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cet aquarium est le moyen le plus simple pour démarrer votre collection de poissons. Il est très économique et peut contenir jusqu'à 10 petits poissons et 5 petites décorations. Pour obtenir votre réservoir a commencé, inclus avec cet achat est le pack de petits poissons. Les poissons sont inclus: Coral Beauty Angelfish, Fire Fish, Flame Angelfish, Serpae Tetra, et Catalina Goby. Il s'agit d'un élément animé actif. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con este tanque puedes comenzar de manera más fácil tu colección de peces. Es muy económico y admite hasta 10 peces pequeños y 5 adornos pequeños. Para obtener su tanque comenzó, incluido con esta compra es el paquete de peces pequeños. El pescado se incluyen: Coral Beauty Angelfish, Fire Fish, Flame Angelfish, Serpae Tetra, y Catalina Goby. Este es un elemento activo animado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Aquarium ist der einfachste Weg, um Ihre Sammlung an Fischen zu beginnen.  Es ist sehr wirtschaftlich und kann bis zu 10 kleine Fische und 5 kleine Dekorationen enthalten. Um den Tank gestartet, inklusive mit diesem Kauf die kleinen Fische Packung ist. Der Fisch enthalten sind: Coral Beauty Angelfish, Fire Fish, Flame Angelfish, serpae Tetra und Catalina Goby. Dies ist eine animierte aktive Element. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa vasca è il modo più facile di iniziare la tua collezione di pesci. È molto economica e contiene fino a 10 pesci piccoli e 5 piccole decorazioni. Per ottenere il vostro carro armato iniziato, incluso con l'acquisto è il pacchetto dei pesci piccoli. I pesci sono compresi: Coral Beauty Angelfish, Fire Fish, Flame Angelfish, Serpae Tetra, e Catalina Goby. Questo è un elemento animato attiva. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This tank is the easiest way to start your fish collection.  It's very economical and holds up to 10 small fish and 5 small decorations. To get your tank started, Included with this purchase is the Small Fish Pack. The fish included are: Coral Beauty Angelfish, Fire Fish, Flame Angelfish, Serpae Tetra, and Catalina Goby. This is an animated active item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This tank is the easiest way to start your fish collection.  It's very economical and holds up to 10 small fish and 5 small decorations. To get your tank started, Included with this purchase is the Small Fish Pack. The fish included are: Coral Beauty Angelfish, Fire Fish, Flame Angelfish, Serpae Tetra, and Catalina Goby. This is an animated active item. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>