<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ascension Tattoo Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble de tatouages Ascension</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ascension-Tattoo-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto tatuaggio Ascensione</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de tatuajes Ascensión</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_0</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_0</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ascension Tattoo Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_0</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_0</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ascension Tattoo Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ascend to new heights with this complete package: Obsidian and Ivory Ascension tattoos for both Male and Female. Includes Obsidian Ascension Tattoo[M], Obsidian Ascension Forearm and Calf Tattoos [M], Obsidian Ascension Lower Back and Calf Tattoos [F], Obsidian Ascension Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F], Ivory Ascension Tattoo[M], Ivory Ascension Forearm and Calf Tattoos [M], Ivory Ascension Lower Back and Calf Tattoos [F], and Ivory Ascension Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F].

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Élevez-vous vers de nouveaux sommets avec ce pack complet: Tatouages Ascension Obsidienne et Ivoire pour homme et femme. Inclus Tatouages Ascension Obsidienne pour avant-bras et mollet [homme], Tatouage Ascension Obsidienne [homme], Tatouages Ascension Ivoire pour avant-bras et mollet [homme], Tatouage Ascension Ivoire [homme], Tatouages Ascension Obsidienne pour avant-bras et mollet [femme], Tatouages Ascension Obsidienne bas du dos et mollet [femme], Tatouages Ascension Ivoire pour avant-bras et mollet [femme], et Tatouages Ascension Ivoire bas du dos et mollet [femme].

Remarque : Tous les tatouages pour torse ou jambe ne sont pas égaux. Lors de l’achat de cet accessoire de tatouage, il est possible qu’il ne soit pas adapté à tous les habits. N’hésitez pas à prendre notre article gratuit « Torse nu » pour homme ou femme afin d’afficher correctement votre nouveau tatouage ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Steige mit diesem Komplettpaket in neue Höhen auf: Obsidian- und Ivory Ascension-Tattoos für beiderlei Geschlecht. Obsidian Ascension-Tattoos für Unterarm und Wade [Männlich], Obsidian Ascension-Tattoo [Männlich], Ivory Ascension-Tattoos für Unterarm und Wade [Männlich], Ivory Ascension-Tattoo [Männlich], Obsidian Ascension-Tattoos für Unterarm und Wade  [Weiblich], Obsidian Ascension-Tattoos für den unteren Rücken und Wade [Weiblich], Ivory Ascension-Tattoos für Unterarm und Wade [Weiblich], und Ivory Ascension-Tattoos für den unteren Rücken und Wade [Weiblich].

Hinweis: Nicht alle Gegenstände für Oberkörper oder Beine sind gleich gestaltet. Wenn du dieses Tattoo-Zubehör kaufst, könnte es nicht mit allen Kleidungsstücken harmonieren. Gerne kannst du dir unseren kostenlosen “blanken” Oberkörper für Männer/Frauen holen, um deine neuen Tattoos angemessen zeigen zu können![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un nuovo pacchetto completo per ascendere a nuovi livelli: tatuaggi unisex Ascensione color nero ossidiana e bianco avorio. Tatuaggi Ascensione nero ossidiana per avambraccio e polpaccio [maschili], Tatuaggio Ascensione nero ossidiana avorio [maschili], Tatuaggi Ascensione bianco per avambraccio e polpaccio [maschili], Tatuaggio Ascensione bianco avorio [maschili], Tatuaggi Ascensione nero ossidiana per avambraccio e polpaccio [femminili], Tatuaggi Ascensione nero ossidiana per la parte inferiore della schiena e polpaccio [femminili], Tatuaggi Ascensione bianco per avambraccio e polpaccio [femminili], e Tatuaggi Ascensione bianco per la parte inferiore della schiena e polpaccio [femminili].

Nota: non tutti gli oggetti per torso o gamba sono creati allo stesso modo. Il tatuaggio che ti appresti ad acquistare potrebbe non andare bene su tutti gli articoli di abbigliamento. A questo scopo non esitare a scaricare gratuitamente l'oggetto unisex "Tela nuda" torso per visualizzare correttamente i tuoi nuovi tatuaggi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Asciende a nuevas alturas con este pack completo: tatuajes Ascensión obsidiana y marfil para hombre y mujer. Tatuajes Ascensión obsidiana antebrazo y pantorrilla [hombre], Tatuaje Ascensión obsidiana [hombre], Tatuajes Ascensión marfil antebrazo y pantorrilla [hombre], Tatuaje Ascensión marfil [hombre], Tatuajes Ascensión obsidiana antebrazo y pantorrilla [mujer], Tatuajes Ascensión obsidiana parte baja de la espalda y pantorrilla [mujer], Tatuajes Ascensión marfil antebrazo y pantorrilla [mujer], y Tatuajes Ascensión marfil parte baja de la espalda y pantorrilla [mujer].

Nota: no todos los objetos para torso y piernas se crean por igual. Cuando compres este accesorio para un tatuaje, quizá no quede bien con cualquier prenda de ropa. ¡Elige nuestro "Lienzo en blanco" de regalo para hombre o mujer y así podrás lucir tu nuevo tatuaje como se merece![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_0 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_0 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ascend to new heights with this complete package: Obsidian and Ivory Ascension tattoos for both Male and Female. Includes Obsidian Ascension Tattoo[M], Obsidian Ascension Forearm and Calf Tattoos [M], Obsidian Ascension Lower Back and Calf Tattoos [F], Obsidian Ascension Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F], Ivory Ascension Tattoo[M], Ivory Ascension Forearm and Calf Tattoos [M], Ivory Ascension Lower Back and Calf Tattoos [F], and Ivory Ascension Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F].

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_0 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_0 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ascend to new heights with this complete package: Obsidian and Ivory Ascension tattoos for both Male and Female. Includes Obsidian Ascension Tattoo[M], Obsidian Ascension Forearm and Calf Tattoos [M], Obsidian Ascension Lower Back and Calf Tattoos [F], Obsidian Ascension Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F], Ivory Ascension Tattoo[M], Ivory Ascension Forearm and Calf Tattoos [M], Ivory Ascension Lower Back and Calf Tattoos [F], and Ivory Ascension Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F].

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>