<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Drey Ruby Red Vintage Lace Skirt with Black Belt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jupe Vintage en Dentelle Drey Rouge Rubis et sa Ceinture Noire</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rubinroter Drey Retro-Spitzenrock mit schwarzem Gürtel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gonna di pizzo vintage Drey rosso rubino con cintura nera</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Falda de encaje vintage rojo rubí con cinturón negro de Drey</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">【Drey】ブラックベルト付きヴィンテージレーススカート　ルビーレッド</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">검은색 벨트와 "드레이" 루비 레드 빈티지 레이스 스커트 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Drey Ruby Red Vintage Lace Skirt with Black Belt (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Drey深紅色復古蕾絲裙含黑色腰帶 (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Drey深紅色復古蕾絲裙含黑色腰帶 (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Drey Ruby Red Vintage Lace Skirt with Black Belt</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Showcase your style credentials in this vintage skirt and beautiful belt. With a two–tier design and floral lace pattern, this feminine separate offers a fresh take on a classic staple. \n\n Style: Full circle\n Rise: Medium\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Affirmez votre style grâce à cette jupe vintage et sa magnifique ceinture. Avec son motif floral et son design plissé, cette jupe très féminine donne une bouffée d'air frais à un grand classique. \n\n Style : En corolle\n Taille : Moyenne\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeige deinen Modegeschmack mit diesem Retro-Rock mit schönem Gürtel. Mit seinem zweilagigen Design und dem Spitzen-Blumenmuster ist er ein femininer Klassiker. \n\n Stil: Vollkreis\n Länge: Mittel\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fai vedere che sei un'esperta di moda indossando questa gonna vintage e questa fantastica cintura. Con i suoi due veli di pizzo e la fantasia floreale, questo coordinato estremamente femminile riporta in auge, rimodernato, un grande classico. \n\n  Stile: a tutto tondo\n  Vita: media\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Muestra tu estilo propio con esta falda vintage y el hermoso cinturón. Con un diseño de dos capas y encaje floral, esta femenina pieza independiente ofrece una versión moderna de un clásico clave. \n\n Estilo: acampanada\n Largo: mediano\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">みんなに一目おかれるヴィンテージスカートとベルトを着てみませんか？花柄のレースパターンのデザインが他のデザインに比べてかわいく仕上げました。\n\n スタイル：フルサークル [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 빈티지 스커트와 아름다운 벨트로 당신의 안목 높은 스타일을 뽐내 보세요. 이중의 디자인과 꽃 무늬 레이스 패턴이 클래식함을 강조한 옷에 더욱 여성스러운 신선함을 주니까요. \n\n 스타일: 완벽한 원\n 높이: 중간\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Showcase your style credentials in this vintage skirt and beautiful belt. With a two–tier design and floral lace pattern, this feminine separate offers a fresh take on a classic staple. \n\n Style: Full circle\n Rise: Medium\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這件復古短裙和美麗腰帶，就是你的流行學證書。擁有雙層設計和花邊蕾絲圖案，讓這套女飾經典必備款有了全新定義。\n\n 風格：正圓形\n 裙長：中\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這件復古短裙和美麗腰帶，就是你的流行學證書。擁有雙層設計和花邊蕾絲圖案，讓這套女飾經典必備款有了全新定義。\n\n 風格：正圓形\n 裙長：中\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Showcase your style credentials in this vintage skirt and beautiful belt. With a two–tier design and floral lace pattern, this feminine separate offers a fresh take on a classic staple. \n\n Style: Full circle\n Rise: Medium\n [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>