<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Torso_school_10</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Short School Uniform Top (Red Lining, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Haut d'uniforme court d'écolier (Doublure rouge, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kurze Schuluniform, Oberteil (Rote Fütterung, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Giacca corta uniforme scolastica (fodera rossa, U)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Parte superior de uniforme escolar corto (forro rojo, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">学生服短ラン（インナー赤・男性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">짧게 개조된 학생복 상의（빨간색 이너, 남성）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Short School Uniform (Red Inner Shirt/Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">學生服短外套(紅色襯底/男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">學生服短外套(紅色襯底/男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Short School Uniform Top (Red Lining, M)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Torso_school_10_description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A school uniform top with a shorter length than usual. Matched with a red undershirt that complements the top's red lining.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un haut d'uniforme d'écolier plus court que d'ordinaire. S'accorde avec un tee-shirt rouge rappelant la doublure de la veste.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Schuluniform-Oberteil, das etwas kürzer ist als üblich. Dazu ein passendes rotes Unterhemd, welches auf die Fütterung des Oberteils abgestimmt ist.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Uniforme scolastica leggermente più corta del normale. Abbinata a una maglietta rossa che richiama lo stesso colore della fodera interna.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una parte superior de uniforme escolar más corta de lo normal. Lleva una camiseta rojo a juego con el forro interior rojo de la chaqueta.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">着丈が短い、学生服の上着。服の裏地とインナーを、赤でそろえたタイプ。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">길이가 짧은 학생복 상의. 옷의 안감과 이너를 빨간색으로 통일한 타입. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A short school uniform top. The inner lining of the jacket and the shirt are matching red.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">短學生服外套。外套內裡和襯底均統一為紅色的造型。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">短學生服外套。外套內裡和襯底均統一為紅色的造型。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A school uniform top with a shorter length than usual. Matched with a red undershirt that complements the top's red lining.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>