<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Raven Table</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Table Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Raven-Tisch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tavolo Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mesa de Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">テーブル レーヴン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Raven 테이블</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Raven Table</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raven桌子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raven桌子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Raven Table</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Raven table's probably seen more cash flow than a small country's GDP. If this table could talk, it probably wouldn't bother speaking to you... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette table Raven a certainement vu passer des mallettes d'argent plus lourdes que le PIB d'un petit pays. Si elle pouvait parler, elle ne prendrait probablement pas la peine de discuter avec vous... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über diesen Raven-Tisch ist schon mehr Geld gewandert, als manche kleinere Länder als Bruttoinlandsprodukt vorweisen können. Wenn dieser Tisch sprechen könnte, würde er sich vermutlich nicht mit Ihnen abgeben ... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Su questo tavolo della Raven sono passati più soldi di quanti ce ne siano nel prodotto interno lordo di una piccola nazione. Se potesse parlare probabilmente non si sprecherebbe a farlo con voi... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta mesa de Raven ha visto más billetes que el gobierno de cualquier país. Si pudiera hablar, no se molestaría en hacerlo contigo... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">小国規模のGDPくらいのキャッシュフローがこのテーブルの上で取引されている。このテーブルが口を訊けたら、君なんかとは会話しないほどテーブルが大物だ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 Raven의 테이블은 소규모 국가의 재정규모 이상의 돈이 오가는 것을 지켜봤다고 합니다. 만약 테이블이 말을 할 수 있다면, 당신 같은 서민에게는 말을 걸지 않겠지요... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This Raven table’s probably seen more cash flow than a small country’s GDP. If this table could talk, it probably wouldn’t bother speaking to you... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這張 Raven 桌子，造價可能比小國的 GDP 還要高。如果這張桌子能夠說話，它很可能不屑和你對談。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這張 Raven 桌子，造價可能比小國的 GDP 還要高。如果這張桌子能夠說話，它很可能不屑和你對談。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This Raven table’s probably seen more cash flow than a small country’s GDP. If this table could talk, it probably wouldn’t bother speaking to you... [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>