<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gunslinger Torso and Widowmaker Rifle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pistolero Torse et le fusil Widowmaker (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Revolverhelden-Torso und Gewehr Widowmaker (Männer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Torso da pistolero e fucile Widowmaker (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Torso de forajido y rifle La Parca (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Gunslinger Torso and Widowmaker Rifle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Gunslinger Torso and Widowmaker Rifle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Gunslinger Torso and Widowmaker Rifle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Gunslinger Torso and Widowmaker Rifle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Gunslinger Torso and Widowmaker Rifle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gunslinger Torso and Widowmaker Rifle (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The symbol of a true Gunslinger, these clothes will silence any room. Strapped on the back is the Widowmaker rifle, the perfect weapon for hunting or putting down a small army. It's not widely known but rumour is that each vial on a Gunslinger's bandoleer is trophy from a past duel. Exactly what's inside each vial is a mystery only the wearer knows the answer to. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le symbole d'un vrai Pistolero, ces vêtements feront régner le silence. Le fusil Widowmaker attaché à l’arriéré est l'arme parfaite pour la chasse ou écraser des une petite armée. Ce n'est pas très connu, mais d’après, la rumeur sur ​​chaque flacon de Gunslinger se trouve le trophée d'un duel passé. Ce qui est exactement à l'intérieur de chaque flacon est un mystère dont seul le porteur connaît le secret. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese Kleidung ist das wahre Symbol eines Revolverhelden und bringt jeden Raum zum schweigen. Auf dem Rücken ist das Widowmaker-Gewehr geschnallt, die perfekte Waffe für die Jagd oder den Kampf gegen eine kleine Armee. Gerüchten zufolge ist jedes Fläschchen am Patronengurt des Revolverhelden eine Trophäe aus einem früheren Duell. Was genau sich in den Fläschchen befindet, weiß nur der Träger des Patronengurtes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Simbolo di un vero pistolero, questi abiti metteranno tutti a tacere. In spalla il fedele fucile Widowmaker, l'arma perfetta per cacciare o eliminare un piccolo esercito. La cosa non è molto risaputa, ma si dice che ogni boccetta sulla bandoliera di un pistolero è un trofeo di un duello passato. Cosa c'è esattamente in ogni boccetta è un mistero che può svelare solo chi la indossa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El símbolo de un verdadero forajido. Estas prendas son capaces de silenciar cualquier sala. Atado a la espalda lleva el rifle La Parca, el arma perfecta para dar caza a un ejército pequeño. Se rumorea que cada frasco que cuelga de la bandolera de un forajido simboliza un trofeo de un duelo pasado. El contenido de cada frasco es un misterio que solo el portador del mismo conoce. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">The symbol of a true Gunslinger, these clothes will silence any room. Strapped on the back is the Widowmaker rifle, the perfect weapon for hunting or putting down a small army. It's not widely known but rumor is that each vial on a Gunslinger's bandoleer is trophy from a past duel. Exactly what's inside each vial is a mystery only the wearer knows the answer to. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">The symbol of a true Gunslinger, these clothes will silence any room. Strapped on the back is the Widowmaker rifle, the perfect weapon for hunting or putting down a small army. It's not widely known but rumor is that each vial on a Gunslinger's bandoleer is trophy from a past duel. Exactly what's inside each vial is a mystery only the wearer knows the answer to. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The symbol of a true Gunslinger, these clothes will silence any room. Strapped on the back is the Widowmaker rifle, the perfect weapon for hunting or putting down a small army. It's not widely known but rumor is that each vial on a Gunslinger's bandoleer is trophy from a past duel. Exactly what's inside each vial is a mystery only the wearer knows the answer to. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">The symbol of a true Gunslinger, these clothes will silence any room. Strapped on the back is the Widowmaker rifle, the perfect weapon for hunting or putting down a small army. It's not widely known but rumor is that each vial on a Gunslinger's bandoleer is trophy from a past duel. Exactly what's inside each vial is a mystery only the wearer knows the answer to. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">The symbol of a true Gunslinger, these clothes will silence any room. Strapped on the back is the Widowmaker rifle, the perfect weapon for hunting or putting down a small army. It's not widely known but rumor is that each vial on a Gunslinger's bandoleer is trophy from a past duel. Exactly what's inside each vial is a mystery only the wearer knows the answer to. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The symbol of a true Gunslinger, these clothes will silence any room. Strapped on the back is the Widowmaker rifle, the perfect weapon for hunting or putting down a small army. It's not widely known but rumor is that each vial on a Gunslinger's bandoleer is trophy from a past duel. Exactly what's inside each vial is a mystery only the wearer knows the answer to. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>