<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Piccadilly Lilly Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Piccadilly Lilly Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Piccadilly Lilly Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Piccadilly Lilly Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Piccadilly Lilly Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup02_GreenUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup02_GreenUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup02_GreenUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup02_GreenUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup02_GreenUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Piccadilly Lilly Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Piccadilly Lilly will get you a salute from every Tom, Dick and Willy in Home!   This hot pin-up is a full character costume complete with retro uniform, sexy tats, traditional pin-up hair and make-up and comes with custom walk, run and pin-up pose animations, you'll storm more than a hill with this hot babe![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Piccadilly Lilly te vaudra un salut de chaque Tom, Dick et Willy. Cette belle pin-up est un costume à part entière avec un uniforme retro, sexy tatouages, Cheveux at maquillage traditionnels de Pin-up et vient avec une marche personnalisée, course et pose animées de Pin-up, tu prendras plus d'une montagne d'assaut avec cette belle minette![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Von Piccardy Lilly bekommst du einen gelösten Stoff von jedem Tom, Dick und Willy zu Hause! Dieses heiße Pin-Up Girl kommt als komplettes Charakterkostüm zusammen mit Retro-Uniform, sexy Tätowierungen, traditioneller Pin-Up Frisur, sowie benutzerdefinierten Animationen für Gang, Lauf und Pin-Up Posen. Mit diesem heißen Babe wirst du mehr als über einen Hügel stürmen![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Piccadilly Lilly ti porterá un saluto da tutti i Mario, Giovanni e Luigi che sono a Casa! Questa sexy pin-up é un costume completo con uniforme retro, lustrini sexy, capelli da pin-up tradizionali e trucco insieme ad animazioni di camminata, corsa e pose da pin-up, tutto diventa una sfida con questa bambola sexy! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Piccadilly Lilly te llevará un saludo de todos los Juanes, Pedros y Pablos en Casa!  Esta guapa pin-up es un disfráz completo del personaje que tiene uniforme retro, motivos sexys, peinado y maquillaje tradicional de pin-up y viene con animaciones de caminata especial, y poses de pin-up, todo se convierte en un desafío con esta guapísima nena! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup02_GreenUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup02_GreenUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup02_GreenUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup02_GreenUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup02_GreenUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Piccadilly Lilly will get you a salute from every Tom, Dick and Willy in Home!   This hot pin-up is a full character costume complete with retro uniform, sexy tats, traditional pin-up hair and make-up and comes with custom walk, run and pin-up pose animations, you'll storm more than a hill with this hot babe![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>