<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Molotov DX Fuel Additive x650</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Additif pour carburant Molotov DX x650</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Molotov DX- Treibstoffzusatz x650</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Additivo al carburante Molotov DX x650</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aditivo de combustible Molotov DX x650</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Molotov DX 燃料添加物 x650</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Molotov DX연료 첨가제 x650</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Molotov DX Fuel Additive x650</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Molotov DX 燃料添加物 x650</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Molotov DX 燃料添加物 x650</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Molotov DX Fuel Additive x650</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A balanced fuel additive for your Sodium2 racer that marginally increases both your top speed and your acceleration. This is a 650 use item that will be used automatically in a race if equipped. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un additif pour carburant équilibré pour votre racer Sodium2 qui augmente très légèrement votre vitesse et votre accélération. Il s'agit d'un objet d'utilité 650 qui sera automatiquement utilisé lors d'une course s'il est équipé. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein ausgewogenerer Treibstoffzusatz für deinen Sodium2 Racer, der sowohl deine Höchstgeschwindigkeit als auch deine Beschleunigung geringfügig verbessert. Dies ist ein Gegenstand, mit 650 Anwendungen, der automatisch in einem Rennen benutzt wird, wenn er ausgerüstet wurde. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un additivo per carburante equilibrato e adatto alla vostra macchina da corsa Sodium2 che aumenta marginalmente sia la vostra velocità massima che l'accelerazione. Quest'oggetto può essere usato 650 volta(e). Dopo averlo equipaggiato, sarà utilizzato automaticamente in gara. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un aditivo para combustible equilibrado para tu corredor de Sodium2 que aumenta ligeramente tanto la velocidad máxima como la aceleración. Este es un objeto de 650 uso(s) que se utilizará automáticamente en carrera cuando esté equipado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">トップスピードと加速を向上させる、バランス型の燃料添加物。このアイテム650は装備する事によりレースで自動的に使用されます。\n650回使用可能です。\n\n※本アイテムは消費型アイテムです。追加購入が可能です。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">최고 속도와 추진력 모두를 한 단계 높여주는 여러분의 Sodium2 레이서를 위한 균형 잡힌 연료첨가제. 이것이 일단 갖추게 되면 경주에서 자동으로 적용될 650 사용 아이템입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A balanced fuel additive for your Sodium2 racer that marginally increases both your top speed and your acceleration. This is a 650 use item that will be used automatically in a race if equipped. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">最均衡的Sodium2賽車燃料添加物，可小幅提升極速和加速度。本物品只能使用650次，裝上後就會在出賽時自動啟用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">最均衡的Sodium2賽車燃料添加物，可小幅提升極速和加速度。本物品只能使用650次，裝上後就會在出賽時自動啟用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A balanced fuel additive for your Sodium2 racer that marginally increases both your top speed and your acceleration. This is a 650 use item that will be used automatically in a race if equipped. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>