<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mrs Christmas Hat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Madam Noël chapeau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Frau Weihnachten Hut</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Signora natalecappello</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">señora Navidad sombrero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mrs Christmas Hat</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dress for the season and have some festive fun!  Show the world you’re ready to party in our Christmas clothing collection!  Live the magic and feel the snow because after all….. There’s Snow Place like PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Habillez-vous en conséquence pour que les fêtes puissent enfin commencer. Montrez au monde entier que vous êtes fin prêt à célébrer Noël grâce à notre collection de vêtements assortis!  Vivez la magie de la neige hivernale….. Il n’existe rien de plus beau sur PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kleide dich für die Saison und genieße den festlichen Spaß! Zeige der Welt, dass du bereit bist, in unserer Weihnachtskleidungs-Kollektion zu feiern!  Lebe die Magie und fühle den Schnee, denn trotz allem ..... Zu Hause ist es so schön wie PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vestiti con abiti perfetti per la stagione e dai il via alle festività! Fai vedere a tutti che non vedi l'ora di far festa con la nostra collezione moda natalizia!  Vivi la magia e senti la neve che cade, perché, in fondo, non c'è nulla come essere a casa, sotto la neve con PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Vístete para estas fiestas y sal a divertirte! ¡Que todo el mundo vea lo bien que te queda la ropa de nuestra colección de Navidad!  ¡Vive la magia y la nieve desde el calor de PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dress for the season and have some festive fun!  Show the world you’re ready to party in our Christmas clothing collection!  Live the magic and feel the snow because after all….. There’s Snow Place like PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>