<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">5000 VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">5000 Jetons à imprimer VEEMEE 3D</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">5000 Marken für VEEMEE-3D-Drucker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">5000 Buoni per Stampante 3D VEEMEE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">5000 Vales VEEMEE Impresora 3D</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">5000 VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">5000 VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">5000 VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">5000 VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A pack of 5000 vouchers for use with the VEEMEE 3D Printer. Choose from a varied selection of reward items to print in the comfort of your (virtual) home, or use the vouchers to send an item to a friend's 3D Printer. The larger the pack of vouchers, the better the value. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un paquet de 5000 jetons à utiliser avec l'imprimante VEEMEE 3D. Faites votre choix dans une sélection variée de récompenses à imprimer confortablement dans votre foyer (virtuel), ou utilisez les jetons pour envoyer un article vers l'imprimante 3D d'un ami. Plus le paquet de jetons est gros, plus sa valeur augmente. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Packung mit 5000 Marken zur Verwendung mit dem VEEMEE-3D-Drucker. Wählen Sie aus, welche der vielen verschiedenen Objekte Sie in Ihrem (virtuellen) Zuhause ausdrucken wollen. Sie können die Marken auch dazu verwenden, einen Gegenstand als Geschenk an den 3D-Drucker eines Freundes oder einer Freundin zu senden. Je größer die Packung, umso höher der Wert [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un pacco da 5000 buoni da utilizzare per la Stampante 3D VEEMEE. Scegli tra un'ampia selezione di articoli premio da stampare nella comodità della tua casa (virtuale) o utilizza i buoni per inviare un articolo alla Stampante 3D di un tuo amico. Più è grande il pacco di buoni, maggiore è il valore. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un conjunto de 5000 vales para utilizar con la impresora VEEMEE 3D. Elige entre una amplia variedad de premios e imprime sin salir del confort de tu casa (virtual), o usa los vales para enviar un artículo a la impresora 3D de algún amigo. Cuanto mayor sea el volumen de vales, más valor tendrán. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">A pack of 5000 vouchers for use with the VEEMEE 3D Printer. Choose from a varied selection of reward items to print in the comfort of your (virtual) home, or use the vouchers to send an item to a friend's 3D Printer. The larger the pack of vouchers, the better the value. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A pack of 5000 vouchers for use with the VEEMEE 3D Printer. Choose from a varied selection of reward items to print in the comfort of your (virtual) home, or use the vouchers to send an item to a friend's 3D Printer. The larger the pack of vouchers, the better the value. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">A pack of 5000 vouchers for use with the VEEMEE 3D Printer. Choose from a varied selection of reward items to print in the comfort of your (virtual) home, or use the vouchers to send an item to a friend's 3D Printer. The larger the pack of vouchers, the better the value. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">A pack of 5000 vouchers for use with the VEEMEE 3D Printer. Choose from a varied selection of reward items to print in the comfort of your (virtual) home, or use the vouchers to send an item to a friend's 3D Printer. The larger the pack of vouchers, the better the value. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>