<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Street Style - Bundle Outfit Pack 03 - White (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Street Style - Lot pack tenue 03 - Blanc (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Street Style - Paket 03 - Weiß (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Street Style - Set completo pacco 03 -Bianco (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Street Style - Pack Conjunto de ropa 03 - Blanco (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wear the whole package with this Street Style Outfit Pack!\n
This bundle contains:\n
(1) Street Style - SVE Cap - White (Women)\n
(2) Street Style - Star Shoulder Slung Top - White (Women)\n
(3) Street Style - One Up Jogging Bottoms With High Tops - Charcoal (Women) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Portez l'ensemble complet avec ce pack Street Style !\n
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                             Ce lot contient :\n
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                            (1) Street Style - Casquette SVE - Blanc (femme)\n
(2) Street Style - Haut à épaule dénudée Star - Blanc (femme)\n
(3) Street Style - Pantalon de jogging One Up avec baskets montantes - Fusain (femme) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tragen Sie das gesamte Outfit in diesem Street Style Outfit-Paket!\n
Dieses Paket enthält:\n
(1) Street Style - SVE Kappe - Weiß (Damen)\n
(2) Street Style - Schulterfreies T-Shirt mit Stern - Weiß (Damen)\n
(3) Street Style - One Up Jogginghose mit Hi-Top-Sneakern - Grau (Damen) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Indossa tutti i capi con questo Pacchetto di Abbigliamento Street Style!\n
Il set comprende:\n
(1) Street Style - Berretto SVE - Bianco (Donna)\n
(2) Street Style - Maglia con spalla scoperta e motivo a stella - Bianco (Donna)\n
(3) Street Style - Pantaloni da ginnastica con una gamba su e sneaker high-top - Grigio antracite (Donna) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Ponte el conjunto entero con este Pack de Ropa Street Style!\n
Este pack contiene:\n
(1) Street Style - SVE Gorra - Blanco (Mujer)\n
(2) Street Style - Camiseta de estrella con escote asimétrico - Blanco (Mujer)\n
(3) Street Style - One Up Pantalones de chándal y zapatillas altas - Color carbón (Mujer) [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>