<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ethnic Beaded Flower Earring - Right Ear (For Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Boucle d'oreille à perles ethnique - Oreille droite (pour femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blumenohrring aus Trachtenperlen – rechtes Ohr (für Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Orecchino etnico a fiore con perline - Destro (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pendiente de flor de abalorios étnico: oreja derecha (para mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ethnic Beaded Flower Earring - Right Ear (For Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A flower earring for the right ear made of ethnic-style beads perfect for anyone looking for a rustically fashionable look!\nSometimes even earrings can make a whole outfit fun! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Boucle d'oreille pour oreille droite en perles de style ethnique, idéale pour celles qui souhaitent avoir un look à la fois branché et rustique !\nParfois, des boucles d'oreilles suffisent à donner de la gaieté à une tenue ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blumenohrring aus Trachtenperlen für das rechte Ohr. Geeignet für alle, die ländliche Mode bevorzugen!\nManchmal erhält ein Outfit erst durch die Ohrringe den letzten Schliff! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Orecchino a fiore in stile etnico fatto di perline per l'orecchio destro, per un look semplice e alla moda!\nSpesso, gli orecchini trascinano un intero completo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Un pendiente de flor para la oreja derecha hecho de abalorios de estilo étnico perfecto si buscas un estilo elegante a la par que rústico!\n¡A veces, unos pendientes pueden darle el toque divertido a todo el atuendo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A flower earring for the right ear made of ethnic-style beads perfect for anyone looking for a rustically fashionable look!\nSometimes even earrings can make a whole outfit fun! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>