<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">St Patrick's Wishing Well</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Puits aux souhaits de la Saint-Patrick</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">St. Patrick's Day Wunschbrunnen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pozzo dei desideri di San Patrizio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pozo de los deseos de San Patricio</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A wishing well for St Patricks Day in AMP [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un puits aux souhaits pour la Saint-Patrick dans AMP [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wunschbrunnen für St. Patrick's Day im AMP [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un pozzo dei desideri per San Patrizio in AMP [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un pozo de los deseos para el Día de San Patricio en el PCB [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">WellTalk1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You need to be more generous with your gifting to be given a special reward from the well...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si vous voulez recevoir une récompense du puits, vous devriez être plus généreux avec vos cadeaux...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie müssen großzügigere Geschenke machen, wenn Sie eine besondere Belohnung vom Wunschbrunnen erhalten wollen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Devi essere più generoso e fare più regali se vuoi ricevere il premio speciale dal pozzo...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tienes que ser más generoso con tus regalos para que el pozo te obsequio con un premio especial...</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">WellTalk2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Maybe you should try being more generous with your gifts?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous devriez peut-être essayer d'être plus généreux avec vos cadeaux ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vielleicht sollten Sie großzügigere Geschenke machen….?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Magari dovresti provare a essere più generoso e fare più regali?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Quizás deberías intentar ser más generoso con tus regalos.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">WellTalk3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Congratulations! You've shared gifts with the community and here's a special reward.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Félicitations ! Vous avez partagé vos cadeaux avec la communauté : voici une récompense spéciale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Herzlichen Glückwunsch! Sie haben der Gemeinschaft großzügige Geschenke gemacht und erhalten daher eine besondere Belohnung.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Congratulazioni! Hai scambiato regali con la comunità e ti meriti un premio speciale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Felicidades! Has compartido regalos con la comunidad y aquí tienes un premio especial.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">WellTalk4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You've already had a gift from the well!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez déjà obtenu un cadeau du puits !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben bereits ein Geschenk vom Brunnen erhalten!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai già ricevuto un regalo dal pozzo!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡El pozo ya te ha obsequiado con un regalo!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sortie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beenden</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salida</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>