<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mood Cloud</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mood Cloud</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stimmungswolke</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mood Cloud</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nube de Humor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LMO-ムーディーズ：ムード・クラウド</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Mood Cloud</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mood Cloud</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Watch your own personal Mood Cloud transform to fit your mood by choosing Happy, Sad, Angry, or Confused in the Status menu! A speed boost will automatically engage when moving at full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Observez votre Mood Cloud personnel se transformer pour correspondre à votre humeur en sélectionnant heureux, triste, furieux ou perplexe dans le menu d'états ! Un turbo s'active automatiquement lors d'une course à pleine vitesse. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sieh dir an, wie deine persönliche Stimmungswolke sich je nach Laune verändert, indem du Fröhlich, Traurig, Wütend oder Verwirrt im Statusmenü auswählst! Ein Geschwindigkeitsschub setzt automatisch ein, wenn du dich mit voller Geschwindigkeit bewegst. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guarda la tua Mood Cloud trasformarsi a seconda dell'umore scelto nel menù dello Status tra Felice, Triste, Arrabbiato o Confuso. La velocità aumenta automaticamente quando ci si sposta a tutta velocità. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Observa tu “Nube de Humor” personal transformarse de acuerdo a tu estado de humor al seleccionar “Feliz”, “Triste”, “Enojado” o “Confundido” en el menú de “Estado”! Un incremento de tu velocidad entrará en marcha automáticamente cuando vayas a máxima velocidad. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ジェスチャーメニュー（R1ボタン）から「ステータス」を選ぶと、その内容に応じてムード・クラウドが変わります！\n移動速度アップ：◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆\nLMO（ロコモーション）はポータブルアイテムです。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Watch your own personal Mood Cloud transform to fit your mood by choosing Happy, Sad, Angry, or Confused in the Status menu! A speed boost will automatically engage when moving at full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Watch your own personal Mood Cloud transform to fit your mood by choosing Happy, Sad, Angry, or Confused in the Status menu! A speed boost will automatically engage when moving at full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>