<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Forsaken Planet – Zombie (Animated)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Forsaken Planet – Zombie (Animé)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Forsaken Planet – Zombie (Lebhaft)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Forsaken Planet – Zombie (Animato)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Forsaken Planet – Zombi (Animado)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Forsaken Planet – Zombie (inActive)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Forsaken Planet – Zombie (inActive)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Zombies! Run! Wait, it’s just standing there. It’s okay! It just wants to be friends.  Looking for even sweeter Forsaken Planet deals and in-game rewards? Check out the Forsaken Planet Bundles in the LOOT™ Store! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Des zombies ! Courrez ! Oh attendez, ils ne font rien, c'est bon ! Ils veulent juste être amis. Vous cherchez des bonnes affaires Forsaken Planet encore plus intéressantes ainsi que des récompenses dans le jeu ? Jetez un oeil sur les Lots Forsaken Planet dans la Boutique LOOT™ ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zombies! Weglaufen! Warten Sie, es ist einfach da. Es ist okay! Es will nur Freunde sein. Möchtest du noch bessere Deals Forsaken Planet und Spielgegenstände abgreifen? Schau dir die Forsaken Planet-Bundles im LOOT™ Store an! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Zombie! Fuggire! Aspetta, è solo lì. Va tutto bene! Si vuole solo essere amici. Cerchi altre offerte e altri premi Forsaken Planet? Dai un'occhiata ai Pacchetti Forsaken Planet nel LOOT™ Store! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Zombies! ¡Corre! Espera, que está de pie allí. No pasa nada! Sólo quiere que seamos amigos. ¿Quieres ofertas y premios aún más jugosos de Forsaken Planet? ¡No te pierdas los lotes de Forsaken Planet en la tienda LOOT™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Zombies! Run! Wait, it’s just standing there. It’s okay! It just wants to be friends.  Looking for even sweeter Forsaken Planet deals and in-game rewards? Check out the Forsaken Planet Bundles in the LOOT™ Store! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Zombies! Run! Wait, it’s just standing there. It’s okay! It just wants to be friends.  Looking for even sweeter Forsaken Planet deals and in-game rewards? Check out the Forsaken Planet Bundles in the LOOT™ Store! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>