<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Neon Ice Chair (Green)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaise glacée néon (vert)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Neon Eis Stuhl (grün)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sedia ghiaccio neon (verde)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Silla hielo neón (verde)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Neon Ice Chair (Green)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Decorate your Snow Globe in style or let the festive feeling flow with our range of furniture and festive items.  Live the magic and feel the snow because after all….. There’s Snow Place like PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Décorez votre globe à neige avec classe, laissez-vous emporter par l’effervescence des fêtes et craquez pour nos meubles et articles festifs.  Vivez la magie de la neige hivernale….. Il n’existe rien de plus beau sur PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dekoriere deine Schneekugel mit Stil, lasse das feierliche Gefühl fließen mit unserer Auswahl an Möbeln und festlichen Artikeln.  Lebe die Magie und fühle den Schnee, denn trotz allem ….. Zu Hause ist es so schön wie PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Decora la tua globo di neve con stile e senti l'atmosfera fesiva grazie alla nostra vasta gamma di mobili e oggetti delle feste.  Vivi la magia e senti la neve che cade, perché, in fondo, non c'è nulla come essere a casa, sotto la neve con PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Decora tu Globo de Nieve como más te guste y deja que el espíritu de la Navidad fluya con nuestra amplia gama de muebles y objetos navideños.  ¡Vive la magia y la nieve desde el calor de PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Decorate your Snow Globe in style or let the festive feeling flow with our range of furniture and festive items.  Live the magic and feel the snow because after all….. There’s Snow Place like PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>