<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Spyder" Reinforced 2nd Gen  Leg Armour</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jambières renforcées 2ème génération "Spyder"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verstärkter Beinschutz „Spyder“ (2. Generation)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Armatura rinforzata seconda generazione "Spyder" per le gambe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Blindaje para piernas reforzado de 2.a gen. "Spyder"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">高性能複合素材レッグ"スパイダー"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">차세대 강화 다리보호구 - "스파이더"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Spyder" Reinforced 2nd Gen Leg Armor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「Spyder」強化第二代護腿</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「Spyder」強化第二代護腿</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Spyder" Reinforced 2nd Gen Leg Armor</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Raven's battle gear incorporates proprietary synthetic fibres, polychloroprene compounds and a silicon coated form factor to create a uniquely flexible protective system that maintains superior performance in all battle conditions. Available in black. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'équipement de combat Raven incorpore des fibres synthétiques et des composés de polychloroprène déposés, recouverts de silicone, pour un système de protection polyvalent et novateur, garantissant les meilleures performances en situation de combat. Disponible en noir. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In der Kampfausrüstung von Raven wurden die firmeneigenen Synthetikfasern, Polychloropren-Verbunde und mit Silikon ummantelte Formen miteinander verarbeitet, um ein einzigartiges, flexibles Schutzsystem zu erschaffen, das in allen Gefechtssituationen überragende Leistungswerte aufweist. Erhältlich in schwarzer Ausführung. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'equipaggiamento della Raven incorpora fibre sintetiche brevettate, composti di policloroprene e rivestimento in silicone che rendono l'armatura incredibilmente elastica mantenendo prestazioni ottimali in qualsiasi condizione di battaglia. È disponibile in nero. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El equipo de combate de Raven incorpora fibras sintéticas, compuestos de policloropreno y un factor de forma revestido de silicona que dan lugar a un sistema de protección increíblemente flexible que rinde a la perfección en todo tipo de condiciones de combate. Disponible en negro. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">レーヴンの戦闘ギアは独自技術を駆使した合成ファイバー、ポリクロロプレン化合物で作られており、シリコンコーティングが施されている。この専用技術は特有の伸縮性を生み、あらゆる戦場で着用できる。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Raven의 전투 장비는 독점 개발한 합성 수지와 섬유로 만들어졌습니다. 실리콘 코팅을 가한 내피는 각 요원의 체형에 맞게 설계되어 일체감을 줍니다. 어떠한 상황에서도 최상의 보호를 제공하며, 검은색으로 출고됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Raven's battle gear incorporates proprietory synthetic fibers, polychloroprene compounds and a silicon coated form factor to create a uniquely flexible protective system that maintains superior performance in all battle conditions. Available in black. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raven的戰鬥裝備，集合獨有的合成纖維、氯丁橡膠混合物和矽膠塗層形成因子，製成獨一無二的彈性防護系統，在所有戰鬥條件下都能維持優質效能。現有黑色裝備供應。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raven的戰鬥裝備，集合獨有的合成纖維、氯丁橡膠混合物和矽膠塗層形成因子，製成獨一無二的彈性防護系統，在所有戰鬥條件下都能維持優質效能。現有黑色裝備供應。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Raven's battle gear incorporates proprietary synthetic fibers, polychloroprene compounds and a silicon coated form factor to create a uniquely flexible protective system that maintains superior performance in all battle conditions. Available in black. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>