<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Savage Manor Journal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le journal du manoir sauvage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Savage Manor-Tagebuch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Diario del maniero selvaggio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Diario de la Mansión salvaje</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">戦慄の館ジャーナル</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">공포의 저택 일지</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Savage Manor Journal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">野蠻莊園日誌</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">野蠻莊園日誌</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Savage Manor Journal</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Journal MiniGame [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Journal minijeu [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tagebuch-Minispiel [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Minigioco Diario [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mini juego del diario [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ジャーナル ミニゲーム [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">일지 미니게임 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Journal MiniGame [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">日誌迷你遊戲 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">日誌迷你遊戲 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Journal MiniGame [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BYE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Until Next Time!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">À la prochaine fois !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bis zum nächsten Mal!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Alla prossima!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Hasta la próxima!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">次回までお楽しみに！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">다음에 또 만나요!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Until Next Time!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">下次再見！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">下次再見！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Until Next Time!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CAN_NOT_PLAY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Only the owner of the apartment, may interact with this!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'interaction n'est possible qu'avec le propriétaire de l'appartement !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nur der Besitzer des Apartments kann das benutzen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Solo il proprietario dell'appartamento può interagire con questo!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Solo el dueño de este lugar puede interactuar con esto!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">洋館の所有者のみが、この交流を利用できる！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">아파트의 주인만이 이것과 상호작용을 할 수 있습니다!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Only the owner of the apartment, may interact with this!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">只有公寓的主人可與之互動!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">只有公寓的主人可與之互動!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Only the owner of the apartment, may interact with this!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">THE JOURNAL SO FAR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The story so far...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'histoire jusque-là...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Was bisher geschah ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La storia...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La historia hasta ahora…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">今までのストーリー...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">지금까지의 이야기는…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The story so far...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這個故事迄今為止……</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這個故事迄今為止……</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The story so far...</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">[CIRCLE] EXIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] EXIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] QUITTER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE] VERLASSEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE] ESCI</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] SALIR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[DECLINE] 終了</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[DECLINE] 나가기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[DECLINE] EXIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[DECLINE]退出</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[DECLINE]退出</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE] EXIT</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment01</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">History: Finally, you are here. We have been waiting for you! Who we are and what happened here? This my friend, is what we have been waiting so long to tell you! It is not a story for the faint-hearted but before I begin you should take time to acquaint yourself with my manor. After all, not all history can be told. Some you must discover for yourself in the pith of the place.  A reflection may be a glimpse of another tortured soul, a breath of air the whisper of someone long since dead. In places such as this, history lives. Inhale it, let it seep into your being and don't be afraid, as we all know there are no real monsters, only ourselves.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'histoire : Enfin, vous êtes ici. Nous vous attendions ! Nous avons patienter très longtemps pour vous raconter qui nous sommes et ce qui est arrivé ici ! Les âmes sensibles devraient s'abstenir, mais avant que je ne commence, prenez le temps de vous familiariser avec le manoir. Après tout, l'histoire ne dit pas tout. Vous devez en découvrir une partie vous-même au cœur même de l'endroit. Une âme tourmentée peut se glisser dans une réflexion, le murmure d'une personne disparue depuis longtemps devient un souffle d'air. Dans ces endroits, l'histoire est vivante. Étreignez-la, laissez la s'infiltrer en vous et n'ayez pas peur, il n'y a pas de vrais montres ici, il n'y a que nous.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Geschichte: Endlich bist du da. Wir haben dich bereits erwartet! Wer wir sind und was hier geschehen ist? Dies, mein Freund, ist das, wovon wir dir schon so lange erzählen wollten! Es ist keine Geschichte für schwache Nerven, doch bevor ich beginne, solltest du dir ein wenig Zeit nehmen, um dich mit meinem Landsitz vertraut zu machen. Schließlich kann nicht die ganze Geschichte erzählt werden. Manches musst du an Ort und Stelle selbst herausfinden. Ein Spiegelbild kann dir eine andere gepeinigte Seele enthüllen, ein Luftzug das Flüstern eines längst Gestorbenen sein. An Orten wie diesem lebt die Geschichte fort. Atme tief ein, lass dich davon durchdringen und hab keine Angst, denn wir alle wissen ja, dass es keine Monster gibt, nur uns selbst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Storia: finalmente sei qui. Ti stavamo aspettando! Chi siamo? Cosa succede qui? Questo è proprio quello che volevamo raccontarti! Non è una storia per deboli di cuore; e prima che cominci, dovresti familiarizzare con il mio maniero. Infatti, non tutta la storia può essere raccontata; una parte la devi scoprire tu, nell'essenza di questo posto. Un riflesso potrebbe essere l'occhiata di un'anima tormentata, un soffio d'aria il sussurro di qualcuno morto da tempo. In posti come questo, la storia vive. Inala, lascia che entri dentro di te e non aver paura: sappiamo tutti che non ci sono veri mostri, ci siamo solo noi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Historia: por fin has llegado. ¡Te estábamos esperando! ¿Quiénes somos y qué ha ocurrido aquí? Por esto hemos esperado, amigo mío, ¡para contártelo! No es una historia para pusilánimes. Pero antes de empezar, tómate tu tiempo para familiarizarte con mi mansión. Después de todo, no toda la historia se puede contar. Hay partes que deberás descubrir en el corazón del lugar. Un reflejo puede ser un atisbo de un alma torturada, un soplo de aire, el suspiro de alguien que murió hace mucho tiempo. En lugares como este, la historia está viva. Respírala, deja que te cale hondo. Y no te asustes, pues, como todos sabemos, los monstruos no existen, somos nosotros.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">歴史 - あなたがここにいらっしゃるのを楽しみにしていました！私たちのこと、そしてこの館で起きたことを知りたい？あなたにストーリーを知ってもらうことを心待ちにしていました！勇気ある者だけが知ることのできるストーリーをお話しする前に、私の館を紹介しましょう。詰まるところ、ここで全ての歴史をお伝えすることはできません。あなたが自分の力で、ここに存在する歴史を発見するのです。そこに映し出されるのは、拷問に苦しんだ魂や、さまよえる死人のささやき。このような場所で歴史は今でも生き続けます。この歴史をじっくりと体に感じてみてください。恐れることはありません。モンスターなどといった敵はここに存在しません。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">과거: 마침내 오셨군요. 당신을 기다리고 있었답니다! 우리는 누구고 이곳엔 무슨 일이 일어난 거냐고요? 당신에게 그것을 알려주기 위해 우린 오랜 시간을 기다려 왔답니다! 심약한 사람들은 이 이야기를 듣지 않는 것이 좋습니다. 먼저 제 저택에 대해 몇 가지 알아두는 것이 좋을 것 같습니다. 모든 과거를 전부 설명해 드릴 수는 없습니다. 어떤 과거는 당신이 이곳에서 직접 알아내야 할 겁니다. 반사된 모습은 고문당한 영혼의 흐릿한 이미지일지도 모르며 이미 오래 전에 죽은 자의 속삭임일지도 모릅니다. 이런 곳에선 과거는 현재에도 살아 숨쉰답니다. 과거를 숨쉬고 마시세요. 하지만 우리 외에 진짜 괴물은 존재하지 않으니 겁먹을 필요는 없답니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">History: Finally, you are here. We have been waiting for you! Who we are and what happened here? This my friend, is what we have been waiting so long to tell you! It is not a story for the faint-hearted but before I begin you should take time to acquaint yourself with my manor. After all, not all history can be told. Some you must discover for yourself in the pith of the place.  A reflection may be a glimpse of another tortured soul, a breath of air the whisper of someone long since dead. In places such as this, history lives. Inhale it, let it seep into your being and don't be afraid, as we all know there are no real monsters, only ourselves.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">歷史：你終於來了。我們一直在等你！想知道我們是誰以及這裡發生了什麽事嗎？這是我的朋友，我們等了這麼久就是爲了告訴你這裡發生的一切！這個故事不適合膽小脆弱之人，但在我開始講述之前，你應該花些時間熟悉我的莊園。畢竟，不是所有的歷史都能公之於眾。有些歷史必須由你親自深入莊園的核心去發掘。某個映像或許可讓你窺見另一個備受折磨的靈魂，或讓你感受到一縷微風裹挾著早已作古的某人的呢喃。在像這樣的地方，歷史是有生命的。請呼吸歷史的氣息，讓其滲入你的身心。不要害怕，我們都知道這裡沒有真正的怪物，只有我們自己。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">歷史：你終於來了。我們一直在等你！想知道我們是誰以及這裡發生了什麽事嗎？這是我的朋友，我們等了這麼久就是爲了告訴你這裡發生的一切！這個故事不適合膽小脆弱之人，但在我開始講述之前，你應該花些時間熟悉我的莊園。畢竟，不是所有的歷史都能公之於眾。有些歷史必須由你親自深入莊園的核心去發掘。某個映像或許可讓你窺見另一個備受折磨的靈魂，或讓你感受到一縷微風裹挾著早已作古的某人的呢喃。在像這樣的地方，歷史是有生命的。請呼吸歷史的氣息，讓其滲入你的身心。不要害怕，我們都知道這裡沒有真正的怪物，只有我們自己。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">History: Finally, you are here. We have been waiting for you! Who we are and what happened here? This my friend, is what we have been waiting so long to tell you! It is not a story for the faint-hearted but before I begin you should take time to acquaint yourself with my manor. After all, not all history can be told. Some you must discover for yourself in the pith of the place.  A reflection may be a glimpse of another tortured soul, a breath of air the whisper of someone long since dead. In places such as this, history lives. Inhale it, let it seep into your being and don't be afraid, as we all know there are no real monsters, only ourselves.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment02</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Savage Manor: Every town has a dark place. The manor was ours. Our parents gave us red-faced warnings but were they never children? 'Abandoned', 'dangerous', these were words of enchantment to our impressionable minds. They drew us to its boundaries and the merest glint of light on a window or creak from a gable would have us tumbling and screaming back to the safety of our streets. But while the others never elevated it above 'haunted house', I let it seep into my psyche. Are children more attuned to resonances from alternate realities? Oh yes and in my dreams I roamed there, hearing it's whispers, searching for its truths. It would be many years before it was mine in fact but even then it was mine inside.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le manoir sauvage : Chaque village a son côté sombre. Pour nous, c'était le manoir. Nos parents en colère nous avertirent, mais n'avaient-ils jamais été enfants ? « Abandonné », « dangereux », c'était des mots envoûtants pour nos esprits impressionnables. Ils nous avaient attirés à ses limites et le moindre éclairage d'une fenêtre ou un grincement dans les combles nous auraient renvoyés en criant dans la sécurité de nos rues. Mais alors que les autres ne le considéraient jamais plus qu'une « maison hantée », je le laissais s'infiltrer dans mon esprit. Les enfants sont-ils plus en harmonie avec les résonances de réalités parallèles ? Oh que oui, et dans mes rêves, je le parcourais, écoutant ses murmures, en quête de ses vérités. Ça aura pris plusieurs années avant qu'il ne m'appartienne vraiment, mais à cette époque déjà, il était à moi, spirituellement.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Savage Manor: Jede Stadt hat eine dunkle Ecke. Der Landsitz war unsere. Unsere Eltern haben uns eindringlich davor gewarnt, aber waren die denn niemals Kinder? Wörter wie 'verlassen' und 'gefährlich' klangen für uns wie verlockende Zauberformeln. Sie zogen uns magisch zu dem Landsitz hin, und schon beim kleinsten Funkeln eines Sonnenstrahls in einem Fenster oder das Knarzen des Giebels ließ uns schreiend zurück zu unserer Straße rennen. Doch während der Landsitz für andere nie mehr als das 'Spukhaus' war, ließ ich ihn meine Seele in Besitz nehmen. Sind Kinder vielleicht empfänglicher für Schwingungen aus Parallelwelten? Oh, ja, und in meinen Träumen war ich dort, hörte das Flüstern und suchte nach der Wahrheit. Es sollte viele Jahre dauern, bis ich sie finden sollte, und selbst dann gehörte sie mir nur dort.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maniero selvaggio: ogni città ha un luogo sinistro. Il nostro era il maniero. I genitori ci fecero le facce rosse a furia di avvertimenti. Ma loro non erano mai stati bambini? 'Abbandonato', 'pericoloso', queste parole erano magiche per le nostre menti impressionabili. E ci condussero fino ai suoi confini: il più debole dei bagliori su una finestra o lo scricchiolio della struttura ci facevano scappare urlando. Ma mentre gli altri non andarono mai oltre la 'casa infestata', io lasciai che il maniero penetrasse nella mia psiche. I bambini percepiscono meglio le risonanze delle realtà alternative? Oh sì, e nei miei sogni io ero lì, ascoltavo i mormorii, alla ricerca della verità. Ci sarebbero voluti anni prima che diventasse mio, ma dentro di me già lo era.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mansión salvaje: todas las ciudades tienen un lugar oscuro. La mansión era el de la nuestra. Los padres nos advertían enfadados, pero ¿acaso ellos no fueron niños? "Abandonada", "peligrosa"… eran palabras que hechizaban a nuestras influenciables mentes. Nos llevaban al límite y el más leve destello de luz en una ventana o crujido de un gablete nos hacía gritar y correr hacia la seguridad de nuestras calles. Aunque el resto solo pensaban en ella como en la "casa encantada", yo dejé que calara en mi psique. ¿Los niños están en sintonía con las reverberaciones de realidades alternativas? Claro que sí. En mis sueños deambulaba por allí, oía sus susurros, buscaba sus verdades. Pasaron muchos años hasta que me convertí en su propietario, pero incluso entonces la sentía mía.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">戦慄の館 - どんな街にも行ってはいけない場所が存在します。この館もそんな危ない場所でした。大人は、館に近寄らないよう子供達に言い聞かせ、感化されやすい子供心に対し「廃墟」や「危険」といった言葉を使って警告しました。このような警告によって、館との間に境界が生まれました。館の窓に現れた一瞬の光や、館のキーキーという音を聞いた子供たちは、叫び声をあげて街の安全な場所にころがり返ってきたものです。他の者は、ただの「幽霊屋敷」としてこの館を忘れました。しかし、私の心の奥深くで館は存在し続けました。子供というものは大人に比べ、別の世界の響きを感じる力に優れています。私自身、夢の中で館の中を歩き回り、そこでささやきを聞いたり、真実を探ったりしたものです。この館が私のものになる何年も前にそんな夢を見ましたが、あの時からすでに館は私の中に生き続けていたのです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">공포의 저택: 모든 마을에는 어둠의 장소가 있죠. 우리 마을에는 공포의 저택이 바로 그런 곳이었답니다. 부모님께서는 우리에게 경고를 하셨지만 그들도 우리처럼 어린 시절이 있었겠죠? '버려지고' '위험한'과 같은 경고성 단어들은 감수성이 예민한 우리들에게 더욱 매력적으로 들렸죠. 그렇게 우린 저택의 영역에 홀리듯 들어갔고 창문의 옅은 반짝거림이 보이거나 나무의 삐걱거림이 들리면 우리는 펄쩍 뛰고 소리치며 안전한 길가로 뛰어나가곤 했습니다. 하지만 다른 아이들은 그 집을 단순히 '귀신 들린 집'으로 치부했지만 저는 그 저택에 매혹되어 버렸습니다. 어린이들은 또 다른 세상의 울림을 더 잘 들을 수 있는 걸까요? 맞습니다. 꿈 속에서 전 그곳을 배회하며 속삭임을 듣고 진실을 찾아다녔습니다. 그곳이 제 소유가 되기 훨씬 전의 일이었지만 마음 속에서 그곳은 이미 제 소유였답니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Savage Manor: Every town has a dark place. The manor was ours. Our parents gave us red-faced warnings but were they never children? 'Abandoned', 'dangerous', these were words of enchantment to our impressionable minds. They drew us to its boundaries and the merest glint of light on a window or creak from a gable would have us tumbling and screaming back to the safety of our streets. But while the others never elevated it above 'haunted house', I let it seep into my psyche. Are children more attuned to resonances from alternate realities? Oh yes and in my dreams I roamed there, hearing it's whispers, searching for its truths. It would be many years before it was mine in fact but even then it was mine inside.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">野蠻莊園：每座城鎮都有其陰暗之處。莊園在我們的城鎮正是這樣的一個地方。父母曾嚴厲地警告我們，但是難道他們從來沒當過孩子嗎？在我們敏感的心靈中，「廢棄」、「危險」這些字眼有著無窮的魔力，吸引我們來到莊園外。而窗戶上閃爍的細微光亮或山牆嘎吱嘎吱作響都會讓我們連滾帶爬尖叫著逃回安全的街道。儘管其他人只把它當做「鬼屋」，而我卻讓它深入了我的靈魂。孩子們對來自異世界的共鳴會更敏感嗎？是的，在我的夢中，我曾在那裡漫遊，聆聽它的低語，搜尋它的事實真相。多年之後，莊園才真正為我所有，但我在當時就已經在心裡認定它是我的了。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">野蠻莊園：每座城鎮都有其陰暗之處。莊園在我們的城鎮正是這樣的一個地方。父母曾嚴厲地警告我們，但是難道他們從來沒當過孩子嗎？在我們敏感的心靈中，「廢棄」、「危險」這些字眼有著無窮的魔力，吸引我們來到莊園外。而窗戶上閃爍的細微光亮或山牆嘎吱嘎吱作響都會讓我們連滾帶爬尖叫著逃回安全的街道。儘管其他人只把它當做「鬼屋」，而我卻讓它深入了我的靈魂。孩子們對來自異世界的共鳴會更敏感嗎？是的，在我的夢中，我曾在那裡漫遊，聆聽它的低語，搜尋它的事實真相。多年之後，莊園才真正為我所有，但我在當時就已經在心裡認定它是我的了。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Savage Manor: Every town has a dark place. The manor was ours. Our parents gave us red-faced warnings but were they never children? 'Abandoned', 'dangerous', these were words of enchantment to our impressionable minds. They drew us to its boundaries and the merest glint of light on a window or creak from a gable would have us tumbling and screaming back to the safety of our streets. But while the others never elevated it above 'haunted house', I let it seep into my psyche. Are children more attuned to resonances from alternate realities? Oh yes and in my dreams I roamed there, hearing it's whispers, searching for its truths. It would be many years before it was mine in fact but even then it was mine inside.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment03</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nature: Dear guest, you must be wondering about the origins of my behaviour, that I am the product of a broken home. The tyranny of violence that was my constant companion showed me there was but one way to approach life. No doubt this is someone's sad story but it is not mine. My upbringing was measured, comfortable and dare I say dull. But I believe two facets of my upbringing did have had some bearing on my psyche: I have an inquiring mind given me by my mother and of equal import, my father's cold detachment. So simple a thing but one of the saddest truths - where love is held back something darker all too often fills its vacuum.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La nature : Cher hôte, vous devez vous interroger sur les origines de mon comportement. Je suis le produit d'une famille décomposée. La tyrannie de la violence étant ma seule compagne, elle m'a appris qu'il n'y avait qu'un seul moyen d'aborder la vie. Cette triste histoire appartient sûrement à quelqu'un, mais ce n'est pas la mienne. Mon éducation a été équilibrée, confortable et si j'ose dire, ennuyeuse. Mais je pense que deux facettes de mon éducation ont vraiment pesé sur mon mental : j'ai l'esprit curieux de ma mère et je tiens, à égale mesure, le détachement froid de mon père. Une chose tellement simple, mais d'une triste vérité : quand l'amour manque, quelque chose de plus sombre comble le vide.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Natur: Werter Gast, du fragst dich sicher, warum ich mich so seltsam verhalte, und denkst, dass ich aus einem kaputten Zuhause stamme. Die Tyrannei der Gewalt war mein steter Wegbegleiter, der mir zeigte, dass es nur eine Art zu leben gab. Zweifellos ist dies eine traurige Geschichte, doch es ist nicht meine. Ich wuchs wohl behütet und, wenn ich so sagen darf, gelangweilt auf. Doch ich glaube, zwei Facetten meiner Kindheit hatten Einfluss auf meine Psyche: Von meiner Mutter habe ich den scharfen Verstand geerbt, und von meinem Vater die kühle Distanziertheit. Es ist so einfach, aber auch so traurig: Wo die Liebe fehlt, füllt nur allzu oft etwas Dunkleres das Vakuum aus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Natura: gentile ospite, ti starai interrogando sulle origini del mio comportamento, penserai che sia il frutto di una famiglia a pezzi, che la tirannia della violenza sia stata la mia compagna fedele e mi abbia mostrato l'unico modo per prendere la vita. Certo è una storia triste, ma non è la mia. La mia giovinezza è stata moderata, comoda e, oserei dire, noiosa. Ma credo che due aspetti della mia educazione abbiano avuto delle ripercussioni sulla mia psiche: ho la mente curiosa di mia madre e il freddo distacco di mio padre. Una cosa così semplice, ma una delle più tristi verità: quando non viene dato abbastanza amore, troppo spesso qualcosa di più oscuro va a riempire quel vuoto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Naturaleza: querido huésped, te estarás planteando el origen de mi comportamiento, si soy el producto de un hogar desestructurado. La tiranía de la violencia que era mi constante compañera, me mostró que solo hay una forma de enfrentarse a la vida. Seguro que es la triste historia de alguien, pero no la mía. Mi educación fue moderada, cómoda e incluso me atrevo a decir que aburrida. Pero creo que dos facetas de mi educación afectaron a mi psique: de mi madre heredé una mente curiosa e, igual de importante, de mi padre heredé la fría indiferencia. Es algo muy sencillo, pero una de las verdades más tristes: cuando no se da amor, normalmente algo oscuro llena su vacío.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">生まれ - ゲストの皆様は、私の奇妙な言動や、その発端である複雑な家庭環境について疑問にお感じでしょう。私は常にこの館で起きた絶え間ない暴力を見てきました。しかしそれは、私ではない、他の誰かの人生であり、悲しみのストーリーなのです。私の育ちと言えば、適正で何不自由なく、あえて言うと退屈な環境でした。しかし、私の家庭環境が持つ二つの局面が、私の心を形成したことは確かです。その二局面とは、母から受けた探求心、そして相反する父のそっけない無関心さです。これは実に単純ですが、最も悲しい真実でもあります。愛情によって満たされなかった闇に残るのは虚無感なのです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">본성: 손님들은 저의 이상한 말과 행동의 발단이 되는 복잡한 가정환경에 대해 궁금하실겁니다. 저는 이 집에서 늘상 일어났던 폭력을 봐왔습니다. 이것은 누군가의 슬픈 이야기임엔 틀림없지만 제 이야기는 아닙니다. 제가 자라온 이야기는 평범하고 안락해서 굳이 말하자면 지루할 수도 있습니다. 하지만 전 제가 자라온 과정 중에서 두 가지 측면이 제 정신 세계에 큰 영향을 끼쳤다고 믿고 있습니다. 그 하나는 어머니로부터 물려받은 강한 탐구심, 그리고 다른 하나는 아버지의 차가운 무관심입니다. 이것은 실로 단순하지만 가장 슬픈 진실입니다. 사랑이 없는 곳엔 너무나도 쉽게 어둠의 존재가 그 공허를 채우기 마련이라는 것입니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Nature: Dear guest, you must be wondering about the origins of my behaviour, that I am the product of a broken home. The tyranny of violence that was my constant companion showed me there was but one way to approach life. No doubt this is someone's sad story but it is not mine. My upbringing was measured, comfortable and dare I say dull. But I believe two facets of my upbringing did have had some bearing on my psyche: I have an inquiring mind given me by my mother and of equal import, my father's cold detachment. So simple a thing but one of the saddest truths - where love is held back something darker all too often fills its vacuum.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">天性：尊敬的客人，你肯定正在猜測我行為的原由，認為我來自一個破碎的家庭。常伴左右的暴力專政讓我明白生活只有一條路可走。這無疑是某個人的悲慘故事，但卻不是我的。我的成長經歷從容不迫、舒適安逸，而且恕我直言，相當的平淡無趣。但我認為我成長經歷的兩方面確實對我的心智具有一定的影響：母親賦予我的求索之心以及父親的冷靜超然，二者同樣重要。很簡單但又最悲慘的一個真理是 — 在愛被遏制的地方，陰暗往往會填補其真空。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">天性：尊敬的客人，你肯定正在猜測我行為的原由，認為我來自一個破碎的家庭。常伴左右的暴力專政讓我明白生活只有一條路可走。這無疑是某個人的悲慘故事，但卻不是我的。我的成長經歷從容不迫、舒適安逸，而且恕我直言，相當的平淡無趣。但我認為我成長經歷的兩方面確實對我的心智具有一定的影響：母親賦予我的求索之心以及父親的冷靜超然，二者同樣重要。很簡單但又最悲慘的一個真理是 — 在愛被遏制的地方，陰暗往往會填補其真空。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Nature: Dear guest, you must be wondering about the origins of my behaviour, that I am the product of a broken home. The tyranny of violence that was my constant companion showed me there was but one way to approach life. No doubt this is someone's sad story but it is not mine. My upbringing was measured, comfortable and dare I say dull. But I believe two facets of my upbringing did have had some bearing on my psyche: I have an inquiring mind given me by my mother and of equal import, my father's cold detachment. So simple a thing but one of the saddest truths - where love is held back something darker all too often fills its vacuum.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment04</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Twins: I was telling you of nature but nurture is even more important to a growing mind. How... we contort ourselves... to fit in. The politics of the school yard were such that I fell in with the dark twins, two homunculi with beetled brow and bloodied knuckles. Even then the manor had an old walk-in cold room. Ignoring our parents' warnings, we would catch small animals, a mouse, a bird and take them up to the cold room... The twins didn't have the imagination to take it further. My quest for knowledge had begun.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les Jumelles : La nature, certes, mais l'éducation est encore plus importante pour un esprit en pleine croissance. Le rôle que nous jouons... pour nous intégrer. Dans la cour de récréation, je me suis retrouvé avec les sombres jumelles, deux homuncules aux sourcils épais et aux poings couverts de sang. Le manoir avait déjà une vieille chambre froide. Ignorant les avertissements de nos parents, nous attrapions de petits animaux (souris, oiseaux) et les emmenions dans la chambre froide... Les jumelles n'avaient aucune imagination après cela. Ce fut le début de ma quête du savoir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Zwillinge: Ich hatte dir von der Natur erzählt, doch für einen Heranwachsenden ist noch wichtiger, wie er gefördert wird. Wie wir uns ... verrenken ... um uns anzupassen. Auf dem Pausenhof habe ich mich mit den beiden finsteren Zwillingen eingelassen, zwei Homunculi mit käfergleichen Augen und blutigen Fingerknöcheln. Schon damals hatte der Landsitz einen alten begehbaren Kühlraum. Wir schlugen die Warnungen unserer Eltern in den Wind, fingen kleine Tiere, eine Maus, einen Vogel, und brachten sie in den Kühlraum ... Den Zwillingen fehlte die Fantasie, um das Spiel weiterzutreiben. Doch meine Suche nach Wissen hatte gerade erst begonnen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I gemelli: ti stavo parlando della natura, ma l'educazione è ancora più importante per una mente che si sta sviluppando. Come... ci contorciamo... per starci dentro. All'interno della scuola, le dinamiche fecero sì che diventassi amico dei gemelli oscuri, due omuncoli con le sopracciglia folte e le nocche insanguinate. Anche allora il maniero aveva una stanza che faceva da ingresso, sempre fredda. Ignorando gli avvertimenti dei genitori, catturavamo dei piccoli animali: un topo, un uccellino e li portavamo in quella stanza fredda... I gemelli non avevano l'immaginazione per andare oltre. La mia ricerca di conoscenza era cominciata.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las gemelas: te estaba hablando de la naturaleza, pero la educación es aún más importante para una mente en pleno desarrollo. Cómo… nos retorcemos… para encajar. Por las políticas del patio del colegio acabé juntándome con las gemelas oscuras, dos homúnculos de ceños fruncidos y nudillos ensangrentados. Incluso entonces, la mansión tenía una cámara frigorífica. Ignorando las advertencias de nuestros padres, cazábamos pequeños animales, un ratón, un pájaro y los metíamos en la cámara... Las gemelas no tenían más imaginación. Mi búsqueda del conocimiento había empezado.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">双子 - 私の生まれについて先ほどお話ししましたが、精神的成長期にとってより重要なのは環境です。つまり... どのようにして私たちは... 社会に適応するため自分自身をねじ曲げてきたかということです。学校生活の中で、私は、陰険なケンカ好きの背の低い双子と連れ添うようになりました。その当時、館には古くて寒い部屋がありました。大人の忠告をよそに、私たちは、ネズミや鳥などの小動物を捕まえては、それらをその寒い部屋に持っていきました... 双子は、館に対する理解力と想像力に欠けていました。しかしそれは、私にとって館の謎を知るための探索の始まりだったのです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">쌍둥이: 제가 앞서 본성에 대해 설명을 하긴 했지만 자라나는 이에게 더욱 중요한 것은 양육입니다. 우리가…. 어울리기 위해 어떻게 스스로를 일그러뜨려왔는지. 튀어나온 눈썹과 피로 물든 주먹을 가진 음험한 쌍둥이들과 항상 붙어다녔습니다. 그 당시 저택에는 차가운 방이 있었습니다. 부모님의 경고를 무시하고 쥐나 새 같은 작은 동물을 잡아 그 차가운 방에 가져갔습니다… 쌍둥이는 이것 말고는 다른게 생각나지 않았습니다. 하지만 이건 나에게 있어 집 안의 미스테리의 궁금증을 해소하기 위한 첫 걸음이 되었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Twins: I was telling you of nature but nurture is even more important to a growing mind. How... we contort ourselves... to fit in. The politics of the school yard were such that I fell in with the dark twins, two homunculi with beetled brow and bloodied knuckles. Even then the manor had an old walk-in cold room. Ignoring our parents' warnings, we would catch small animals, a mouse, a bird and take them up to the cold room... The twins didn't have the imagination to take it further. My quest for knowledge had begun.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">雙胞胎：我剛剛和你談的是天性，但是對於不斷成長的心智而言，後天的培養更加重要。即我們是如何……扭曲自己……來適應的。校園政治讓我偶然結識了黑暗雙胞胎 — 兩個眉毛突起、指節流血的侏儒。莊園在那時有個可直接步入的古老冷藏室。我們不顧父母的警告，會捉些小動物（如老鼠、鳥）帶到冷藏室……那對雙胞胎並沒有進行進一步行動的想像力。而我對知識的追求已經開始了。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">雙胞胎：我剛剛和你談的是天性，但是對於不斷成長的心智而言，後天的培養更加重要。即我們是如何……扭曲自己……來適應的。校園政治讓我偶然結識了黑暗雙胞胎 — 兩個眉毛突起、指節流血的侏儒。莊園在那時有個可直接步入的古老冷藏室。我們不顧父母的警告，會捉些小動物（如老鼠、鳥）帶到冷藏室……那對雙胞胎並沒有進行進一步行動的想像力。而我對知識的追求已經開始了。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Twins: I was telling you of nature but nurture is even more important to a growing mind. How... we contort ourselves... to fit in. The politics of the school yard were such that I fell in with the dark twins, two homunculi with beetled brow and bloodied knuckles. Even then the manor had an old walk-in cold room. Ignoring our parents' warnings, we would catch small animals, a mouse, a bird and take them up to the cold room... The twins didn't have the imagination to take it further. My quest for knowledge had begun.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment05</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Visitor: Need you wonder about the twins? Need you? The police conducted a manhunt and within the day they were found. Need I tell you where? I donned my mask of innocence like all the other kids and watched the furore open mouthed. Oh fools, they didn't get close! I maintained my mask and gradually the horror became myth and the myth a faint odour, all but forgotten. Even I, a model son once more, forgot what should never have been forgotten. And then a month after my 16th birthday, a visitor came to our town, attracted by that faint odour of death that still lingered. Three dead in as many months, it was very exciting. Parents climbed out of their dull skins and showed their claws; the lone men were watched with suspicion and barely contained hatred. A madness was loosed and oh, the air crackled with the ozone of chaos unbound. I wanted that hatred... most of all I wanted to deserve that hatred! As the murders all took place to a full moon, all the talk was of a werewolf. Silly yes, but often a germ of truth adheres to such things. I was curious and I took it upon myself to investigate further.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le visiteur : Est-il bien nécessaire de parler des jumelles ? Vraiment ? La police entreprit une chasse à l'homme et elles furent retrouvées dans la journée. Dois-je vous dire où ? J'ai revêtu mon masque d'innocence comme tous les autres enfants et regardé le scandale, la bouche ouverte. Les idiots n'élucidèrent jamais l'affaire ! Je gardais mon masque et petit à petit, l'horreur devint mythe, et le mythe se transforma en une subtile odeur, presque oubliée. Moi-même, fils modèle à nouveau, oubliai ce qui ne devait jamais être oublié. Puis, un mois après mon 16e anniversaire, un visiteur arriva au village, attiré par une légère odeur de mort qui persistait encore. Trois morts en trois mois, c'était palpitant. Les parents délaissèrent leur vie monotone pour montrer leurs griffes, observant les hommes solitaires avec méfiance et haine à peine contenue. Une folie régnait et on pouvait entendre crépiter l'air chargé d'un chaos sans limites. Je voulais cette haine... par-dessus tout je voulais la mériter ! Comme tous les meurtres arrivaient à la pleine lune, on parlait d'un loup-garou. Ridicule, bien sûr, mais souvent il y a un grain de vérité. J'étais curieux et je décidai d'enquêter un peu plus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Besucher: Muss man sich wegen der Zwillinge noch wundern? Muss man? Die Polizei veranlasste eine Großfahndung, und noch am gleichen Tage fand man sie. Muss ich noch sagen, wo? Ich setzte wie all die anderen Kinder meine Unschuldsmiene auf und sah mir das Spektakel mit offenem Mund an. Was für Narren, die kamen der Sache nicht mal nahe! Ich behielt meine Unschuldsmiene, und nach und nach wurde das Grauen zur Legende und die Legende zu einem Hauch, der so gut wie vergessen war. Selbst ich als Bilderbuchsohn vergaß, was niemals hätte vergessen werden sollen. Und einen Monat nach meinem 16. Geburtstag kam dann ein Besucher in unsere Stadt, angezogen von jenem schwachen Hauch des Todes, der immer noch nicht verflogen war. Drei Tote in ebenso vielen Monaten, das war schon sehr spannend. Eltern fuhren aus ihrer langweiligen Haut und zeigten ihre Krallen. Die einsamen Männer wurden argwöhnisch und mit kaum verhohlenem Hass betrachtet. Ein wahrer Wahn war entfesselt worden und, oh, wie die Luft vom Ozon des Chaos knisterte. Ich wollte jenen Hass ... und am meisten wollte ich jenen Hass verdienen! Da die Morde alle bei Vollmond geschehen waren, sprach man allenthalben von einem Werwolf. Albern, sicher, aber oft steckt in solchen Sachen ja ein Fünkchen Wahrheit. Ich war neugierig und fing an selbst Ermittlungen anzustellen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il visitatore: ti chiedi che ne è stato dei gemelli? La polizia condusse una caccia all'uomo e in ventiquattr'ore li ritrovarono. Devo dirti dove? Indossai la mia maschera d'innocenza, come tutti gli altri bambini, e osservai a bocca aperta il clamore suscitato. Oh folli, non si avvicinarono neanche alla verità! Io mantenni la mia maschera e gradualmente l'orrore divenne mito e il mito un lieve odore, quasi dimenticato. Anch'io, di nuovo figlio modello, dimenticai quello che non avrei mai dovuto dimenticare. E poi, un mese dopo il mio sedicesimo compleanno, in città arrivò un visitatore, attratto da quel lieve odore di morte che ancora aleggiava. Tre morti in tre mesi, niente male. I genitori uscirono dalla loro pelle fatta di noia e mostrarono gli artigli; gli uomini solitari erano guardati con sospetto e con odio malcelato. La follia era tra noi e, oh, l'aria crepitò con l'ozono del caos liberato! Dato che gli omicidi avvennero tutti con la luna piena, non si parlava d'altro che di lupi mannari. Sciocco, sì, ma spesso in queste dicerie c'è una gemma di verità. Ero curioso e decisi di investigare oltre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El visitante: ¿Te preguntas por las gemelas? La policía realizó una batida y las encontraron en un día. ¿Quieres saber dónde? Me puse la máscara de la inocencia como el resto de niños y observé el escándalo con la boca abierta. Necios, ¡ni se acercaron! Seguí con mi máscara y, poco a poco, el terror se convirtió en mito y el mito en una leve fragancia olvidada. Incluso yo, que volvía a ser un hijo modelo, olvidé lo que nunca debería haberse olvidado. Un mes después de mi 16 cumpleaños, un visitante llego a la ciudad, atraído por la tenue fragancia de muerte que permanecía en el ambiente. Tres muertos en tres meses: era emocionante. Los padres salieron de sus aburridas pieles y enseñaron las garras; se miraba a los hombre solitarios con recelo y apenas se contenía el odio. Se desató una locura y el aire crepitaba con el ozono del caos desatado. Quería aquel odio... ¡Quería merecer aquel odio! Dado que los asesinatos tuvieron lugar con luna llena, todos los rumores apuntaban a un hombre lobo. Aunque parezca absurdo, en este tipo de cosas hay alguna verdad. Tenía curiosidad y me encargué de investigar más.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">訪問者 - その後、その双子はどうなったかって？警察による捜査が開始され、双子は即日発見されました。双子がどこで発見されたかは、もうお分かりでしょう。私は、他の子供達と同様、無実の仮面を被り、マスコミの騒ぎ立てを楽しんでいました。愚かなマスコミの予想はこれぽっちも当たらなかったのです！私は無実の仮面を着けたまま時を過ごしました。いつしか人々の間でこの騒動は神話となり、かすかな死臭を残し、忘れ去られました。優等生の私でさえ、あの強烈な過去を忘れていました。ところが、今だに残る死臭に誘われ、街に訪問者がやって来たのです。それは、私の16歳の誕生日から一ヵ月後でした。殺人鬼は数か月で三人の死者を出し、私を楽しませてくれました。親たちは子供を守ろうと必死でした。独り者の無実の男が疑われ、街は狂気に溢れ混乱の渦に包まれました。私は、憎悪を願っていた... 何よりも人々に憎悪を味あわせてやりたかった！殺人が満月の夜に犯されたことから、人々の話題の的はオオカミ人間に絞られました。オオカミ人間なんて馬鹿げている。しかし、ささいな真実は、このような事件を可能にする。私は、好奇心からこの事件に関する調査を開始したのです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">방문객: 쌍둥이가 어떻게 됐는지 궁금한가요? 정말 알고싶나요? 경찰이 수색 작업을 벌였고 하루가 채 지나기도 전에 쌍둥이가 발견됐습니다. 어디서 발견됐는지 얘기해 줄까요? 저는 다른 아이들처럼 순수함의 가면을 쓰고 그 소동을 넋이 나간채 지켜봤습니다. 멍청한 사람들. 전혀 눈치채지 못하더군요! 저는 제 가면을 유지했고 차츰 공포는 전설이 되고 전설은 희미한 악취로 변했으며 결국 모두 잊혀졌습니다. 모범생이었던 저조차도 절대 잊어서는 안 될 그 일을 잊고 말았습니다. 그리고 제 16번째 생일이 한 달이 지난 시점에 한 방문객이 우리 마을을 찾아왔는데 아직까지도 남아있는 그 희미한 죽음의 악취에 이끌려 온 것이죠. 수개월 동안 3명이 죽었고, 상당히 흥분되는 일이었죠. 부모님들은 무표정한 표정을 버리고 그들의 발톱을 보이기 시작했습니다. 의심스러운 눈길로 홀로된 사람들을 지켜보고 증오심을 감추지 못했죠. 광기가 시작되고 공기는 속박에서 풀려난 혼란으로 금이 가기 시작했습니다. 전 그 증오를 원했어요... 전 사실 그 증오의 대상이 되길 바랬던 겁니다! 모든 살인이 보름달이 뜬 날에만 일어났기 때문에 늑대인간이 범인이라는 이야기도 있었어요. 맞아요. 바보같은 소리예요. 하지만 진실의 기원은 그런 것에 들러붙기 마련이죠. 전 호기심이 생겼고 직접 조사를 나서기에 이르렀죠.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Visitor: Need you wonder about the twins? Need you? The police conducted a manhunt and within the day they were found. Need I tell you where? I donned my mask of innocence like all the other kids and watched the furore open mouthed. Oh fools, they didn't get close! I maintained my mask and gradually the horror became myth and the myth a faint odour, all but forgotten. Even I, a model son once more, forgot what should never have been forgotten. And then a month after my 16th birthday, a visitor came to our town, attracted by that faint odour of death that still lingered. Three dead in as many months, it was very exciting. Parents climbed out of their dull skins and showed their claws; the lone men were watched with suspicion and barely contained hatred. A madness was loosed and oh, the air crackled with the ozone of chaos unbound. I wanted that hatred... most of all I wanted to deserve that hatred! As the murders all took place to a full moon, all the talk was of a werewolf. Silly yes, but often a germ of truth adheres to such things. I was curious and I took it upon myself to investigate further.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">訪客：你想知道那對雙胞胎發生了什麽嗎？需要嗎？警方進行了搜捕行動，並在當天內就發現了他們。需要我告訴你在什麽地方嗎？我戴上了與所有其他孩子別無二致的純真面具，驚異地看著這場騷亂風波。哦，傻瓜，他們都沒有與我交談！我保持著我的偽裝，而這一恐怖事件漸漸流為傳言，又由傳言化為淡淡的氣味，幾乎全被淡忘了。即使是曾為模範兒子的我也忘記了本不該被遺忘的事情。在我 16 歲生日的一個月後，我們的鎮子來了一位被那股仍然縈繞不散的淡淡死亡氣味吸引而來的訪客。數月內即有三人死亡是非常讓人興奮的。家長們紛紛打破呆板的形象、伸出利爪；離群索居的人被人們以懷疑乃至幾乎包含仇恨的目光打探著。瘋狂在各處難以控制地肆意蔓延，空氣中不受約束的混亂情緒劈啪作響。我想要的正是這種仇恨……最重要的是，我希望能配得上這種仇恨！由於謀殺均發生在滿月時，大家都在談論狼人。是的，這很愚蠢，但往往真理會隨之而來。我很好奇，於是我開始擅自進行進一步調查。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">訪客：你想知道那對雙胞胎發生了什麽嗎？需要嗎？警方進行了搜捕行動，並在當天內就發現了他們。需要我告訴你在什麽地方嗎？我戴上了與所有其他孩子別無二致的純真面具，驚異地看著這場騷亂風波。哦，傻瓜，他們都沒有與我交談！我保持著我的偽裝，而這一恐怖事件漸漸流為傳言，又由傳言化為淡淡的氣味，幾乎全被淡忘了。即使是曾為模範兒子的我也忘記了本不該被遺忘的事情。在我 16 歲生日的一個月後，我們的鎮子來了一位被那股仍然縈繞不散的淡淡死亡氣味吸引而來的訪客。數月內即有三人死亡是非常讓人興奮的。家長們紛紛打破呆板的形象、伸出利爪；離群索居的人被人們以懷疑乃至幾乎包含仇恨的目光打探著。瘋狂在各處難以控制地肆意蔓延，空氣中不受約束的混亂情緒劈啪作響。我想要的正是這種仇恨……最重要的是，我希望能配得上這種仇恨！由於謀殺均發生在滿月時，大家都在談論狼人。是的，這很愚蠢，但往往真理會隨之而來。我很好奇，於是我開始擅自進行進一步調查。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Visitor: Need you wonder about the twins? Need you? The police conducted a manhunt and within the day they were found. Need I tell you where? I donned my mask of innocence like all the other kids and watched the furore open mouthed. Oh fools, they didn't get close! I maintained my mask and gradually the horror became myth and the myth a faint odour, all but forgotten. Even I, a model son once more, forgot what should never have been forgotten. And then a month after my 16th birthday, a visitor came to our town, attracted by that faint odour of death that still lingered. Three dead in as many months, it was very exciting. Parents climbed out of their dull skins and showed their claws; the lone men were watched with suspicion and barely contained hatred. A madness was loosed and oh, the air crackled with the ozone of chaos unbound. I wanted that hatred... most of all I wanted to deserve that hatred! As the murders all took place to a full moon, all the talk was of a werewolf. Silly yes, but often a germ of truth adheres to such things. I was curious and I took it upon myself to investigate further.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment06</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Man-Wolf: I presented myself as a victim and by the light of the moon the werewolf approached me. He was a man of course, a man inside the skin of a dog but the effect was thrilling. He could see I wasn't the least bit scared and delayed his attack. I offered him a cigarette and as easy as that he slid his hood off. A sweat stained, pock-ravished faced emerged. Cheers he said and that moment I knew this creature did not deserve the furore he had caused, certainly not such a rare fleece. He wasn't mad, few really are. He believed man long ago had made a pact the creator, trading our bodies, good and strong for the ability to reason. He was seeking to make amends, to re-engage his primitivism. Entering wholly into the spirit, I slay him with an ancient rock, took his fleece and all the vile crimes he had committed for my own and for the next year rolled in the stink of his legend, building upon it when the opportunity arose.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'homme-loup : Je m'offris en tant que victime et dans le clair de lune, le loup-garou m'approcha. C'était un homme bien entendu, un homme dans la peau d'un chien, mais l'effet était fascinant. Il vit que je n'étais point effrayé et repoussa son attaque. Je lui offris une cigarette, et très simplement, il retira sa capuche. Un visage en sueur et couvert de cicatrices émergea. Merci, dit-il et à ce moment, je sus que cette créature ne méritait pas le scandale qu'il avait provoqué, et encore moins une telle réputation. Il n'était pas fou, peu le sont vraiment. Il avait foi dans le fait que l'homme avait, jadis, scellé un pacte avec le créateur, échangeant nos corps, bons et forts, contre la capacité de raisonner. Il cherchait à faire amende honorable, à rétablir son primitivisme. En m'immergeant totalement dans cet esprit, je le tuai avec une pierre ancienne, pris sa toison et tous ses crimes infâmes à mon compte et l'année suivante, je me roulai dans la puanteur de sa légende, en la continuant dès qu'une opportunité se présentait.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mannwolf: Ich bot mich als Opfer an, und im Mondschein näherte sich mir der Werwolf. Natürlich war es ein Mann, ein Mann unter dem Fell eines Hundes, aber unheimlich war es schon. Als er merkte, dass ich überhaupt keine Angst hatte, wartete er mit seinem Angriff. Ich bot ihm eine Zigarette an, und er ließ ganz einfach die Kapuze sinken. Ein schweißnasses pockennarbiges Gesicht erschien. "Danke", sagte er, und da wusste ich, dass dieses Geschöpf nicht all den Aufruhr verdiente, den er verursacht hatte, und schon gar nicht so ein kostbares Vlies. Er war nicht verrückt, was eh kaum jemand wirklich ist. Er glaubte, der Mensch habe vor langer Zeit einen Pakt mit dem Schöpfer geschlossen und unsere Körper, gut und stark, gegen die Vernunft eingetauscht. Er wollte wieder zurück zu seinem primitiven Dasein. Ich ließ ich voll und ganz darauf ein, erschlug ihn mit einem uralten Stein und eignete mir sein Vlies und all die schrecklichen Verbrechen an, die er begangen hatte, und das ganze folgende Jahr lang suhlte ich mich im Gestank seiner Legende und baute sie aus, wann immer sich die Gelegenheit ergab.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Uomo-lupo: mi presentai come una vittima e, sotto la luce della luna, il lupo mannaro si avvicinò. Naturalmente era un uomo, un uomo dentro la pelle di un cane, ma l'effetto era spaventoso. Si accorse che non avevo alcuna paura e ritardò il suo attacco. Gli offrii una sigaretta e, come niente, si levò il cappuccio. Ne emerse un volto sudato, orribilmente butterato. Mi ringraziò e lì capii che quella creatura non meritava il clamore che aveva suscitato. Non era pazzo, sono in pochi a essere veramente pazzi. Credeva che molto tempo addietro l'uomo avesse fatto un patto con il creatore e gli avesse ceduto i nostri corpi, belli e forti, in cambio dell'abilità di ragionare. Lui stava cercando di fare ammenda, di riavvicinarsi al primitivismo. Completamento immerso in quello spirito, lo uccisi con una roccia antica, mi accollai la pelle di cane e i vili crimini che aveva commesso e per tutto l'anno seguente mi rotolai nel puzzo della sua leggenda, costruendoci sopra quando se ne presentava l'occasione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hombre lobo: me ofrecí como víctima y, a la luz de la luna, el hombre lobo se me acercó. Por supuesto, era un hombre que llevaba la piel de un perro, pero el efecto era electrizante. Notó que no estaba mínimamente asustado y retrasó su ataque. Le ofrecí un cigarrillo y se quitó la capucha. Apareció una cara bañada en sudor y marcas. Me dio las gracias y en ese momento supe que aquella criatura no merecía el revuelo que había causado, ni tampoco aquel vellón tan excepcional. No estaba loco, pocos de ellos lo están. Creía que, hacía mucho tiempo, un hombre hizo un pacto con el creador y cambió nuestros cuerpos, los buenos y los fuertes, por la capacidad de razonar. Pretendía enmendar sus errores, volver a su primitivismo. Me metí en el papel y acabé con él con una vieja piedra, me quedé con su vellón y con todos los crímenes que había cometido como si fueran míos. El año siguiente viví de su leyenda, haciéndola realidad cuando tenía la oportunidad.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オオカミ人間 - 私は、満月の夜、自分自身を犠牲にしてオオカミ人間が出てくるのを待ちました。もちろん殺人鬼は人間でした。奴は野獣の皮を被った男でした。そこで面白いことが起こりました。オオカミ人間の姿にまったく怯えることのない私の様子に驚き、男は攻撃にうろたえたのです。私がタバコをすすめると、男は躊躇することなく頭巾を外しました。男は、汗にまみれたアバタまみれの顔を現しました。私は、礼を言う男の顔を見て、奴が犯した罪にこのような仕打ちは値しないと感じました。中には本当に狂った奴もいますが、男は狂人ではなかったです。男は原始の精神を再構築したいと考えていた。古代の人類が行った生贄の儀式によってパワーを得れると信じていたのです。完全に魂と一体化させてやるため、私は、その男を古代の岩で殺害し、奴が犯した卑劣な殺人行為を戒めてやりました。今後、この悪臭が取り巻く伝説は語り継がれることでしょう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">늑대인간: 전 제 스스로를 미끼로 늑대인간을 기다렸고, 달빛 아래 늑대인간이 다가왔습니다. 그는 물론 인간이었습니다. 개의 가죽 속에 모습을 감춘 인간. 하지만 그 효과 만큼은 소름끼쳤죠. 그도 제가 전혀 두려워하지 않는다는 것을 눈치채고 공격을 잠시 멈췄습니다. 그에게 담배를 건냈고, 그리고 그는 쉽게 그의 두건을 벗었습니다. 땀에 찌들고 곰보인 얼굴이 드러났죠. 그는 건배를 외쳤고, 그 순간 이 사람은 그 소동의 장본인이 될 자격이 없음을 깨달았고 진귀한 털을 뒤집어 쓸 자격조차 없다고 생각했습니다. 그는 미치광이도 아니었습니다. 그는 오래 전 인간이 생각하는 능력을 위해 창조주와 우리의 시체를 거래하는 계약을 맺었다고 믿고 있었습니다. 그는 원시의 상태로 돌아가기 위해 노력했습니다. 분위기에 빠져들면서 전 오래된 바위로 그를 죽이고 그가 저지른 용납할 수 없는 모든 범죄를 정죄하였습니다. 그리고 이 악취나는 전설은 이어져 가게 되었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Man-Wolf: I presented myself as a victim and by the light of the moon the werewolf approached me. He was a man of course, a man inside the skin of a dog but the effect was thrilling. He could see I wasn't the least bit scared and delayed his attack. I offered him a cigarette and as easy as that he slid his hood off. A sweat stained, pock-ravished faced emerged. Cheers he said and that moment I knew this creature did not deserve the furore he had caused, certainly not such a rare fleece. He wasn't mad, few really are. He believed man long ago had made a pact the creator, trading our bodies, good and strong for the ability to reason. He was seeking to make amends, to re-engage his primitivism. Entering wholly into the spirit, I slay him with an ancient rock, took his fleece and all the vile crimes he had committed for my own and for the next year rolled in the stink of his legend, building upon it when the opportunity arose.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">狼人：我將自己裝扮成受害者，而狼人借著月光向我走來。他當然是個人，一個披著狗皮的人，但效果卻令人毛骨悚然。他能看出我一點也不害怕，於是延緩了進攻。我給了他一支煙，就這麼簡單，他摘下了兜帽，露出一張汗涔涔、滿是麻子的臉，說了一聲謝謝。就在那一刻，我意識到這個生物根本配不上他所造成的轟動，這樣少見的詐騙肯定是不配的。他沒瘋，很少有人是真的瘋狂。他認為，人類在很久以前曾與造物主達成協定，用我們優秀強壯的身體來交換推理能力。他正設法進行彌補，想重新實行原始主義。在完全進入精神後，我用一塊古老的岩石殺了他，把他的欺詐行為和犯下的所有卑鄙罪行留給我自己，並在第二年以此為基礎在機會出現時源源不斷地建立起他的惡名。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">狼人：我將自己裝扮成受害者，而狼人借著月光向我走來。他當然是個人，一個披著狗皮的人，但效果卻令人毛骨悚然。他能看出我一點也不害怕，於是延緩了進攻。我給了他一支煙，就這麼簡單，他摘下了兜帽，露出一張汗涔涔、滿是麻子的臉，說了一聲謝謝。就在那一刻，我意識到這個生物根本配不上他所造成的轟動，這樣少見的詐騙肯定是不配的。他沒瘋，很少有人是真的瘋狂。他認為，人類在很久以前曾與造物主達成協定，用我們優秀強壯的身體來交換推理能力。他正設法進行彌補，想重新實行原始主義。在完全進入精神後，我用一塊古老的岩石殺了他，把他的欺詐行為和犯下的所有卑鄙罪行留給我自己，並在第二年以此為基礎在機會出現時源源不斷地建立起他的惡名。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Man-Wolf: I presented myself as a victim and by the light of the moon the werewolf approached me. He was a man of course, a man inside the skin of a dog but the effect was thrilling. He could see I wasn't the least bit scared and delayed his attack. I offered him a cigarette and as easy as that he slid his hood off. A sweat stained, pock-ravished faced emerged. Cheers he said and that moment I knew this creature did not deserve the furore he had caused, certainly not such a rare fleece. He wasn't mad, few really are. He believed man long ago had made a pact the creator, trading our bodies, good and strong for the ability to reason. He was seeking to make amends, to re-engage his primitivism. Entering wholly into the spirit, I slay him with an ancient rock, took his fleece and all the vile crimes he had committed for my own and for the next year rolled in the stink of his legend, building upon it when the opportunity arose.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment07</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Inadequacies of Man: I must speak to you of the inadequacies of man. Look at yourself - thin skinned, a gesture of fur, slow on your feet, easily hurt. How puny! Having to rely on augmentation and collaboration to succeed. That miserable creature was right after all and he -he!- was looking to better creation's design! Since that revelation I too have been obsessed by our inadequacies. Since you are currently in my kitchen you must have by now seen evidence of my studies. The skin is what others see of us, our self presented to the world. But is it us? What lays beneath, in the sinew and bone, surely this is where the true person hides. There was but one way to find out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les déficiences de l'homme : Je dois vous parler des déficiences de l'homme. Regardez-vous : une peau fine, un poil de fourrure, la lenteur du bipède, facilement blessé. Quel être chétif ! Devoir compter sur l'augmentation et la collaboration pour le succès. Cette misérable créature avait raison finalement, et il... lui !... était à la recherche d'un meilleur modèle de création ! Depuis cette révélation, je suis moi aussi obsédé par nos déficiences. Puisque vous vous trouvez dans ma cuisine, vous aurez remarqué les indications de mes études. La peau est ce que le monde percóit de nous. Mais, est-ce bien nous ? Qu'y a-t-il en dessous, dans la chair et les os, c'est sûrement là que la vraie personne se cache. Il n'y avait qu'un moyen de le savoir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Unzulänglichkeiten des Menschen: Ich muss dir von den Unzulänglichkeiten des Menschen erzählen. Sieh dich nur an - dünnhäutig, Flaum statt Fell, langsam auf den Beinen, leicht zu verletzen. Jämmerlich! Du musst dich auf Hilfsmittel und andere verlassen, um erfolgreich zu sein. Dieses elendige Geschöpf hatte letzten Endes doch recht, und er - ER! - wollte die Schöpfung verbessern! Seit jener Offenbarung bin auch ich von unseren Unzulänglichkeiten besessen. Da du gerade in meiner Küche bist, hast sicherlich schon Beweise für meine Studien gesehen. Die Haut ist das, was andere von uns sehen, unser Selbst, wie es sich der Welt zeigt. Doch sind wir das wirklich? Der wahre Mensch verbirgt sich gewiss darunter, wo die Sehnen und Knochen sind. Es gab nur einen Weg, das herauszufinden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le inadeguatezze dell'uomo: devo parlarti delle inadeguatezze dell'uomo. Guardati: pelle sottile, appena un po' di peluria, poca agilità, facile da braccare. Che debolezza! Dover fare affidamento su incremento e collaborazione per affermarsi. Dopotutto quella miserabile creatura aveva ragione e si stava solo dando da fare per migliorare la creazione! Dopo quella rivelazione, iniziai a essere ossessionato dalle nostre inadeguatezze. Dato che sei nella mia cucina, avrai capito la natura dei miei studi. La pelle è ciò che gli altri vedono di noi, siamo noi che ci presentiamo al mondo. Ma siamo davvero noi? Quello che c'è sotto, nei nervi e nelle ossa... Dev'essere là che si cela la vera persona. C'era solo un modo per scoprirlo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las ineptitudes del hombre: debo hablarte de las ineptitudes del hombre. Mírate, tienes la piel fina, un ademán de furia, eres lento, se te puede herir con facilidad. ¡Menudo enclenque! Dependes del crecimiento y la colaboración para tener éxito. Aquella miserable criatura llevaba razón... ¡buscaba mejorar el diseño de la creación! Desde su revelación, a mí también me han obsesionado nuestras ineptitudes. Dado que ahora estás en mi cocina, habrás visto los indicios de mis estudios. La piel es lo que otros ven de nosotros, lo que presentamos al mundo. Pero, ¿somos nosotros realmente? Lo que hay debajo, en los tendones y los huesos, ahí es donde se oculta la persona. Solo había una forma de averiguarlo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">人間の弱さ - 人間の弱さについて話そう。自分自身を見てみろ。怒りっぽく、のろまで、その上すぐに傷つく。なんて弱々しい！増強や協力に頼って成功を得ようとする。哀れな者たちはより良い設計に注目している。あの新事実によって、私もまた人間の弱さに取りつかれている。私の台所では、この通り、私の研究の証拠が明らかだ。人間の皮膚は、他人の目に入るものだ。つまり社会に現される自分自身なのだ。しかしこれが我々の本当の姿なのだろうか？人間の皮膚の下に在るもの。それは、筋肉と骨。これこそが、人間の真の姿が隠された場所なのだ。それを知るためにはたった一つの方法しかない。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">인간의 약점: 인간의 약점에 대해 이야기를 해야할 것 같군요. 자신을 보십시오. 얇은 피부, 부족한 털, 느린 발, 그리고 쉽게 다칩니다. 정말 하찮은 존재죠! 성공을 위해선 도구와 협력에 의존해야 하는 존재. 그 비참한 존재가 결국 옳았어요. 그는 고차원의 생명체를 꿈꾸고 있었던 거라고요! 그 일이 있은 후 저도 우리 인간의 약점에 집착하게 됐습니다. 제 주방에 있으니까 이미 제 연구의 증거도 목격했겠죠. 피부는 다른 이들이 우리를 평가하고 세상에 우리를 내놓는 도구입니다. 하지만 그것이 정말 우리를 대변할까요? 뼈와 근육 속, 그 안에 진정한 인간이 숨어있는 것이 틀림없습니다. 그것을 확인하는 방법은 단 한가지 뿐이죠.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Inadequacies of Man: I must speak to you of the inadequacies of man. Look at yourself - thin skinned, a gesture of fur, slow on your feet, easily hurt. How puny! Having to rely on augmentation and collaboration to succeed. That miserable creature was right after all and he -he!- was looking to better creation's design! Since that revelation I too have been obsessed by our inadequacies. Since you are currently in my kitchen you must have by now seen evidence of my studies. The skin is what others see of us, our self presented to the world. But is it us? What lays beneath, in the sinew and bone, surely this is where the true person hides. There was but one way to find out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">人的不足之處：我必須跟你談談人的不足之處。看看你自己吧 — 皮膚纖薄、姿態嬌弱、步伐緩慢、易受傷害。多麼的孱弱！要依賴增強和協作才能獲得成功。那個可憐人終究還是正確的，而且他! 一直在尋求更好的造物設計！在發現這一點後，我也深受我們不足之處的困擾。既然你現在在我的廚房裡，你肯定已經見識過我的研究證據了。皮囊是其他人看到的我們，是我們自己向世界展示的表像。但它是我們嗎？皮囊之下、深入筋骨的才是真人的隱藏之地。只有一個辦法可以將其找出。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">人的不足之處：我必須跟你談談人的不足之處。看看你自己吧 — 皮膚纖薄、姿態嬌弱、步伐緩慢、易受傷害。多麼的孱弱！要依賴增強和協作才能獲得成功。那個可憐人終究還是正確的，而且他! 一直在尋求更好的造物設計！在發現這一點後，我也深受我們不足之處的困擾。既然你現在在我的廚房裡，你肯定已經見識過我的研究證據了。皮囊是其他人看到的我們，是我們自己向世界展示的表像。但它是我們嗎？皮囊之下、深入筋骨的才是真人的隱藏之地。只有一個辦法可以將其找出。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Inadequacies of Man: I must speak to you of the inadequacies of man. Look at yourself - thin skinned, a gesture of fur, slow on your feet, easily hurt. How puny! Having to rely on augmentation and collaboration to succeed. That miserable creature was right after all and he -he!- was looking to better creation's design! Since that revelation I too have been obsessed by our inadequacies. Since you are currently in my kitchen you must have by now seen evidence of my studies. The skin is what others see of us, our self presented to the world. But is it us? What lays beneath, in the sinew and bone, surely this is where the true person hides. There was but one way to find out.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment08</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sick: Oh no, the sickness it eats at me tie me down, remove my hands before I do it again, before it is too late, nail me down and remove the skin of me show me for what I am, sick, venal, rip it off, reveal the sickness to all. those people those poor people, I took from this place into the darkness they deserved none of it, spare nothing, break every last piece of me limb from limb and burn me until not even a stain remains. I must be erased I am sick, I AM SICK I am sorry I am sorry I am sorry.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Malade : Dieu tout puissant, la maladie me dévore attachez-moi, coupez-moi les mains avant que je ne le refasse, avant qu'il ne soit trop tard, arrêtez-moi et dépecez-moi, montrez ce que je suis, malade, vénal, arrachez-la, révélez la maladie à tous ces gens, ces pauvres gens, je les ai pris de cet endroit pour les mener dans l'obscurité, ils ne méritaient rien de tout cela, n'épargnez rien, brisez-moi jusqu'au dernier morceau d'un membre à l'autre et brûlez-moi jusqu'à ce que toute impureté ait disparu. Je dois être supprimé je suis malade, JE SUIS MALADE, je suis désolé, désolé, désolé.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Krank: Oh, Gott im Himmel, die Krankheit nagt an mir, bindet mich fest, nehmt mir die Hände, bevor ich es wieder tue, bevor es zu spät ist, nagelt mich fest und häutet mich, zeigt mir, was ich wirklich bin, krank, verdorben, reißt sie herunter, lasst alle meine Krankheit sehen. Diese Leute, diese armen Leute, die ich von hier in die Finsternis gebracht habe, die hatten das alles nicht verdient, schont nichts, brecht mir noch den letzten Knochen und verbrennt mich, bis nicht mal ein Fleck von mir übrig ist. Ich muss ausgelöscht werden, ich bin krank, ICH BIN KRANK, es tut mir leid, es tut mir leid, es tut mir leid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Malattia: oh, dèi celesti, la malattia mi mangia, mi disturba, toglietemi le mani, prima che lo faccia di nuovo, prima che sia troppo tardi, inchiodatemi a terra, toglietemi la pelle e mostratemi per quel che sono: folle, venale, togliete tutto, mostrate a tutti la malattia. Quella gente, quella povera gente, li ho presi e li ho portati in un'oscurità in cui non meritavano di finire. Non risparmiatemi, fatemi a pezzi e bruciatemi finché non sarà rimasta neanche una macchia. Mi dovete eliminare, sono malato, SONO MALATO! Mi dispiace, mi dispiace, mi dispiace, mi dispiace.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Enfermo: Oh, Dios del cielo, la enfermedad me corroe. Átame, arráncame las manos antes de que lo vuelva a hacer, de que sea demasiado tarde. Clávame y quítame la piel, muéstrame como soy: enfermo, corrupto. Arráncala y revela la enfermedad a todos. Aquellas pobres personas que arrastré desde este lugar a la oscuridad no lo merecían. No dejes nada, destrózame, miembro a miembro, y quémame hasta que no quede el mínimo rastro. Tienes que eliminarme. Estoy enfermo, ESTOY ENFERMO, lo siento, lo siento, lo siento.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">病魔 - 神よ、どうか病魔に食い尽くされた私の心が再び罪を犯す前に、私をねじ伏せ、この手を切り取ってください。そして私の皮膚を剥ぎ取り、病魔が蝕む腐敗した姿を人々に見せてやってください。この場所に連れてこられ、暗闇の中に葬られたかわいそうな人々よ。私が犯した重い罪は彼らに値しない。どうか私のこの体の最後の血の一滴も残らないよう完全に燃やし尽くしてください。病魔に侵された私を消してください。神様、私をお許しください！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">질병: 오, 신이시여. 질병은 절 초조하게 만듭니다. 너무 늦기 전에 제 두 손을 묶어 못을 박고, 제 피부를 벗겨내어 아프고, 부패한 제 모습을 보여주십시오. 이곳으로 이끌려 어둠의 깊은 늪으로 묻혀버린 불쌍한 이들이여. 제가 범한 무거운 죄는 씻을 수 없습니다. 제발 제 몸의 피 한발울도 남기지 말고 완전히 불태워주십시오. 병마에 침식된 저를 없애주십시오. 신이시여, 죄송합니다. 절 용서하여 주옵소서.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sick: Oh no, the sickness it eats at me tie me down, remove my hands before I do it again, before it is too late, nail me down and remove the skin of me show me for what I am, sick, venal, rip it off, reveal the sickness to all. those people those poor people, I took from this place into the darkness they deserved none of it, spare nothing, break every last piece of me limb from limb and burn me until not even a stain remains. I must be erased I am sick, I AM SICK I am sorry I am sorry I am sorry.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">生病：哦，上帝啊。疾病吞噬著我，束縛著我。在我再這樣做之前，在為時已晚之前，除去我的雙手，用釘子把我釘住，然後扒下我的皮展示真正的我，是多麼的病態腐化，撕掉我的皮囊，向所有人展示我的病癥。那些人，那些可憐的人，那些被我從這裡拖入黑暗的人，他們不配做這些。盡全力將我一塊塊肢解並燒至不留任何痕跡。我必須被殺掉，我生病了，我生病了，我很抱歉，我很抱歉，我很抱歉。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">生病：哦，上帝啊。疾病吞噬著我，束縛著我。在我再這樣做之前，在為時已晚之前，除去我的雙手，用釘子把我釘住，然後扒下我的皮展示真正的我，是多麼的病態腐化，撕掉我的皮囊，向所有人展示我的病癥。那些人，那些可憐的人，那些被我從這裡拖入黑暗的人，他們不配做這些。盡全力將我一塊塊肢解並燒至不留任何痕跡。我必須被殺掉，我生病了，我生病了，我很抱歉，我很抱歉，我很抱歉。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sick: Oh no, the sickness it eats at me tie me down, remove my hands before I do it again, before it is too late, nail me down and remove the skin of me show me for what I am, sick, venal, rip it off, reveal the sickness to all. those people those poor people, I took from this place into the darkness they deserved none of it, spare nothing, break every last piece of me limb from limb and burn me until not even a stain remains. I must be erased I am sick, I AM SICK I am sorry I am sorry I am sorry.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment09</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Morality: You may feel I have long abandoned all claims to decent moral thought but this is not the case. This was not mindless slaughter I was indulging in but a higher calling. As I have explained my younger hand was guided by a fascination with the unknown and unknowable. Later I was able to find a focus to my quest - the search for truth. Is this not every scientist's quest? To reveal the mysteries of nature and get the better of nature! They may not admit as such but it is true. How can such a grail not be worth some small sacrifice? It worries me sometimes and I get sick - is this not proof that I care? - but the spirit that exists in this place explains it to me, in ways you cannot yet begin to imagine, and brings me to my senses. By courage and application we can change the world you and I, banish sickness and weakness to the past.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La moralité : Vous pourriez penser que j'ai abandonné il y a bien longtemps toute prétention de pensées morales décentes, mais ce n'est pas vrai. Je ne m'adonnais pas à un massacre aveugle, j'avais une noble mission. Comme je l'ai expliqué, ma jeune main était guidée par la fascination de l'inconnu et de l'inconnaissable. Plus tard, j'ai pu trouver un objectif à ma quête : la recherche de la vérité. N'est-ce pas le but de toute quête scientifique ? Révéler tous les mystères de la nature et en obtenir le meilleur ! Ils ne l'admettraient peut-être pas, mais c'est vrai. Comment un tel Graal ne vaut-il pas quelques petits sacrifices ? Cela m'ennuie parfois et me rend malade — C'est bien la preuve que j'aie un cœur ? — mais l'esprit de cet endroit me ramène à la raison, par des moyens au-delà de l'imaginable. Avec courage et précision, nous pouvons changer ce monde, vous et moi, bannir la maladie et la faiblesse, les laisser dans le passé.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Moral: Vielleicht denkst du ja, dass ich schon längst alle Moral habe fahren lassen, doch dem ist nicht so. Das war kein hirnloses Gemetzel, dem ich da gefrönt habe, sondern das war meine Berufung. Wie ich bereits erklärt habe, führte mir in meiner Jugend die Faszination mit dem Unbekannten und Unbegreiflichen die Hand. Später fand ich dann ein Ziel, nach dem ich streben konnte - die Wahrheit. Und sucht danach nicht jeder Wissenschaftler? Die Rätsel der Natur zu lösen und über die Natur zu triumphieren! Sie mögen es nicht zugeben, doch es ist wahr. Wie kann ein solch heiliger Gral nicht so ein kleines Opfer wert sein? Das beunruhigt mich manchmal und ich werde krank - ist das nicht der Beweis, dass mich das nicht kalt lässt? - , doch der Geist an diesem Ort erklärt es mir dann, und zwar auf eine Art und Weise, die du dir noch gar nicht vorstellen kannst, und bringt mich wieder zur Vernunft. Durch Mut und Tatkraft können wir die Welt verändern, du und ich, und Krankheit und Schwäche in die Vergangenheit verbannen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Moralità: forse ritieni che io abbia ormai abbandonato qualunque pretesa di un pensiero moralmente decente, ma ti sbagli. Non è stata violenza cieca, aveva un nobile intento. Come ti ho spiegato, la mia giovane mano era guidata dal fascino verso lo sconosciuto e l'inconoscibile. Solo più tardi sono riuscito a trovare un obiettivo alla mia missione: la ricerca della verità. Non è questa la missione di qualunque scienziato? Rivelare i misteri della natura e ottenere il meglio da questa! C'è chi non lo vuole ammettere, ma è la verità. Come può un calice di tale valore non valere qualche piccolo sacrificio? A volte mi preoccupo e la malattia mi prende: non ti dimostra niente? Ma lo spirito di questo posto mi dà conforto, in modi che tu non puoi neanche immaginare, e mi riporta in rotta. Con coraggio e applicazione possiamo cambiare il mondo, tu ed io, rendere la malattia e la debolezza cose del passato.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Moralidad: es posible que pienses que hace tiempo perdí el derecho a reclamar una moral decente, pero no es el caso. No me estaba dando el gusto con una matanza sin sentido, sino que respondía a una llamada de un ser superior. Como ya he explicado, mi mano más joven se guiaba por una fascinación por lo desconocido y lo que no se puede conocer. Después conseguí centrar mi búsqueda, la búsqueda de la verdad. ¿No es lo que busca cualquier científico? ¡Desvelar los misterios de la naturaleza y obtener lo mejor de ella! Puede que no lo admitan, pero es cierto. ¿Un grial así no merece un pequeño sacrificio? A veces me preocupa y me pone enfermo, ¿no demuestra esto que me importa? Pero el espíritu que existe en este lugar me lo explica de formas que aún no puedes imaginar y me hace entrar en razón. Con el valor y la aplicación podemos cambiar el mundo los dos, relegar la enfermedad y la debilidad al pasado.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">道徳性 - あなたは、私が正当な道徳感をすべて放棄したとお考えでしょうが、それは間違いです。私のミッションは、くだらない猟奇殺人よりも価値のあるものでした。先ほどお話ししたように、私は子供の頃、知られざる世界や不可知の世界に魅せられていました。やがて大人になり、自分の課題が真理の探求であることが解りまた。真理の探究とはすべての科学者の目的ではないでしょうか？自然界の謎を暴きそのしくみを理解する！科学者はこれを否定するでしょう。このような真実を得るためにはわずかな犠牲も必要では？このような考えは、正に私が真摯に仕事に取り組む証拠なのではないでしょうか？この館に住む幽霊は、想像を絶する方法で私に心理を教えてくれました。勇気と正しい方法によって、私たちは世界を変えることができます。そして人間の病魔や弱さをなくすことが可能なのです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">도덕: 제가 오래 전부터 올바른 윤리를 모두 저버렸다고 느낄지 모르겠지만 그렇지 않습니다. 제가 자행한 이 행위는 어리석은 도살이 아니며 사실 신의 계시였습니다. 제가 설명했듯이 어린 시절 저는 미지와 불가사의에 매혹되어 인도되었습니다. 이후 저는 제 모험의 근원을 알아차렸습니다. 바로 진실 추구입니다. 이것이 모든 과학자들이 추구하는 것 아닙니까? 자연의 수수께끼를 밝혀내고 자연에 조금 더 가까이 다가가기 위해서 말이죠! 사람들은 인정하지 않을지 모르지만 그것이 진실입니다. 그런 중요한 일에 작은 희생이 뭐가 대수란 말입니까? 때론 저도 걱정이 되고 아프기도 합니다. 이것이 바로 제가 진심이라는 증거가 아니라면 무엇입니까? 하지만 이곳에 존재하는 영혼이 당신이 상상할 수도 없는 방법으로 제게 다가와 설명하고 제가 정신을 차릴 수 있게 도와줍니다. 용기와 전심을 다하면 우린 질병과 나약함을 과거로 몰아내고 세상을 바꿀 수 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Morality: You may feel I have long abandoned all claims to decent moral thought but this is not the case. This was not mindless slaughter I was indulging in but a higher calling. As I have explained my younger hand was guided by a fascination with the unknown and unknowable. Later I was able to find a focus to my quest - the search for truth. Is this not every scientist's quest? To reveal the mysteries of nature and get the better of nature! They may not admit as such but it is true. How can such a grail not be worth some small sacrifice? It worries me sometimes and I get sick - is this not proof that I care? - but the spirit that exists in this place explains it to me, in ways you cannot yet begin to imagine, and brings me to my senses. By courage and application we can change the world you and I, banish sickness and weakness to the past.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">道德：你可能會覺得我早就拋棄了對良好道德思想的所有要求了，但是情況並非如此。我所沉醉的並非盲目的屠殺，而是更崇高的使命。正如我已經說明的，對未知和不可知事物的癡迷指引著我的青年時期。後來，我就能夠找到自己的探索重點了 — 對真理的追求。這難道不是每位科學家的追求嗎？目標是揭示天性的奧秘並獲得更好的天性！他們可能並不承認這些，但是這是真的。這樣的聖杯當然值得一些小小的犧牲！這有時會讓我憂心繼而生病（這難道不是我關心在乎的證據嗎？），但這個地方存在的幽靈以一種你無法想像的方式為我釋疑，讓我覺醒過來。憑藉勇氣和實踐，我們可以改變你、我以及世界，並將疾病和虛弱驅逐至過去。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">道德：你可能會覺得我早就拋棄了對良好道德思想的所有要求了，但是情況並非如此。我所沉醉的並非盲目的屠殺，而是更崇高的使命。正如我已經說明的，對未知和不可知事物的癡迷指引著我的青年時期。後來，我就能夠找到自己的探索重點了 — 對真理的追求。這難道不是每位科學家的追求嗎？目標是揭示天性的奧秘並獲得更好的天性！他們可能並不承認這些，但是這是真的。這樣的聖杯當然值得一些小小的犧牲！這有時會讓我憂心繼而生病（這難道不是我關心在乎的證據嗎？），但這個地方存在的幽靈以一種你無法想像的方式為我釋疑，讓我覺醒過來。憑藉勇氣和實踐，我們可以改變你、我以及世界，並將疾病和虛弱驅逐至過去。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Morality: You may feel I have long abandoned all claims to decent moral thought but this is not the case. This was not mindless slaughter I was indulging in but a higher calling. As I have explained my younger hand was guided by a fascination with the unknown and unknowable. Later I was able to find a focus to my quest - the search for truth. Is this not every scientist's quest? To reveal the mysteries of nature and get the better of nature! They may not admit as such but it is true. How can such a grail not be worth some small sacrifice? It worries me sometimes and I get sick - is this not proof that I care? - but the spirit that exists in this place explains it to me, in ways you cannot yet begin to imagine, and brings me to my senses. By courage and application we can change the world you and I, banish sickness and weakness to the past.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment10</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Family: The only deaths in this sorry tale that can not be attributed to my quest are those of my family. Mother, father and my little sister went out for a drive one day and never came home. The car went out of control and nose dived off the bay bridge into the roiling river below. The accident could be attributed to many things, inattentiveness, tiredness, the tires were found to be bald, I could go on. But I knew it was no accident. I knew. There are more that the five senses, once you are attuned to the preternatural one can see things and I tell you I knew. They were claimed. As a message to me. Later I would know exactly what that message meant but for now being young still and arrogant I took it as an affront, a challenge even. For my family I grieved but deep down I seethed and swore vengeance on things that could never be avenged.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La famille : Le décès des membres de ma famille n'a pour une fois rien à voir avec ma quête. Mes parents et ma petite sœur sont, un jour, partis se balader en voiture et ne sont jamais revenus. Ils ont perdu le contrôle de la voiture et plongé du pont dans les eaux déchaînées. Il y avait plusieurs causes possibles à cet accident, l'inattention, la fatigue, les pneus étaient lisses, et la liste continue. Mais je savais que ce n'était pas un accident. Je le savais. Il y a plus de cinq sens, une fois habitué au surnaturel, on voit des choses et je vous assure que je savais. Ils ont été pris. Un message qui m'était adressé. Plus tard, je saurai exactement ce qu'il signifiait, mais à cette époque, étant jeune et arrogant, ce n'était qu'un affront, un défi même. Je pleurais ma famille, mais intérieurement, je bouillais et jurais vengeance pour ce qui ne pouvait être vengé.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Familie: Die einzigen Todesfälle in dieser traurigen Geschichte, die nicht auf meine Suche zurückzuführen sind, sind die meiner Familie. Mutter, Vater und meine kleine Schwester machten eines Tages eine Spritztour und kamen nie wieder zurück. Der Wagen geriet außer Kontrolle und stürzte frontal von der Brücke über die Bucht hinab in den reißenden Fluss. Der Unfall ließe sich auf vieles zurückführen, Unachtsamkeit, Müdigkeit, abgefahrene Reifen, und so weiter. Doch ich wusste, dass es kein Unfall war. Ich wusste es einfach. Es gibt mehr als nur fünf Sinne, und sobald man sich auf das Übernatürliche eingestellt hat, kann man Dinge sehen, und ich sage dir, dass ich es wusste. Sie waren geholt worden. Um mir etwas mitzuteilen. Später sollte ich dann erfahren, was genau mir mitgeteilt werden sollte, doch damals, als ich noch jung und arrogant war, kam es mir einem Affront gleich, einer Herausforderung gar. Ich trauerte um meine Familie, doch tief in meinem Inneren kochte ich vor Wut und schwor Rache für Dinge, die niemals gerächt werden konnten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Famiglia: le sole morti di questa triste storia che non hanno nulla a che vedere con la mia missione sono quelle dei miei famigliari. Un giorno mia madre, mio padre e la mia sorellina uscirono in macchina e non fecero più ritorno. La macchina perse il controllo sul ponte della baia e precipitò dentro il fiume. L'incidente può essere attribuito a molti fattori: disattenzione, stanchezza, le gomme lisce, potrei continuare. Ma io sapevo che non era un incidente. Lo sapevo. Ci sono più di cinque sensi e, quando uno comincia ad abituarsi a quello preternaturale, inizia a vedere le cose; e ti dico che io lo sapevo. Era un messaggio per me. Più tardi avrei capito il significato di quel messaggio, ma al momento, essendo ancora giovane e arrogante, lo presi come un affronto, quasi una sfida. La sorte della mia famiglia mi rattristò molto: dentro di me giurai vendetta per un qualcosa che non poteva trovare vendetta.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Familia: las únicas muertes de esta triste historia que no se me pueden atribuir son las de mi familia. Mis padres y mi hermana salieron a dar una vuelta y no regresaron. Perdieron el control del vehículo y cayeron por el puente del muelle al enturbiado río. El accidente pudo atribuirse a muchos factores: la falta de atención, el cansancio, las ruedas desgastadas... Pero yo sabía que no era un accidente. Lo sabía. Existen más de cinco sentidos y cuando estás en armonía con lo sobrenatural, puedes ver cosas. Y yo lo sabía. Se cobraron sus vidas para mandarme un mensaje. Después descubriría el significado de dicho mensaje, pero entonces era joven, arrogante y lo tomé como una afrenta, como un desafío incluso. Me entristeció la muerte de mi familia, pero en el fondo estaba furioso y juré venganza a cosas con las que uno no puede vengarse.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">家族 - 私の家族の死は、唯一私の探求とは無関係のお話です。ある日ドライブに出かけた私の母、父、妹は、それ以来帰らぬ人となりました。三人を乗せた車両は、制御不能となり、ベイ・ブリッジを超えて濁流の中に消えていきました。この事故の原因として、不注意、疲労、タイヤの劣化など様々なことが考えられます。しかし、私はこの事故がただの事故ではないと知っていました。超自然現象を理解したり、五感以上の感覚を持つ私にとって、これが交通事故でないことは明らかでした。私の家族の命は奪われたのです。私はメッセージを受けました。私は後にそのメッセージの真の意味を理解するのでしょう。しかし、若く高慢な現在の私にとって、この家族の死は、侮辱や挑戦と考えています。私は家族の死を心から悔やむ一方、晴らされることできない恨みに対する復讐を誓いました。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">가족: 저의 가족의 죽음은 유일하게 제 탐구에 의한 결과물이 아닙니다. 어머니, 아버지, 그리고 여동생은 어느날 차를 타고 나가서 돌아오지 않았습니다. 세 명을 태운 그 차는 방향을 잃고 항만 다리에서 떨어져 그 아래 흐르는 강물 속으로 사라져 버렸습니다. 그 사고는 부주의, 피곤함, 닳아버린 타이어 등 다양한 원인 때문에 일어났을 수 있습니다. 하지만 전 그것이 사고가 아니란 것을 알고 있었습니다. 확실히 알고 있었죠. 한 번 초자연적인 것에 적응을 하면 오감 이외의 것들을 감지할 수 있게 됩니다. 저는 분명 알고 있었습니다. 그들은 부름을 받은 것입니다. 그건 저에게 보내는 메시지였습니다. 이후 저는 그 메시지가 정확히 어떤 것을 의미하는지 깨달았지만, 아직 젊고 오만했던 저는 그것을 모욕과 도전으로 받아들였습니다. 전 제 가족의 죽음을 마음 속 깊이 분노했고, 그 사라지지 않는 원한의 복수를 맹세하였습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Family: The only deaths in this sorry tale that can not be attributed to my quest are those of my family. Mother, father and my little sister went out for a drive one day and never came home. The car went out of control and nose dived off the bay bridge into the roiling river below. The accident could be attributed to many things, inattentiveness, tiredness, the tires were found to be bald, I could go on. But I knew it was no accident. I knew. There are more that the five senses, once you are attuned to the preternatural one can see things and I tell you I knew. They were claimed. As a message to me. Later I would know exactly what that message meant but for now being young still and arrogant I took it as an affront, a challenge even. For my family I grieved but deep down I seethed and swore vengeance on things that could never be avenged.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">家人：在這個遺憾的故事中，只有我家人的逝世不能歸咎于我的追求。我的母親、父親還有小妹某天開車外出兜風，就再也沒有回過家。汽車失去了控制，車頭朝下扎進了海灣大橋下面滾滾的河流。這起事故的原因可能有很多，注意力不集中、疲勞、車胎被發現為光頭胎，我還可以繼續羅列下去。但是我知道這絕非意外。我就是知道。感官不止五種，一旦你適應超自然，你就可以產生幻覺，所以我可以告訴你我知道那不是意外。作為給我的神示，他們被召喚了。後來我才知道那條神示是什麽意思，但是現在，仍然年輕且傲慢的我將其視為一種侮辱甚至挑戰。我為家人感到悲痛，但在內心深處我極度憤怒，並發誓在絕對無法報復的事情上進行復仇。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">家人：在這個遺憾的故事中，只有我家人的逝世不能歸咎于我的追求。我的母親、父親還有小妹某天開車外出兜風，就再也沒有回過家。汽車失去了控制，車頭朝下扎進了海灣大橋下面滾滾的河流。這起事故的原因可能有很多，注意力不集中、疲勞、車胎被發現為光頭胎，我還可以繼續羅列下去。但是我知道這絕非意外。我就是知道。感官不止五種，一旦你適應超自然，你就可以產生幻覺，所以我可以告訴你我知道那不是意外。作為給我的神示，他們被召喚了。後來我才知道那條神示是什麽意思，但是現在，仍然年輕且傲慢的我將其視為一種侮辱甚至挑戰。我為家人感到悲痛，但在內心深處我極度憤怒，並發誓在絕對無法報復的事情上進行復仇。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Family: The only deaths in this sorry tale that can not be attributed to my quest are those of my family. Mother, father and my little sister went out for a drive one day and never came home. The car went out of control and nose dived off the bay bridge into the roiling river below. The accident could be attributed to many things, inattentiveness, tiredness, the tires were found to be bald, I could go on. But I knew it was no accident. I knew. There are more that the five senses, once you are attuned to the preternatural one can see things and I tell you I knew. They were claimed. As a message to me. Later I would know exactly what that message meant but for now being young still and arrogant I took it as an affront, a challenge even. For my family I grieved but deep down I seethed and swore vengeance on things that could never be avenged.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Inheritance: Such a perverse thing inheritance. A loved one's loss is our gain. It is a challenge suffused with sadness, greed, guilt and we rarely come thru it with decorum fully intact. Can you not see it is the devil's invention? So the manor became mine via the most fitting fashion - death. I received a large insurance payout and there was never any doubt what I would do with it. The manor that had been mine in spirit now became mine wholly. If you have had the fortune to meet the one, your life partner, you may know the feeling I had as I walked up that path, like two incomplete parts of the whole finding one another. I felt it bare its teeth into a smile and breathe it's warm rotten smell over me, then it took me in its warm embrace. A good day for lovers, a bad one for everyone else.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'héritage : L'héritage est une chose tellement perverse. Le gain de la perte d'un être cher. La tristesse, l'avidité, la culpabilité imprègnent cette épreuve et il est bien rare de sortir indemne de ce décorum. Ne voyez-vous donc pas que c'est l'intention du diable ? Le manoir vint donc en ma possession par la plus appropriée des manières, la mort. Je reçus un versement important des assurances et il y avait nul doute quant à ce que je ferai de cet argent. Le manoir qui m'appartenait spirituellement devint alors ma propriété complète. Si vous avez eu la chance de rencontrer votre moitié, votre partenaire à vie, vous connaissez peut-être le sentiment que j'éprouvais alors que je marchais sur ce chemin, telles deux parts incomplètes d'un tout qui se retrouvait. Je l'ai senti sourire de toutes ses dents et me souffler son odeur tiède putride, puis j'ai senti sa douce étreinte. Une journée magnifique pour les amoureux, horrible pour les autres.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erbschaft: Erbschaften sind einfach nur pervers. Der Verlust eines geliebten Menschen ist unser Gewinn. Es ist eine Herausforderung durchsetzt mit Trauer, Gier und Schuld und nur selten können wir sie unbeschadet meistern. Siehst du denn nicht, dass sie der Wille des Teufels ist? So wurde der Landsitz mein, und zwar auf dem passendsten Wege - Tod. Ich bekam eine große Summe von der Versicherung, und es bestand nie ein Zweifel daran, was ich damit tun würde. Der Landsitz, der mir im Geiste schon immer gehört hatte, wurde nun wirklich vollständig mein. Wenn du das Glück hattest, den oder die eine zu treffen, deinen Partner fürs Leben, dann kennst du vielleicht das Gefühl, das ich hatte, als ich jenen Weg beschritt, als würden sich zwei unvollständige Teile eines Ganzen endlich finden. Ich spürte, wie es seine Zähne zu einem Lächeln entblößte, und roch seinen warmen, fauligen Atem. Dann überließ ich mich seiner innigen Umarmung. Ein guter Tag für Verliebte, ein schlechter für alle anderen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Eredità: che cosa perversa l'eredità. La perdita di un tuo caro diventa un guadagno per te. È una sfida piena di tristezza, avarizia e colpa; e raramente la superiamo con il decoro completamente intatto. Non vedi che è un'invenzione del diavolo? Dunque, il maniero divenne mio nel modo più adeguato: attraverso la morte. Ricevetti molti soldi dall'assicurazione e non ebbi mai alcun dubbio su come usarli. Il maniero che nello spirito era già mio, lo divenne anche materialmente. Se hai avuto la fortuna di incontrare la tua anima gemella, forse capirai i miei sentimenti quando m'incamminai per quel sentiero, come due parti del tutto che si ritrovano. Mi sembrò che serrasse i denti in un sorriso, che esalasse il suo caldo odore di muffa sopra di me, quindi mi afferrò nel suo caldo abbraccio. Un bel giorno per gli amanti, ma pessimo per tutti gli altri.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Herencia: la herencia es algo perverso. Nos beneficiamos de la pérdida de los seres queridos. Es un desafío lleno de tristeza, codicia, culpa y casi nunca salimos de él con decoro. ¿No ves que es el invento del diablo? Pasé a ser el propietario de la mansión de la forma más adecuada: la muerte. Recibí un gran pago del seguro y nunca dudé lo que iba a hacer con él. La mansión que había sido mía en espíritu lo era de pleno derecho. Si has tenido la suerte de conocer a esa persona, al compañero de tu vida, puede que conozcas la sensación que tuve cuando subí por el camino, como cuando dos partes incompletas se encuentran. Sentí que sonreía y exhalaba su olor cálido y putrefacto y que me abrazaba. Un buen día para los amantes, un mal día para el resto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">相続 - 邪道な悪徳は受け継がれます。愛される人々の死は私たちの利益となるのです。これは悲しみや強欲、また罪の意識によって生まれた挑戦なのです。これは悪魔の創造だと分かりますか？私は、死という最も適した方法を使って、この館を手に入れました。私は莫大な遺産を受け取り、それを全く正当に利用しているのです。幼いころから私の心で生き続けたこの館は、本当に完全に私の物となったのです。この館を最初に訪れた時から、私は人生の伴侶に出会った時のような気持ちにとらわれました。それは、不完全な私の心を埋め合わせてくれるような気持ちでした。この館は、私に笑顔を与え、その腐敗した臭いで私を優しく包んでくれました。これが私の最高のパートナーとの出会いでもあり、他人の悪夢の始まりでもあったのです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">상속: 상속이란 것은 아주 삐뚤어진 것이죠. 사랑하는 이의 죽음이 나의 이익이 되니까요. 슬픔, 탐욕, 죄책감으로 가득찬 문제이며 그것을 점잖게 처리하는 경우는 아주 드뭅니다. 그것이 악마의 발명품이란 걸 모르시겠습니까? 어쨌든 저택은 가장 적합한 방식인 죽음을 통해서 저의 소유가 됐습니다. 저는 많은 유산을 상속받았고, 제가 받은 유산을 가지고 무엇을 할 것인지는 확고했습니다. 마음 속으로만 제 소유였던 저택은 이제 온전히 제 소유가 됐습니다. 삶의 동반자를 만나는 행운을 경험했다면, 불완전한 두 존재가 만나 하나의 완전한 존재로 거듭나는 듯한 저의 느낌을 이해할 수 있을 것입니다. 그 존재가 이빨을 드러내며 미소를 짓고, 부패하고 썪은 입냄새를 내게 내뿜는 것을 느꼈으며, 그 존재는 날 따뜻하게 받아들였습니다. 연인들에게는 좋은 날이지만, 다른 모든 이들에게는 불행한 날이죠.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Inheritance: Such a perverse thing inheritance. A loved one's loss is our gain. It is a challenge suffused with sadness, greed, guilt and we rarely come thru it with decorum fully intact. Can you not see it is the devil's invention? So the manor became mine via the most fitting fashion - death. I received a large insurance payout and there was never any doubt what I would do with it. The manor that had been mine in spirit now became mine wholly. If you have had the fortune to meet the one, your life partner, you may know the feeling I had as I walked up that path, like two incomplete parts of the whole finding one another. I felt it bare its teeth into a smile and breathe it's warm rotten smell over me, then it took me in its warm embrace. A good day for lovers, a bad one for everyone else.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">遺產：遺產真是違反常理的東西。心愛之人的離去卻令我們受益。它是個充滿悲傷、貪婪和內疚的難題，而我們很少能以完整無缺的體面禮儀將其兌現。你難道看不出它是魔鬼的發明嗎？所以，這座莊園是透過最恰當的方式 — 死亡而為我所有的。我獲得了高額的保險理賠，而我會用這筆錢來做什麽絕對是毋庸置疑的。這座莊園曾在精神上為我所有，現如今則完全屬於我了。如果你曾有幸遇見你的人生伴侶，你或許能瞭解當我走上那條路時的感受，就好像屬於一個整體的兩個不完整的部份終於找到了彼此。我感到它露齒微笑起來，呼吸著它籠罩在我身上溫暖的腐爛氣味，然後它給了我一個溫暖的擁抱。這是情人的美好時光，也是其他人的倒楣日。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">遺產：遺產真是違反常理的東西。心愛之人的離去卻令我們受益。它是個充滿悲傷、貪婪和內疚的難題，而我們很少能以完整無缺的體面禮儀將其兌現。你難道看不出它是魔鬼的發明嗎？所以，這座莊園是透過最恰當的方式 — 死亡而為我所有的。我獲得了高額的保險理賠，而我會用這筆錢來做什麽絕對是毋庸置疑的。這座莊園曾在精神上為我所有，現如今則完全屬於我了。如果你曾有幸遇見你的人生伴侶，你或許能瞭解當我走上那條路時的感受，就好像屬於一個整體的兩個不完整的部份終於找到了彼此。我感到它露齒微笑起來，呼吸著它籠罩在我身上溫暖的腐爛氣味，然後它給了我一個溫暖的擁抱。這是情人的美好時光，也是其他人的倒楣日。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Inheritance: Such a perverse thing inheritance. A loved one's loss is our gain. It is a challenge suffused with sadness, greed, guilt and we rarely come thru it with decorum fully intact. Can you not see it is the devil's invention? So the manor became mine via the most fitting fashion - death. I received a large insurance payout and there was never any doubt what I would do with it. The manor that had been mine in spirit now became mine wholly. If you have had the fortune to meet the one, your life partner, you may know the feeling I had as I walked up that path, like two incomplete parts of the whole finding one another. I felt it bare its teeth into a smile and breathe it's warm rotten smell over me, then it took me in its warm embrace. A good day for lovers, a bad one for everyone else.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment12</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sacks: Freed of the drudgery of making a living I was now able to begin my search in earnest. What was I looking for? The real truths. The real answers. To find these you have to be bleakly honest with the questions. So friend, what are you? Are you that outer skin, daubed with ink and the fat of dead animals... or are you sum of what is inside, a thousand sordid little thoughts, those secret longings and those dead, dark thoughts so evil you can never make whole? Don't worry, I already know. Your skin is a facade, a sack for YOU to walk around in. Now I would concern myself with ridding us all of these sacks, to see what lay beneath.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les sacs : Libéré de la corvée de travailler, je pus alors commencer mes recherches sérieusement. Qu'est ce que je recherchais ? Les vérités pures. Les vraies réponses. Afin de les trouver, vous devez être complètement honnête avec les questions. Et vous, quel genre de personne êtes-vous ? Êtes-vous cette peau extérieure, couverte d'encre et de la graisse d'animaux morts... ou, êtes-vous le résultat de ce qu'il y a à l'intérieur, un millier de petites pensées sordides, ces envies secrètes et ces pensées sombres et mortes tellement diaboliques que vous ne faites jamais qu'un ? Ne vous inquiétez pas, je le sais déjà. Votre peau est une façade, un sac dans lequel VOUS vous promenez. Je m'occuperais de débarrasser le monde de ces sacs pour voir ce qu'il y a en dessous.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Säcke: Befreit von der Qual, mir meinen Lebensunterhalt verdienen zu müssen, konnte ich mich nun endlich richtig auf die Suche machen. Wonach ich suchte? Die echte Wahrheit. Die echten Antworten. Um sie zu finden, muss man entwaffnend ehrlich mit seinen Fragen sein. Also, werter Freund, was bist du? Bist du diese äußere Hülle, beschmiert mit Tinte und dem Fett toter Tiere ... oder bist du die Summe dessen, was in dir steckt, tausend schmutzige kleine Gedanken, diese geheimen Wünsche und diese toten, finsteren Gedanken, die so böse sind, dass du niemals deinen Frieden findest? Keine Sorge, ich weiß schon. Deine Haut ist eine Fassade, ein Sack, in dem DU herumläufst. Nun, ich würde mich damit befassen, uns alle von diesen Säcken zu befreien, um zu sehen, was darunter liegt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sacchi: senza l'incombenza di dover sbarcare il lunario, ora potevo cominciare davvero la mia ricerca. Che cosa cercavo? La pura verità. Le risposte reali. Per trovarle, bisogna essere assolutamente onesti con le domande: tu, cosa sei? Sei la pelle esterna, imbrattata con l'inchiostro e il grasso di animali morti... O sei la somma di quel che c'è dentro, mille piccoli pensieri sordidi, smanie segrete, idee così oscure e diaboliche da non poter essere sistemate? Non preoccuparti, lo so già. La tua pelle è una facciata, un sacco dentro cui TU vuoi camminare. In quel momento il mio solo pensiero era sbarazzarmi di quei sacchi e vedere cosa si nascondeva sotto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sacos: liberado de la carga de buscarme la vida, pude iniciar mi búsqueda concienzudamente. ¿Qué buscaba? Las verdades. Las respuestas reales. Para encontrarlas, es necesario ser desoladamente honesto con las preguntas. Así que, amigo, ¿qué eres? ¿Eres la piel exterior, embadurnada de tinta y grasa de animales muertos... o eres la suma de lo que está en el interior, de miles de pensamientos sórdidos, deseos secretos y pensamientos oscuros, mortales, tan malignos que nunca estarás completo? No te preocupes, ya lo sé. Tu piel es una fachada, un saco con el que pasearte. Me interesaría quitarnos los sacos, ver lo que hay en el interior.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">袋 - 私は生計を立てるための骨折り仕事から解放され、本腰を入れて探求に没頭するようになりました。私が探求していたのは正しい真理、つまり本当の答えです。これらを見つけ出すためには質問に対し全く正直である必要があります。あなたに尋ねよう。自分の本当の姿をご存じかな。インクと死んだ動物の脂肪で塗られた、ただの外皮... それとも、無数の下劣な考えや邪悪な秘密が詰まった集合体かな？ご心配なく。私にはすでにあなたの姿がお見通しです。あなたの皮膚は真の自分の姿を覆うただの袋にすぎない。今から私は、これら全ての袋の中身を知るための難問を考慮します。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">짐: 생계 유지의 단조롭고 지루한 생활에서 벗어나서 저는 본격적으로 연구를 시작할 수 있게 되었습니다. 제가 찾는 것이 무엇이었냐고요? 진정한 진실이었습니다. 진정한 해답. 그것을 찾으려면 문제에 대해 솔직해져야 합니다. 친구여, 당신은 무엇입니까? 잉크와 죽은 동물의 비계로 어설프게 만들어진 가죽에 불과합니까… 아니면 그 안에 있는 수천가지의 작고 비열한 생각들과 비밀스러운 갈망, 그리고 차마 가늠할 수 없을 정도로 악하고 어둡고 죽음으로 가득찬 생각이 당신입니까? 걱정 마십시오. 전 이미 알고 있습니다. 이제 저는 이런 짐들을 모두 없애는 일에 집중하여 그 아래에 무엇이 있는지 확인할 것입니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sacks: Freed of the drudgery of making a living I was now able to begin my search in earnest. What was I looking for? The real truths. The real answers. To find these you have to be bleakly honest with the questions. So friend, what are you? Are you that outer skin, daubed with ink and the fat of dead animals... or are you sum of what is inside, a thousand sordid little thoughts, those secret longings and those dead, dark thoughts so evil you can never make whole? Don't worry, I already know. Your skin is a facade, a sack for YOU to walk around in. Now I would concern myself with ridding us all of these sacks, to see what lay beneath.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">麻袋：擺脫了謀生的苦差事，我現在可以誠摯地開始我的探索了。想知道我在尋找什麽嗎？是真正的真理、真正的答案。如要找到這些，你必須誠實地對待這些問題。那麼朋友，你是什麽？你是塗抹著墨水和已死動物脂肪的外在皮囊……還是內在那些無數卑鄙的小念頭、隱秘的渴望以及無法全然包羅的絕對陰暗邪惡的想法的總和？別擔心，我已經知道了。你的皮囊只是個門面，供您四處走動時穿著的麻袋。現在我會致力於讓我們擺脫這些麻袋，從而看到我們的內在。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">麻袋：擺脫了謀生的苦差事，我現在可以誠摯地開始我的探索了。想知道我在尋找什麽嗎？是真正的真理、真正的答案。如要找到這些，你必須誠實地對待這些問題。那麼朋友，你是什麽？你是塗抹著墨水和已死動物脂肪的外在皮囊……還是內在那些無數卑鄙的小念頭、隱秘的渴望以及無法全然包羅的絕對陰暗邪惡的想法的總和？別擔心，我已經知道了。你的皮囊只是個門面，供您四處走動時穿著的麻袋。現在我會致力於讓我們擺脫這些麻袋，從而看到我們的內在。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sacks: Freed of the drudgery of making a living I was now able to begin my search in earnest. What was I looking for? The real truths. The real answers. To find these you have to be bleakly honest with the questions. So friend, what are you? Are you that outer skin, daubed with ink and the fat of dead animals... or are you sum of what is inside, a thousand sordid little thoughts, those secret longings and those dead, dark thoughts so evil you can never make whole? Don't worry, I already know. Your skin is a facade, a sack for YOU to walk around in. Now I would concern myself with ridding us all of these sacks, to see what lay beneath.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Humbled: On the occasion of boredom during my studies, I turned my curiosity to the manor's history. My fanciful mind had the manor built on top of a cemetery or crossing ancient lay lines but this was banal compared to the truth. The owners, I soon discovered, were the Volants and they made their fortune mining silicate minerals - asbestos to the rest of us. The two million tons their mines produced became the very fabric of modern society, used in concrete, bricks, insulation, furniture, cigarette filters and my favourite - artificial snow. Did the Volants know the effects of asbestos? What do you think dear guest, what does your knowledge of human nature tell you? You are right, they knew and they suppressed the truth. Before they could be brought to justice the whole Volant family disappeared, never to be seen again. Even in their absence I feel humbled by them. A foundling in their maw, my pathetic story naught by comparison. This, this is true horror.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'humilité : Lorsque je m'ennuyais pendant mes études, je m'intéressais à l'histoire du manoir. Mon esprit fantaisiste imaginait le manoir construit sur un cimetière ou bien, à un croisement d'anciennes lignes de Ley, mais cela n'était rien comparé à la vérité. Je découvris bientôt que les propriétaires étaient les Volants, qui avaient construit leur fortune grâce à l'exploitation minière de silicates, ou amiante. Les deux millions de tonnes produites par leurs mines devinrent le tissu même de la société moderne, utilisées dans le béton, les briques, l'isolation, les meubles, les filtres de cigarettes, et mon préféré, la neige artificielle. Est-ce que les Volants connaissaient les effets de l'amiante ? Qu'en pensez-vous, cher hôte, que vous a enseigné la nature humaine ? Vous avez raison, ils le savaient et ils dissimulèrent la vérité. Avant qu'ils ne puissent paraître devant un juge, toute la famille Volant disparut, et on ne les revit jamais. Même en leur absence, ils me font me sentir humble. Un enfant abandonné dans leur gueule, mon histoire pathétique n'est rien en comparaison. Ceci est l'horreur véritable.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gedemütigt: Als mich meine Studien zu langweilen begannen, wandte ich mich der Geschichte des Landsitzes zu. In meiner blühenden Fantasie hatte ich mir ausgemalt, dass der Landsitz auf einem Friedhof oder einer uralten Wegkreuzung gebaut worden war, doch verglichen mit der Wahrheit war das einfach nur banal. Die Eigentümer, wie ich bald herausfand, waren die Volants, die ihr Vermögen mit dem Abbau von Silikat-Mineralien gemacht hatten - sonst auch Asbest genannt. Die zwei Millionen Tonnen, die man aus ihren Minen geholt hatte, wurden zum Grundstoff der modernen Gesellschaft, verwendet zur Herstellung von Beton, Ziegeln, Isolierung, Möbeln, Zigarettenfiltern und, mein Favorit, Kunstschnee. Wussten die Volants, welche Nebenwirkungen Asbest hat? Was meinst du, werter Gast, was sagt dir dein Wissen um die menschliche Natur? Du hast recht, sie wussten es und ließen die Wahrheit vertuschen. Bevor man sie zur Rechenschaft ziehen konnte, verschwand die gesamte Familie Volant und ließ sich nie wieder blicken. Selbst in ihrer Abwesenheit fühlte ich mich von ihnen gedemütigt. Ein Findelkind in ihrem Schlund, meine erbärmliche Geschichte ein Nichts gegen ihre. Das hier, das ist das wahre Grauen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ridimensionato: quando, durante i miei studi, mi annoiavo, rivolgevo la mia curiosità alla storia del maniero. La mia mente fantasiosa pensava che il maniero fosse stato costruito sopra un cimitero o sopra antiche linee temporanee, ma tutto ciò si rivelò banale se paragonato alla verità. Presto scoprii che i proprietari erano i Volant, i quali fecero fortuna con le miniere di minerali silicati - a tutti noti come amianto. I due milioni di tonnellate che le loro miniere produssero divennero una colonna portante della società moderna, usate per asfalto, mattoni, come isolante, per i mobili, per i filtri di sigaretta e per la neve artificiale. I Volant conoscevano gli effetti dell'amianto? Cosa ne pensi, gentile ospite, che cosa ti dice la tua conoscenza della natura umana? Proprio così, sapevano ma nascosero la verità. Prima di poter essere portata a giudizio, l'intera famiglia Volant scomparve nel nulla. Anche nella loro assenza, mi sento ridimensionato dinanzi a loro. Un cucciolo nelle loro fauci, la mia storia un nulla in paragone. Questo, questo è il vero orrore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Humilde: en un momento de aburrimiento durante mis estudios, mi curiosidad se centró en la historia de la mansión. En mi imaginación, la mansión se había construido sobre un cementerio o una antigua línea ley. Todo era trivial en comparación con la verdad. Los dueños, según descubrí pronto, eran los Volant y obtenían su fortuna de la minería de silicatos (amianto para el resto de los mortales). Los dos millones de toneladas que producían sus minas se convirtieron en la estructura de la sociedad moderna. Se utilizaban en hormigón, ladrillos, aislamientos, muebles, filtros de cigarrillos y, mi favorito, nieve artificial. ¿Conocían los Volant los efectos del amianto? ¿Qué opinas, querido huésped? ¿Qué te dice tu conocimiento de la naturaleza humana? Llevas razón, los conocían y ocultaron la verdad. Antes de que los llevaran ante la justicia, toda la familia desapareció y no se les volvió a ver. Incluso en su ausencia me siento humilde. Un expósito en sus fauces, mi patética historia convertida en nada en comparación. Esto, amigo mío, es el terror.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">謙虚 - 探求に退屈した時期、私は、この館の歴史に注目しました。この洋館が墓場や考古学的重要ポイントの上に建っているではと想像を膨らませましたが、そんな私の予想をはるかに上回る真実を発見しました。この館はボルタン家によって所有され、彼らはケイ酸塩鉱物の鉱業、現在のアスベストによって富を得ました。ボルタン氏が監督する二百万トンものアスベストの採鉱は現代社会の構造の要となり、コンクリート、煉瓦、絶縁材、家具、タバコのフィルター、さらに私の好きな人工雪として使用されました。それでは、ボルタン氏はアスベストが人体に及ぼす影響について周知していたでしょうか？人間の本性を理解していれば答えは簡単でしょう。彼らはアスベストの危険性を知っていましたが、その真実を隠していたのです。ボルタン家は裁判で裁かれる前に全員姿を消してしまいました。一家がいなくなったこの洋館で、私は謙虚な気持ちにさせられます。私の身の上話などは、彼らが経験した恐ろしいストーリーに比べるとつまらないものなのです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">겸허한 마음: 연구 중에 지루하게 느껴질 때 저는 저택의 과거에 호기심을 집중합니다. 제 별난 정신세계는 저택을 공동 묘지 꼭대기에 지어놓곤 하지만, 이런 것은 진실에 비하면 지극히 평범한 것입니다. 저는 얼마 지나지 않아서 소유주가 볼란트가 사람들이었다는 사실과 그들이 규산염 광물을 캐면서 엄청난 돈을 벌어들였다는 것을 밝혀냈습니다. 우리에겐 석면으로 알려져 있죠. 그들이 생산한 이백만 톤의 석면은 콘크리트, 벽돌, 절연재, 가구, 담배 필터, 그리고 제가 가장 좋아하는 인공 눈에 쓰이면서 현대 사회의 기초를 다졌습니다. 볼란트가 사람들은 석면의 영향을 알고 있었을까요? 어떻게 생각하시나요? 인간의 본성을 고려할 때 당신의 생각은 어떤가요? 맞습니다. 그들은 알고 있었고 진실을 숨겼습니다. 정의의 심판을 받기도 전에 볼란트가 사람들은 사라졌고 다시는 나타나지 않았습니다. 그들이 없는 중에도 저는 그들 때문에 겸허한 마음이 듭니다. 그와 비교하면 제 한심한 이야기는 보잘것 없습니다. 바로 이것이 진정한 공포입니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Humbled: On the occasion of boredom during my studies, I turned my curiosity to the manor's history. My fanciful mind had the manor built on top of a cemetery or crossing ancient lay lines but this was banal compared to the truth. The owners, I soon discovered, were the Volants and they made their fortune mining silicate minerals - asbestos to the rest of us. The two million tons their mines produced became the very fabric of modern society, used in concrete, bricks, insulation, furniture, cigarette filters and my favourite - artificial snow. Did the Volants know the effects of asbestos? What do you think dear guest, what does your knowledge of human nature tell you? You are right, they knew and they suppressed the truth. Before they could be brought to justice the whole Volant family disappeared, never to be seen again. Even in their absence I feel humbled by them. A foundling in their maw, my pathetic story naught by comparison. This, this is true horror.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">謙遜：在研究期間的無聊之際，我將好奇心轉向了莊園的歷史。我充滿幻想的頭腦認定莊園建在一處墓地之上或者穿越了古老的層線，但是與真相相比，這想法實在是平庸陳腐。我很快就發現，莊園的主人為飛行族人，而且他們透過挖掘硅酸鹽礦物 — 石棉創造財富給我們其餘的人。他們礦山生產的兩百萬噸石棉構成了現代社會建築的根基，可用於混凝土、磚、隔熱隔涼設備、傢具、香煙過濾器以及我的最愛 — 人造雪。飛行族人是否瞭解石棉的效用呢？尊敬的客人，你有什麽看法，以你對人類本性的瞭解能得出什麽？你是對的，他們知道並隱瞞了真相。而在飛行族可能被繩之以法前，他們就全體消失了，再也看不到了。即使在他們消失不見的情況下，我仍感到為其折服。即使是其懷中的棄子，仍可讓我的悲慘故事在比較之下毫無價值。這才是真正的恐怖。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">謙遜：在研究期間的無聊之際，我將好奇心轉向了莊園的歷史。我充滿幻想的頭腦認定莊園建在一處墓地之上或者穿越了古老的層線，但是與真相相比，這想法實在是平庸陳腐。我很快就發現，莊園的主人為飛行族人，而且他們透過挖掘硅酸鹽礦物 — 石棉創造財富給我們其餘的人。他們礦山生產的兩百萬噸石棉構成了現代社會建築的根基，可用於混凝土、磚、隔熱隔涼設備、傢具、香煙過濾器以及我的最愛 — 人造雪。飛行族人是否瞭解石棉的效用呢？尊敬的客人，你有什麽看法，以你對人類本性的瞭解能得出什麽？你是對的，他們知道並隱瞞了真相。而在飛行族可能被繩之以法前，他們就全體消失了，再也看不到了。即使在他們消失不見的情況下，我仍感到為其折服。即使是其懷中的棄子，仍可讓我的悲慘故事在比較之下毫無價值。這才是真正的恐怖。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Humbled: On the occasion of boredom during my studies, I turned my curiosity to the manor's history. My fanciful mind had the manor built on top of a cemetery or crossing ancient lay lines but this was banal compared to the truth. The owners, I soon discovered, were the Volants and they made their fortune mining silicate minerals - asbestos to the rest of us. The two million tons their mines produced became the very fabric of modern society, used in concrete, bricks, insulation, furniture, cigarette filters and my favourite - artificial snow. Did the Volants know the effects of asbestos? What do you think dear guest, what does your knowledge of human nature tell you? You are right, they knew and they suppressed the truth. Before they could be brought to justice the whole Volant family disappeared, never to be seen again. Even in their absence I feel humbled by them. A foundling in their maw, my pathetic story naught by comparison. This, this is true horror.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment14</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Protection: Why was I never found out? It is inevitable that those who engage in these crimes (the law calls it crime so I would do well to do the same) will one day meet their day of reckoning, so why not me? I have been careful of course, plain common sense. It in itself - the act of slaughter - is but 1% of the whole. The rest is foresight, planning, the creation of false trails and alibis, etc.  To not pay all this the respect it deserves will result in a fatal voltage being passed though ones body very swiftly. But that isn't all. A few unseen occurrences should have resulted in my capture. Each time luck swung my way but perhaps this was not luck at all... I seek answers in hope that one day a new being will rise from our debris. Others no doubt seek to undermine creation for different reasons, to end the rule of law and replace it with the rule of chaos. Who or what? Well there... I prefer not to speculate but I feel a great and infernal presence over-seeing my every step.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La protection : Pourquoi ne m'a-t-on jamais trouvé ? Ceux qui se livrent à ces crimes (la loi les qualifie de crimes, donc j'en ferai autant) voient inévitablement le jour du jugement, alors, pourquoi pas moi ? J'ai fait attention bien sûr, ça tombe sous le sens. Le massacre en soi, n'est en fait que 1 % du tout. Il faut aussi prévoir, organiser, créer de fausses pistes et alibis, etc. Si ces détails ne sont pas respectés à la lettre, le courant à haute tension passe rapidement à travers un corps. Mais ce n'est pas tout. Quelques faits passés inaperçus auraient dû entraîner ma capture. Chaque fois, la chance m'a souri, mais peut-être n'était-ce pas de la chance finalement... Je cherche des réponses dans l'espoir qu'un jour peut-être, un nouvel être naîtra des décombres de notre ruine. D'autres, sans nul doute, cherchent à nuire à la création pour différentes raisons, pour mettre fin à la règle de droit et la remplacer par la règle du chaos. Qui ou quoi ? Bien il y... Je préfère ne pas supposer, mais je ressens une puissante présence diabolique surveillant chacun de mes pas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schutz: Warum ist mir nie jemand auf die Schliche gekommen? Wer sich solcher Verbrechen schuldig macht (laut Gesetz sind es Verbrechen, also sollte ich sie auch so nennen), über den wir eines Tages gerichtet, also warum dann nicht auch über mich? Ich war vorsichtig, natürlich, einfach aus gesundem Menschenverstand. Für sich genommen ist der Akt des Abschlachtens nur 1% des Ganzen. Der Rest ist weise Voraussicht, Planung, das Anlegen falscher Spuren und Alibis usw. All dem nicht den nötigen Respekt angedeihen zu lassen, führt dazu, dass nur allzu bald eine tödliche elektrische Ladung durch den eigenen Körper gejagt wird. Doch das ist noch nicht alles. Einige unvorhergesehene Vorkommnisse hätten zu meiner Verhaftung führen sollen. Jedes Mal war das Glück auf meiner Seite, doch vielleicht war es ja gar kein Glück ... Ich suche Antworten in der Hoffnung, dass sich eines Tages aus unseren Ruinen ein neues Wesen erheben wird. Andere versuchen zweifellos, die Schöpfung aus anderen Gründen zu hintertreiben, um Recht und Ordnung ein Ende zu machen und an ihrer Stelle das Chaos zu etablieren. Wer oder was? Nun ... Ich ziehe es vor, mich nicht in Spekulationen zu ergehen, doch ich spüre, dass eine große, infernalische Präsenz über jeden meiner Schritte wacht.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Protezione: Perché non mi hanno mai scoperto? È inevitabile che chi commette tali crimini (la legge li chiama crimini ed io mi ci adeguo) un giorno ne pagherà le conseguenze. Ma perché non io? Naturalmente ho sempre fatto attenzione, ho usato il buonsenso. L'atto dell'uccidere in sé è solo l'1% del tutto. Il resto è previsione, pianificazione, la creazione di tracce fasulle, alibi, ecc. Non prestare abbastanza attenzione a tutto questo si paga con la sedia elettrica. Ma non è tutto. Alcuni episodi imprevisti avrebbero dovuto portare alla mia cattura. Ogni volta la fortuna è stata dalla mia parte, ma forse non era fortuna... Cerco delle risposte nella speranza che un giorno un nuovo essere sorgerà dalle nostre macerie. C'è chi vuole minare la creazione per altre ragioni, per mettere fine al regno della legge e rimpiazzarlo con il caos. Chi o cosa? Beh... Preferisco non pensarci, ma sento una potente presenza infernale che scruta ogni mio passo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Protección: ¿Por qué no me descubrieron? Es inevitable que los que cometen estos crímenes (la ley los llama crímenes y hago bien en hacer lo mismo) tenga un juicio final, ¿por qué yo no? Tuve mucho cuidado, utilicé el sentido común. El acto en sí (la matanza) solo es un 1% del total. El resto es previsión, planificación, creación de coartadas y rastros falsos, etc. Si no hubiese prestado a todo esto la atención que merecía, un voltaje mortal habría recorrido mi cuerpo rápidamente. Pero esto no es todo. Unos cuantos acontecimientos improvistos habrían resultado en mi captura. La suerte me acompañaba, pero quizá no era suerte... Busco respuestas con la esperanza de que, un día, un nuevo ser emergerá de nuestros restos. Sin duda, otros pretenden minar la creación por distintos motivos, acabar con la ley y sustituirla por el caos. ¿Quién o qué? Bueno... prefiero no especular, pero siento una presencia enorme e infernal que observa todos mis movimientos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">保護 - 私はなぜ捕まらないのでしょうか？このような犯罪（私の偉業は法律上犯罪とされます）を犯した者は法による裁きを免れません。私が捕まらない理由は簡単です。慎重さです。私の計画において、実際の殺人はその1パーセントに過ぎません。残りは洞察力、計画性、痕跡やアリバイの作成などです。これらの綿密性を怠ることは、致命的な電圧によって一気にに死ぬことを意味します。それだけではりません。私の取り組みで今まで見たことのない現象が発生したのです。どんな殺人の時も、私は運がよかったのです。けれども、これは運ではない何かでした... 私はこの答えを誰かが見つけることを願っています。ことなる目的によって、創造を脅かすことを疑わない者もいるでしょう。その者達は法の原則を、混沌の法則に置きかえるのです。しかしだれが、何のために？今その答えを予想したくはありませんが、私は私の行く手を守ってくれる悪魔の存在に感謝するのです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">보호: 왜 저는 발견되지 않았을까요? 이런 범죄를 저지른 이들은 언젠가는 심판을 받게 되어 있습니다. 하지만 왜 저는 그렇지 않을까요? 물론 제가 조심했기 때문이기도 합니다. 상식적인 이유죠. 그러나 살육의 행위는 전체의 1%에 불과합니다. 그 나머지는 통찰력을 가지고 계획을 세우고, 거짓 발자국과 알리바이를 만드는 등의 일입니다. 이 모든 일에 노력을 쏟지 않는다면 금새 전기의자에 앉게 될 것입니다. 하지만 그것이 전부는 아닙니다. 눈에 보이지 않는 몇몇 사건들로 인해서도 붙잡힐 수 있습니다. 매번 행운은 저의 편이었지만 아마도 그건 행운이 아니었는지도 모릅니다... 저는 언젠가 우리의 잔해 속에서 새로운 존재가 나타나리라는 기대를 가지고 해답을 찾고 있습니다. 다른 이들은 다른 목적을 가지고 생명을 훼손하고 있죠. 법 체제를 무너뜨리고 혼란의 규칙을 불러일으키겠다는 목적말입니다. 도대체 누가 또는 무엇이? 짐작하고 싶진 않지만 엄청난 지옥의 존재가 제 모든 일거수 일투족을 지켜보고 있다는 느낌이 듭니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Protection: Why was I never found out? It is inevitable that those who engage in these crimes (the law calls it crime so I would do well to do the same) will one day meet their day of reckoning, so why not me? I have been careful of course, plain common sense. It in itself - the act of slaughter - is but 1% of the whole. The rest is foresight, planning, the creation of false trails and alibis, etc.  To not pay all this the respect it deserves will result in a fatal voltage being passed though ones body very swiftly. But that isn't all. A few unseen occurrences should have resulted in my capture. Each time luck swung my way but perhaps this was not luck at all... I seek answers in hope that one day a new being will rise from our debris. Others no doubt seek to undermine creation for different reasons, to end the rule of law and replace it with the rule of chaos. Who or what? Well there... I prefer not to speculate but I feel a great and infernal presence over-seeing my every step.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">保護：爲什麽我從來沒有被發現呢？從事這些犯罪行為（法律將其稱之為犯罪，所以我最好也這樣做）的人都避免不了在某天迎來最後審判日，那麼爲什麽我不會這樣呢？我當然一直都很小心，這是普通的常識。它本身（屠殺行為）不過是整體行動的 1%。其餘則是預見、規劃及創建假消息和不在場證明等。不對所有這些給予應有的尊重將導致致命電壓極為迅速地透過人體。但這還不是全部。一些未被發覺的突發事故本來是可以導致我被抓的。但每次運氣總能發揮作用，但也許這根本就不是運氣……帶著總有一天我們的殘骸會產生新生命的希望，我一直在找尋答案。其他人無疑會出於不同的理由設法暗中破壞這種創造，以結束法治並代之以亂治。那麼是誰或者是什麽呢？好吧……我不喜歡猜測，但我覺得我的每一步都有偉大而惡魔般的存在在進行監督。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">保護：爲什麽我從來沒有被發現呢？從事這些犯罪行為（法律將其稱之為犯罪，所以我最好也這樣做）的人都避免不了在某天迎來最後審判日，那麼爲什麽我不會這樣呢？我當然一直都很小心，這是普通的常識。它本身（屠殺行為）不過是整體行動的 1%。其餘則是預見、規劃及創建假消息和不在場證明等。不對所有這些給予應有的尊重將導致致命電壓極為迅速地透過人體。但這還不是全部。一些未被發覺的突發事故本來是可以導致我被抓的。但每次運氣總能發揮作用，但也許這根本就不是運氣……帶著總有一天我們的殘骸會產生新生命的希望，我一直在找尋答案。其他人無疑會出於不同的理由設法暗中破壞這種創造，以結束法治並代之以亂治。那麼是誰或者是什麽呢？好吧……我不喜歡猜測，但我覺得我的每一步都有偉大而惡魔般的存在在進行監督。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Protection: Why was I never found out? It is inevitable that those who engage in these crimes (the law calls it crime so I would do well to do the same) will one day meet their day of reckoning, so why not me? I have been careful of course, plain common sense. It in itself - the act of slaughter - is but 1% of the whole. The rest is foresight, planning, the creation of false trails and alibis, etc.  To not pay all this the respect it deserves will result in a fatal voltage being passed though ones body very swiftly. But that isn't all. A few unseen occurrences should have resulted in my capture. Each time luck swung my way but perhaps this was not luck at all... I seek answers in hope that one day a new being will rise from our debris. Others no doubt seek to undermine creation for different reasons, to end the rule of law and replace it with the rule of chaos. Who or what? Well there... I prefer not to speculate but I feel a great and infernal presence over-seeing my every step.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment15</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">More Than One: It wasn't enough! The manor was mine and I was its but I still did not understand fully. It was alive most certainly: whispering, hot and cold patches, unsettling scurrying noises and growls from behind the walls. It was a living thing, I always knew this but there was something I was not quite grasping. Then one day I became ill and the manor became ill too. As I writhed in my bed, wracked in pain I could feel the house twisting too, the walls and floorboard cracking. In that moment of lucidity as my fever passed into the eye of the storm, I realised the house and I were more than one. The whispers that had been my constant companion were the evocation of my very thoughts, the coldness that plagued its rooms despite the constant fire, the mirroring of my own heartlessness. That was when I stopped being afraid of the beast that lurked behind the walls. Penned in, trapped, pacing and full of barely contained fury... I was the beast.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plus qu'un : Ce n'était pas assez ! Le manoir était à moi et je lui appartenais, mais des zones d'ombre subsistaient. Il était certainement en vie : murmurant, chaud ou froid par endroits, des bruits de pas troublants et des grognements derrière les murs. C'était une chose vivante, je l'avais toujours su, mais il restait quelque chose que je ne saisissais pas. Et un jour, je suis tombé malade et le manoir aussi. Alors que je me tordais de douleur dans mon lit, je pouvais sentir la maison qui tournait, ses murs et son plancher craquaient. Pendant ce moment de lucidité au plus fort de ma fièvre, je réalisai soudain que la maison et moi étions plus qu'un tout. Les murmures qui m'accompagnaient constamment n'étaient que l'évocation de mes pensées, la persistance du froid dans les pièces alors que le feu brûlait sans cesse, la réflexion de ma cruauté. À partir de ce moment, la bête tapie derrière le mur ne m'effraya plus. Cernée, piégée, arpentant la pièce dans une fureur à peine maîtrisée... J'étais la bête.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mehr als einer: Es hat nicht gereicht! Der Landsitz gehörte mir und ich ihm, aber ich verstand ihn noch immer nicht vollständig. Keine Frage, er war lebendig, er flüsterte, es gab heiße und kalte Stellen und aus den Wänden kamen beängstigende huschende Geräusche und dumpfes Grollen. Er war lebendig, das wusste ich schon immer, doch da war noch etwas, das ich noch nicht ganz begriffen hatte. Dann wurde ich eines Tages krank und der Landsitz auch. Als ich mich im Bett vor Schmerzen wand, konnte ich spüren, wie sich das Haus ebenfalls wand, dass die Wände und Bodenbretter ächzten. In diesem Moment der Klarheit, als mein Fieber das Auge des Sturms passierte, wurde mir klar, dass das Haus und ich mehr als eins sind. Das Flüstern, das mein ständiger Begleiter gewesen war, war Ausdruck meiner eigenen Gedanken, die Kälte, die trotz des Feuers jedes Zimmer beherrschte, spiegelte meine eigene Herzlosigkeit wider. Und da hörte ich auf, vor der Bestie Angst zu haben, die hinter den Wänden lauerte. Eingesperrt, gefangen, hin und her laufend, voll kaum gebändigtem Zorn ... Ich war die Bestie.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un tutt'uno: non era abbastanza! Il maniero era mio ed io ero suo, ma ancora non lo capivo pienamente. Quasi certamente era vivo: mormorii, parti calde e fredde, rumori di passi affrettati e ringhi da dietro i muri. Era una cosa viva, l'avevo sempre saputo, ma c'era qualcosa che non riuscivo a capire. Poi un giorno mi ammalai e con me si ammalò anche il maniero. Mentre mi rigiravo nel letto, in preda ai dolori, potevo sentire la casa muoversi, i muri e i pavimenti scricchiolare. In quel momento di lucidità, in cui la febbre attraversava l'occhio del ciclone, mi resi conto che la casa ed io eravamo un tutt'uno. I mormorii che mi avevano costantemente accompagnato erano l'evocazione dei miei pensieri, il freddo delle sue stanze, nonostante il fuoco sempre acceso, lo specchio della mia insensibilità. Da quel momento in poi, smisi di aver paura della bestia che si aggirava dietro i muri. Confinata, intrappolata, scalpitante e piena di furia pronta a esplodere... La bestia ero io.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Más de uno: ¡No era suficiente! La mansión era mía y yo era suyo, pero seguía sin entenderlo del todo. Era evidente que estaba viva: los susurros, las zonas frías y calientes, los perturbadores ruidos y gruñidos que corrían detrás de las paredes. Estaba viva, siempre lo supe, pero había algo que se me escapaba. Hasta que un día me puse enfermo y la mansión enfermó conmigo. Cuando me retorcía de dolor en la cama, la casa también se retorcía, las paredes y las tablas del suelo crujían. En aquel momento de lucidez, cuando la fiebre pasaba por el ojo de la tormenta, me di cuenta de que la casa y yo éramos más que una persona. Los susurros que me habían acompañado constantemente eran la evocación de mis pensamientos, el frío que invadía las habitaciones a pesar de estar encendido el fuego, un reflejo de mi crueldad. Entonces dejé de temer a la bestia que acechaba tras las paredes. Encerrada, atrapada, caminando y llena de furia apenas contenida... Yo era la bestia.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">一度だけではない - 私はこの館を手に入れるだけでは満足できませんでした。館を所有するだけでは完全にこの場所を理解できませんでした。この館から聞こえるささやき、温度の違い、小刻みに聞こえる音や、壁の裏から聞こえてくるうなり声は、確かにこの館が生きている証拠でした。館は生きていたのです。常にこのことを私は知っていましたが、はっきりとしたことは不明でした。ある日、私は病気になりました。すると館も病気になったのです。痛みに襲われ私がベットで身もだえしていると、屋敷がきしみ、壁や床板がヒビ割れだしたのです。この屋敷と私は一心同体であることに気付いたのです。館で絶え間なく聞こえてくるささやきは、私自身の考えの喚起であり、部屋に充満する寒気は私自身の無慈悲な心を反映していました。それ以後、私は壁の裏に住み着いた野獣を恐れなくなりました。なぜなら、壁の裏に閉じ込もる傷ついた野獣は私自身の姿そのものだったからです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">하나 이상: 충분치 않았습니다! 저택은 제 소유였고 저는 저택의 소유였지만 아직 모든 것을 이해한 것은 아니었습니다. 속삭임, 뜨겁고 차가운 방, 벽 뒤에서 들리는 불안하게 만드는 잰 걸음 소리와 으르렁 소리까지. 저택은 분명 살아있었습니다. 살아있는 존재였죠. 저는 언제나 이 사실을 알고 있었지만 완전히 이해하지 못하는 부분이 있었습니다. 어느날 제가 몸이 아프게 되자 저택도 아프게 되었습니다. 제가 침대에서 고통에 몸부림치면 집도 뒤틀리며 벽과 바닥이 소리를 내는 것을 느꼈습니다. 제 열병이 잠시 가라앉은 찰라의 순간에 저는 집과 제가 단순한 하나가 아닌 그 이상이라는 것을 깨달았습니다. 항상 저와 함께 했던 속삭임은 제 생각의 발현이었고, 불을 피워도 차가웠던 방은 제 비정함의 반영이었습니다. 바로 그때 저는 벽 뒤에 숨어있는 짐승의 존재를 두려워하지 않게 되었습니다. 터질것 같은 분노로 가득한 존재... 바로 제가 그 짐승이었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">More Than One: It wasn't enough! The manor was mine and I was its but I still did not understand fully. It was alive most certainly: whispering, hot and cold patches, unsettling scurrying noises and growls from behind the walls. It was a living thing, I always knew this but there was something I was not quite grasping. Then one day I became ill and the manor became ill too. As I writhed in my bed, wracked in pain I could feel the house twisting too, the walls and floorboard cracking. In that moment of lucidity as my fever passed into the eye of the storm, I realised the house and I were more than one. The whispers that had been my constant companion were the evocation of my very thoughts, the coldness that plagued its rooms despite the constant fire, the mirroring of my own heartlessness. That was when I stopped being afraid of the beast that lurked behind the walls. Penned in, trapped, pacing and full of barely contained fury... I was the beast.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">不只是一體：這還遠遠不夠！莊園和我彼此相許，但我仍然無法完全理解。它幾乎肯定是活著的：不斷的呢喃、冷熱時期變化、墻後傳來的急促噪音和咆哮聲。它是有生命的。我一直都知道這一點，但有些事我無法領會。之後有一天，我生病了，莊園也病倒了。當我在床上備受折磨地痛苦翻騰時，我能感覺到房子也在扭曲，牆壁和地板還發出噼啪的斷裂聲。在那個清醒的瞬間，隨著我的高燒傳入風暴眼，我意識到房子和我不只是一體。常伴我左右的耳語是我自身被喚醒的思想，是儘管有持續燃燒的烈火卻仍在各房間肆虐的嚴寒，也是我自身冷漠無情的真實反映。從那時起，我不再害怕潛伏在墻後的野獸了。圈禁、受困、不斷踱步且幾乎飽含著憤怒……我本身就是野獸。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">不只是一體：這還遠遠不夠！莊園和我彼此相許，但我仍然無法完全理解。它幾乎肯定是活著的：不斷的呢喃、冷熱時期變化、墻後傳來的急促噪音和咆哮聲。它是有生命的。我一直都知道這一點，但有些事我無法領會。之後有一天，我生病了，莊園也病倒了。當我在床上備受折磨地痛苦翻騰時，我能感覺到房子也在扭曲，牆壁和地板還發出噼啪的斷裂聲。在那個清醒的瞬間，隨著我的高燒傳入風暴眼，我意識到房子和我不只是一體。常伴我左右的耳語是我自身被喚醒的思想，是儘管有持續燃燒的烈火卻仍在各房間肆虐的嚴寒，也是我自身冷漠無情的真實反映。從那時起，我不再害怕潛伏在墻後的野獸了。圈禁、受困、不斷踱步且幾乎飽含著憤怒……我本身就是野獸。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">More Than One: It wasn't enough! The manor was mine and I was its but I still did not understand fully. It was alive most certainly: whispering, hot and cold patches, unsettling scurrying noises and growls from behind the walls. It was a living thing, I always knew this but there was something I was not quite grasping. Then one day I became ill and the manor became ill too. As I writhed in my bed, wracked in pain I could feel the house twisting too, the walls and floorboard cracking. In that moment of lucidity as my fever passed into the eye of the storm, I realised the house and I were more than one. The whispers that had been my constant companion were the evocation of my very thoughts, the coldness that plagued its rooms despite the constant fire, the mirroring of my own heartlessness. That was when I stopped being afraid of the beast that lurked behind the walls. Penned in, trapped, pacing and full of barely contained fury... I was the beast.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment16</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Jealous: So the manor was a physical manifestation of my psyche. Surely such a symbiotic relationship meant we got on but no! On many occasion I lashed out at this damned place and unfortunately the manor did so too. You will remember the dark twins and their chilling end. One day I was in the cold room retrieving a steak after spending a productive day hunting an investment property, when the door slammed shut behind me. It was no errant gust of wind. For four hours the room chilled and throttled the life out of me. At the moment of expiration the door suddenly opened once more, air rushed in and I revived enough to cry out, only for the door to slam shut again. As I succumb once more, drooling and insensible, the dark twins climbed slowly out of the walls. They were ten years dead, looked as such and I was in no doubt they were about to enjoy their vengeance. As they touched me the door flew open once more and an invisible hand drew them back to their hell hole. I have never enjoyed quite the same spring in my step since but the lesson was learnt and I never again thought of buying other property.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jaloux : Le manoir était donc une manifestation physique de mon mental. Une telle symbiose signifiait sûrement une bonne entente. Bien au contraire ! À plusieurs occasions, je me déchaînai à cette maudite maison, et malheureusement, le manoir fit de même. Vous vous souviendrez sûrement de la fin à faire froid dans le dos des jumelles. Un jour que j'étais dans la chambre froide pour prendre un steak après une bonne journée à chercher un bien immobilier, la porte se ferma en claquant derrière moi. Ce n'était pas un simple coup de vent. Pendant quatre heures, la chambre m'a gelé et étranglé jusqu'à mon dernier souffle. Au moment d'expirer, la porte s'ouvrit soudainement, l'air s'engouffra et je repris assez de force pour crier, avant que la porte ne se referme. Alors que je succombais une fois de plus, bavant et insensible, les jumelles maléfiques sortirent lentement des murs. EIles étaient mortes depuis dix ans et ça se voyait. J'étais certain qu'elles étaient sur le point de goûter à leur vengeance. Quand elles me touchèrent, la porte s'ouvrit à nouveau et une main invisible les renvoya dans leur enfer. Je n'eus jamais plus la même vigueur, mais je retins la leçon et je ne pensai jamais plus à acheter une autre propriété.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eifersüchtig: Der Landsitz war also eine physische Manifestierung meiner Psyche. Eine solche symbiotische Beziehung setzte voraus, dass wir uns verstanden, aber nein! Bei vielen Gelegenheiten hatte ich mich gegen diesen verfluchten Ort gewandt, und der Landsitz leider auch gegen mich. Du erinnerst dich sicher noch an die finsteren Zwillinge und ihr grausiges Ende. Eines Tages war ich gerade im Kühlraum, um mir nach einen produktiven Tag auf der Jagd nach einer Immobilie ein Steak zu holen, als hinter mir die Tür zufiel. Es war kein Windstoß gewesen. Vier Stunden lang fror ich bitterlich in dem Raum. Als ich fast schon am Ende meiner Kräfte war, öffnete sich plötzlich die Tür. Luft wehte herein und ich kam wieder so weit zur Besinnung, dass ich laut aufschreien konnte, worauf die Tür wieder zufiel. Als ich wieder langsam das Bewusstsein verlor und besinnungslos sabberte, entstiegen die finsteren Zwillinge langsam den Wänden. Sie waren seit zehn Jahren tot und sahen auch so aus, und ich hatte keinen Zweifel daran, dass sie jetzt ihre Rache würden genießen wollen. Als sie mich berührten, flog die Tür erneut auf und eine unsichtbare Hand zog sie wieder zurück in ihr Höllenloch. Seitdem bin ich deutlich ruhiger geworden, doch ich habe meine Lektion gelernt und nie mehr wieder über den Kauf einer anderen Immobilie nachgedacht.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gelosia: dunque il maniero era una manifestazione fisica della mia psiche. Di sicuro una relazione così simbiotica ti farebbe pensare che andassimo d'accordo. Ma no! In più occasioni me la presi con il maniero e purtroppo il maniero mi ripagò con la stessa moneta. Ti ricordi i gemelli oscuri e la loro orribile fine? Un giorno, dopo aver passato la giornata alla ricerca di una proprietà su cui investire, andai a recuperare una bistecca nella stanza fredda. All'improvviso la porta si chiuse dietro di me sbattendo. Non era una raffica di vento. Per quattro ore la stanza sembrò come strozzarmi e spremermi via la vita. Quando stavo per cedere, la porta all'improvviso si aprì, l'aria tornò a circolare e mi ripresi abbastanza da gridare, ma la porta si chiuse nuovamente. Mentre ero lì, a terra, sbavando, come insensibile, i gemelli oscuri uscirono lentamente dal muro. Erano morti da dieci anni e non avevo dubbi sul fatto che fossero tornati per vendicarsi. Non appena mi toccarono, la porta si aprì un'altra volta e una mano invisibile li riportò nella loro prigione magica. È da allora che non faccio uno scatto del genere! Ad ogni modo, avevo imparato una lezione e dimenticai l'idea di comprare un'altra proprietà.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Celoso: la mansión era una manifestación física de mi psique. Con una simbiosis así debíamos llevarnos bien, ¡pero nada más lejos de la realidad! En muchas ocasiones arremetí contra este maldito lugar y, por desgracia, la mansión hizo lo propio. Recordarás a las gemelas oscuras y su escalofriante final. Un día estaba en la cámara cogiendo un filete tras pasar un día productivo buscando una propiedad en la que invertir, cuando la puerta se cerró detrás de mí. No fue una ráfaga de aire. Durante cuatro horas, la habitación me congeló y me estranguló. Cuando estaba a punto de morir, la puerta se volvió a abrir, entró aire y volví a la vida lo justo para gritar. La puerta cerró. Cuando volví a sucumbir, babeando y sin conocimiento, las gemelas oscuras salieron despacio de las paredes. Llevaban diez años muertas y su aspecto lo confirmaba. Tuve claro que estaban a punto de disfrutar su venganza. En el momento en que me tocaron, la puerta se abrió de par en par y una mano invisible los devolvió a su lugar maldito. Nunca he vuelto a pasar por lo mismo, pero aprendí la lección y no he intentado comprar otra casa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">嫉妬 - 館は私の心の奥を映し出す物理的発現でした。このような共存生活で私たちは常に友好的関係を築いたわけではありません。私がこのボロ家に対してつらく当たれば、館も同じように私に仕返しをしてきました。そのようなことは何度もありました。あの死んだ双子を憶えているでしょう。いつの日か、館の寒い部屋で、私が投資物件の調査に熱を入れていた時のことでした。部屋の扉がバタンと閉まり、それから四時間もの間、私は冷え込んだ部屋に閉じ込められ、あやうく死にかけました。私が息を吹き返したと同時に扉が開き、部屋に空気が入り込んできたかと思うと、扉は再び勢いよく閉まりました。私が切望に屈していると、あの陰険な双子がゆっくりと壁を這い上がってきたのです。死後十年を経たその双子は、復讐を楽しもうというわんばかりの表情で私に近づいてきました。双子が私を捕まえようとしたその時、再び扉が開き、見えない手によってその双子は地獄の穴に落ちていきました。それ以来、私は決して他の物件を購入することを考慮しませんでした。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">질투: 저택은 제 정신 세계의 물리적인 표현이었습니다. 그런 공생의 관계에도 불구하고 우리는 사이좋게 지내지 못했습니다! 저는 자주 이 저주받은 곳을 몰아세우고 불행하게도 저택도 저를 몰아세웠습니다. 어둠의 쌍둥이와 그 소름끼치는 결말을 기억하실겁니다. 하루는 차가운 방에서 투자를 생각하던 부동산에 대한 조사에 열을 올리고 있었습니다. 갑자기 제 뒤에 있던 문이 쾅하고 닫혀버렸습니다. 그것은 세찬 돌풍 때문이 아니었습니다. 4시간 동안 방의 온도는 내려갔고 저는 점점 숨이 막혀 갔습니다. 자칫 죽을 수도 있는 상황에 이르자 문이 열렸고 공기가 들어오면서 비명을 지를 수 있을 정도의 숨을 들이마셨지만, 다시 문은 닫히고 말았습니다. 제가 침을 흘리고 의식이 혼미해지면서 다시 한 번 굴복할 때 쯤 어둠의 쌍둥이가 벽에서 천천히 기어나왔습니다. 그들이 죽은지는 10년이 지났고, 복수를 즐기는 듯한 표정으로 나에게 다가왔습니다. 그들이 날 붙잡으려는 순간 문이 다시 한 번 열리고 보이지 않는 손이 나와 그들을 지옥의 구멍으로 끌고 들어갔습니다. 그때 저는 그 일을 교훈 삼아 그 이후 다른 부동산 구입은 절대 꿈도 꾸지 않았습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Jealous: So the manor was a physical manifestation of my psyche. Surely such a symbiotic relationship meant we got on but no! On many occasion I lashed out at this damned place and unfortunately the manor did so too. You will remember the dark twins and their chilling end. One day I was in the cold room retrieving a steak after spending a productive day hunting an investment property, when the door slammed shut behind me. It was no errant gust of wind. For four hours the room chilled and throttled the life out of me. At the moment of expiration the door suddenly opened once more, air rushed in and I revived enough to cry out, only for the door to slam shut again. As I succumb once more, drooling and insensible, the dark twins climbed slowly out of the walls. They were ten years dead, looked as such and I was in no doubt they were about to enjoy their vengeance. As they touched me the door flew open once more and an invisible hand drew them back to their hell hole. I have never enjoyed quite the same spring in my step since but the lesson was learnt and I never again thought of buying other property.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">嫉妒：因而莊園是我靈魂的一個物理表現。這種共生關係當然意味著我們應該相處融洽，但事實並非如此！我曾在許多場合痛斥這個該死的地方，但不幸的是，莊園對我也好不到哪裡去。你應該還記得黑暗雙胞胎和他們令人恐懼的結局。有一天，在頗有成效地尋找了一整天的投資物業後，我正在冷藏室找一塊牛排，這時門在我身後砰地一聲關上了。這可不是什麽亂吹的怪風。在四個小時的時間里，房間不斷變冷，幾乎要了我的命。就在我快要不行了的那一刻，門突然再次打開了，空氣湧了進來，我終於蘇醒過來並大聲抱怨，結果門卻再次重重地關上了。當我再次暈倒、流著口水、毫無意識的時候，黑暗雙胞胎慢慢從墻中爬出。他們去世十年了，看到這些，我毫不懷疑他們是想享受復仇的樂趣。當他們觸碰到我時，門再次突然打開了，一隻無形的手將其拉回了地獄之洞。從那時起，我的活力不復從前，而我也得到了教訓，再也不會想著購買其他的物業了。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">嫉妒：因而莊園是我靈魂的一個物理表現。這種共生關係當然意味著我們應該相處融洽，但事實並非如此！我曾在許多場合痛斥這個該死的地方，但不幸的是，莊園對我也好不到哪裡去。你應該還記得黑暗雙胞胎和他們令人恐懼的結局。有一天，在頗有成效地尋找了一整天的投資物業後，我正在冷藏室找一塊牛排，這時門在我身後砰地一聲關上了。這可不是什麽亂吹的怪風。在四個小時的時間里，房間不斷變冷，幾乎要了我的命。就在我快要不行了的那一刻，門突然再次打開了，空氣湧了進來，我終於蘇醒過來並大聲抱怨，結果門卻再次重重地關上了。當我再次暈倒、流著口水、毫無意識的時候，黑暗雙胞胎慢慢從墻中爬出。他們去世十年了，看到這些，我毫不懷疑他們是想享受復仇的樂趣。當他們觸碰到我時，門再次突然打開了，一隻無形的手將其拉回了地獄之洞。從那時起，我的活力不復從前，而我也得到了教訓，再也不會想著購買其他的物業了。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Jealous: So the manor was a physical manifestation of my psyche. Surely such a symbiotic relationship meant we got on but no! On many occasion I lashed out at this damned place and unfortunately the manor did so too. You will remember the dark twins and their chilling end. One day I was in the cold room retrieving a steak after spending a productive day hunting an investment property, when the door slammed shut behind me. It was no errant gust of wind. For four hours the room chilled and throttled the life out of me. At the moment of expiration the door suddenly opened once more, air rushed in and I revived enough to cry out, only for the door to slam shut again. As I succumb once more, drooling and insensible, the dark twins climbed slowly out of the walls. They were ten years dead, looked as such and I was in no doubt they were about to enjoy their vengeance. As they touched me the door flew open once more and an invisible hand drew them back to their hell hole. I have never enjoyed quite the same spring in my step since but the lesson was learnt and I never again thought of buying other property.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment17</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fever: A fever caught hold of me, an abscess appeared on my chest. The normal part of me (one cannot hide from justice without some appearance of normality) desired a swift recovery but as a man of science I was fascinated as it grew daily from pustule to cavity. What was this? Need I say the pain was exquisite but there it is you see, there it is, pain is fleeting while knowledge is eternal. I was able ... carefully... to reach inside... to see...  A great cry issued from the manor. It was as though every pore of it had been violated and then a great wall of pressure came tearing through the rooms and slammed me into the wall. A confirmation. I really didn't want to see but neither did I want to face a punishment so I bandaged myself up and went off into the house to discover the source of its pain. The discovery I made in the dining room was as appalling for me as  it was for you no doubt. If you have not yet discovered... it, there is no time like the present.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La fièvre — une fièvre s'est emparée de moi, un abcès est apparu sur ma poitrine. La partie normale de moi-même (on ne peut rester à l'ombre de la justice sans apparaître quelque peu normal) désirait un prompt rétablissement, mais étant un homme de la science, j'étais fasciné par cette pustule se transformant en cavité. Qu'était-ce donc ? Nul besoin de vous dire que la douleur était vive, mais voyez-vous, la douleur est passagère tandis que le savoir est éternel. J'étais capable... doucement... d'atteindre l'intérieur... pour voir... Un grand cri surgit du manoir. C'était comme si tous ses pores avaient été violés, puis une immense pression vint détruire les pièces et me plaqua contre un mur. Une confirmation. Contre ma volonté et de peur d'être châtié, je m'appliquai un bandage et allai inspecter la maison pour découvrir la source de sa douleur. Ma découverte dans le salon fut aussi effroyable pour moi qu'elle l'a été pour vous, sans aucun doute. Si vous n'avez pas encore découvert... cela, maintenant semble propice.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fieber - Ein Fieber kam über mich, ein Abszess erschien auf meiner Brust. Der normale Teil von mir (man kann sich nicht vor dem Gesetz verbergen, ohne zumindest den Anschein von Normalität zu erwecken) sehnte sich nach einer schnellen Gesundung, doch als Mann der Wissenschaft war ich fasziniert, wie er sich mit jedem Tag von einer Pustel zu einer Höhlung entwickelte. Was war das? Ich muss wohl nicht sagen, dass die Schmerzen exorbitant waren, aber genau das ist es, genau das: Schmerzen sind flüchtig, doch Wissen ist ewig. Ich konnte ... vorsichtig ... hineingreifen ... und sah ... Der Landsitz wurde von einem lauten Schrei erschüttert. Es war, als wäre jeder Faser seines Wesens Gewalt angetan worden, und dann raste eine gewaltige Druckwelle durch alle Räume und schleuderte mich gegen die Wand. Eine Bestätigung. Ich wollte es wirklich nicht sehen, aber ich wollte mich auch nicht bestrafen lassen, also verband ich meine Wunden und ging ins Haus, um mir anzusehen, was ihm solche Schmerzen bereitete. Die Entdeckung, die ich im Speisezimmer machte, war für mich so abstoßend wie sie zweifellos auch für dich war. Falls du ... es noch nicht entdeckt hast, nun, es geht doch nichts über die Gegenwart.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Febbre: mi colse la febbre, un ascesso apparve sul mio petto. La parte normale di me (è impossibile sfuggire alla giustizia senza una qualche apparenza di normalità) desiderava una pronta guarigione, ma come uomo di scienze ero affascinato da quella pustola che di giorno in giorno si trasformava in cavità. Che cos'era? Il dolore era piacevole... Vedi, la sofferenza è caduca, mentre la conoscenza è eterna. Riuscii... attentamente... a raggiungere l'interno... e guardare... Un urlo si levò dal maniero. Era come se ogni suo poro fosse stato profanato: fu allora che una muraglia di pressione attraversò le stanze e mi sbatté contro il muro. Una conferma. Non volevo vedere, ma non volevo neanche essere punito, per cui mi fasciai e mi misi alla ricerca della fonte del suo dolore. La scoperta che feci nella sala da pranzo fu spaventosa per me, come immagino sia stata per te. Se non hai ancora fatto questa scoperta, ora è il momento migliore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fiebre: la fiebre se apoderó de mí y en el pecho apareció un absceso. Mi parte normal (uno no puede huir de la justicia sin aparentar normalidad) deseaba una rápida recuperación, pero como hombre de ciencia, me fascinaba, pues crecía a diario, de pústula a cavidad. ¿Qué era? No hace falta que diga que el dolor era tremendo, pero he ahí la cuestión: el dolor es breve, mientras que el conocimiento es eterno. Podía... con cuidado... alcanzar el interior... ver... Un enorme grito emergió de la mansión. Fue como si todos sus poros se hubieran abierto y un gran muro de presión desgarró las habitaciones y me tiró contra la pared. Una confirmación. No quería ver, pero tampoco quería enfrentarme a un castigo, por lo que me puse una venda y fui a buscar la fuente del dolor de la casa. Lo que descubrí en el comedor fue tan atroz para mí como seguro que lo ha sido para ti. Si aún no lo has descubierto... este es el momento perfecto para hacerlo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">熱病 - 私は熱病に侵され、胸に膿瘍が現れました。私の中の正常な心は（裁きを逃れるためには正常な心を装うことも必要です）はやい回復を望みました。しかし科学者である私は、膿瘍が膿胞から膿瘍腔に変化するまでの変化に魅了されました。この観察には耐え難い痛みを要しましたが、残らない痛みと違い、知識は永遠に残るものでした。私は、慎重に.. この膿瘍を観察し... 実態を見つけ出したかったのです。館はおびただしい悲鳴をあげて苦しみました。全ての気孔が妨害され、部屋を切り裂いて巨大な圧力が押し寄せ、私の体を壁に打ち付けました。私は知りたくありませんでしたが、制裁を恐れたので、自分の体に包帯を巻き、痛みの根源を発見するためにダイニングルームに入って行ったのです。ダイニングルームでの発見はひどいものでした。まだ、そこへいらしてないのなら、そこへ行って自分の目で確かめてください。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">열병: 열병에 걸려서 가슴에 종기가 생겼습니다. 저의 정상적인 마음은(심판을 피하기 위해선 정상적인 마음을 갖추는 것도 필요합니다) 빠른 회복을 원했지만, 과학을 탐구하는 인간으로서 저는 종기가 매일 자라나는 모습에 매혹되고 말았습니다. 그것은 무엇이었을까요? 이런 관찰에는참기 어려운 고통이 수반되었지만, 그 고통은 한순간이고 지식은 영원하죠. 저는... 조심스럽게… 관찰하고 실태를 발견해 나가고 싶었습니다… 저택이 비명을 지르며 괴로워했습니다. 숨쉬기조차 힘들어 방을 갈기갈기 찢어놓고 엄청난 압력으로 절 짖누르고 저의 몸을 벽에 꽂아버리는 느낌이었습니다. 알고 싶지 않았지만, 그로 인한 벌을 받기 싫었기에 스스로 반창고를 붙이고 식당으로 고통의 근원을 찾아나섰습니다. 식당에서 발견한 사실은 제게도 소름끼치는 것이었습니다. 아직 발견하지 못했다면... 지금 당장 확인하는 것이 좋을 겁니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Fever: A fever caught hold of me, an abscess appeared on my chest. The normal part of me (one cannot hide from justice without some appearance of normality) desired a swift recovery but as a man of science I was fascinated as it grew daily from pustule to cavity. What was this? Need I say the pain was exquisite but there it is you see, there it is, pain is fleeting while knowledge is eternal. I was able ... carefully... to reach inside... to see...  A great cry issued from the manor. It was as though every pore of it had been violated and then a great wall of pressure came tearing through the rooms and slammed me into the wall. A confirmation. I really didn't want to see but neither did I want to face a punishment so I bandaged myself up and went off into the house to discover the source of its pain. The discovery I made in the dining room was as appalling for me as  it was for you no doubt. If you have not yet discovered... it, there is no time like the present.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">熱病：我得了熱病，胸口出現膿腫。我正常的那部份（沒有些正常的外觀，人是無法躲避司法制裁的）希望可以迅速恢復，但是作為一個科學人，隨著膿皰一天天發展為凹洞，我感到很是著迷。這是什麽？我必須說，那痛感極其強烈，但是它就在那裡，痛苦是短暫的，而知識是永恆的。我能夠……小心地……觸碰其内裏……以查看……莊園發出了巨大的叫喊聲，好像它的每個毛孔都被侵犯了一樣，隨後一堵巨大的壓力之墻排山倒海而來並將我重重地撞在了墻上。這進一步證實了我的想法。我真的不想去看，但又不想面臨懲罰，所以我將自己包扎好並前往房子以找出其痛苦之源。我在餐廳發現對我對你都無疑是駭人聽聞的。如果你還沒有發現……它，現在正是絕佳的時機。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">熱病：我得了熱病，胸口出現膿腫。我正常的那部份（沒有些正常的外觀，人是無法躲避司法制裁的）希望可以迅速恢復，但是作為一個科學人，隨著膿皰一天天發展為凹洞，我感到很是著迷。這是什麽？我必須說，那痛感極其強烈，但是它就在那裡，痛苦是短暫的，而知識是永恆的。我能夠……小心地……觸碰其内裏……以查看……莊園發出了巨大的叫喊聲，好像它的每個毛孔都被侵犯了一樣，隨後一堵巨大的壓力之墻排山倒海而來並將我重重地撞在了墻上。這進一步證實了我的想法。我真的不想去看，但又不想面臨懲罰，所以我將自己包扎好並前往房子以找出其痛苦之源。我在餐廳發現對我對你都無疑是駭人聽聞的。如果你還沒有發現……它，現在正是絕佳的時機。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fever: A fever caught hold of me, an abscess appeared on my chest. The normal part of me (one cannot hide from justice without some appearance of normality) desired a swift recovery but as a man of science I was fascinated as it grew daily from pustule to cavity. What was this? Need I say the pain was exquisite but there it is you see, there it is, pain is fleeting while knowledge is eternal. I was able ... carefully... to reach inside... to see...  A great cry issued from the manor. It was as though every pore of it had been violated and then a great wall of pressure came tearing through the rooms and slammed me into the wall. A confirmation. I really didn't want to see but neither did I want to face a punishment so I bandaged myself up and went off into the house to discover the source of its pain. The discovery I made in the dining room was as appalling for me as  it was for you no doubt. If you have not yet discovered... it, there is no time like the present.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment18</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Old Friends: The whole back of the room was a red, inflamed, virulent abscess. Could this be me? I touched my wound and a great roar bellowed out, burning the air with its greasy stench and the abscess emptied itself of unimaginable green and curdled funk. A fury overtook me and I reached into myself to punish the manor but the abscess swelled so as to fill the room and grasped me in its maw. It sphincter grip could have crushed me to a pulp but instead it began to swallow me whole, work me down it's headless throat, all the way down into itself, screaming as it went, it and I, fates never not unbound. To my horror I discovered I was not alone. Roiled ever deeper by this monstrous esophagus I felt hands pawing at me -  it was the Volants. They had found their hell after all. And others, worming and winding their bodies all around me. My victims... every last broken, stoved-in one of them, grinning.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vieux amis : Tout le fond de la pièce était un abcès rouge, enflammé et virulent. Était-il possible que cela soit moi ? Alors que je touchai ma blessure, il y eut un rugissement, brûlant l'air d'une puanteur graisseuse, et l'abcès se vida avec une odeur infecte inimaginable. Une fureur s'empara de moi et j'essayai de plonger à l'intérieur de moi-même pour punir le manoir, mais l'abcès gonfla et remplit la pièce me saisissant dans sa gueule. En me serrant dans son sphincter, il aurait pu m'écraser, mais il commença à m'avaler, tout entier, à me faire glisser dans sa gorge sans tête, jusqu'au plus profond de lui-même, criant en même temps, lui et moi, destins déliés à jamais. J'ai découvert avec horreur que je n'étais pas seul. Poussé toujours plus profondément par cet œsophage monstrueux, je sentis des mains me toucher. C'était les Volants. Ils avaient trouvé leur enfer finalement. Et d'autres, rampant et enroulant leur corps autour de moi. Mes victimes... chacune d'entre elles jusqu'à la dernière, brisée, fracassée, souriante.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Alte Freunde: Die ganze Rückseite des Raums war ein roter, entzündeter und virulenter Abszess. Sollte ich das sein? Ich berührte meine Wunde und ein lauter Schrei heulte auf, verbrannte die Luft mit seinem schmierigen Gestank, und der Abszess entleerte sich mit einem unvorstellbaren Schwall aus grünlich-körnigem Schleim. Wut überkam mich und ich griff in mich hinein, um den Landsitz zu bestrafen, doch der Abszess schwoll an, füllte den gesamten Raum aus und packte mich mit seinem Schlund. Sein stahlharter Griff hätte mich leicht zerquetschen können, doch stattdessen begann er, mich komplett zu verschlingen, in seinen kopflosen Hals zu schieben, ganz in sich hinein, wobei wir beide schrien, denn wir teilten das gleiche Schicksal. Zu meinem Schrecken sah ich, dass ich nicht allein war. Als ich immer weiter durch diese monströse Speiseröhre gezogen wurde, spürte ich, wie Hände nach mir griffen - es waren die Volants. Sie hatten also doch ihre Hölle gefunden. Wie auch andere, deren Körper sich wie Würmer um mich herum wanden. Meine Opfer ... jedes einzelne von ihnen gebrochen, hier hineingestopft und dennoch mit einem Grinsen im Gesicht.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vecchi amici: l'intero retro della stanza presentava un ascesso virulento, rosso e infiammato. Ero io? Toccai la mia ferita e si levò un ruggito, che bruciava l'aria con il suo puzzo grasso. Dall'ascesso uscì un umore verde coagulato. Fui preso dalla furia, volevo punire il maniero, ma l'ascesso si gonfiò fino a riempire tutta la stanza e mi prese tra le sue fauci. La sua presa avrebbe potuto ridurmi in poltiglia, invece iniziò a inghiottirmi, a spingermi dentro quella gola senza testa, sempre più giù. Si levò un urlo, era mio e suo: il destino era segnato. Con sorpresa e orrore scoprii che non ero solo. Dalle profondità di questo mostruoso esofago sentii delle mani che cercavano di afferrarmi: erano i Volant; dopotutto, avevano trovato il loro inferno. E ce n'erano altri, che strusciavano i loro corpi contro di me, cercando di avvinghiarsi. Erano le mie vittime... Erano tutte lì per me e sogghignavano.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Viejos amigos: la parte trasera de la habitación era un absceso rojo, inflamado y virulento. ¿Es posible que fuera yo? Me toqué la herida y se oyó un gran rugido que quemó el aire con su fetidez grasienta. El absceso se vació de algo verde y espeso. Me invadió la ira y fui a tocarme para castigar a la mansión, pero el absceso se inflamó tanto que llenó la habitación y me atrapó en sus fauces. El esfínter me atrapó de tal forma que podría haberme destrozado, pero empezó a tragarme y bajé por la garganta acéfala hacia su interior. Ambos gritamos, nuestros destinos estaban unidos. Horrorizado, descubrí que no estaba solo. Enturbiado por el monstruoso esófago, noté que algo me manoseaba: eran los Volant. Al final habían encontrado su infierno. Y había otros, que retorcían sus cuerpos a mi alrededor. Mis víctimas, todas las que destrocé, sonreían.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">旧友 - 部屋の裏は真っ赤に腫れあがった悪性の腫瘍でした。これが私の姿なのでしょうか？私がその傷に触れると、大きな唸り声が聞こえ、緑色の腐った腫瘍は酷い悪臭を放ちました。私は館に対し激しく激怒しましたが、腫瘍は膨れ上がり部屋の悪臭に閉じ込められました。館は、その括約筋によって私を磨り潰す代わりに、私の体ごと呑み込んでしまったのです。私は館の喉を通り、その叫び声と共に館の体内へと流されました。そこには恐怖の発見が待っていました。館の巨大な食道の奥深くに居たのは私だけではありませんでした。その地獄で私を待っていたのは、ボルタン家の人々、そして私が殺した犠牲者... 私の犠牲者は一人残らず不快な笑みを浮かべ、私を見ていたのです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">오랜 친구: 방의 뒷면은 전부 붉은색의 염증과 치명적인 종양으로 뒤덮여 있었습니다. 이게 나란 말인가? 전 제 상처를 만졌고, 큰 포효소리가 터져나오면서 종기는 상상할 수도 없는 녹색의 멍울진 지독한 악취를 내뿜었습니다. 분노에 찬 저는 저택을 벌하기 위해 제 몸 안에 손을 댔지만 종기가 부어올라 생기는 악취에 완전히 방 안에 갇혀버렸습니다. 저택은 괄약근의 힘으로 저를 으깨버릴 수도 있었지만, 저를 통째로 삼켜 식도를 통해 집의 체내로 보내졌습니다. 무서운 사실은 식도 깊은 곳에 있었던 건 저 혼자가 아니었다는 것입니다. 이 지옥에서 기다리고 있었던 것은 바로 볼란트가의 사람들 그리고 제가 죽인 희생자들... 한명도 남김없이 불쾌한 웃음을 지으며 절 보고 있었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Old Friends: The whole back of the room was a red, inflamed, virulent abscess. Could this be me? I touched my wound and a great roar bellowed out, burning the air with its greasy stench and the abscess emptied itself of unimaginable green and curdled funk. A fury overtook me and I reached into myself to punish the manor but the abscess swelled so as to fill the room and grasped me in its maw. It sphincter grip could have crushed me to a pulp but instead it began to swallow me whole, work me down it's headless throat, all the way down into itself, screaming as it went, it and I, fates never not unbound. To my horror I discovered I was not alone. Roiled ever deeper by this monstrous esophagus I felt hands pawing at me -  it was the Volants. They had found their hell after all. And others, worming and winding their bodies all around me. My victims... every last broken, stoved-in one of them, grinning.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">老朋友：房間的整個後部都是一個紅色發炎的惡性膿腫。這難道是我嗎？我碰了一下自己的傷口，結果有巨大的吼叫聲發出，灼熱的空氣瀰漫著油膩的惡臭，而膿腫則排空了其內部難以想像的綠色凝結霉臭味。我壓制不住憤怒，將手伸向自己以懲罰莊園，但是膿腫膨脹起來，填滿了整個屋子，並將我吞入腹中。其括約肌的握力本可以將我粉碎成漿糊，但它卻開始將我整個吞咽，送下它愚蠢的喉嚨，並一路直至其本身。它開始大喊大叫，而它和我的命運從未分開過。讓我感到恐懼的是，我發現我並不是獨自一人。被這個畸形醜陋的食道愈發激怒的我感覺到好多隻手在撫摸我 — 是飛行族人。他們終究還是找到了自己的地獄。而其他人在我身邊不斷蠕動扭曲著身體。是我的那些受害者……他們每一位被肢解並放入爐中的人都在露齒微笑。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">老朋友：房間的整個後部都是一個紅色發炎的惡性膿腫。這難道是我嗎？我碰了一下自己的傷口，結果有巨大的吼叫聲發出，灼熱的空氣瀰漫著油膩的惡臭，而膿腫則排空了其內部難以想像的綠色凝結霉臭味。我壓制不住憤怒，將手伸向自己以懲罰莊園，但是膿腫膨脹起來，填滿了整個屋子，並將我吞入腹中。其括約肌的握力本可以將我粉碎成漿糊，但它卻開始將我整個吞咽，送下它愚蠢的喉嚨，並一路直至其本身。它開始大喊大叫，而它和我的命運從未分開過。讓我感到恐懼的是，我發現我並不是獨自一人。被這個畸形醜陋的食道愈發激怒的我感覺到好多隻手在撫摸我 — 是飛行族人。他們終究還是找到了自己的地獄。而其他人在我身邊不斷蠕動扭曲著身體。是我的那些受害者……他們每一位被肢解並放入爐中的人都在露齒微笑。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Old Friends: The whole back of the room was a red, inflamed, virulent abscess. Could this be me? I touched my wound and a great roar bellowed out, burning the air with its greasy stench and the abscess emptied itself of unimaginable green and curdled funk. A fury overtook me and I reached into myself to punish the manor but the abscess swelled so as to fill the room and grasped me in its maw. It sphincter grip could have crushed me to a pulp but instead it began to swallow me whole, work me down it's headless throat, all the way down into itself, screaming as it went, it and I, fates never not unbound. To my horror I discovered I was not alone. Roiled ever deeper by this monstrous esophagus I felt hands pawing at me -  it was the Volants. They had found their hell after all. And others, worming and winding their bodies all around me. My victims... every last broken, stoved-in one of them, grinning.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment19</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Beast:  I can feel you. You are drawn here to this room are you not? Not to the abscess or to I... no... you are not the sort that is inclined to sympathy. You are drawn by the rent in the wall, yes. By fear, by curiosity... by something else? What happened here one can scarcely imagine... a portal ripped thru the wall, deep indentations in the floor, the last known moments of a poor soul as he is dragged from the light into the darkness beyond. Look closely, why are you here friend? Listen to the whispers. Can you hear what they are saying? Listen closely! ... You...do you remember? What do you recall from these last few days here? I was not here to do this but you... you are drawn here by remembrance of things past, aren't you? It was you who did this.. I am the beast no longer, IT IS YOU.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La Bête — Je peux te sentir. Cette pièce vous attire, n'est-ce pas ? Ce n'est pas l'abcès ou moi... non... vous n'êtes pas du genre à ressentir de la sympathie. C'est la déchirure dans le mur qui vous attire. Par peur, par curiosité... autre chose ? Personne ne peut imaginer ce qui est arrivé ici... un portail qui passe au travers d'un mur, de profondes empreintes dans le sol, les derniers moments d'une pauvre âme alors qu'il est traîné vers l'obscurité de l'au-delà. Regardez de plus près, pourquoi êtes-vous ici ? Écoutez les murmures. Pouvez-vous entendre ce qu'ils disent ? Écoutez plus attentivement ! ... Vous... Vous rappelez-vous ? Quels sont vos souvenirs de ces derniers jours ici ? Je n'étais pas ici pour faire cela, mais vous... quelque chose du passé vous ramène ici, n'est-ce pas ? C'est vous qui avez fait cela... Je ne suis plus la bête désormais, C'EST VOUS.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Bestie - ich kann dich spüren. Du fühlst dich zu diesem Raum hingezogen, nicht wahr? Nicht zum Abszess oder zu mir ... nein ... du gehörst nicht zu der Sorte, die zu Sympathien neigt. Dich zieht der Riss in der Wand an, ja. Aus Angst, Neugier ... oder ist etwas anderes der Grund? Was hier geschehen ist, kann man sich kaum vorstellen ... ein Portal hat ein Loch in die Wand gerissen. Tiefe Dellen im Boden deuten auf die letzten Augenblicke einer armen Seele hin, die aus dem Licht in die Finsternis dahinter gerissen wurde. Sieh ganz genau hin - warum bist du hier, mein Freund? Hör dir das Flüstern an. Kannst du es verstehen? Hör ganz genau hin! ... Du ... erinnerst dich? Was weißt du noch von diesen letzten Tagen hier? Ich war nicht hier, um das zu tun, aber dich ... dich hat die Erinnerung wieder an diesen Ort geführt, oder? Du hast das hier getan ... Ich bin nicht mehr die Bestie, SONDERN DU.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La bestia: posso sentirti. Qualcosa ti attira in questa stanza, vero? Non l'ascesso, non io... No... La compassione non è il tuo forte. È la crepa nel muro che ti attira, eh? È la paura, la curiosità... O qualcos'altro? Quello che è successo qui è difficile da immaginare... Un portale si è aperto nel muro, dei solchi profondi sul pavimento, gli ultimi momenti di una povera anima trascinata nell'oscurità. Guarda più attentamente, perché sei qui? Ascolta i mormorii. Senti quello che dicono? Ascolta attentamente! ... Tu... Ti ricordi? Che cosa ti ricordi di questi ultimi giorni passati qui? Non sono stato io a fare tutto questo, ma tu... Sono i ricordi delle cose passate che ti hanno attirato qui, vero? La responsabilità di tutto questo è tua... Non sono più io la bestia, SEI TU.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La bestia: te siento. Te sientes atraído por esta habitación, ¿verdad? No por el absceso o por mí… no… no eres compasivo. Te atraen las rasgaduras de la pared. Te atrae el miedo, la curiosidad… ¿algo más? Apenas es posible imaginar lo que ocurrió aquí... un portal rasgó la pared, aparecieron hendiduras profundas en el suelo, los últimos momentos de una pobre alma arrastrada desde la luz hacia la oscuridad. Piénsalo bien, amigo mío, ¿por qué estás aquí? Escucha los susurros. ¿Oyes lo que dicen? ¡Escucha con atención! Te... ¿te acuerdas? ¿Qué recuerdas de los últimos días en la mansión? Yo no he estado aquí para hacerlo, pero tú... te sientes atraído por el recuerdo del pasado, ¿no es así? Tú has hecho esto... Yo ya no soy la bestia: LO ERES TÚ.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">野獣 - あなたがそこに居るの分かっている。この部屋に引き寄せられてきたのでしょう？腫瘍や私ではなく... 違う... あなたは同情するような人ではない。あなたは壁に隠れた恐怖や好奇心に引き寄せられてここへ来たのでは？それとも他に理由があるのでしょうか。こここでは誰にも想像できないことが起こりました... 壁を破る入口、床の深いへこみ、そして死の闇に葬られた哀れな魂。あなたはなぜここへ来たのですか？さあよく考えて。ささやきに耳を傾けて何を言っているかよく聞いてください。あなたは.... 憶えていますか？あなたがこの館で過ごした数日間に何がありましたか？過去の思い出によってここへ引き寄せれらましたよね？私は野獣であり、もうあなたではありません。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">짐승: 이해합니다. 당신은 이 방에 이끌려서 온 거죠, 안 그래요? 종기나 제게 이끌려 온 것이 아니라요… 아니겠죠… 당신은 동정심을 느끼는 부류는 아닌군요. 그래요. 당신은 벽 안에 세들어 사는 존재에게 이끌려 온거군요. 공포에 이끌려, 호기심에 이끌려… 아니면 다른 것에 이끌려서? 이곳에서 벌어진 일은 그 누구도 상상할 수 없는 일입니다… 벽이 찢어지며 생긴 차원문, 바닥의 깊은 자국. 빛에서 어둠으로 끌려들어온 불쌍한 영혼이 마지막 순간을 보내는 곳이죠. 자세히 보세요. 여기에 왜 온 건가요? 속삭임을 들어보세요. 그들이 얘기하는 것이 들리나요? 자세히 들어보세요! ... 당신... 기억하나요? 이곳에서의 지난 며칠 중에서 무엇이 기억에 남죠? 전 이런 것을 원하고 여기에 왔던 것이 아니었지만 당신은... 당신은 과거의 기억에 의해 이곳으로 이끌려 온 거예요, 그렇죠? 이렇게 만든 것은 바로 당신이군요... 전 더 이상 짐승이 아니에요. 바로 당신이죠.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Beast:  I can feel you. You are drawn here to this room are you not? Not to the abscess or to I... no... you are not the sort that is inclined to sympathy. You are drawn by the rent in the wall, yes. By fear, by curiosity... by something else? What happened here one can scarcely imagine... a portal ripped thru the wall, deep indentations in the floor, the last known moments of a poor soul as he is dragged from the light into the darkness beyond. Look closely, why are you here friend? Listen to the whispers. Can you hear what they are saying? Listen closely! ... You...do you remember? What do you recall from these last few days here? I was not here to do this but you... you are drawn here by remembrance of things past, aren't you? It was you who did this.. I am the beast no longer, IT IS YOU.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">野獸：我能感受到你。你被這個房間吸引的，不是嗎？而不是被膿腫或是我吸引……不……你可不是那種會同情他人的人。你是被牆上貼出的租金吸引來的。或是被恐懼、好奇心……還有別的什麽？這裡曾經發生的一切幾乎是無法想像的……牆上裂開的入口、地板上犬牙交錯的凹痕、某個可憐人從光明被拖進無盡黑暗時那已知的最後時刻。仔細看看吧，朋友。你爲什麽會在這裡？認真聽一聽那些低語。你能聽到他們在說些什麽嗎？仔細聽聽！……你……還記得嗎？過去幾天中這裡所發生的事你還能記得什麽？我在這裡什麽都沒做，但……透過回憶過去發生的事情，你被吸引到了這裡，不是嗎？是你做了這一切……我不再是怪獸了，現在你才是怪獸。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">野獸：我能感受到你。你被這個房間吸引的，不是嗎？而不是被膿腫或是我吸引……不……你可不是那種會同情他人的人。你是被牆上貼出的租金吸引來的。或是被恐懼、好奇心……還有別的什麽？這裡曾經發生的一切幾乎是無法想像的……牆上裂開的入口、地板上犬牙交錯的凹痕、某個可憐人從光明被拖進無盡黑暗時那已知的最後時刻。仔細看看吧，朋友。你爲什麽會在這裡？認真聽一聽那些低語。你能聽到他們在說些什麽嗎？仔細聽聽！……你……還記得嗎？過去幾天中這裡所發生的事你還能記得什麽？我在這裡什麽都沒做，但……透過回憶過去發生的事情，你被吸引到了這裡，不是嗎？是你做了這一切……我不再是怪獸了，現在你才是怪獸。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Beast:  I can feel you. You are drawn here to this room are you not? Not to the abscess or to I... no... you are not the sort that is inclined to sympathy. You are drawn by the rent in the wall, yes. By fear, by curiosity... by something else? What happened here one can scarcely imagine... a portal ripped thru the wall, deep indentations in the floor, the last known moments of a poor soul as he is dragged from the light into the darkness beyond. Look closely, why are you here friend? Listen to the whispers. Can you hear what they are saying? Listen closely! ... You...do you remember? What do you recall from these last few days here? I was not here to do this but you... you are drawn here by remembrance of things past, aren't you? It was you who did this.. I am the beast no longer, IT IS YOU.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">JournalFragment20</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bequethal: At first I maintained a hope that the manor was teaching me another of its lessons. One day it would decide the lesson had been learnt and it would release me from this terrible dark wound. But now you are here I realise this will not be the case. Here I will remain in these infernal bowels, welded forever to my past. The manor has brought you here, not I, and not as my guest but as my successor. All this, the rank carpets the stupid deer heads, the paintings, the stains, the stairs, the books and history, the cold room, the emanations, the beast, all this is now yours. If I were you, if you have any decency left in you I would drop everything - leave now, do not stop to think, pray it doesn't close the doors on you, trap you, entomb you forever like me, make you it's beloved. Go, GO- before it is too late-</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La succession — Au début j'ai nourri l'espoir que le manoir m'enseignait une autre de ses leçons. Un jour, il déciderait que la leçon était retenue et me libèrerait de cette terrible et sombre blessure. Mais maintenant que vous êtes ici, je réalise que ce ne sera pas le cas. Je vais demeurer ici, dans ces entrailles infernales, uni à jamais à mon passé. Le manoir vous a amené ici, pas pour moi, et pas comme mon hôte, mais comme mon successeur. Tout ceci, ces moquettes écœurantes, les têtes de cerfs ridicules, les tableaux, les taches, les escaliers, les livres et l'histoire, la chambre froide, les émanations, la bête, tout cela est à vous, désormais. Si j'étais à votre place, si vous avez encore un tant soit peu de décence, j'abandonnerais tout. Partez maintenant, ne vous arrêtez pas pour réfléchir, priez pour qu'il ne referme pas ses portes sur vous, vous piège, vous enterre pour toujours, comme il a fait avec moi, pour faire de vous son amour. Partez, PARTEZ, avant qu'il ne soit trop tard.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vermächtnis - Anfangs hatte ich noch die Hoffnung, dass der Landsitz mir nur wieder eine seiner Lektionen erteilen wollte. Eines Tages würde er zu dem Schluss kommen, dass ich meine Lektion gelernt habe, und mich aus dieser schrecklichen finsteren Wunde wieder entlassen. Doch jetzt, wo du hier bist, wird mir klar, dass das nicht geschehen wird. Ich werde in diesen infernalischen Eingeweiden bleiben, für immer an meine Vergangenheit geschweißt. Der Landsitz hat dich hierher geführt, nicht ich, und zwar nicht als meinen Gast, sondern als meinen Nachfolger. Das alles hier, die muffigen Teppiche, die dämlich glotzenden Hirschköpfe, die Gemälde, die Flecken, die Treppen, die Bücher und die Geschichte, der Kühlraum, die Erscheinungen, die Bestie, all das gehört nun dir. An deiner Stelle würde ich, wenn du noch einen Funken Anstand hast, alles stehen und liegen lassen - geh jetzt, halte nicht zum Nachdenken inne, bete, dass sich nicht die Türen vor dir schließen, dich einsperren und dich für immer bei lebendigem Leibe begraben und dich zum Liebsten des Landsitzes machen. Geh, GEH, bevor es zu spät ist ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lascito: inizialmente speravo che il maniero mi stesse insegnando un'altra lezione. Un giorno avrebbe deciso che la lezione era stata imparata e mi avrebbe liberato da questa terribile ferita oscura. Ma ora che tu sei qui, capisco che questo non è il caso. Resterò qui in queste viscere infernali, incatenato per sempre al mio passato. Il maniero ti ha portato qui, non io, e non come ospite ma come successore. Tutto questo, il tappeto, le stupide teste di cervo, i dipinti, le macchie, le scale, i libri e la storia, la stanza fredda, le emanazioni, la bestia, ora tutto questo è tuo. Se fossi in te, se ti resta ancora un po' di decenza, lascerei perdere tutto. Vattene ora, non fermarti a pensare, prega che il maniero non ti sbarri le porte, intrappolandoti qui per sempre, come è successo a me, e non faccia di te il suo amante. Vai, VAI, prima che sia troppo tardi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Legado: al principio tenía la esperanza de que la mansión me estuviera enseñando otra de sus lecciones. Un día decidiría que había aprendido la lección y me liberaría de esta terrible y oscura herida. Pero ahora que estás aquí entiendo que no va a ser así. Permaneceré en estas entrañas infernales, unido a mi pasado para siempre. La mansión, no yo, te ha traído hasta aquí, no para que seas mi invitado, sino mi sucesor. Todo esto, las repugnantes alfombras, las malditas cabezas de ciervo, los cuadros, las manchas, los libros y la historia, la cámara, los efluvios, la bestia, ahora todo es tuyo. Si estuviese en tu lugar, si me quedara algo de decencia, lo dejaría todo. Vete ahora, no te pares a pensar, reza para que no te cierre las puertas, te atrape, te confine para siempre como a mí, te haga su amante. Vete, VETE antes de que sea demasiado tarde.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">遺言 - 最初にお話ししたように、私は、この館から教訓を得ようと願っていました。いつの日か、この教訓によって過去の辛い傷が癒されると。しかし、今日あなたがここに居るかぎりそれは可能ではなくなりました。私は、一生自分の過去に縛られ、この地獄のような館の腹の中に残ります。ここにあなたを引き寄せたのは私ではなく、この館です。あなたは、ゲストとしてではなく私の後継者としてここへ来たのです。古臭いカーペット、馬鹿げた鹿野の剥製、絵画、染み、階段、本、歴史、寒い部屋、悪臭、野獣は全てあなたの物となるのです。もし私があなたなら、あるいは、あなたに少しでも良識があるならば、すべてを放棄して今すぐここを出ていきなさい。扉が閉まり、ここに一生閉じ込められ、葬られないよう願い、手遅れになる前に今すぐここを出るのです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">유산: 처음에는 저도 저택이 또 다른 교훈을 줄 거라는 희망을 가지고 있었습니다. 언젠가 저택도 제가 교훈을 얻었다는 것을 이해하고, 이 무섭고 어두운 상처로부터 절 풀어줄 거라고 생각했던 거죠. 하지만 이제 당신이 이렇게 온 걸 보고 제게 해방이란 것은 없다는 것을 깨닫게 됐습니다. 저는 이곳 지옥의 창자에 남아 제 과거에서 벗어나지 못할 것입니다. 당신을 이곳으로 불러들인 것은 제가 아니라 저택입니다. 제 손님이 아니라 제 상속자로 온 것이죠. 계급 카페트, 멍청한 사슴 머리, 그림, 얼룩, 계단, 책, 과거, 차가운 방, 방사물, 짐승, 이 모든 것은 이제 당신 것입니다. 제가 당신이라면 그리고 당신에게 약간의 선함이라도 남아있다면, 저는 당장 모든 것을 버리고 떠날 것입니다. 지금 당장 떠나세요. 생각하기 위해 멈추지 마세요. 문이 닫히고 갇혀서 저처럼 영원히 매장 당하지 않게 해달라고 기도하세요. 너무 늦기 전에 어서 가세요.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Bequethal: At first I maintained a hope that the manor was teaching me another of its lessons. One day it would decide the lesson had been learnt and it would release me from this terrible dark wound. But now you are here I realise this will not be the case. Here I will remain in these infernal bowels, welded forever to my past. The manor has brought you here, not I, and not as my guest but as my successor. All this, the rank carpets the stupid deer heads, the paintings, the stains, the stairs, the books and history, the cold room, the emanations, the beast, all this is now yours. If I were you, if you have any decency left in you I would drop everything - leave now, do not stop to think, pray it doesn't close the doors on you, trap you, entomb you forever like me, make you it's beloved. Go, GO- before it is too late-</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">遺贈：起初我還保有希望，莊園不過是想再給我一個教訓。總有一天它會覺得我受够了教訓而把我從這個可怕陰暗的傷口中釋放出來的。但是現在你來了，我意識到情況並非如此。我將留在這些與我的過去密不可分的地獄般的內臟中。把你帶到這裡的是莊園而不是我。而你的身份也不是我的客人而是我的繼任者。所有這一切，惡臭的地毯、愚蠢的鹿頭、油畫、污漬、樓梯、書籍和歷史、冷藏室、散髮出的氣味、野獸，這一切現在都是你的了。如果我是你，如果你還有尚未泯滅的正直良知，我會拋下一切 — 現在就離開，不要停下來思考，祈禱莊園不會在你面前把門關上繼而把你像我這樣永遠地禁錮、埋葬、變成它的玩物吧。快走，快走 — 在一切為時已晚之前。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">遺贈：起初我還保有希望，莊園不過是想再給我一個教訓。總有一天它會覺得我受够了教訓而把我從這個可怕陰暗的傷口中釋放出來的。但是現在你來了，我意識到情況並非如此。我將留在這些與我的過去密不可分的地獄般的內臟中。把你帶到這裡的是莊園而不是我。而你的身份也不是我的客人而是我的繼任者。所有這一切，惡臭的地毯、愚蠢的鹿頭、油畫、污漬、樓梯、書籍和歷史、冷藏室、散髮出的氣味、野獸，這一切現在都是你的了。如果我是你，如果你還有尚未泯滅的正直良知，我會拋下一切 — 現在就離開，不要停下來思考，祈禱莊園不會在你面前把門關上繼而把你像我這樣永遠地禁錮、埋葬、變成它的玩物吧。快走，快走 — 在一切為時已晚之前。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Bequethal: At first I maintained a hope that the manor was teaching me another of its lessons. One day it would decide the lesson had been learnt and it would release me from this terrible dark wound. But now you are here I realise this will not be the case. Here I will remain in these infernal bowels, welded forever to my past. The manor has brought you here, not I, and not as my guest but as my successor. All this, the rank carpets the stupid deer heads, the paintings, the stains, the stairs, the books and history, the cold room, the emanations, the beast, all this is now yours. If I were you, if you have any decency left in you I would drop everything - leave now, do not stop to think, pray it doesn't close the doors on you, trap you, entomb you forever like me, make you it's beloved. Go, GO- before it is too late-</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>