<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Uncharted 2 Nepalese Village</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Uncharted 2 : Village népalais</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Uncharted 2: Nepalesisches Dorf</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Uncharted 2: Villaggio nepalese</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aldea nepalí de Uncharted 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Uncharted 2 Nepalese Village</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Become the ultimate Fortune Hunter in this Nepalese Village based on the critically-acclaimed UNCHARTED 2: Among Thieves™. Can you find all the pieces to Mask Mayhem?  Will you beat the highscore in Torch Race?  Travel to the Nepalese Village and further explore the UNCHARTED universe.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Incarnez votre chasseur de trésors préféré dans ce village népalais tiré d'UNCHARTED 2: Among Thieves™. Trouverez-vous tous les morceaux dans Masque Mayhem ? Battrez-vous le record dans Relais de Torches ? Rendez-vous dans le village népalais pour découvrir un peu plus l'univers d'UNCHARTED.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Werden Sie zum ultimativen Schatzsucher in diesem nepalesischen Dorf nach dem Vorbild des hoch gelobten UNCHARTED 2: Among Thieves™. Können Sie alle Teile beim Maskenchaos finden? Schaffen Sie den Rekord beim Fackelrennen? Reisen Sie in das nepalesische Dorf und erforschen Sie die Welt von UNCHARTED weiter.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vesti i panni di un cacciatore di tesori ed esplora il Villaggio nepalese, basato sull'acclamato UNCHARTED 2: Il covo dei ladri™. Troverai tutti i pezzi del Volto di pietra? Otterrai il punteggio più alto in Gara di torce? Scoprilo subito esplorando il Villaggio nepalese, l'ultima novità dell'universo UNCHARTED.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conviértete en el cazafortunas definitivo en esta aldea nepalí basada en el elogiado UNCHARTED 2: El reino de los ladrones™. ¿Encontrarás todas las piezas del Caos enmascarado?  ¿Superarás el récord en la Carrera de antorchas?  Viaja hasta esta aldea nepalí y explora el universo de UNCHARTED.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Become the ultimate Fortune Hunter in this Nepalese Village based on the critically-acclaimed UNCHARTED 2: Among Thieves™. Can you find all the pieces to Mask Mayhem?  Will you beat the highscore in Torch Race?  Travel to the Nepalese Village and further explore the UNCHARTED universe.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>