<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wrangler - Dark Blue Short Sleeve Striped Polo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Wrangler — Polo rayé à manches courtes bleu foncé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wrangler - Gestreiftes Kurzarmpolo in Dunkelblau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Wrangler - Polo a strisce con maniche corte di colore blu scuro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Wrangler - Polo a Rayas Azul Oscuro de Manga Corta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Wrangler - Dark Blue Short Sleeve Striped Polo (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Wrangler - Dark Blue Short Sleeve Striped Polo (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Wrangler - Dark Blue Short Sleeve Striped Polo (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Wrangler - Dark Blue Short Sleeve Striped Polo (Men)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Summer favorite! Stylish polo shirt in a white and blue classic striped design, three button fastening at the neckline, and embroidered lettering at the left chest. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un favori de l'été ! Un polo stylé rayé bleu et blanc classique, trois boutons au col et inscription brodée sur la poitrine gauche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Lieblingsstück für den Sommer! Stylisches Poloshirt in klassichem weiß-blau-gestreiften Design, mit drei Knöpfen am Halsausschnitt und gestickter Aufschrift auf der linken Brust. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ideale per l'estate! Elegante polo dal design classico a strisce bianche e blu, allacciatura collo a tre bottoni e lettere ricamate sulla parte sinistra del petto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Un clásico del verano! Estiloso polo en un clásico diseño a rayas azul y blanco, tres botones en el cuello y letras bordadas en la parte izquierda del pecho. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>