<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dragosaur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Dragosaur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drachosaurus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dragosauro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dragosaurio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドラゴサウルス</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">드라고사우루스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">火恐龍</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">火恐龍</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dragosaur</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">From the ancient lost city of LOOTania comes the most dreaded creature that ever lived. With scales as black as night, it roams the land in search of prey. It’s the Dragosaur, our fire-breathing genetic mutation of the Lootosaurus. Careful, if she gets too close - Shoot her! Shoot her!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La créature la plus redoutable ayant jamais existé vient de la cité perdue de LOOTania. Avec des écailles aussi noires que la nuit, elle erre en quête d'une proie. C'est le Dragosaur, notre mutation génétique du Lootosaurus qui crache du feu. Attention, s'il s'approche - Tuez-le ! Tuez-le !  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aus der versunkenen antiken Stadt LOOTania stammt die gefürchtetste Kreatur, die es je gab. Mit Schuppen so schwarz wie die Nacht durchstreift es das Land auf der Suche nach Beute. Es ist der Drachosaurus eine feuerspeiende genetische Mutation des Lootosaurus. Seid vorsichtig, und wenn er zu nahe kommt - schießt! Schießt!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Arriva dalla antica città perduta di LOOTania la creatura più terrificante mai esistita. Vedrai le sue squame nerissime vagare in cerca di prede. Stiamo parlando del Dragosauro, draghetto sputafuoco risultato della mutazione del Lootosauro. Occhio eh! Se si avvicina troppo sparagli! Sparagli! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Desde la antigua ciudad perdida de LOOTania llega la criatura más temida que jamás ha existido. Con unas escamas negras como la noche, vaga por las tierras en busca de su presa: es el Dragosaurio, una mutación genética del Lootosaurus que escupe fuego. ¡Cuidado, si se te acerca demasiado, dispara! ¡Dispaaara! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">失われた古代の街LOOTタニアより史上最強の生物が登場。夜の暗闇のごとき真っ黒のウロコを備えて獲物を探し回る。それはドラゴサウルス、火を吹くLOOTサウルスの突然変異体。気をつけて…近づいてきたら、撃て！撃ってやれ！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">고대 도시 루타니아에서 온 인류 역사상 가장 위험한 생물이 여기 있어요. 비늘이 칠흑 같은 검정이고 먹이를 찾아 어슬렁거리며 돌아다니는 드라고사우루스예요, 루토사우루스의 변종으로 불을 뿜어내죠. 조심하세요, 너무 가까이 오면-쏘세요! 쏘세요!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">來自失落的史前城市路坦尼亞，世界上最令人恐懼的生物。有著和黑夜一樣黑的鱗片，遊走在地面上找尋獵物。她就是露多恐龍基因突變，會噴火的火恐龍。小心，如果她靠你太近，快攻擊她！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">來自失落的史前城市路坦尼亞，世界上最令人恐懼的生物。有著和黑夜一樣黑的鱗片，遊走在地面上找尋獵物。她就是露多恐龍基因突變，會噴火的火恐龍。小心，如果她靠你太近，快攻擊她！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">From the ancient lost city of LOOTania comes the most dreaded creature that ever lived. With scales as black as night, it roams the land in search of prey. It’s the Dragosaur, our fire-breathing genetic mutation of the Lootosaurus. Careful, if she gets too close - Shoot her! Shoot her! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>