<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wrangler - Sand Herringbone Worker Cap</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Wrangler — Casquette travailleur à chevrons couleur sable</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wrangler - Arbeits-Cap in Sand mit Fischgrätenmuster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Wrangler - Cappello da lavoro con design a spina di pesce di color sabbia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Wrangler - Gorra de Espiga de Obrero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Wrangler - Sand Herringbone Worker Cap (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Wrangler - Sand Herringbone Worker Cap (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Wrangler - Sand Herringbone Worker Cap (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Wrangler - Sand Herringbone Worker Cap (Men)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">In a subtle sandy shade, this worker cap features herringbone fabric and a flat top design. With stitch detail throughout the peak, this cap also features secure buckle fastening at the rear for a snug fit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Dans une teinte sable subtile, cette casquette de travailleur est fabriquée dans un tissu à chevrons et possède un dessus plat. Avec des coutures apparentes sur la visière, cette casquette présente également une fermeture à boucle à l'arrière pour un bon ajustage. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Arbeits-Cap mit einem dezenten Sandton hat ein Fischgrätenmuster und ein flaches Design. Neben Nahtdetails entlang der Oberseite hat dieses Cap außerdem einen sicheren Clipverschluss hinten für einen guten Sitz. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dalla delicata tonalità sabbia, questo cappello da lavoro presenta una trama  intessuta a spina di pesce con parte superiore piatta. Con cuciture a contrasto che corrono lungo tutta la visiera, il cappello presenta anche  fibbie di sicurezza che permettono di regolare l'allacciatura sul retro. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">En un sutil tono arenoso, esta gorra de obrero en tejido de espiga tiene un diseño  plano en la parte superior. Con bordado en la visera, esta gorra cuenta también con hebilla trasera para un ajustado más cómodo. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>