<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MiniBot: Battlebox Gadget Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble de gadgets MiniBot : Battlebox</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MiniBot: Battlebox Gadget-Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto di gadget MiniBots: Battlebox</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de dispositivos MiniBot: Battlebox</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MiniBot: Battlebox Gadget Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Maximize your MiniBots experience! This bundle contains male and female versions of the Rocket Boots clothing item, the Pulse Field Chair, Teleport Beacon, and Stealth Sofa furniture items and the Turret and Sentry Companions. BONUS: unlocks the following gadgets for use in MiniBots: Battlebox and MiniBots multiplayer:  Rocket Boots, Deployable Turret, Sentry Companion, Pulse Field, Teleport Beacon, and Stealth Field. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Profitez au maximum des MiniBots ! Cet ensemble contient les versions homme et femme des bottes fusées, le siège à champ pulsé, la balise de téléportation et le sofa de camouflage, ainsi que les compagnons tourelle et sentinelle. BONUS : déverrouille les gadgets suivants utilisables dans MiniBots : Battlebox et MiniBots multijoueur:  bottes fusées, tourelle déployable, compagnon tourelle, compagnon sentinelle, champ pulsé, balise de téléportation et champ de camouflage. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Maximieren Sie Ihr MiniBots-Erlebnis! Dieses Bundle enthält als Bekleidungsobjekt Raketenstiefel in der Herren-/Damenausführung, den Impulsfeld-Stuhl, die Teleportations-Leuchtbake sowie Tarnungssofa-Einrichtungsobjekte und die Turm- und Wachgefährten. BONUS: Schaltet die folgenden Gadgets für die Anwendung in MiniBots: Battlebox und MiniBots-Multiplayer-Modus frei:  Raketenstiefel, Einsetzbarer Turm, Wachgefährte, Impulsfeld, Teleportations-Leuchtbarke und Tarnungsfeld. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sfrutta al massimo i MiniBot! Questo pacchetto contiene le versioni maschili e femminili degli Stivali razzo, gli arredi di gioco Sedia con campo a impulsi, Faro teletrasporto e Divano dell'invisibilità e gli alleati Torretta e Sentinella. BONUS: sblocca i gadget seguenti per usarli in MiniBots: Battlebox e modalità multigiocatore di MiniBots: Stivali razzo, Torretta strategica, Sentinella alleata, Campo a impulsi, Faro teletrasporto e Campo di invisibilità. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Aprovecha al máximo tu experiencia MiniBots! Este paquete contiene versiones femeninas y masculinas de la ropa de Botas espaciales, la Silla de campo pulsante, el Faro de teletransporte y el Sofá sigiloso y los compañeros Torreón y Centinela. BONUS:  libera los siguientes dispositivos para utilizarlos en MiniBots: Battlebox y el modo varios jugadores de MiniBots:  Botas espaciales, Torreón listo para la acción, Compañero centinela, Campo pulsante, Faro de teletransporte y Campo sigiloso. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Maximize your MiniBots experience! This bundle contains male and female versions of the Rocket Boots clothing item, the Pulse Field Chair, Teleport Beacon, and Stealth Sofa furniture items and the Turret and Sentry Companions. BONUS: unlocks the following gadgets for use in MiniBots: Battlebox and MiniBots multiplayer:  Rocket Boots, Deployable Turret, Sentry Companion, Pulse Field, Teleport Beacon, and Stealth Field. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>