<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Avalon Keep</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avalon Forteresse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Avalon Festung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Avalon fortezza</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Avalon Fortaleza</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Avalon Keep</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Avalon Keep</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Avalon Keep</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Avalon Keep</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Avalon Keep</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Avalon Keep</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Avalon Keep is an impregnable fortress on your very own floating island. The magical  crystals of Avalon allow the landmass to stay afloat and power all the new technological advances that have swept the world of Avalon. Your Keep sets you apart as one of the nobility that have taken residence in the skies around Avalon. Master all the mini-games and share the wealth with the latest in gift machine technology. Can you unlock all the secrets of your Keep? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Avalon Forteresse est une forteresse imprenable sur votre île flottante très propre. Lescristaux magiques d'Avalon permettre à la masse pour rester à flot et la puissance de toutes les nouvelles avancées technologiques qui ont balayé le monde d'Avalon. Votre Forteresse qui vous distingue comme l'un de la noblesse qui ont pris résidence dans les cieux près de Avalon. Maîtrisez toutes les mini-jeux et de partager la richesse avec la dernière technologie de la machine cadeau. Pouvez-vous débloquer tous les secrets de votre Forteresse?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das halten Avalon ist eine uneinnehmbare Festung auf Ihre ganz eigene schwimmende Insel. Die Avalon magische Kristalle erlauben die Masse über Wasser zu halten und die Kraft aller neuen technologischen Fortschritte, die die Welt von Avalon gefegt haben. Ihr Verlies unterscheidet Sie als einer der Adel, die Residenz in den Himmeln der Nähe von Avalon nahm. Meistern Sie alle Minispiele und teilen den Reichtum mit der neuesten Maschinentechnik Geschenk. Kannst du die Geheimnisse deines halten?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mastio Avalon è una fortezza inespugnabile sulla vostra isola galleggiante molto personale. I cristalli magici Avalon permettono la messa a stare a galla e la forza di tutti i nuovi progressi tecnologici che hanno travolto il mondo di Avalon. La tua prigione si distingue come uno dei nobili che hanno preso residenza nei cieli vicino a Avalon. Domina tutti i minigiochi e condividere la ricchezza con il dono più recente tecnologia della macchina. Riesci a svelare i segreti del tuo Tenere?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La torre del homenaje Avalon es una fortaleza inexpugnable en su isla flotante propio. Los cristales mágicos Avalon permitir que la masa para mantenerse a flote y el poder de todos los nuevos avances tecnológicos que han barrido el mundo de Avalon. Su calabozo que le distingue como uno de los nobles que tomaron la residencia en el cielo cerca de Avalon. Dominar todos los minijuegos y compartir la riqueza con el don de la máquina más avanzada tecnología. ¿Puedes descubrir los secretos de tu fortaleza?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Avalon Keep[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Avalon Keep[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Avalon Keep is an impregnable fortress on your very own floating island. The magical  crystals of Avalon allow the landmass to stay afloat and power all the new technological advances that have swept the world of Avalon. Your Keep sets you apart as one of the nobility that have taken residence in the skies around Avalon. Master all the mini-games and share the wealth with the latest in gift machine technology. Can you unlock all the secrets of your Keep? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Avalon Keep[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Avalon Keep[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Avalon Keep is an impregnable fortress on your very own floating island. The magical  crystals of Avalon allow the landmass to stay afloat and power all the new technological advances that have swept the world of Avalon. Your Keep sets you apart as one of the nobility that have taken residence in the skies around Avalon. Master all the mini-games and share the wealth with the latest in gift machine technology. Can you unlock all the secrets of your Keep? [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>