<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tuscan Villa Mega Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Villa toscane méga pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Toskanische Villa: Megapaket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mega pacchetto Villa toscana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mega paquete Villa toscana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Tuscan Villa Mega Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">투스칸 빌라 메가 번들</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Tuscan Villa Mega Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">托斯卡納別墅豪華組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">托斯卡納別墅豪華組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Tuscan Villa Mega Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Available as a single purchase, the Tuscan Villa Mega Bundle includes the apartment, clubhouse, and furniture bundle for this space. Now you can enjoy everything this elaborate space has to offer! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Disponible en un seul achat, Villa toscane méga pack comprend l'appartement, chalet, et le faisceau de meubles pour cet espace. Maintenant, vous pouvez profiter de tout cet espace complexe a à offrir! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das "Toskanische Villa"-Megapaket ist als Einzelkauf erhältlich und beinhaltet das Apartment, das Clubhaus und das Möbelset für diesen Bereich. Jetzt kannst du alles erleben, was dieser vielfältige Bereich zu bieten hat! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Disponibile come un unico acquisto, il Mega pacchetto Villa toscana include l'appartamento, la sede del club e il pacchetto arredamento per questo spazio. Adesso potrai godere di tutto ciò che ha da offrire questo spazio ricercato! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Disponible como compra única, el mega paquete Villa toscana incluye el apartamento, la sede del club y un conjunto de muebles para este espacio. Ahora puedes disfrutar de todo lo que tiene que ofrecer este espacio tan elaborado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Available as a single purchase, the Tuscan Villa Mega Bundle includes the apartment, clubhouse, and furniture bundle for this space. Now you can enjoy everything this elaborate space has to offer! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">한 번의 구매로 모든 것을 제공하는 이 투스칸 빌라 메가 번들에는 다음 아이템이 포함됩니다.\n\n


●투스칸 빌라 아파트\n
●투스칸 빌라 클럽하우스\n
●투스칸 빌라 커피 테이블\n
●투스칸 빌라 소파\n
●투스칸 빌라 식물\n
●투스칸 빌라 의자\n
●투스칸 빌라 라운지 의자\n\n

이제 여러분은 이 화려한 스페이스가 제공하는 모든 것을 즐길 수 있습니다! *투스칸 빌라 클럽하우스 에 입장하려면 먼저 클럽을 구매해야 합니다.\n\n

*구매 후 각 아이템은 해당 카테고리에 추가됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Available as a single purchase, the Tuscan Villa Mega Bundle includes the following items.\n\n

・Tuscan Villa Apartment\n
・Tuscan Villa Clubhouse\n
・Tuscan Villa Coffee Table\n
・Tuscan Villa Couch\n
・Tuscan Villa Plant\n
・Tuscan Villa Chair\n
・Tuscan Villa Lounge Chair\n\n

Now you can enjoy everything this elaborate space has to offer! *Please note, in order to access the Tuscan Villa Clubhouse you will need to have purchased the Club Slot.\n
*When purchased, each item is added to its respective category.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">托斯卡納別墅豪華組合包。\n
本組合包包含：\n\n

●托斯卡納別墅公寓\n
●托斯卡納別墅聯盟俱樂部\n
●托斯卡納別墅咖啡桌\n
●托斯卡納別墅長沙發\n
●托斯卡納別墅盆栽\n
●托斯卡納別墅椅子\n
●托斯卡納別墅休息椅\n\n

現在你可盡享這個豪華空間！※請注意，要使用托斯卡納別墅聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。\n\n

※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別內。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">托斯卡納別墅豪華組合包。\n
本組合包包含：\n\n

●托斯卡納別墅公寓\n
●托斯卡納別墅聯盟俱樂部\n
●托斯卡納別墅咖啡桌\n
●托斯卡納別墅長沙發\n
●托斯卡納別墅盆栽\n
●托斯卡納別墅椅子\n
●托斯卡納別墅休息椅\n\n

現在你可盡享這個豪華空間！※請注意，要使用托斯卡納別墅聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。\n\n

※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別內。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Available as a single purchase, the Tuscan Villa Mega Bundle includes the apartment, clubhouse, and furniture bundle for this space. Now you can enjoy everything this elaborate space has to offer! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>