<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Double Time Paint Splat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Eclat de peinture Double Time</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Double Time Farbklecks</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Double Time - Schizzo di pittura</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salpicadura de pintura de Double Time</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Double Time Paint Splat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Double Time Paint Splat</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Those paintballers may be sneaky about leaving their mark, but you found them out! Visit the Lockwood Publishing Showcase for Double Time's full range of sportswear and merchandise. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ces paintballers sont peut-être sournois lorsqu'ils laissent leur marque, mais tu les as tout de même trouvé!  Visite l'exposition Lockwood Publishing pour la gamme complète de vêtements de sport et produits Double Time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese Paintballspieler mögen zwar raffiert beim Hinterlassen ihrer Markierungen sein, aber du hast sie entdeckt! Besuch die Lockwood Publishing Ausstellung um das gesamte Sortiment an Sportbekleidung und Merchandiseartikeln kennenzulernen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quelle palle di colore possono essere subdole e lasciare il segno, ma tu le hai scoperte! Visita lo showcase di Lockwood Publishing per la gamma completa di abbigliamento sportivo e articoli vari di Double Time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los jugadores de paintball son muy cautelosos, pero no siempre consiguen no dejar rastro. Visita la Muestra Lockwood Publishing para disfrutar de la gama completa de productos y ropa de deporte de Double Time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Those paintballers may be sneaky about leaving their mark, but you found them out! Visit the Lockwood Publishing Showcase for Double Time's full range of sportswear and merchandise. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Those paintballers may be sneaky about leaving their mark, but you found them out! Visit the Lockwood Publishing Showcase for Double Time's full range of sportswear and merchandise. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>