<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Radec's Combat Boots</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rangers de Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Radecs Kampfstiefel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stivali da combattimento di Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Botas de combate de Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">라덱 대령의 전투화</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Radec's Combat Boots</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Radec戰鬥軍靴</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Radec戰鬥軍靴</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Radec's Combat Boots</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Descr</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Frequently used to crush those who opposed him, Colonel Radec's combat boots are fitted with custom-designed toe and heel guards. The high-grip soles are fashioned from a sound-absorbing synthetic polymer, which further enhanced Radec's already formidable stealth abilities. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">s furtives de Radec. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Colonel Radecs Kampfstiefel wurden von ihm häufig eingesetzt, um seine Gegner zu zermalmen und sind mit speziell angefertigtem Zehen- und Fersenschutz ausgestattet. Die äußerst griffigen Sohlen sind aus geräuschabsorbierendem synthetischen Polymer gefertigt, das Radecs bereits vorzügliche Tarnung noch weiter verbesserte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Spesso utilizzati per schiacciare gli avversari, gli stivali da combattimento del colonnello Radec sono dotati di speciali protezioni rinforzate per tacco e punta. Le suole garantiscono la massima aderenza e sono ricavate da un materiale sintetico in grado di assorbire il suono, in questo modo Radec era in grado di agire furtivamente con maggior efficacia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Usadas con frecuencia para aplastar a sus opositores, las botas de combate del coronel Radec cuentan con protecciones a medida para los dedos y el talón. Las suelas, de alto agarre, están fabricadas con un polímero sintético que absorbe el sonido, lo que mejoraba más si cabe las ya formidables habilidades de sigilo de Radec. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">라덱 대령은 이 전투화를 사용하여 자신에게 항거하는 자를 짖밟았습니다. 발가락과 발뒷꿈치를 보호하는 장갑판과, 소음을 흡수하는 합성 폴리머 재질은 라덱 대령의 무시무시한 은폐 능력을 한층 강화시켰습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Frequently used to crush those who opposed him, Colonel Radec's combat boots are fitted with custom-designed toe and heel guards. The high-grip soles are fashioned from a sound-absorbing synthetic polymer, which further enhanced Radec's already formidable stealth abilities. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Radec上校經常使用他的戰鬥軍靴來踐踏他的反抗者，所以這對軍靴的腳趾和鞋跟部份經過特別強化。高度防滑的鞋底是以吸音的合成聚合物製成，進一步提升Radec本來已是無人能及的潛行技巧。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Radec上校經常使用他的戰鬥軍靴來踐踏他的反抗者，所以這對軍靴的腳趾和鞋跟部份經過特別強化。高度防滑的鞋底是以吸音的合成聚合物製成，進一步提升Radec本來已是無人能及的潛行技巧。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Frequently used to crush those who opposed him, Colonel Radec's combat boots are fitted with custom-designed toe and heel guards. The high-grip soles are fashioned from a sound-absorbing synthetic polymer, which further enhanced Radec's already formidable stealth abilities. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>