<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ninjutsu Warrior - Li'l Ninja</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guerrier Ninjutsu - P'tit Ninja</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ninjutsu-Krieger - Ninjachen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guerriero Ninjutsu - piccolo ninja</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guerrero Ninjutsu: minininja.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">忍者・リトル忍者</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">닌자 워리어 - 꼬마 닌자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ninjutsu Warrior - Li'l Ninja</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">忍者 - 小小忍者</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">忍者 - 小小忍者</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ninjutsu Warrior - Li'l Ninja</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The stealthiest of all companions. The perfect sidekick for when you are doing secret ninja stuff. Watch as he stays in your shadow before unleashing an attack on your foes. A perfect accessory for the Ninja that has everything. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le plus furtif de tous les compagnons. L’allié parfait pour vous adonner aux trucs secrets que font les ninjas. Il restera dans l’ombre avant d’attaquer vos ennemis sans pitié. L’accessoire parfait pour tout ninja digne de ce nom. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der beste Schleicher aller Begleiter. Der perfekte Kumpan, wenn du geheime Ninja-Sachen machst. Er verbirgt sich in deinem Schatten, bevor er deine Feinde angreift. Das perfekte Accessoire für den Ninja, der alles hat. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il più furtivo di tutti i compagni e un perfetto assistente per le tue azioni ninja segrete. Osservalo mentre attende nell'ombra il momento giusto per scatenare un attacco sui i tuoi nemici. Un accessorio perfetto per il Ninja completo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El compañero más silencioso. El compinche perfecto para cuando estás haciendo misiones secretas de ninja. Observa cómo te sigue, como una sombre, antes de atacar a tus enemigos. Un accesorio perfecto para el ninja que lo tiene todo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">最も隠密にキミを援助してくれる仲間だ。秘密の忍術を使うときに完璧なサイドキックをかましてくれる。敵に攻撃を与える前、キミの影についてきます。最強の忍者にぴったりのアクセサリーです。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">컴패니언 중 은신 능력이 가장 뛰어납니다. 비밀 닌자 활동을 할 때 완벽한 보조 캐릭터죠. 적에게 공격을 퍼붓기 전에 당신의 그림자에 숨어 있는 모습을 감상하세요. 모든 것을 가진 닌자에게 완벽한 액세서리입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The stealthiest of all companions. The perfect sidekick for when you are doing secret ninja stuff. Watch as he stays in your shadow before unleashing an attack on your foes. A perfect accessory for the Ninja that has everything. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">最神秘的隨身夥伴。從事秘密忍者活動的最佳同夥。在向敵人攻擊之前，會跟著你的影子移動。堪稱適合全副武裝忍者的完美裝飾。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">最神秘的隨身夥伴。從事秘密忍者活動的最佳同夥。在向敵人攻擊之前，會跟著你的影子移動。堪稱適合全副武裝忍者的完美裝飾。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The stealthiest of all companions. The perfect sidekick for when you are doing secret ninja stuff. Watch as he stays in your shadow before unleashing an attack on your foes. A perfect accessory for the Ninja that has everything. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>