<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Treasure Earring (Opal, Left Ear, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Boucle d'oreille trésor (opale, oreille gauche, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ohrring aus einem Schatz (Opal, linkes Ohr, Damen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Orecchino prezioso (opale, orecchio sinistro, donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Pendiente del tesoro (ópalo, oreja izquierda, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">宝のイヤリング（オパール・左耳・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">보석 귀걸이(오팔, 왼쪽 귀, 여성)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Treasure Earring (Opal, Left Ear, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">寶物耳環（蛋白石/左耳/女用)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">寶物耳環（蛋白石/左耳/女用)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Treasure Earring (Opal, Left Ear, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">This highly popular gem features a rainbow-coloured sparkle against a milk-white background. For the left ear. (Mohs hardness: 6)[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette pierre très populaire est d'un blanc laiteux et scintille comme un arc-en-ciel. Pour l'oreille gauche. (Échelle de Mohs : 6)[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser beliebte Edelstein zeichnet sich durch seinen regenbogenfarbenen Glanz auf milchweißem Hintergrund aus. Für das linke Ohr (Mohssche Härte: 6) [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Una gemma molto famosa con i colori dell'arcobaleno su uno sfondo bianco latte. Orecchio sinistro. (Durezza in scala Mohs: 6)[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Esta gema tan popular tiene un brillo arcoíris en un fondo lechoso. Para la oreja izquierda. (Dureza en la escala de Mohs: 6) [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">乳白色の地に虹色の輝きを持つ人気の高い宝石。左耳用。（モース硬度６）[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">유백색의 바탕에 무지갯빛을 지닌, 인기가 많은 보석. 왼쪽 귀 전용.(모스 경도6)[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">This highly popular gem features a rainbow-colored sparkle against a milk-white background. For the left ear. (Mohs hardness: 6)[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">這種奶白色的寶石散發著彩虹的光芒，很受歡迎。供左耳用。（摩斯硬度6）[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">這種奶白色的寶石散發著彩虹的光芒，很受歡迎。供左耳用。（摩斯硬度6）[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">This highly popular gem features a rainbow-coloured sparkle against a milk-white background. For the left ear. (Mohs hardness: 6)[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
