<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Conquest Boardshorts - Neo Lime (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Short de planchiste Conquest - Néocitron (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Conquest Boardshorts - Zitronengelb (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Conquest Short da mare Verde Neo Lime (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Conquest Bañador - Neo Lima (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">When domination is the call, the Conquest boardshort should be your first line of defense. You'll power through the sets with unrestricted movement. Plus, its rapid dry time will keep you from being dragged down. Details include an engineered print and a wave applique. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lorsque c'est l'appel de la domination, le short de planchiste Conquest doit être votre première ligne de défense. Vous brillerez pendant les manches en toute liberté de mouvement. De plus, son temps de séchage rapide vous empêchera de couler. Avec un motif design et un effet vague. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Angriff ist die beste Verteidigung - und die Conquest Boardshorts ist dabei Ihre beste Waffe. Damit powern Sie mit unbegrenzter Bewegungsfreiheit durch die Sets. Die extrem schnelle Trocknungszeit sorgt außerdem für höchsten Komfort beim Surfen.  Mit angepasstem Motiv und Wellenmuster. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quando si tratta di dominare le onde, gli short da mare Conquest saranno la tua prima linea di difesa. Cavalca le onde con la massima libertà di movimento. In più, grazie all'asciugatura rapida non verrai trascinato giù dal peso. I dettagli comprendono stampa ingegnerizzata e appliqué con l'onda. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuando la consigna es dominar o ser dominado, el bañador Conquest debe ser tu primera línea de defensa.  Te enfrentarás a lo que sea con total libertad de movimiento, y su secado rápido impedirá que te "hundas". Los detalles incluyen estampado localizado y motivo de la ola. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>