<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Flames Paint-job</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Peinture de guerre enflammée</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Flammen-Lackierung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Verniciatura a fiamme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pintura con llamas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">フレイムペイントセット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">화염 도장 세트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Flames Paint-job Set</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">船身油漆圖案：火焰組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">船身油漆圖案：火焰組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Flames Paint-job</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Show your ship's scorching fury with the Flames Paint-job! The Flames Pilot's Helmet is included, so you can heat it up on the go! This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Affichez la furie ardente de votre vaisseau grâce à cette peinture de guerre enflammée ! Le casque de pilote enflammé est inclus, vous pourrez donc transmettre votre chaleur partout! Ce lot comprend les versions homme et femme. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stelle mit der Flammen-Lackierung die lodernde Wildheit Deines Schiffs zur Schau. Der Pilotenhelm im Flammenmuster ist inklusive, so dass Du überall das Feuer lodern lassen kannst! Dieses Paket enthält sowohl männliche als auch weibliche Versionen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mostra la furia cocente della tua nave con la verniciatura a fiamme! Il casco in coordinato è incluso, per essere sempre pronti a far fuoco! Il pacchetto comprende sia la versione femminile sia quella maschile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Demuestra la furia abrasadora de tu nave con esta pintura con llamas! Se incluye el casco de piloto con llamas para que puedas calentar el ambiente donde vayas. Este paquete incluye las versiones masculina y femenina. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">フレイムペイント加工で怒りを表現しよう！フレイムペイントパイロット用ヘルメットも含まれているので、いつでも燃えたぎっていられる！\n※購入すると、ミニゲーム「ノーバス・プライム」内の戦闘機にこのペイント加工を施せます。\n\n本セットには、アバターのカスタマイズ用の以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n・フレイムペイントヘルメット（男性用）（頭）\n・フレイムペイントヘルメット（女性用）（頭）\n※購入すると、「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">화염 도장으로 여러분의 불타는 분노를 함선에 표현하십시오! 화염 장식 조종사 헬멧이 포함되어 있어 언제라도 불타오를 수 있습니다! 이 번들에는 남성용과 여성용이 모두 포함되어 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Show your ship's scorching fury with the Flames Paint-job! The Flames Pilot's Helmet is included, so you can heat it up on the go! This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">以火燄船身油漆圖案，顯示你的太空船正火冒三丈！附有火焰飛行員頭盔，讓你在旅途上繼續升溫！本組合包包括男用及女用頭盔。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">以火燄船身油漆圖案，顯示你的太空船正火冒三丈！附有火焰飛行員頭盔，讓你在旅途上繼續升溫！本組合包包括男用及女用頭盔。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Show your ship's scorching fury with the Flames Paint-job! The Flames Pilot's Helmet is included, so you can heat it up on the go! This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>