<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">U Love Green One-Shouldered Top (green)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Haut monomanche U Love Green (vert)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">One-Shoulder-Top von U Love Green (grün)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Top monomanica U Love Green (verde)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Top con hombro descubierto U Love Green (verde)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">U Love Greenワンショルダートップ（緑）(女性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">당신은 자연을 사랑해 한쪽 어깨 탑 (녹색, 여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">U Love Green One-Shouldered Top (Green, Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">你愛綠色單肩上衣（綠色/女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">你愛綠色單肩上衣（綠色/女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">U Love Green One-Shouldered Top (green)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Update your look with this asymetrical one-shouldered top. Its modern design will renew your style. Made from organic cotton, it gives you cozy comfort. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Donnez un coup d’éclat à votre look avec ce haut monomanche asymétrique. Son design moderne avivera votre style. Fabriqué à base de coton biologique, il vous procure un confort douillet. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lege dir mit diesem asymmetrischen, einschultrigen Top einen brandneuen Look zu. Sein modernes Design wird deinen Stil revolutionieren. Und das aus Biobaumwolle bestehende Material ist kuschelig weich und bequem. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scegli un look originale con questo top monomanica asimmetrico. Rinnova il tuo stile con questo design moderno e scegli il massimo comfort grazie al tessuto in cotone organico. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mejora tu look con este top con un hombro descubierto. Su moderno diseño renovará tu estilo. Hecho de algodón ecológico, da gusto ponérselo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このアシメトリーのワンショルダートップで違うあなたを表現しましょう。モダンなデザインが新しいスタイルを演出します。オーガニックコットン製なので、心地良い快適さを与えてくれます。by U Love Green[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">당신의 외모를 이 비대칭 어깨 탑으로 새롭게 하세요. 현대적인 디자인이 여러분의 스타일을 산뜻하게 바꿀 것입니다. 유기농 솜으로 만들어, 안락한 편안함을 제공합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Update your look with this asymetrical one-shouldered top. Its modern design will renew your style. Made from organic cotton, it gives you cozy comfort. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用這件不對稱的單肩上衣來令你的打扮煥然一新，其現代設計可為你的風格增添新鮮感。採用有機棉的質料，穿著舒適。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用這件不對稱的單肩上衣來令你的打扮煥然一新，其現代設計可為你的風格增添新鮮感。採用有機棉的質料，穿著舒適。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Update your look with this asymetrical one-shouldered top. Its modern design will renew your style. Made from organic cotton, it gives you cozy comfort. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>