<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Home Private Beta 2011 Souvenir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Home Private Beta 2011 Souvenir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Home Private Beta 2011 Souvenir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Home Private Beta 2011 Souvenir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Home Private Beta 2011 Souvenir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Home Private Beta 2011 Souvenir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Home Private Beta 2011 Souvenir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Home Private Beta 2011 Souvenir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Home Private Beta 2011 Souvenir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Home Private Beta 2011 Souvenir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Home Private Beta 2011 Souvenir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Thanks for participating in the 2011 Home Private Beta! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Thanks for participating in the 2011 Home Private Beta! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Thanks for participating in the 2011 Home Private Beta! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Thanks for participating in the 2011 Home Private Beta! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Thanks for participating in the 2011 Home Private Beta! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Thanks for participating in the 2011 Home Private Beta! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Thanks for participating in the 2011 Home Private Beta! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Thanks for participating in the 2011 Home Private Beta! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Thanks for participating in the 2011 Home Private Beta! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Thanks for participating in the 2011 Home Private Beta! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Thanks for participating in the 2011 Home Private Beta! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">disallowed_legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE] Quit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">disallowed_banner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Unable to Relocate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Unable to Relocate</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">disallowed_text</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You must be a member of the Private Beta Test to relocate.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You must be a member of the Private Beta Test to relocate.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">eula_legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] I Agree    [LEFTSTICK] Scroll Text    [DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] I Agree    [LEFTSTICK] Scroll Text    [DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">waiting_legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Waiting...    [LEFTSTICK] Scroll Text</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Waiting...    [LEFTSTICK] Scroll Text</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">eula_banner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You Must Read and Accept the EULA to Proceed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You Must Read and Accept the EULA to Proceed</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">already_seen_text</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [ACCEPT] to enter the Private Beta. After you've had a chance to explore, head to the "PlayStation® Home Private Beta" forum at www.community.us.playstation.com and give us your feedback.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Press [ACCEPT] to enter the Private Beta. After you've had a chance to explore, head to the "PlayStation® Home Private Beta" forum at www.community.us.playstation.com and give us your feedback.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">already_seen_legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Teleport Now    [DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Teleport Now    [DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">already_seen_banner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Access Granted</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Access Granted</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">eula_text</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Beta Test Agreement\n\nApril 1, 2011, Version 1.0\n\nPLEASE READ THIS ENTIRE BETA TEST AGREEMENT (“AGREEMENT”) AND INDICATE WHETHER YOU AGREE TO ITS TERMS BY CLICKING THE “I AGREE” BUTTON.  THIS AGREEMENT IS BETWEEN YOU AND SONY COMPUTER ENTERTAINMENT AMERICA LLC (“SCEA”) AND CAN BE ACCEPTED ONLY BY AN ADULT 18 YEARS OR OLDER.   IN ADDITION, YOU MAY BE SUBJECT TO ADDITIONAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SCEA OR THIRD PARTY PUBLISHER FOR CERTAIN BETA MATERIALS.  PLEASE REVIEW THOSE ADDITIONAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY.  IF YOU DO NOT MEET THE AGE REQUIREMENT, OR DO NOT AGREE TO ALL APPLICABLE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS OR DOWNLOAD ANY OF THE BETA MATERIALS.  OTHERWISE, YOUR ACCESS OR DOWNLOAD TO ANY BETA MATERIAL MEANS THAT YOU HAVE ACCEPTED ALL TERMS AND CONDITIONS.\n\n1. Beta Materials and Program. SCEA may provide you with software, documentation, and access to the beta program (“Beta Materials”) that is required for participation in the Beta Test Program for PlayStation® Home (“Program”). The Program may include Beta Materials published by SCEA or its third party publishers.  Participation in the Program is subject to the terms of this Agreement, and will require you to have access to the internet, and certain hardware and equipment which are not provided to you under the terms of this Agreement.  SCEA may terminate this Program at any time without cause or advance notice to you. \n\n2. Participant Feedback. You agree that SCEA or its authorized third parties may obtain information from you regarding the use of the Beta Materials or your participation in the Program, including information such as online or gaming communications, activities or feedback.  In addition, you agree that notwithstanding any selections you may have made previously to decline receipt of information, or be contacted by SCEA, SCEA or its authorized service provider may contact you to solicit information on your use of the Beta Materials in connection with this Program.  You also agree to provide reasonable information to SCEA or authorized service provider regarding your experiences using the Beta Materials, such as the usability of the Beta Materials.  Such information may include responding to questions, surveys or reporting bug problems.  All information you provide to SCEA or its authorized service provider in connection with the Program, including ideas or inventions collected by SCEA or its authorized service provider is referred to as “Feedback.” You agree that all Feedback (i) is your original idea or invention and provided by you to SCEA or its authorized service provider without payment, restrictions or conditions; (ii) once conveyed to SCEA or its authorized service provider, the Feedback becomes the property and confidential information of SCEA; (iii) that by virtue of the Feedback becoming SCEA’s property, SCEA may use or distribute the Feedback for any purpose in connection with Beta Materials or development of any other product or services, including disclosure of such information to affiliates, subsidiaries, or third party developers and publishers; and (iv) that SCEA may use and collect your personal information in connection with the Program in accordance with SCEA’s privacy policy. \n\n3. Ownership of the Program and Beta Materials. You understand that SCEA or its affiliates owns the Program and all of the Beta Materials, including all intellectual property rights therein. You shall keep the Beta Materials free of all security interests, liens, or other encumbrances. You may not copy, distribute, sell, lease, license, loan or otherwise transfer or dispose of any of the Beta Materials. You shall keep the Beta Materials in your possession, custody and control in your own home. You will not permit any third party to use or access the Beta Materials for any reason. You will be responsible for any loss or damage to the Beta Materials or to SCEA’s intellectual property rights therein, including the disclosure of such Beta Materials or any information pertaining to the Program to any third party.\n\n4. Confidential Nature of Beta Materials, Program. You acknowledge and agree that:\n\n(a) the Beta Materials and the Program are SCEA’s confidential information.  You agree that you will use the Beta Materials only in your home solely for the purpose of testing the Beta Materials in connection with the Program, and you will not transfer, distribute or disclose any of the Beta Materials, Feedback, or any information in connection with the Program to any third party, including to any public exhibition or display of such information;\n\n(b) the Beta Materials are not thoroughly tested and are pre-release materials which are not intended for public release;\n\n(c) the features provided in the Beta Materials may not be available in the final release;\n\n(d) the Beta Materials may be serially numbered for tracking purposes and traceable to you; and\n\n(e) disclosure of any part of the Beta Materials, Program, or Feedback to any third party, including the public, any trade or consumer press, news agency or any competitor of SCEA, will cause significant and irreparable harm to SCEA, the extent of which may be difficult to ascertain. Accordingly, you agree that SCEA shall be entitled to injunctive relief as well as all other legal remedies that may be available in the event you breach this Agreement.\n\n5. Participant’s Warrants and Representations. You warrant and represent that you:\n\n(a) have no physical condition, such as epilepsy or history of photosensitivity, that would be aggravated or triggered by playing video games; \n\n(b) knowingly agree to assume the risk that any latent physical defects you may have could be aggravated by participation in this Program;\n\n(c) will conduct yourself responsibly in regards to participation in the Program and treatment of the Beta Materials and Feedback, following a reasonable, common-sense code of conduct;\n\n(d) will not in any way cause harm to SCEA, its parent company, or any affiliates, subsidiaries, publishers, or other third parties;\n\n(e) agree that if you allow anyone else to use the Beta Materials, you accept responsibility for their acts, including any violations of this Agreement which could result in the termination of your  PlayStation® Network account;\n\n(f) will immediately notify SCEA if you become aware that the Beta Materials provided to you part of this Program are distributed or transferred to a third party, and you will use your best efforts to help recover such Beta  Materials and prevent any further loss of disclosure.\n\n(g) will not misappropriate any of the intellectual property of SCEA or any other party;\n\n(h) will not reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble the Beta Materials or engage in the unauthorized transfer, exhibition, export, import or transmission of programs and will not use any devices to circumvent any authentication schemes; and\n\n(i) will read and become familiar with the use of the appropriate PlayStation® system, and the warnings and instructions for any Beta Materials before any installation or setup of such Beta Materials. \n\n6. Limitations and Service. Some ISPs limit the number of devices that may be connected to the service. If you are unsure about your service terms, please contact your ISP.  \n\n7. Acknowledgment of Data Collection.  Some Beta Materials may contain software that uses a general form of authentication or “DNAS” (Dynamic Network Authentication System), a proprietary authentication system created by Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. (“SCEI”).  Such software program may retrieve information about a user’s hardware and software for authentication, copy protection, account booking, system, rules, game management and other purposes. The information collected does not identify the user personally. However, a software publisher can combine this information with information from its records if the user had provided personally identifying information to that publisher. Before providing any personal identifying information to a publisher, please be sure to review the publisher’s privacy policy and terms and conditions of use. Do not provide personally identifying information to a publisher unless you accept the conditions of use and terms of their privacy policy.\n\n8. No Guarantee of Server Uptime/Disclaimer.  SCEA and its subsidiaries or affiliates do not guarantee the continuous operation of the servers used in connection with this Program.  SCEA is not liable for your inability to use the Beta Materials or delay or failure of the servers to perform.  If you receive a message during login identifying an error, please contact SCEA Consumer Services at 1-866-466-5333.\n\n9. NO WARRANTIES AND REPRESENTATIONS.  THE BETA MATERIALS, THE PROGRAM, AND ANY SOFTWARE OR HARDWARE PROVIDED BY SCEA UNDER THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PROVIDED UNDER LAW, SCEA DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT.  WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, SCEA DOES NOT GUARANTEE THAT YOU WILL BE ABLE TO USE THE BETA MATERIALS ON OR OFFLINE, OR PARTICIPATE IN THE PROGRAM AT ANY TIME.  FROM TIME TO TIME, THERE MAY BE PROBLEMS RELATED TO ACCESS, DELAY OR FAILURE TO PERFORM THAT ARE BEYOND SCEA’S REASONABLE CONTROL. IN THE EVENT OF A DISPUTE REGARDING YOUR USE OF ANY OF THE BETA MATERIALS, HARDWARE, OR SOFTWARE, YOU AGREE THAT THE SOLE LIABILITY OF SCEA AND ITS AFFILIATED COMPANIES WILL BE LIMITED TO REPAIR OR REPLACEMENT OF THE BETA MATERIALS AT SCEA’S OPTION. AT ANY TIME, SCEA OR A PARTICIPATING PUBLISHER RESERVES THE RIGHT TO INCLUDE A SELF EXPIRING VERSION OF THE SOFTWARE OR CEASE HOSTING THE SOFTWARE OR PROGRAM AT ANY TIME. YOU AGREE THAT SCEA HAS NO LIABILITY FOR SUCH DISCONTINUANCE. ALL OTHER SOFTWARE NOT PUBLISHED BY SCEA IS THE SOLE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE NAMED PUBLISHER.  PLEASE CHECK THE PUBLISHER’S TERMS AND CONDITIONS ASSOCIATED WITH SOFTWARE BEFORE PLAYING.\n\n10. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY AND REMEDIES.  You agree that notwithstanding any damages that you might incur for any reason whatsoever (including all direct or general damages), the entire liability of SCEA and any of its affiliates under any provision of this Agreement and your exclusive remedy for all of the foregoing shall be limited to ten dollars ($10 U.S.).  The foregoing limitations, exclusions and disclaimers shall apply to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, even if any remedy fails of its essential purpose.  In no event shall SCEA or its affiliates be liable for any special, incidental, indirect, or consequential damages whatsoever.\n\n11. Term/Termination. You may terminate this Agreement at any time by deleting all electronic Beta Materials and providing written notification of your termination by sending an email to http://community.us.playstation.com/community/general_home/home_private_beta.  Your participation privileges may be terminated immediately if you fail to comply with any of the terms and conditions of this Agreement or if you fail to provide reasonable feedback in a timely manner. SCEA also reserves the right to terminate this Program at any time without cause.\n\n12.  Entire Agreement.   This Agreement is the entire understanding between you and SCEA concerning the Program. However, if you are a PlayStation Home Volunteer, you will also be subject to the terms of the PlayStation Home Community Volunteer Program Notice and Guidelines.  In the event of any conflict between this Agreement and the terms of a third party agreement, including their privacy policy, the terms of this Agreement shall prevail as between you and SCEA.\n\n13. Governing Law and Venue. You agree that the laws of the State of California shall govern the terms of this Agreement and your participation in the Program. You further agree that any action or proceeding relating to this Agreement shall be adjudicated in the courts of San Mateo County, California or the Northern District of California.\n\n14. Questions. Should you have any questions concerning this Agreement, please contact Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC, Legal Department, 919 East Hillsdale Boulevard, Foster City, CA 94404.  If you have questions regarding the Program, please contact Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC at http://community.us.playstation.com/community/general_home/home_private_beta.\n\nFor a printed copy of this Beta Agreement, please go to http://community.us.playstation.com/community/general_home/home_private_beta or  http://www.us.playstation.com/support/UserAgreements.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Beta Test Agreement\n\nApril 1, 2011, Version 1.0\n\nPLEASE READ THIS ENTIRE BETA TEST AGREEMENT (“AGREEMENT”) AND INDICATE WHETHER YOU AGREE TO ITS TERMS BY CLICKING THE “I AGREE” BUTTON.  THIS AGREEMENT IS BETWEEN YOU AND SONY COMPUTER ENTERTAINMENT AMERICA LLC (“SCEA”) AND CAN BE ACCEPTED ONLY BY AN ADULT 18 YEARS OR OLDER.   IN ADDITION, YOU MAY BE SUBJECT TO ADDITIONAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SCEA OR THIRD PARTY PUBLISHER FOR CERTAIN BETA MATERIALS.  PLEASE REVIEW THOSE ADDITIONAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY.  IF YOU DO NOT MEET THE AGE REQUIREMENT, OR DO NOT AGREE TO ALL APPLICABLE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS OR DOWNLOAD ANY OF THE BETA MATERIALS.  OTHERWISE, YOUR ACCESS OR DOWNLOAD TO ANY BETA MATERIAL MEANS THAT YOU HAVE ACCEPTED ALL TERMS AND CONDITIONS.\n\n1. Beta Materials and Program. SCEA may provide you with software, documentation, and access to the beta program (“Beta Materials”) that is required for participation in the Beta Test Program for PlayStation® Home (“Program”). The Program may include Beta Materials published by SCEA or its third party publishers.  Participation in the Program is subject to the terms of this Agreement, and will require you to have access to the internet, and certain hardware and equipment which are not provided to you under the terms of this Agreement.  SCEA may terminate this Program at any time without cause or advance notice to you. \n\n2. Participant Feedback. You agree that SCEA or its authorized third parties may obtain information from you regarding the use of the Beta Materials or your participation in the Program, including information such as online or gaming communications, activities or feedback.  In addition, you agree that notwithstanding any selections you may have made previously to decline receipt of information, or be contacted by SCEA, SCEA or its authorized service provider may contact you to solicit information on your use of the Beta Materials in connection with this Program.  You also agree to provide reasonable information to SCEA or authorized service provider regarding your experiences using the Beta Materials, such as the usability of the Beta Materials.  Such information may include responding to questions, surveys or reporting bug problems.  All information you provide to SCEA or its authorized service provider in connection with the Program, including ideas or inventions collected by SCEA or its authorized service provider is referred to as “Feedback.” You agree that all Feedback (i) is your original idea or invention and provided by you to SCEA or its authorized service provider without payment, restrictions or conditions; (ii) once conveyed to SCEA or its authorized service provider, the Feedback becomes the property and confidential information of SCEA; (iii) that by virtue of the Feedback becoming SCEA’s property, SCEA may use or distribute the Feedback for any purpose in connection with Beta Materials or development of any other product or services, including disclosure of such information to affiliates, subsidiaries, or third party developers and publishers; and (iv) that SCEA may use and collect your personal information in connection with the Program in accordance with SCEA’s privacy policy. \n\n3. Ownership of the Program and Beta Materials. You understand that SCEA or its affiliates owns the Program and all of the Beta Materials, including all intellectual property rights therein. You shall keep the Beta Materials free of all security interests, liens, or other encumbrances. You may not copy, distribute, sell, lease, license, loan or otherwise transfer or dispose of any of the Beta Materials. You shall keep the Beta Materials in your possession, custody and control in your own home. You will not permit any third party to use or access the Beta Materials for any reason. You will be responsible for any loss or damage to the Beta Materials or to SCEA’s intellectual property rights therein, including the disclosure of such Beta Materials or any information pertaining to the Program to any third party.\n\n4. Confidential Nature of Beta Materials, Program. You acknowledge and agree that:\n\n(a) the Beta Materials and the Program are SCEA’s confidential information.  You agree that you will use the Beta Materials only in your home solely for the purpose of testing the Beta Materials in connection with the Program, and you will not transfer, distribute or disclose any of the Beta Materials, Feedback, or any information in connection with the Program to any third party, including to any public exhibition or display of such information;\n\n(b) the Beta Materials are not thoroughly tested and are pre-release materials which are not intended for public release;\n\n(c) the features provided in the Beta Materials may not be available in the final release;\n\n(d) the Beta Materials may be serially numbered for tracking purposes and traceable to you; and\n\n(e) disclosure of any part of the Beta Materials, Program, or Feedback to any third party, including the public, any trade or consumer press, news agency or any competitor of SCEA, will cause significant and irreparable harm to SCEA, the extent of which may be difficult to ascertain. Accordingly, you agree that SCEA shall be entitled to injunctive relief as well as all other legal remedies that may be available in the event you breach this Agreement.\n\n5. Participant’s Warrants and Representations. You warrant and represent that you:\n\n(a) have no physical condition, such as epilepsy or history of photosensitivity, that would be aggravated or triggered by playing video games; \n\n(b) knowingly agree to assume the risk that any latent physical defects you may have could be aggravated by participation in this Program;\n\n(c) will conduct yourself responsibly in regards to participation in the Program and treatment of the Beta Materials and Feedback, following a reasonable, common-sense code of conduct;\n\n(d) will not in any way cause harm to SCEA, its parent company, or any affiliates, subsidiaries, publishers, or other third parties;\n\n(e) agree that if you allow anyone else to use the Beta Materials, you accept responsibility for their acts, including any violations of this Agreement which could result in the termination of your  PlayStation® Network account;\n\n(f) will immediately notify SCEA if you become aware that the Beta Materials provided to you part of this Program are distributed or transferred to a third party, and you will use your best efforts to help recover such Beta  Materials and prevent any further loss of disclosure.\n\n(g) will not misappropriate any of the intellectual property of SCEA or any other party;\n\n(h) will not reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble the Beta Materials or engage in the unauthorized transfer, exhibition, export, import or transmission of programs and will not use any devices to circumvent any authentication schemes; and\n\n(i) will read and become familiar with the use of the appropriate PlayStation® system, and the warnings and instructions for any Beta Materials before any installation or setup of such Beta Materials. \n\n6. Limitations and Service. Some ISPs limit the number of devices that may be connected to the service. If you are unsure about your service terms, please contact your ISP.  \n\n7. Acknowledgment of Data Collection.  Some Beta Materials may contain software that uses a general form of authentication or “DNAS” (Dynamic Network Authentication System), a proprietary authentication system created by Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. (“SCEI”).  Such software program may retrieve information about a user’s hardware and software for authentication, copy protection, account booking, system, rules, game management and other purposes. The information collected does not identify the user personally. However, a software publisher can combine this information with information from its records if the user had provided personally identifying information to that publisher. Before providing any personal identifying information to a publisher, please be sure to review the publisher’s privacy policy and terms and conditions of use. Do not provide personally identifying information to a publisher unless you accept the conditions of use and terms of their privacy policy.\n\n8. No Guarantee of Server Uptime/Disclaimer.  SCEA and its subsidiaries or affiliates do not guarantee the continuous operation of the servers used in connection with this Program.  SCEA is not liable for your inability to use the Beta Materials or delay or failure of the servers to perform.  If you receive a message during login identifying an error, please contact SCEA Consumer Services at 1-866-466-5333.\n\n9. NO WARRANTIES AND REPRESENTATIONS.  THE BETA MATERIALS, THE PROGRAM, AND ANY SOFTWARE OR HARDWARE PROVIDED BY SCEA UNDER THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PROVIDED UNDER LAW, SCEA DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT.  WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, SCEA DOES NOT GUARANTEE THAT YOU WILL BE ABLE TO USE THE BETA MATERIALS ON OR OFFLINE, OR PARTICIPATE IN THE PROGRAM AT ANY TIME.  FROM TIME TO TIME, THERE MAY BE PROBLEMS RELATED TO ACCESS, DELAY OR FAILURE TO PERFORM THAT ARE BEYOND SCEA’S REASONABLE CONTROL. IN THE EVENT OF A DISPUTE REGARDING YOUR USE OF ANY OF THE BETA MATERIALS, HARDWARE, OR SOFTWARE, YOU AGREE THAT THE SOLE LIABILITY OF SCEA AND ITS AFFILIATED COMPANIES WILL BE LIMITED TO REPAIR OR REPLACEMENT OF THE BETA MATERIALS AT SCEA’S OPTION. AT ANY TIME, SCEA OR A PARTICIPATING PUBLISHER RESERVES THE RIGHT TO INCLUDE A SELF EXPIRING VERSION OF THE SOFTWARE OR CEASE HOSTING THE SOFTWARE OR PROGRAM AT ANY TIME. YOU AGREE THAT SCEA HAS NO LIABILITY FOR SUCH DISCONTINUANCE. ALL OTHER SOFTWARE NOT PUBLISHED BY SCEA IS THE SOLE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE NAMED PUBLISHER.  PLEASE CHECK THE PUBLISHER’S TERMS AND CONDITIONS ASSOCIATED WITH SOFTWARE BEFORE PLAYING.\n\n10. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY AND REMEDIES.  You agree that notwithstanding any damages that you might incur for any reason whatsoever (including all direct or general damages), the entire liability of SCEA and any of its affiliates under any provision of this Agreement and your exclusive remedy for all of the foregoing shall be limited to ten dollars ($10 U.S.).  The foregoing limitations, exclusions and disclaimers shall apply to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, even if any remedy fails of its essential purpose.  In no event shall SCEA or its affiliates be liable for any special, incidental, indirect, or consequential damages whatsoever.\n\n11. Term/Termination. You may terminate this Agreement at any time by deleting all electronic Beta Materials and providing written notification of your termination by sending an email to http://community.us.playstation.com/community/general_home/home_private_beta.  Your participation privileges may be terminated immediately if you fail to comply with any of the terms and conditions of this Agreement or if you fail to provide reasonable feedback in a timely manner. SCEA also reserves the right to terminate this Program at any time without cause.\n\n12.  Entire Agreement.   This Agreement is the entire understanding between you and SCEA concerning the Program. However, if you are a PlayStation Home Volunteer, you will also be subject to the terms of the PlayStation Home Community Volunteer Program Notice and Guidelines.  In the event of any conflict between this Agreement and the terms of a third party agreement, including their privacy policy, the terms of this Agreement shall prevail as between you and SCEA.\n\n13. Governing Law and Venue. You agree that the laws of the State of California shall govern the terms of this Agreement and your participation in the Program. You further agree that any action or proceeding relating to this Agreement shall be adjudicated in the courts of San Mateo County, California or the Northern District of California.\n\n14. Questions. Should you have any questions concerning this Agreement, please contact Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC, Legal Department, 919 East Hillsdale Boulevard, Foster City, CA 94404.  If you have questions regarding the Program, please contact Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC at http://community.us.playstation.com/community/general_home/home_private_beta.\n\nFor a printed copy of this Beta Agreement, please go to http://community.us.playstation.com/community/general_home/home_private_beta or  http://www.us.playstation.com/support/UserAgreements.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>