<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">StationIntro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">StationIntro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">StationIntro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">StationIntro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">StationIntro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">StationIntro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">StationIntro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">StationIntro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">StationIntro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">StationIntro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">StationIntro</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Introduction to the Novus Prime station [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Introduction to the Novus Prime station [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Introduction to the Novus Prime station [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Introduction to the Novus Prime station [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Introduction to the Novus Prime station [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Introduction to the Novus Prime station [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Introduction to the Novus Prime station [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Introduction to the Novus Prime station [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Introduction to the Novus Prime station [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Introduction to the Novus Prime station [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Introduction to the Novus Prime station [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kLanguage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">en</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">fr</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">de</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">it</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">es</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ja</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">ko</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">en</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">zh-HK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">zh-TW</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">en</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_001</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Pilot! If you’re available, report to the nearest launch console. We need another fighter for an important mission that’s just getting underway.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pilote ! Si vous êtes disponible, rendez vous à la base de lancement la plus proche. Nous avons besoin d'un nouveau combattant pour une importante mission qui vient de démarrer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Pilot! Wenn Sie einsatzfähig sind, dann melden Sie sich an der nächstgelegenen Konsole. Wir brauchen für eine Mission, die gerade im Gange ist, einen weiteren Jäger.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pilota! Se sei libero, contatta la torre di controllo più vicina. Ci serve un altro caccia per un'importante missione che sta per cominciare.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Piloto! Si estás disponible, repórtate a la consola de lanzamiento más cercana. Necesitamos a otro combatiente para una misión importante que se está llevando a cabo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">パイロット！もし手が空いているのなら近くにある発進台まで報告せよ。重要なミッションが開始するのだが、もう一人戦闘員が必要だ。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">현재 출격이 가능한 조종사는 즉시 인근 임무 시작 콘솔로 이동해라! 현재 진행 중인 중요한 임무에 지원할 전투기가 필요하다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Pilot! If you’re available, report to the nearest launch console. We need another fighter for an important mission that’s just getting underway.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">飛行員！如你有空，請到最近的發射控制台報到。我們需要一名飛行員參與正在進行的重要任務。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">飛行員！如你有空，請到最近的發射控制台報到。我們需要一名飛行員參與正在進行的重要任務。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Pilot! If you’re available, report to the nearest launch console. We need another fighter for an important mission that’s just getting underway.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_002</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to Novus Prime, we are glad to have you aboard.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue sur Novus Prime. Nous sommes heureux de vous avoir à bord.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen auf Novus Prime, wir sind froh Sie an Bord zu haben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuto sulla Novus Prime, è un piacere averti a bordo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido a Novus Prime, estamos felices de tenerte a bordo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムにようこそ。君を仲間に迎えられることを誇らしく思う。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임에 승선하신 것을 환영합니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Welcome to Novus Prime, we are glad to have you aboard.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">歡迎來到Novus Prime，很高興你參與這趟旅程。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">歡迎來到Novus Prime，很高興你參與這趟旅程。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome to Novus Prime, we are glad to have you aboard.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_003</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome back, Recruit.  It’s good to see you again.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Content de vous revoir, recrue.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen zurück, Rekrut. Es ist schön, Sie wieder zu sehen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bentornato, Recluta. Sono felice di rivederti.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido de nuevo, recluta. Es bueno verte de nuevo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">お帰り、新米。よく戻ってきたな。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">어서와라. 다시 만나 반갑다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Welcome back, Recruit.  It’s good to see you again.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">新成員，歡迎回來。能再看到你真好。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">新成員，歡迎回來。能再看到你真好。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome back, Recruit.  It’s good to see you again.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_004</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome back, Private.  Are you ready for your next mission?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Content de vous revoir, soldat. Êtes-vous prêt pour votre prochaine mission ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen zurück, Private. Sind Sie bereit für die nächste Mission?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bentornato, Soldato. Sei pronto per la tua prossima missione?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido de nuevo, soldado. ¿Estás listo para tu próxima misión?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">お帰り、一等兵。次のミッションの覚悟はできたか？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">어서 오세요. 다음 임무를 시작할 준비는 되었습니까?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Welcome back, Private.  Are you ready for your next mission?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">士兵，歡迎回來。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">士兵，歡迎回來。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome back, Private.  Are you ready for your next mission?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_005</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome back, Airman.  Give those Bots hell.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Content de vous revoir, pilote. Faites souffrir ces droîdes !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen zurück, Airman. Heizen Sie Ihnen ordentlich ein.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bentornato, Aviere. Fai a pezzi quei Robot!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido de nuevo, piloto. Has sufrir a esos robots.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">お帰り、航空兵。ボットをぶちのめそうぜ。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">어서 오십시오. 봇들에게 지옥을 맛 보여주십시오.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Welcome back, Airman.  Give those Bots hell.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">航空兵，歡迎回來。令那些機械人生不如死吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">航空兵，歡迎回來。令那些機械人生不如死吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome back, Airman.  Give those Bots hell.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_006</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome back, Captain.  We are awaiting your orders.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Content de vous revoir, capitaine. Nous attendons vos ordres.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen zurück, Captain. Wir warten auf Ihre Befehle.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bentornato, Capitano. Attendiamo i suoi ordini.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido de nuevo, capitán. Estamos esperando sus órdenes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">お帰りなさい、キャプテン。命令があれば何なりと。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">충성. 명령 대기 중.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Welcome back, Captain.  We are awaiting your orders.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">隊長，歡迎回來。我們在等候你的指示。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">隊長，歡迎回來。我們在等候你的指示。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome back, Captain.  We are awaiting your orders.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_007</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Attention recruits: You will receive an armored jacket upon reaching the rank of Private. From there, additional items will be awarded as you progress further through the ranks.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Votre attention, les recrues. Vous recevrez une veste blindée après avoir atteint le grade de soldat. Par la suite, de nouveaux items seront disponibles à mesure que vous obtenez de nouveaux rangs.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aufgepasst Rekruten: Sie erhalten eine gepanzerte Jacke, wenn Sie den Rang eines Private erreichen. Ab diesem Rang erhalten Sie für jeden weiteren Aufstieg zusätzliche Belohnungen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Reclute, attenzione: ottenendo il grado di Soldato riceverete una corazza. In seguito, riceverete altri oggetti avanzando di grado in grado.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Atención reclutas: Recibiréis una chaqueta blindada cuando alcancéis el rango de soldado. En adelante, seréis premiados con artículos adicionales cuando alcancéis nuevos rangos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">新米への注意：一等兵のランクまでいけば装甲ジャケットが支給される。そこから更にランクが上がるたびにアイテムが追加されるぞ。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">주목하라, 신병. 이등병 계급으로 진급함에 따라 방탄 자켓이 제공될 것이다. 앞으로도 계급이 상승하면 새로운 보상이 주어질 것이다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Attention recruits: You will receive an armored jacket upon reaching the rank of Private. From there, additional items will be awarded as you progress further through the ranks.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">新成員注意：升級為士兵後，你將獲得裝甲外套。繼續晉升，你將可獲得額外道具作獎勵。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">新成員注意：升級為士兵後，你將獲得裝甲外套。繼續晉升，你將可獲得額外道具作獎勵。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Attention recruits: You will receive an armored jacket upon reaching the rank of Private. From there, additional items will be awarded as you progress further through the ranks.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_008</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A bounty has been added for the defeat of enemy ships. Payout is added to your account instantly, so please proceed to the central consoles and Join the fight!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une prime est versée en cas de défaite des vaisseaux ennemis. Le paiement s'effectue instantanément donc rendez vous aux consoles centrales et rejoignez la lutte !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Kopfgeld wurde auf das Abschießen von feindlichen Schiffen ausgesetzt. Der Betrag wird umgehend ausgezahlt, bitte begeben Sie sich zur Hauptkonsole und nehmen Sie am Kampf Teil.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai incassato una taglia per la sconfitta della nave nemica. Il compenso ti viene accreditato sul conto all'istante, quindi ti prego di procedere verso la console centrale e di partecipare al combattimento!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una recompensa ha sido agregada por vencer naves enemigas. Los fondos son agregados a tu cuenta instantáneamente, por favor proceda a la central de consolas y ¡únase a la batalla!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">敵戦艦破壊で得られるネブロンが増えたぞ。君の口座に早速振り込まれたから中央コンソールで手続きをして戦闘に参加しよう！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">적군 함선 파괴에 포상금이 추가되었습니다. 완수 보수는 즉시 계좌로 전송됩니다. 여러분도 이제 중앙 콘솔을 통해 전투에 참가하십시오!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A bounty has been added for the defeat of enemy ships. Payout is added to your account instantly, so please proceed to the central consoles and Join the fight!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">成功打倒敵方的戰鬥機所獲得的獎金會馬上存入你的戶口，請前往中央控制台然後參加戰爭！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">成功打倒敵方的戰鬥機所獲得的獎金會馬上存入你的戶口，請前往中央控制台然後參加戰爭！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A bounty has been added for the defeat of enemy ships. Payout is added to your account instantly, so please proceed to the central consoles and Join the fight!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_009</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The commercially-sold stealth fighter known as the Kunai has been approved for use on Earth Fleet missions. This ship can be purchased at the kiosks within the station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le chasseur furtif vendu sous le nom de Kunai a été approuvé pour les missions de la Flotte Terrestre. Ce vaisseau peut être acheté dans les kiosques au sein de la station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der kommerziell erhältliche Tarnkappenjäger, bekannt als Kunai, ist einsatzfähig für Missionen in der Erd-Flotte. Der Jäger kann im Laden der Station erworben werden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I caccia stealth in commercio conosciuti come Kunai sono stati approvati per l'utilizzo nelle missioni delle truppe di terra. Questo velivolo può esser acquistato presso i chioschi all'interno della stazione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El avión furtivo comercial llamado Kunai ha sido aprobado para ser usado en las misiones de la Flota de la Tierra. Esta nave puede ser comprada en los quioscos dentro de la estación.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">クナイという名の市販用ステルス戦闘機は地球軍のミッションでの使用が許可された。この船はステーション内にあるキオスクで購入可能。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">유료 함선인 기습용 기체 쿠나이가 지구 함대 임무에서 사용할 수 있게 되었습니다. 이 기체는 정거장 내의 상점에서 구입할 수 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The commercially-sold stealth fighter known as the Kunai has been approved for use on Earth Fleet missions. This ship can be purchased at the kiosks within the station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">公開發售的Kunai隱形戰鬥機已獲准在地球艦隊的任務裡使用。你可在太空站的商店裡購買。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">公開發售的Kunai隱形戰鬥機已獲准在地球艦隊的任務裡使用。你可在太空站的商店裡購買。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The commercially-sold stealth fighter known as the Kunai has been approved for use on Earth Fleet missions. This ship can be purchased at the kiosks within the station.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_010</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Codebreaker, a ship capable of reprogramming enemy vessels, is now available for sale in the workshop, as well as the store kiosks within the station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Codebreaker, un navire capable de reprogrammer les vaisseaux ennemis, est maintenant en vente à l'atelier ainsi que dans les kiosques de la station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Codebreaker, ein Jäger, der feindliche Schiffe umprogrammieren kann, ist sowohl in der Werkstatt als auch im Laden der Station zum Kauf erhältlich.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Codebreaker, un velivolo in grado di riprogrammare le unità nemiche, è ora disponibile presso l'officina e i chioschi all'interno della stazione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Codebreaker, es una nave capaz de reprogramar a navíos enemigos, está disponible a la venta en el taller, así como en los quioscos tienda en la estación.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コードブレイカーは敵の船を再プログラムすることができる。ワークショップでもステーション内にあるキオスクでも購入可能。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">적 함선의 정보를 수정할 수 있는 코드 브레이커를 이제 작업장에서 구입할 수 있습니다. 또한 정거장 내의 상점에서도 구입할 수 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Codebreaker, a ship capable of reprogramming enemy vessels, is now available for sale in the workshop, as well as the store kiosks within the station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Codebreaker太空船能改寫敵方戰鬥機的電腦程式。現於工作坊及太空站的商店裡發售。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Codebreaker太空船能改寫敵方戰鬥機的電腦程式。現於工作坊及太空站的商店裡發售。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Codebreaker, a ship capable of reprogramming enemy vessels, is now available for sale in the workshop, as well as the store kiosks within the station.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_011</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Turbo-Matrix Speed Booster has been approved by the Novus Prime safety commission. This upgrade increases the top speed of any fighter ship considerably.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le boost Turbo-Matrix a été approuvé par la commission de sécurité de Novus Prime. Cette amélioration augmente considérablement la vitesse de pointe de tout vaisseau de combat.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Turbo-Matrix-Geschwindigkeitsverstärker wurde von der Novus Prime Sicherheitskommission genehmigt. Das Upgrade erhöht die Topgeschwindigkeit eines jeden Jägers erheblich.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'acceleratore turbo-matrix è stato approvato dalla commissione di sicurezza della Novus Prime. Questa modifica aumenta notevolmente la velocità massima di ogni unità.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El acelerador de velocidad Turbo-Matrix ha sido aprobado por la comisión de seguridad de Novus Prime. Esta mejora incrementa considerablemente la velocidad máxima de cualquier nave de batalla.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ターボマトリックス加速ブースターがノーバス・プライム安全委員会により許可された。このアップグレードにより戦闘機のスピードが大幅にアップされる。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">터보 매트릭스 속도증폭기가 노부스 프라임 안전 위원회의 검수를 마쳤습니다. 이 업그레이드는 모든 함선의 최고 속도를 크게 상승시킵니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Turbo-Matrix Speed Booster has been approved by the Novus Prime safety commission. This upgrade increases the top speed of any fighter ship considerably.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">渦輪裝置速度增幅器已獲得Novus Prime安全委員會認可，能大幅提升任何戰鬥機的最高速度。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">渦輪裝置速度增幅器已獲得Novus Prime安全委員會認可，能大幅提升任何戰鬥機的最高速度。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Turbo-Matrix Speed Booster has been approved by the Novus Prime safety commission. This upgrade increases the top speed of any fighter ship considerably.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_012</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Ion Beam has passed all required safety inspections. This turret-mounted cannon can be purchased at the workshop, as well as the store kiosks within the station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Faisceau à Ion a passé toutes les inspections de sécurité requises. Cette tourelle-canon peut être achetée à l'atelier ainsi que dans les kiosques de la station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Ionenstrahler hat allen notwendingen Sicherheitsüberprüfungen standgehalten. Dieser Geschützturm ist sowohl in der Werkstatt als auch im Laden der Station zum Kauf erhältlich.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il raggio a ioni ha passato tutti i test di sicurezza obbligatori. Questo cannone su torretta può esser acquistato presso l'officina e i chioschi all'interno della stazione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El rayo de Iones ha pasado todas las inspecciones de seguridad necesarias. Estos cañones montados en las torres pueden ser comprados en el taller, así como en los quioscos tienda en la estación.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">イオンビームはあらゆる安全検査に合格した。このタレットに装備する大砲はワークショップやステーション内にあるキオスクで購入可能。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이온 광선이 모든 안전 검수를 통과했습니다. 이 포탑은 작업장 또는 정거장 내의 상점에서 구입할 수 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Ion Beam has passed all required safety inspections. This turret-mounted cannon can be purchased at the workshop, as well as the store kiosks within the station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">離子光束已通過了所有安全測試。你可在工作坊及太空站的商店裡購買這個配備迴轉砲塔的大炮。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">離子光束已通過了所有安全測試。你可在工作坊及太空站的商店裡購買這個配備迴轉砲塔的大炮。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Ion Beam has passed all required safety inspections. This turret-mounted cannon can be purchased at the workshop, as well as the store kiosks within the station.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_013</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A swarm of parasitic crawlers is attacking the station's hull.  All available hands should procure a blaster pistol and proceed to the Spacewalk entrance at the center of the station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un essaim de robots parasites s'attaque à la coque de la station. Toutes les mains disponibles doivent se procurer un pistolet blaster et se rendre à l'accès vers l'Espace se trouvant au milieu de la station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Schwarm von Parasiten greift die Außenhülle der Station an. Jeder der eine freie Hand hat, sollte sich eine Strahlenpistole nehmen und zum Weltraumausgang im Zentrum der Station gehen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una schiera di parassiti cingolati sta attaccando lo scafo della base. Tutti gli uomini disponibili devono procurarsi una pistola Blaster e dirigersi all'entrata Spacewalk al centro della stazione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un enjambre de robots parásitos está atacando el casco de la estación. Todo el personal disponible deben obtener una arma desintegradora y proceder a la puerta de caminata espacial en el centro de la estación.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">寄生虫系ロボットの大群がステーションの船体を攻撃中。手が空いているもの全員ブラスターピストルを調達しステーションの中央にあるスペースウォークの入り口まで進むのだ。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">크롤러 무리가 정거장 선체를 공격하고 있습니다. 모든 여유 인력은 블래스터 권총을 장착하고, 정거장 중앙에 위치한 우주유영 입구로 이동해주십시오.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A swarm of parasitic crawlers is attacking the station's hull.  All available hands should procure a blaster pistol and proceed to the Spacewalk entrance at the center of the station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">一群寄生爬行獸在攻擊太空站的船身。所有閒置的人應購買激光槍，然後前往位於太空站中央的太空漫步入口。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">一群寄生爬行獸在攻擊太空站的船身。所有閒置的人應購買激光槍，然後前往位於太空站中央的太空漫步入口。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A swarm of parasitic crawlers is attacking the station's hull.  All available hands should procure a blaster pistol and proceed to the Spacewalk entrance at the center of the station.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_014</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The bounty on parasitic crawlers has increased.  Proceed to the spacewalk entrance at the center of the station to take advantage of the bonus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La prime sur les robots parasites a augmenté. Rendez vous à l'accès vers l'Espace se trouvant au milieu de la station pour profiter de ce bonus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Kopfgeld auf die Parasiten wurde erhöht. Begeben Sie sich zum Ausgang der Station im Zentrum der Sation, um sich den Bonus zu holen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La taglia sui parassiti cingolati è aumentata. Dirigiti verso l'entrata Spacewalk al centro della stazione per sfruttare il bonus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La recompensa por los robots parásitos ha sido incrementada. Proceda a la puerta de caminata espacial en el centro de la estación para aprovechar esta bonificación.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スペースウォーク[外部]の敵ボット退治で受け取れるネブロンが増えたぞ。ステーションの中央にあるスペースウォークの入り口まで進み、このボーナスを手に入れろ。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">크롤러 파괴 포상금이 상승했습니다. 보너스를 받으려면 정거장 중앙의 우주유영 입구로 이동하십시오.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The bounty on parasitic crawlers has increased.  Proceed to the spacewalk entrance at the center of the station to take advantage of the bonus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">擊倒寄生爬行獸的獎賞已增加了。前往位於太空站中央的太空漫步入口，享用額外獎賞。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">擊倒寄生爬行獸的獎賞已增加了。前往位於太空站中央的太空漫步入口，享用額外獎賞。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The bounty on parasitic crawlers has increased.  Proceed to the spacewalk entrance at the center of the station to take advantage of the bonus.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_015</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The use of Zero-gravity simulators within the station is now permitted. These devices allow the user to float anywhere, and they can be purchased at any kiosk in the station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'utilisation de simulateurs de gravité-zéro au sein de la station est désormais permise. Ces dispositifs permettent à l'utilisateur de flotter n'importe où. Ils peuvent être achetés dans n'importe quel kiosque de la station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Nutzen von Null-Gravitationssimulatoren ist auf der Station verboten. Dieses Gerät erlaubt es dem Nutzer, frei herum zu schweben, und kann im Laden der Station gekauft werden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Da adesso hail il permesso di usare i simulatori di gravità-zero all'interno della stazione. Questi dispositivi permettono di fluttuare ovunque, e possono essere acquistati presso ogni chiosco nella stazione</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El uso de simuladores de gravedad cero en la estación ha sido permitido. Estos dispositivos permiten al usuario flotar donde sea, y pueden ser comprados en cualquier quiosco en la estación.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステーション内にある無重力シミュレーターの使用が許可された。これらの装置があればどこでも遊泳ができる。ステーション内のどのキオスクでも購入が可能。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">정거장 내의 무중력 시뮬레이터 사용이 허가되었습니다. 이 장치는 어디서든 무중력 상태로 이동할 수 있게 해주며, 정거장 내 모든 상점에서 구입할 수 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The use of Zero-gravity simulators within the station is now permitted. These devices allow the user to float anywhere, and they can be purchased at any kiosk in the station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">現已批准在太空站內使用零重力模擬器。模擬器讓玩家在任何地方漂浮，可在太空站內任何商店購買。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">現已批准在太空站內使用零重力模擬器。模擬器讓玩家在任何地方漂浮，可在太空站內任何商店購買。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The use of Zero-gravity simulators within the station is now permitted. These devices allow the user to float anywhere, and they can be purchased at any kiosk in the station.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_016</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Spacewalk propulsion boots have been approved by the Novus Prime safety commission. They are now available for purchase at the kiosks within the station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les bottes à propulsion spatiale ont été approuvées par la commission de sécurité de Novus Prime. Elles sont dès maintenant disponibles dans les kiosques de la station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Antriebsstiefel für den Weltraumspaziergang wurden von der Novus Prime Sicherheitskommission genehmigt. Sie sind im Laden der Stations zum Kauf erhältlich.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gli stivali per la propulsione della camminata spaziale sono stati approvati dalla commissione di sicurezza della Novus Prime. E' possibile acquistarli presso ogni chiosco nella stazione</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las botas de propulsión para caminatas espaciales han sido aprobadas por la comisión de seguridad de Novus Prime. Estas botas están disponibles a la venta en los quioscos en la estación.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">宇宙遊泳用推進力ブーツがノーバス・プライム安全委員会により許可された。ステーション内のキオスクで購入が可能だ。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">우주유영 추진 부츠가 노부스 프라임 안전 위원회의 검수를 마쳤습니다. 이제 정거장 내의 상점에서 구입할 수 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Spacewalk propulsion boots have been approved by the Novus Prime safety commission. They are now available for purchase at the kiosks within the station.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">太空漫步推進靴已獲得Novus Prime安全委員會認可，可在太空站內任何商店購買。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">太空漫步推進靴已獲得Novus Prime安全委員會認可，可在太空站內任何商店購買。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Spacewalk propulsion boots have been approved by the Novus Prime safety commission. They are now available for purchase at the kiosks within the station.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_017</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Several private officer's suites are currently available for purchase. These spacious units come equipped with Zero-G simulation systems, which allow you and your guests the comfort of weightlessness any time. A private hangar may also be installed to any suite, from which invite-only missions may be launched.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quelques-unes de ces suites privées pour les officiers sont actuellement disponibles à l'achat. Ces unités spacieuses sont équipées d'un système d'apesanteur afin de vous permettre de profiter à tout moment du confort de l'apesanteur avec vos invités. Un hangar privé peut aussi y être installé, permettant ainsi le lancement de missions sur invite seulement.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Derzeit sind verschiedene private Offiziersquartiere zum Kauf erhältlich. Diese großzügig ausgelegten Einheiten verfügen über ein Null-Gravitationssystem, dass Ihnen und Ihren Gästen jederzeit den Komfort von Gewichtslosigkeit bietet. Weiterhin kann ein privater Hangar in Ihre Suite installiert werden. Nur von diesem können Missionen gespielt werden, zu denen Sie eingeladen wurden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sono disponibili alcune suite per ufficiali. Queste ampie unità sono fornite si sistema simulazione gravita zero, che permetterà a te ed ai tuoi ospiti di provare tutta la comodità dell'assenza di peso in ogni momento. È inoltre possibile installare in ogni suite un hangar privato, dal quale è possibile partire solo per missioni su invito.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Varias suite privadas de oficiales están disponibles a la venta. Estas espaciosas unidades están equipadas con sistemas de simulación de gravedad cero, lo cual permite que tú y tus invitados gocen el confort de la ingravidez en cualquier momento. Un hangar privado puede ser instalado en cualquier suite, en la cual sólo serán lanzadas misiones que hayas invitado.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムの士官棟が販売中だ。この広いユニットには無重力シミュレーター完備で客をもてなす時も一緒に気軽に動き回れる。個人格納庫も設置が可能で、ここでミッションに着手できる。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">개인용 장교 생활구역이 판매 중입니다. 이 넓은 시설에는 무중력 시뮬레이션 시스템이 설치되어 있어 손님들과 함께 언제라도 무중력을 즐길 수 있습니다. 또한 개인 격납고를 추가로 설치해, 비공개 임무를 시작할 수 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Several private officer's suites are currently available for purchase. These spacious units come equipped with Zero-G simulation systems, which allow you and your guests the comfort of weightlessness any time. A private hangar may also be installed to any suite, from which invite-only missions may be launched.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">數間士兵官員套房現公開發售。這些寬敞的單位配備零重力模擬系統，讓你和賓客隨時享受零重力的舒適環境。你亦可安裝私人太空船船庫，在那裡執行只有被邀請才能參加的任務。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">數間士兵官員套房現公開發售。這些寬敞的單位配備零重力模擬系統，讓你和賓客隨時享受零重力的舒適環境。你亦可安裝私人太空船船庫，在那裡執行只有被邀請才能參加的任務。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Several private officer's suites are currently available for purchase. These spacious units come equipped with Zero-G simulation systems, which allow you and your guests the comfort of weightlessness any time. A private hangar may also be installed to any suite, from which invite-only missions may be launched.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_18</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Long-Term Memory Conditioning has been approved by Novus Prime Health Services.  This permanent treatment effectively increases base experience point gains to 300% of the norm.  The Conduit Pilot Gloves and Mental Conditioning Chamber are included at no extra cost.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le conditionnement mémoriel à long terme a été approuvé par les services de santé de Novus Prime. Ce traitement permanent augmente efficacement les gains d'expérience de base à 300% de la norme. Les gants pilotes de conduite et la chambre de conditionnement mental sont inclus sans coût supplémentaire.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Langzeitgedächtnistraining wurde vom Novus Prime Gesundheitszentrum bewilligt. Diese bleibende Behandlung erhöht den Zuwachs an Erfahrungspunkten der Basis um effektiv 300% des Normalzustands.  Die Verbindungshandschuhen für Piloten und die mentale Konditionierungskammer sind kostenlos enthalten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il lavaggio del cervello ad effetto prolungato è stato approvato dai Servizi sanitari della Novus Prime. Questo trattamento permanente incrementa l'acquisizione di base dei punti esperienza del 300% rispetto ai valori normali. I Guanti da pilota in guaina e la Stanza per il lavaggio del cervello ad effetto prolungato sono inclusi senza spese aggiuntive.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acondicionamiento de memoria a largo plazo ha sido aprobado por los servicios médicos de Novus Prime. Este tratamiento permanente incrementa efectivamente  los puntos de experiencia base a un 300% de lo normal.  Los guantes de piloto conducto y la cámara de acondicionamiento mental están incluidos sin coste extra.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">長期記憶の条件付けはノーバス・プライムの医療サービスに同意されています。この維持療法は効果的に基礎経験値を通常の300%にまで増大します。コンジット状のパイロット用手袋とメンタルコンディショニング室は追加費用無しで含まれています。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">장기기억 콘디셔닝은 노버스 프라임 헬스 서비스가 승인해 왔습니다. 이 영구적인 대응은 기본 경험포인트 취득을 기준치의 300%까지 효과적으로 증가시켜 줍니다. 추가 비용없이 콘듀잇 조종사 글로브와 멘털 콘디셔닝실이 포함됩니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Long-Term Memory Conditioning has been approved by Novus Prime Health Services.  This permanent treatment effectively increases base experience point gains to 300% of the norm.  The Conduit Pilot Gloves and Mental Conditioning Chamber are included at no extra cost.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">長期記憶訓練被若瓦斯總司令醫療事務所認可。而此永久的治療可有效地增加基本經驗值達到300%。輸送管道飛行員的手套和恢復休息室將不需要其他額外的支出。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">長期記憶訓練被若瓦斯總司令醫療事務所認可。而此永久的治療可有效地增加基本經驗值達到300%。輸送管道飛行員的手套和恢復休息室將不需要其他額外的支出。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Long-Term Memory Conditioning has been approved by Novus Prime Health Services.  This permanent treatment effectively increases base experience point gains to 300% of the norm.  The Conduit Pilot Gloves and Mental Conditioning Chamber are included at no extra cost.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_19</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Attention Obsidian Pilots!  Your Blade fighter ships have been loaded into the Earth Fleet hangars, and may be customized by accessing the Workshop.  You may also view your ships by activating the personal holographic generators built into your suits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Attention pilotes Obsidienne! Vos vaisseaux de combat lame ont été chargés dans les hangars de la flotte terrienne et peuvent être customises en accédant à l'atelier. Vous pouvez aussi voir vos vaisseaux en activant les générateurs holographiques personnels inclus dans vos combinaisons.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Achtung Obsidian-Piloten!  Eure Klingen-Kampfschiffe wurden in die Hangars der Erdflotte verladen und können über die Werkhalle modifiziert werden. Du kannst deine Schiffe auch betrachten, indem du deinen persönlichen Hologrammgenerator, der in deinen Anzug eingebaut ist, aktivierst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">A tutti i Piloti Obsidian! I vostri Caccia sono stati caricati negli hangar della flotta terrestre e possono essere modificati accedendo all'Officina. Potete anche visualizzare i vostri Caccia attivando i generatori olografici personali installati sulle vostre tute.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Alerta pilotos Obsidianos! Las naves de combate Blade han sido cargadas en los hangares de la flota de la Tierra, y pueden ser personalizados accediendo al Taller. También pueden ver sus naves activando los generadores holográficos personales integrados en sus trajes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">黒曜石パイロットに告ぐ！諸君のブレードファイター艦は地球艦隊の格納庫に収容され、作業場へアクセスすることで、改造を受けるかも知れない。諸君のスーツに搭載されているパーソナル・ホログラフィ発生装置を起動させることで自分の艦を見る事になるかも知れん。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">옵시디언 조종사들은 주목하라!  블레이드 파이터 함대는 지구 함대 격납고로 들어왔다. 그리고 워크숍에 접속함으로써 커스터마이즈할 수 있다. 자신의 수트에 장착된 퍼스널 홀로그래픽 제너레이터를 가동시키면 당신의 함대가 보일 것이다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Attention Obsidian Pilots!  Your Blade fighter ships have been loaded into the Earth Fleet hangars, and may be customized by accessing the Workshop.  You may also view your ships by activating the personal holographic generators built into your suits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">黑曜飛行員注意！你們的刀鋒戰鬥機已停放置地球艦隊的停機坪，你也可以藉由內建至飛行衣/戰鬥裝中的影像產生器來檢視你的戰鬥機</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">黑曜飛行員注意！你們的刀鋒戰鬥機已停放置地球艦隊的停機坪，你也可以藉由內建至飛行衣/戰鬥裝中的影像產生器來檢視你的戰鬥機</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Attention Obsidian Pilots!  Your Blade fighter ships have been loaded into the Earth Fleet hangars, and may be customized by accessing the Workshop.  You may also view your ships by activating the personal holographic generators built into your suits.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_20</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Greetings, Commander!  Our pilots are at the ready.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Félicitation, Commandant! Nos pilotes sont tous prêts.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Seit gegrüßt, Commander!  Unsere Piloten sind bereit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Salve, Comandante!
I nostri piloti sono pronti.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Saludos, Comandante! Nuestros pilotos están listos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">お帰りなさい、コマンダー！我が軍のパイロットは全員準備ができております。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">안녕하십니까, 사령관님!  저희 파일럿들은 준비완료되었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Greetings, Commander!  Our pilots are at the ready.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">指揮官好，我們的飛行員都已準備就緒。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">指揮官好，我們的飛行員都已準備就緒。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Greetings, Commander!  Our pilots are at the ready.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_21</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Attention all personnel: Commander on deck!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Attention à tout le personnel : Le commandant est sur le pont!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Achtung an das Personal: Commander an Deck!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">A tutto il personale: il Comandante è sul ponte!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Alerta a todo el personal: ¡El Comandante está en cubierta!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">総員に告ぐ：コマンダーが甲板におられる！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">대원들은 주목하라: 사령관님께서 오셨다!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Attention all personnel: Commander on deck!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">所有人注意: 指揮官到場</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">所有人注意: 指揮官到場</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Attention all personnel: Commander on deck!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_22</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Novus Prime Technologies Research has released the Tech Goggles, which allows use of the Enemy Scanner to expose the weaknesses of a target Bot vessel.  All damage dealt to the target is effectively doubled, for as long at the scan is active.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La recherche Novus Prime Technologies vient de mettre en vente les Lunettes Tech, qui permettent l'usage du scanner d'ennemi pour exposer les faiblesses d'un vaisseau Bot ciblé. Tous les dommages subis par la cible sont efficacement doublés tant que le scan est actif.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Abteilung für Technolgie und Forschung von Novus Prime hat die Tech-Brille freigegeben, die es dir erlaubt den Feindscanner zu aktivieren und die Schwächen anvisierter Bot-Schiffe zu enthüllen. Jeder Schaden der dem Ziel zugefügt wird verdoppelt sich solange der Scanner aktiviert ist.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Divisione per la ricerca tecnologica della Novus Prime ha rilasciato il Visore ad alta tecnologia, che permette di utilizzare lo Scanner Nemici per visualizzare le debolezze delle navi nemiche bot agganciate. Ogni danno inflitto al bersaglio viene raddoppiato fino a quando la scansione è attiva.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Investigación de tecnologías Novus Prime ha lanzado Gafas Tech, las cuales permiten el uso Escáner Enemigo para exponer las debilidades del navío Robot objetivo. Todo el daño hecho al objetivo es duplicado efectivamente, mientras el escáner esté activo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムの技術調査が、標的のロボット艦艇の弱点を明らかにする敵スキャナの使用を可能にする技術ゴーグルを発表した。スキャナが作動している間、標的に対する全てのダメージが効果的に倍増します。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노버스 프라임 기술 연구는 봇 함대의 약점을 노출시키는 에너미 스캐너의 사용을 가능하게 해 준 테크 고글즈에 의해 행해졌다. 스캔 작동 중 타겟을 향해 입히는 모든 데미지는 사실상 2배가 된다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Novus Prime Technologies Research has released the Tech Goggles, which allows use of the Enemy Scanner to expose the weaknesses of a target Bot vessel.  All damage dealt to the target is effectively doubled, for as long at the scan is active.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">若瓦斯總司令科學研發部門發表了一副能執行掃描敵方並暴露目標機械戰鬥機弱點的高科技透視鏡。只要掃描是有效的，對目標的損害將有兩倍的效果</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">若瓦斯總司令科學研發部門發表了一副能執行掃描敵方並暴露目標機械戰鬥機弱點的高科技透視鏡。只要掃描是有效的，對目標的損害將有兩倍的效果</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Novus Prime Technologies Research has released the Tech Goggles, which allows use of the Enemy Scanner to expose the weaknesses of a target Bot vessel.  All damage dealt to the target is effectively doubled, for as long at the scan is active.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_23</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Commodore on deck!  Stand at attention!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Commandeur sur le pont! Tenez-vous attentifs!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Commander an Deck! Achtung!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Commodoro si trova sul ponte! Sugli attenti!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Comodoro en cubierta! ¡Firmes!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">提督が甲板におられる！気をつけ！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사령관님께서 오셨다!  전원 차렷!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Commodore on deck!  Stand at attention!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">指揮官到場！所有人立正！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">指揮官到場！所有人立正！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Commodore on deck!  Stand at attention!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO_24</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">We have announced your arrival, Admiral.  The squadrons are ready for deployment.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nous avons annoncé votre arrivée, Amiral. Les escadrons sont prêts pour le déploiement.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wir haben Ihre Ankunft angekündigt, Admiral. Die Schwadrone sind bereit für den Einsatz.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Abbiamo annunciato il suo arrivo, Ammiraglio. Gli squadroni sono pronti alla partenza.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hemos anunciado su llegada, Almirante. Los escuadrones están listos para partir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">閣下の到着について告知しておきました、准将。飛行隊の配置準備は完了しております。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사령관 각하의 도착을 대원들에게 알렸습니다. 함대 배치 준비는  완료되었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">We have announced your arrival, Admiral.  The squadrons are ready for deployment.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">艦隊司令，我們歡迎您的到來。已經為您調度好您的艦隊了。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">艦隊司令，我們歡迎您的到來。已經為您調度好您的艦隊了。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">We have announced your arrival, Admiral.  The squadrons are ready for deployment.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">COMMAND: "Alright recruit- we're gonna have you test the basic systems on that reconditioned fighter. Go ahead and move the ship to the testing area using the [LEFTSTICK]. Just follow that red arrow 'til you get there."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">COMMANDEMENT : "Très bien. En tant que recrue, vous allez devoir effectuer les tests de routine sur ce chasseur reconditionné. Mettez-vous en route, et déplacez le vaisseau vers la zone de test avec [LEFTSTICK]. Suivez simplement les flèches rouges jusqu'à destination."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">COMMANDER: "Also gut, Rekrut- wir werden dich die Basissysteme an diesem generalüberholten Jäger testen lassen. Begib dich mit dem Schiff ins Testgebiet, indem Du [LEFTSTICK] verwendest. Folge einfach dem roten Pfeil, bis du dort ankommst."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">COMANDO: “Bene recluta, dovrai testare i sistemi di base di quel caccia appena revisionato. Dirigiti con il velivolo verso l'area di prova usando [LEFTSTICK]. Segui la freccia rossa fino alla meta.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">COMANDANCIA: "Muy bien, recluta. Ahora vas a probar los sistemas básicos de esa nave de combate reacondicionada. Avanza y desplaza la nave a la zona de pruebas con [LEFTSTICK]. Sigue la flecha roja hasta que llegues allí."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コマンド:「よく来たな、新米。まずは旧式の戦闘機で基礎的なシステムを試してみよう。さあ、[LEFTSTICK]で試乗エリアまで進んでくれ。赤い矢印に付いていくだけだよ。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사령부: "좋다, 훈련병. 이제 전투기의 기본적인 조작 방법에 대해 알아 보도록 하겠다. [LEFTSTICK]으로 훈련장에서 비행하게. 도착할 때까지 붉은색 화살표를 따르도록 한다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">COMMAND: "Alright recruit- we're gonna have you test the basic systems on that reconditioned fighter. Go ahead and move the ship to the testing area using the [LEFTSTICK]. Just follow that red arrow 'til you get there."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">指揮部：「好了，新成員。你現在要測試那架已修理的戰鬥機的基本系統運作。使用[LEFTSTICK]，將戰鬥機移動到測試區，跟隨紅色箭頭，直止你到達那裏。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">指揮部：「好了，新成員。你現在要測試那架已修理的戰鬥機的基本系統運作。使用[LEFTSTICK]，將戰鬥機移動到測試區，跟隨紅色箭頭，直止你到達那裏。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">COMMAND: "Alright recruit- we're gonna have you test the basic systems on that reconditioned fighter. Go ahead and move the ship to the testing area using the [LEFTSTICK]. Just follow that red arrow 'til you get there."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hold [SQUARE] : Use speed booster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Maintenir [SQUARE] : Utilisez le turbo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[SQUARE] gedrückt halten: Geschwindigkeits-Booster einsetzen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tieni premuto [SQUARE] per usare i motori turbo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mantén pulsado [SQUARE]: Utilizar propulsor de velocidad</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[SQUARE]長押し：スピードブースターを使う</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[SQUARE] 누르고 있기 : 스피드 부스터 사용</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Hold [SQUARE] : Use speed booster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">按住[SQUARE]：使用速度增幅器</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">按住[SQUARE]：使用速度增幅器</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hold [SQUARE] : Use speed booster</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">COMMAND: "The thrusters and steering system look good. Now we can start the fun stuff."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">COMMANDEMENT : "Les systèmes de guidage et d'accélération semble être en bon état. On peut maintenant passer aux choses sérieuses."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">COMMANDER: "Die Strahlruder und das Lenksystem sehen gut aus. Jetzt kommen wir zum spaßigen Teil."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">COMANDO: “I propulsori e il sistema di comando sembrano a posto. Ora possiamo passare alla parte divertente.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">COMANDANCIA: "Parece que los propulsores y el sistema de dirección están bien. Podemos comenzar con la parte divertida."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コマンド：「スラスターとステアシステムに問題はないようだ。さあショータイムだ。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사령부: "추진기와 조향장치 모두 정상 작동하는군. 이제 재미있는 부분이 시작이네."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">COMMAND: "The thrusters and steering system look good. Now we can start the fun stuff."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">指揮部：「火箭推進器和導航系統的狀態看來不錯。現在我們可以開始進行一些有趣的事情。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">指揮部：「火箭推進器和導航系統的狀態看來不錯。現在我們可以開始進行一些有趣的事情。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">COMMAND: "The thrusters and steering system look good. Now we can start the fun stuff."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">COMMAND: "Alright, go ahead and fire your front weapon by pressing the [L2] button."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">COMMANDEMENT : "Très bien. Faites feu avec l'arme montée à l'avant en appuyant sur la touche [L2]."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">COMMANDER: " Na schön, feuere deine vordere Waffe ab, indem Du [L2] drückst."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">COMANDO: “Bene, prosegui diritto e usa l'arma di prua premendo il tasto [L2].”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">COMANDANCIA: "Avanza y pulsa el botón [L2] para disparar el arma delantera."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コマンド：「よし、それじゃあ[L2]を押してフロント兵器を放つんだ。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사령부: "자, [L2]을 눌러 전방의 무기를 발사하도록."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">COMMAND: "Alright, go ahead and fire your front weapon by pressing the [L2] button."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">指揮部：「好了，上前按 [L2] 按鈕用你的前方武器開火。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">指揮部：「好了，上前按 [L2] 按鈕用你的前方武器開火。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">COMMAND: "Alright, go ahead and fire your front weapon by pressing the [L2] button."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj4b</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">COMMAND: "Looking good; your front weapon controls are operating within standards."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">COMMANDEMENT : "L'arme montée à l'avant est parfaitement opérationnelle, tout est O.K."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">COMMANDER: "Das sieht gut aus, die Steuerung für die vordere Waffe funktioniert einwandfrei."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">COMANDO: “Pare sia a posto, i comandi delle armi di prua rispondono correttamente.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">COMANDANCIA: "Parece que todo está bien; los controles del arma delantera funcionan dentro de los estándares."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コマンド：「いいぞ。フロント兵器の操作は基準内で動作している。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사령부: "잘했어. 전방 무기의 조작도가 정상 범위에 있군."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">COMMAND: "Looking good; your front weapon controls are operating within standards."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">指揮部：「看來不錯，你控制前方武器的能力合符標準。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">指揮部：「看來不錯，你控制前方武器的能力合符標準。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">COMMAND: "Looking good; your front weapon controls are operating within standards."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">COMMAND: "Okay, now we need you to fire your turret weapon by pressing the [R2] button. Remember that you can aim the turret with [RIGHTSTICK], and an indicator showing you what direction the turret is pointed will appear while you aim."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">COMMANDEMENT : "Parfait. Vous allez maintenant devoir tirer avec la tourelle en appuyant sur la touche [R2]. Gardez à l'esprit que vous pouvez viser avec la tourelle avec [RIGHTSTICK], un réticule de visée apparaîtra alors pour indiquer la direction dans laquelle la tourelle fait face."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">COMMANDER: "Okay, jetzt wollen wir, dass du deinen Geschützturm abfeuerst, indem Du [R2] drückst. Denke daran, dass du den Geschützturm mit [RIGHTSTICK] ausrichten kannst, während eine Anzeige erscheint und darstellt, in welche Richtung der Geschützturm zielt."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">COMANDO: Ok, ora dovrai far fuoco con la torretta premendo il tasto [R2]. Ricorda che puoi ruotare la torretta con [RIGHTSTICK]: comparirà un indicatore che ti mostrerà in che direzione è puntata mentre prendi la mira.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">COMANDANCIA: "Ahora tendrás que disparar el arma de torre pulsando el botón [R2]. Recuerda que puedes apuntar con la torre con [RIGHTSTICK] y aparecerá un indicador que muestra la dirección hacia la que apunta la torre."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コマンド:「オーケー。[R2]を押してタレット兵器を放つんだ。タレットの照準は[RIGHTSTICK]、照準の間、インディケーターには君のタレットの方向が表示されるから参考にしてくれ。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사령부: "이제 [R2]을 눌러 포탑 무기를 발사하게나. [RIGHTSTICK]을 이용해서 발사 방향을 조종할 수 있네. 포탑이 어느 방향으로 발사하는지는 포탑의 조준 방향으로 확인할 수 있다."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">COMMAND: "Okay, now we need you to fire your turret weapon by pressing the [R2] button. Remember that you can aim the turret with [RIGHTSTICK], and an indicator showing you what direction the turret is pointed will appear while you aim."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">指揮部：「好，現在請你按[R2]按鈕控制迴轉砲塔開火。緊記你可用[RIGHTSTICK]瞄準，而當你進行瞄準時，將有指標告訴你迴轉砲塔瞄準的方向。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">指揮部：「好，現在請你按[R2]按鈕控制迴轉砲塔開火。緊記你可用[RIGHTSTICK]瞄準，而當你進行瞄準時，將有指標告訴你迴轉砲塔瞄準的方向。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">COMMAND: "Okay, now we need you to fire your turret weapon by pressing the [R2] button. Remember that you can aim the turret with [RIGHTSTICK], and an indicator showing you what direction the turret is pointed will appear while you aim."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">COMMAND: "Great job. Your turret controls look to be in top shape."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">COMMANDEMENT : "Bon travail. Les systèmes de contrôle de votre tourelle semblent être en excellent état."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">COMMANDER: "Gute Arbeit. Die Steuerung für den Geschützturm scheint perfekt zu funktionieren."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">COMANDO: “Ottimo lavoro. I comandi della torretta sembrano essere a posto.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">COMANDANCIA: "Bien hecho. Los controles de la torre parecen estar en condiciones óptimas."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コマンド：「よくやった。タレットの操作は好調のようだな。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사령부: "아주 좋아. 포탑 조종에 매우 익숙하군."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">COMMAND: "Great job. Your turret controls look to be in top shape."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">指揮部：「做得好。看來你控制迴轉砲塔的能力很棒。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">指揮部：「做得好。看來你控制迴轉砲塔的能力很棒。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">COMMAND: "Great job. Your turret controls look to be in top shape."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj6b</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">COMMAND: "Nice work. The last thing we need to do is have you shoot up some nebulon-rich asteroids. They've got this purple glow to them, and they show up as enemies on your radar."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">COMMANDEMENT : "Il ne vous reste plus qu'à détruire des astéroïdes riches en nébulon. Ils sont enveloppés d'un halo violet et apparaissent en tant qu'ennemis sur votre radar."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">COMMANDER: "Gut gemacht. Als letztes wollen wir, dass du ein paar nebulonhaltige Asteroiden abschießt. Sie leuchten lilafarben und dein Radar zeigt sie als Feinde an."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">COMANDO: “Molto bene. Il tuo ultimo compito è far esplodere alcuni asteroidi ricchi di nebulon. Emettono una luce violacea e sono indicati sul tuo radar come nemici.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">COMANDANCIA: "Buen trabajo. El último trabajo que nos queda por hacer es disparar a unos asteroides cargados de nebulón. Presentan un aura morada y se muestran como enemigos en el radar."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コマンド：「いい動きだ。後はネブロンをたっぷり含んだ小惑星を撃つことだ。この小惑星は紫の光になるんだ、レーダーでは敵のように見えるぞ。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사령부: "잘했네. 마지막으로 남은 건 네뷸론을 다량으로 포함한 소행성을 파괴하는 일이야. 보라색으로 빛나고 있는 것들이네. 레이더에는 적으로 표시되지."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">COMMAND: "Nice work. The last thing we need to do is have you shoot up some nebulon-rich asteroids. They've got this purple glow to them, and they show up as enemies on your radar."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">指揮部：「不錯。最後我們需要你射擊一些蘊含豐富Nebulon的小行星。這些小行星發出紫色的光，亦會在你的雷達上顯示為敵人。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">指揮部：「不錯。最後我們需要你射擊一些蘊含豐富Nebulon的小行星。這些小行星發出紫色的光，亦會在你的雷達上顯示為敵人。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">COMMAND: "Nice work. The last thing we need to do is have you shoot up some nebulon-rich asteroids. They've got this purple glow to them, and they show up as enemies on your radar."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">COMMAND: "Got one! Most shattered asteroids leave behind a sphere of purple energy. That's nebulon, the most important material in the galaxy, so make sure to pick it up! Alright, go ahead and destroy the other rocks."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">COMMANDEMENT : "Et voilà ! La plupart des astéroïdes anéantis laissent derrière eux une sphère d'énergie violette. Ceci est du nébulon, la plus importante ressource de la galaxie. Assurez-vous donc de les ramasser ! Très bien, continuez à détruire les autres rochers."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">COMMANDER: "Du hast einen erwischt! Die meisten zerstörten Asteroiden hinterlassen eine Kugel von lilafarbener Energie. Das ist Nebulon, die wichtigste Substanz in der Galaxie, vergiss also nicht, sie einzusammeln! In Ordnung, mach weiter und zerstöre die anderen Gesteinsbrocken."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">COMANDO: “Ne hai preso uno! Quando vengono colpiti questi asteroidi rilasciano, in genere, una sfera di energia violacea. È il nebulon, il materiale più prezioso della galassia, quindi cerca di raccoglierlo! Bene, procedi e distruggi le altre rocce.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">COMANDANCIA: "¡Uno menos! La mayoría de asteroides fragmentados dejan una esfera de energía morada, llamada nebulón, el material más importante de la galaxia, así que asegúrate de recogerlo. Avanza y destruye el resto de rocas."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コマンド：「１つゲットだ！小惑星が砕けた後にボール状の紫のエネルギーが残ることがある。それがネブロン、銀河系で最も貴重な資源だ。残さず手に入れるんだ！よし、他の岩も破壊しておくんだ。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사령부: "파괴됐어! 대부분의 소행성은 파괴될 때 보라색 에너지원을 남기지. 그게 바로 이 우주에서 가장 중요한 자원인 네뷸론이야. 반드시 획득하도록 하게나! 이제 나머지 행성들을 파괴하도록."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">COMMAND: "Got one! Most shattered asteroids leave behind a sphere of purple energy. That's nebulon, the most important material in the galaxy, so make sure to pick it up! Alright, go ahead and destroy the other rocks."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">指揮部：「射中了！大部分被炸碎的小行星會剩下一個紫色能量的球體。那就是Nebulon，是銀河系中最重要的物質，所以緊記要收集它！好了，繼續毀滅其他岩石。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">指揮部：「射中了！大部分被炸碎的小行星會剩下一個紫色能量的球體。那就是Nebulon，是銀河系中最重要的物質，所以緊記要收集它！好了，繼續毀滅其他岩石。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">COMMAND: "Got one! Most shattered asteroids leave behind a sphere of purple energy. That's nebulon, the most important material in the galaxy, so make sure to pick it up! Alright, go ahead and destroy the other rocks."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">COMMAND: "I think that's enough for today. Gather up any remaining nebulon from those asteroids, and then head on back to the station. Your payment for this job will be sent to you shortly."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">COMMANDEMENT : "Je pense que ce sera tout pour aujourd'hui. Récoltez le nébulon laissé par les astéroïdes et retournez à la station. Le salaire de cette mission vous sera envoyé dans les plus bref délais."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">COMMANDER: "Ich denke, das reicht für heute. Sammle das verbleibende Nebulon ein und fliege zurück zur Station. Die Bezahlung für diesen Job erhältst du in Kürze."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">COMANDO: “Penso che basti per oggi. Raccogli il nebulon rimasto e poi ritorna alla stazione. Il pagamento per il tuo lavoro sarà effettuato a breve.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">COMANDANCIA: "Creo que es suficiente por hoy. Recoge el nebulón procedente de esos asteroides y vuelve a la estación. En breve se te enviará el pago por este trabajo."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コマンド：「今日はこのくらいにしておこう。残っているネブロンを全部回収したらステーションへ戻ろう。報酬はすぐに送られてくるだろう。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사령부: "오늘의 훈련으로는 충분하군. 남아 있는 네뷸론들을 모은 다음 기지로 돌아가게. 자네의 오늘 일당은 곧 입금될 것이네."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">COMMAND: "I think that's enough for today. Gather up any remaining nebulon from those asteroids, and then head on back to the station. Your payment for this job will be sent to you shortly."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">指揮部：「我想今天就到此為止吧。從那些小行星收集剩下的Nebulon，然後返回太空站。你將很快收到這項任務的工資。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">指揮部：「我想今天就到此為止吧。從那些小行星收集剩下的Nebulon，然後返回太空站。你將很快收到這項任務的工資。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">COMMAND: "I think that's enough for today. Gather up any remaining nebulon from those asteroids, and then head on back to the station. Your payment for this job will be sent to you shortly."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj9</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">TRAINER: "Hey there, recruit! I'll be your trainer today. Just call me Leeroy. We're just going to go through a few excercises, to get accustomed to controlling your ship."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">SERGENT INSTRUCTEUR : "Salut à vous, recrue ! Je serai votre instructeur pour la journée. Appelez-moi simplement Leeroy. On va faire quelques exercices afin que vous vous habituiez à contrôler votre vaisseau."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">AUSBILDER: "Hallo Rekrut! Ich werde heute dein Ausbilder sein. Nenn mich einfach Leeroy. Wir werden jetzt einige Übungen durchgehen, um dich mit der Steuerung des Schiffs vertraut zu machen."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">ISTRUTTORE: “Salve, recluta! Sarò io il tuo istruttore oggi. Puoi chiamarmi Leeroy. Faremo giusto qualche esercizio perché tu prenda dimestichezza con i comandi della nave.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">ENTRENADOR: "¡Eh, recluta! Me llamo Leeroy y seré tu entrenador hoy. Vamos a realizar unos ejercicios para que te acostumbres a controlar la nave."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">トレーナー：「よう、新米！俺が今日のコーチだ。リーロイと呼んでくれ。まずは操縦に慣れるまで基本エクササイズからはじめよう。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">교관: "이봐, 훈련병! 네놈의 오늘 교관은 바로 나다. 내 이름은 리로이. 몇 가지 훈련을 통해서 기체를 조종하는 방법을 배우도록 하겠다."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">TRAINER: "Hey there, recruit! I'll be your trainer today. Just call me Leeroy. We're just going to go through a few excercises, to get accustomed to controlling your ship."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">教練：「喂，新成員！今天我將會是你的教練，叫我里萊。我們將進行數項練習，讓你們熟悉控制戰鬥機。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">教練：「喂，新成員！今天我將會是你的教練，叫我里萊。我們將進行數項練習，讓你們熟悉控制戰鬥機。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">TRAINER: "Hey there, recruit! I'll be your trainer today. Just call me Leeroy. We're just going to go through a few excercises, to get accustomed to controlling your ship."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj10</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LEEROY: "Uh oh- I'm picking up a pack of bots just ahead! Don't you worry, Leeroy will take care of this! Woooooooooooooo!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">LEEROY : "Argh ! Je localise un groupe de droïdes droit devant ! Pas de panique, Leeroy va s'occuper d'eux ! Yeaaaaaaaah !"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LEEROY: "Oh-Oh- Ich empfange ein Rudel Bots direkt voraus! Keine Sorge, Leeroy kümmert sich darum! Wooooooooooooooh!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">LEEROY: “Oh oh... rilevo un gruppo di bot a dritta! Non preoccuparti, me ne occuperò io! Ahhhhhhhhh!”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LEEROY: "¡Eh! ¡He divisado un grupo de robots ahí delante! ¡No te preocupes, Leeroy se ocupará de ellos! ¡Uoooooooooooooo!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">リーロイ：「おっと。眼と鼻の先にボット発見。心配無用、リーロイ様にまかせろって！うおおおおおおおおっしゃああ！」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">리로이: "음, 전방에 다수의 적기가 출현했다! 걱정마, 리로이가 해결할 테니까! 이야아아아앗!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">LEEROY: "Uh oh- I'm picking up a pack of bots just ahead! Don't you worry, Leeroy will take care of this! Woooooooooooooo!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">里萊：「噢，前方有一群機械獸！不用擔心，里萊會處理了！哇～～～～～～！」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">里萊：「噢，前方有一群機械獸！不用擔心，里萊會處理了！哇～～～～～～！」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LEEROY: "Uh oh- I'm picking up a pack of bots just ahead! Don't you worry, Leeroy will take care of this! Woooooooooooooo!"</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">COMPUTER: "Friendly vessel has suffered critical damage. It's hull is expected to rupture within thirty-seconds. Please move close to the disabled ship and hold [CROSS] to begin emergency repairs."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">ORDINATEUR : "Une navette alliée a subit des dégâts critiques. Sa coque va céder dans moins de trente secondes. Rapprochez-vous du vaisseau touché et maintenez [CROSS] pour entreprendre les réparations d'urgences."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">COMPUTER: "Verbündetes Schiff hat schweren Schaden genommen. Sein Rumpf wird voraussichtlich in 30 Sekunden zerbrechen. Bitte an manövrierunfähiges Schiff annähern und [CROSS] gedrückt halten, um Notfall-Reparatur durchzuführen."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">COMPUTER: “La nave amica ha subito danni critici. Lo scafo potrà resistere al massimo altri trenta secondi. Avvicinati alla nave in avaria e tieni premuto [CROSS] per le riparazioni d'emergenza.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">ORDENADOR: "La nave amiga ha sufrido daños críticos. Se espera que el fuselaje se rompa en treinta segundos. Acérquese a la nave dañada y mantenga pulsado [CROSS] para comenzar las reparaciones de emergencia."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コンピュータ：「味方の船が致命的なダメージを受けています。30秒以内に船体に亀裂が入るものと予測されます。操縦不能に陥った船に近付いて[ACCEPT]長押しで緊急修理を行ってください。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">시스템: "아군 기체가 치명적인 손상을 입었습니다. 30초 내에 선체의 내부 파열이 시작됩니다. 파손된 아군기 옆으로 이동하여 [CROSS]으로 비상 수리를 시작하십시오."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">COMPUTER: "Friendly vessel has suffered critical damage. It's hull is expected to rupture within thirty-seconds. Please move close to the disabled ship and hold [CROSS] to begin emergency repairs."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">電腦：「同伴的戰鬥機受到嚴重損毀，其船身預計於三十秒內分裂。請移近該船並按住[CROSS]進行搶修。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">電腦：「同伴的戰鬥機受到嚴重損毀，其船身預計於三十秒內分裂。請移近該船並按住[CROSS]進行搶修。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">COMPUTER: "Friendly vessel has suffered critical damage. It's hull is expected to rupture within thirty-seconds. Please move close to the disabled ship and hold [CROSS] to begin emergency repairs."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj12</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LEEROY: "Heeeeeeeeeelp!!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">LEEROY : "A l'aiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiide !!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LEEROY: "HIIIIIILFE!!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">LEEROY: “Aiutooooooooo!!!”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LEEROY: "¡Ayudaaaaaaaaa!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">リーロイ：「ヘーーールプ！！」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">리로이: "도와줘어어어어엇!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">LEEROY: "Heeeeeeeeeelp!!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">里萊：「救救救救救救救…命啊！！」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">里萊：「救救救救救救救…命啊！！」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LEEROY: "Heeeeeeeeeelp!!"</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LEEROY: "Aw, thanks a lot, pal. I almost had them, but my shields went out on me. I guess I shouldn't get shot so much. Anyway, let's head back to the base, I think you've earned a break."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">LEEROY : "Ouf, merci beaucoup, mon pote. Je les avais presque, mais mes boucliers m'ont lâché. J'imagine que je n'aurais pas dû prendre autant de tirs. Bon, retournons à la base, je pense que tu mérites une bonne pause."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LEEROY: "Puh, vielen Dank, Kumpel. Ich hatte sie fast, aber mir sind die Schutzschilder ausgefallen. Ich sollte wohl etwas weniger Treffer einstecken. Egal, lass uns zurück zur Basis fliegen, du hast dir eine Pause verdient."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">LEEROY: “Ehi, grazie mille, amico. Li avevo quasi raggiunti, ma i miei scudi mi hanno tradito. Immagino che non dovrei espormi tanto al fuoco nemico. Torniamo alla base, ti meriti un po' di riposo.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LEEROY: "Vaya, gracias, colega. Casi los tenía, pero mi escudo me la jugó. Creo que no debería dejar que me disparen tanto. Bueno, volvamos a la base; creo que te has ganado un descanso."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">リーロイ：「おっと。ありがとうよ。あともう少しで仕留められたんだがシールドが壊れてしまった。弾は受けずに避けるようにな。とにかく基地に戻って休憩しよう。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">리로이: "정말 고마워, 덕분에 살았어. 내가 거의 이겼지만 방어막이 중간에 끊기는 바람에 말이야. 회피 비행술을 더 익혀야겠군. 어쨌든 기지로 돌아가자. 모두 휴식이 필요한 것 같군."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">LEEROY: "Aw, thanks a lot, pal. I almost had them, but my shields went out on me. I guess I shouldn't get shot so much. Anyway, let's head back to the base, I think you've earned a break."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">里萊：「啊，很感謝，朋友。我幾乎到手了，但我的防護罩不行了，我想我不應該被射中那麼多。無論如何，回基地吧，你應該休息一下了。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">里萊：「啊，很感謝，朋友。我幾乎到手了，但我的防護罩不行了，我想我不應該被射中那麼多。無論如何，回基地吧，你應該休息一下了。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LEEROY: "Aw, thanks a lot, pal. I almost had them, but my shields went out on me. I guess I shouldn't get shot so much. Anyway, let's head back to the base, I think you've earned a break."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj14</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hold on, Recruit! Surveillance is picking up enemy warp signatures in that area. We've got the warp scramblers back online, but we need you to take care of the few bots that made it through!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tenez bon, recrue ! Nous détectons des signes de la chaîne ennemie dans cette zone. Nos brouilleurs de chaînes sont à nouveau en ligne mais vous devez vous occuper des quelques bots qui sont passés au travers !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Halt, Rekrut! Die Überwachungsstation empfängt feindliche Warp-Signaturen in diesem Gebiet. Der Warp-Scrambler ist online, aber wir müssen uns um die wenigen kümmern, die durchgekommen sind.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aspetta, recluta! La sorveglianza sta rilevando tracce warp dei nemici in quell'area. Noi abbiamo ricollegato i dispositivi di rilevamento warp, ma tu devi liberarti dei robot che sono riusciti a passare!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Un momento recluta! Hemos detectado huellas warp enemigas en esa área. Hemos logrado poner en línea nuestra maquina de interferencia warp, pero necesitamos que te encargues de unos robots primero.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ちょいと待ちな、新米！監視隊がその辺りで敵のワープ痕跡を感知した。ワープ周波数帯変換器を有効にするのも大事だけれど、それより生き残ったボットを何とかしなきゃ。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">기다려 봐, 훈련병! 근처에서 워프 신호가 감지되었다. 교란기를 다시 작동시켰지만 적 몇 기가 우리를 따라온 것 같아! 가서 처치해 주게!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Hold on, Recruit! Surveillance is picking up enemy warp signatures in that area. We've got the warp scramblers back online, but we need you to take care of the few bots that made it through!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">撐住！新成員！監測系統正在掃描該區的敵人時空傳送的痕跡。擾碼器已經重新上線，但我們需要你應付越過了的數頭機械獸！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">撐住！新成員！監測系統正在掃描該區的敵人時空傳送的痕跡。擾碼器已經重新上線，但我們需要你應付越過了的數頭機械獸！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hold on, Recruit! Surveillance is picking up enemy warp signatures in that area. We've got the warp scramblers back online, but we need you to take care of the few bots that made it through!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kM0_obj15</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">All clear. Not bad for your first time out, eh? Why don't you go ahead and bring that fighter on back into the hangar and get some rest.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mission accomplie. Pas mal pour votre première sortie, hein ? Ramenez ce vaisseau au hangar et prenez donc un peu de repos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Alles klar. Nicht schlecht für das erste Mal, oder? Warum gehst du nicht vor und bringst den Jäger zurück in den Hangar. Ruh' dich etwas aus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tutto regolare. Non male come prima volta lì fuori, eh? Perché non vai a prendere quel caccia, lo riporti nell'hangar e vai riposarti?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Misión completa. No está mal para ser tu primera vez, ¿no? Ve y trae de regreso ese caza al hangar para descansar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オールクリア。初めてにしては上出来だな。戦闘機を格納庫に戻して少し休もうぜ。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">해결됐군. 첫 번째 비행 치고는 대단해. 격납고에 전투기를 착륙시키고 휴식을 좀 취하지 그래?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">All clear. Not bad for your first time out, eh? Why don't you go ahead and bring that fighter on back into the hangar and get some rest.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">全部搞定。做為你第一次出擊，表現還不錯吧？你為什麼不上前將那戰鬥機帶回停機庫，然後休息一下。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">全部搞定。做為你第一次出擊，表現還不錯吧？你為什麼不上前將那戰鬥機帶回停機庫，然後休息一下。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">All clear. Not bad for your first time out, eh? Why don't you go ahead and bring that fighter on back into the hangar and get some rest.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>