<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fire Master Phoenix
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Feu Maître Phoenix
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Brandmeister Phoenix
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fuoco Maestro Phoenix
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fuego Maestro Phoenix
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fire Master Phoenix
</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fire Master Phoenix is a general in the Fire Clan Army. Master Phoenix is among the elite in the Fire Clan. He is a legendary warrior and has brought many victories in battle. He fights for the prosperity of the Fire Clan Empire.  
 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Feu Maître Phoenix est un général de l'armée Clan du Feu. Maître Phoenix est parmi l'élite dans le Clan du Feu. Il est un guerrier légendaire et a apporté de nombreuses victoires dans la bataille. Il se bat pour la prospérité de l'Empire Clan du Feu.
 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Brandmeister Phoenix ist ein General in der Armee Feuerclan. Phoenix ist Meister in der Elite in der Feuerclan. Er ist ein legendärer Krieger und hat viele Siege in der Schlacht gebracht. Er kämpft für den Wohlstand des Feuers Clan Reiches.
 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fuoco Maestro Phoenix è un generale in Clan Esercito Fuoco. Maestro Phoenix è tra l'elite del Clan del Fuoco. Lui è un guerriero leggendario e ha portato molte vittorie in battaglia. Egli combatte per la prosperità del clan dell'Impero Fuoco.
 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fuego Maestro Phoenix es un general en el ejército del clan Fuego. Maestro Phoenix está entre la élite en el Clan Fuego. Él es un guerrero legendario y ha traído muchas victorias en la batalla. Él lucha por la prosperidad del Imperio Clan Fuego.
 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fire Master Phoenix is a General in the Fire Clan Army. Master Phoenix is among the elite in the Fire Clan. He is a legendary warrior and has brought many victories in battle. He fights for the prosperity of the Fire Clan Empire.  
 [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>