<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Flip Zip Up Hoodie - Paradise (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Sweat à capuche zippé Flip - Paradis (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Flip Jacke mit Reißverschluss und Kapuze - Paradiesfarben (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Flip Felpa con cappuccio e zip - Paradiso (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Flip Chaqueta de cremallera con capucha - Paraíso (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Flip turns traditional hoodie design inside out by offering cool colourblocking and a contrasting mix of solids with a floral print. Details include a zip front, pockets at front, and a chest pocket. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Flip détourne le concept traditionnel du sweat à capuche en proposant un contraste de couleurs rafraîchissant et un mélange de motifs avec un imprimé floral. Fermeture zippée sur le devant, poches frontales et une poche poitrine. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Flip Jacke mit coolem Farbblock-Design und kontrastierender Mischung aus einfarbigen Flächen und Blumenmustern stellt den traditionellen Stil der Kapuzenjacke völlig auf den Kopf. Mit Frontreißverschluss,  Taschen auf beiden Seiten und einer Brusttasche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Flip trasforma completamente il look tradizionale delle felpe con cappuccio grazie a blocchi di colore super trendy e un mix contrastante tra tinta unita e motivo floreale. Comprende apertura con zip, tasche frontali e tasca sul petto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La Flip supone una revolución del diseño tradicional de chaqueta con capucha, reactualizándolo con una mezcla de colores vivos contrastados en un estampado floral. Cuenta con cremallera frontal, bolsillos delanteros y un bolsillo en el pecho. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Flip turns traditional hoodie design inside out by offering cool colorblocking and a contrasting mix of solids with a floral print. Details include a zip front, pockets at front, and a chest pocket. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>