<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Animated Dance Floor and Board Game construction pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack de construction de piste de danse animée</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Konstruktionspaket für animierten Dancefloor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto costruzioni per pista da ballo animata</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de construcción de pista de baile animada.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アニメーションダンスフロア＆ゲームパック</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">움직이는 댄스 플로어와 보드게임 설치 팩</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Animated Dance Floor and Board Game construction pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">動態舞蹈地板和益智遊戲組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">動態舞蹈地板和益智遊戲組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Animated Dance Floor and Board Game construction pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Construct your own apartment dance floor or board game with these six animated dance floor tiles. Use your skills to create the ultimate dance space or game in your very own apartment. Sweet! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Construisez votre propre piste de danse d'appartement grâce à ces cinq carreaux de piste de danse animée. Utilisez vos compétences pour créer l'ultime piste de danse dans votre propre appartement. C'est la fête! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Konstruiere deinen eigenen Apartment-Dancefloor mit diesen fünf animierten Dancefloor-Fliesen. Nutze deine Fertigkeiten, um die ultimative Tanzfläche in deinem eigenen Apartment zu erstellen. Jetzt geht die Party ab! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Costruisci la tua pista da ballo da appartamento con queste cinque mattonelle animate per pista da ballo. Usa la tua abilità per creare il più bello spazio per ballare nel tuo proprio appartamento. È ora di far festa! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Construye tu propia pista de baile en tu casa con estas cinco baldosas animadas de pista de baile. Usa tu destreza para crear el mejor espacio de baile en tu propia casa. ¡Vamos de fiesta! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">自分だけのダンスフロア、又はゲームをこの６つのアニメーションダンスフロアタイルを使って作ってみよう！創造力を最大限に使って自分だけのダンスフロア、又はゲームを自分のパーソナルスペースをつくろう。\n\n
本セットには、パーソナルスペースのカスタマイズ用の以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n\n
・矢印ダンスフロア（ラグ）\n
・グリーンサークルダンスフロア（ラグ）\n
・クエスチョンダンスフロア（ラグ）\n
・レッドサークルダンスフロア（ラグ）\n
・スターダンスフロア（ラグ）\n
・シマシマダンスフロア（ラグ）\n
・さいころの飾り（装飾品）\n\n

※購入すると、「パーソナルスペースのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">6개의 움직이는 댄스 플로어 타일이나 보드 게임을 사용해 당신만의 낙원을 만들어 보세요. 솜씨를 뽐낼 수 있는 기회입니다! 좋군요!\n\n
본 세트에는 이하의 아이템이 포함되어 있습니다.\n
●화살 모양 댄스 플로어\n
●그린 써클 댄스 플로어\n
●물음표 댄스 플로어\n
●레드 써클 댄스 플로어\n
●별 무늬 댄스 플로어\n
●4 스트립 댄스 플로어\n
●주사위 악세사리\n\n
※구입하면「퍼스널 스페이스 꾸미기」내의 해당 카테고리에 각 아이템이 추가됩니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Construct your own apartment dance floor or board game with these six animated dance floor tiles. Use your skills to create the ultimate dance space or game in your very own apartment. Sweet!\n\n
This set includes:\n
*Arrow Dance Floor\n
*Green Circle Dance Floor\n
*Question Dance Floor\n
*Red Circle Dance Floor\n
*Star Dance Floor\n
*4Strip Dance Floor\n
*Dice Ornament\n\n
※Upon purchase, all items will be added to their corresponding categories in “Redecorate Personal Space”.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用這六種生動的舞蹈地板來建造你個人的公寓舞蹈地板或是益智遊戲。請運用你的技巧在你的公寓裡，創造你專屬的極限舞蹈空間就對了！\n\n
本組合包包括：\n
●箭頭舞蹈地板\n
●綠圓圈舞蹈地板\n
●疑問舞蹈地板\n
●紅圓圈舞蹈地板\n
●巨星舞蹈地板\n
●四塊舞蹈地板\n
●骰子裝飾品\n\n
※已購入的物件會加到「自訂個人空間」的各項所屬類別裡。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用這六種生動的舞蹈地板來建造你個人的公寓舞蹈地板或是益智遊戲。請運用你的技巧在你的公寓裡，創造你專屬的極限舞蹈空間就對了！\n\n
本組合包包括：\n
●箭頭舞蹈地板\n
●綠圓圈舞蹈地板\n
●疑問舞蹈地板\n
●紅圓圈舞蹈地板\n
●巨星舞蹈地板\n
●四塊舞蹈地板\n
●骰子裝飾品\n\n
※已購入的物件會加到「自訂個人空間」的各項所屬類別裡。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Construct your own apartment dance floor or board game with these six animated dance floor tiles. Use your skills to create the ultimate dance space or game in your very own apartment. Sweet! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>