<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Frozen Peak Palace</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Palais des cimes gelées</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Frostgipfelpalast</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Palazzo glaciale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Palacio invernal del pico helado</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Frozen Peak Palace</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">얼어붙은 봉우리의 궁전</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Frozen Peak Palace</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">冰頂峰皇宮</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">冰頂峰皇宮</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Frozen Peak Palace</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Surround yourself in the frosty splendors of the Frozen Peak Palace. Made entirely from blocks of ice, this frosty getaway comes with a rare piece of art and an inglenook with a glacial blue flame. Reward your guests with a Frozen Peak Palace Throne item, exclusive to Frozen Peak Palace personal space. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Entourez-vous dans les splendeurs du palais givré Frozen Peak. Fabriqué entièrement à partir de blocs de glace, cette escapade givrée est livré avec une pièce rare d'art et d'une cantou avec une flamme bleue glaciale. Récompensez vos clients avec un élément Trône Pic Palais congelés, surgelés exclusif à pic Palais espace personnel. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Umgib dich mit der frostigen Herrlichkeit des Frostgipfelpalastes. Dieser frostige Rückzugsort besteht vollständig aus Eisblöcken und ist mit einem seltenen Kunstwerk, einem Kamin mit gletscherblauer Flamme und einem Fernseher von epischen Ausmaßen ausgestattet. Wenn du wirklich etwas Tolles sehen willst, dann kannst du von deinem Balkon aus eines der größten Lichterschauspiele der Natur betrachten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Circondati dei gelidi splendori del Palazzo glaciale. Composto interamente da blocchi di ghiaccio, questo freddo rifugio contiene un vero capolavoro artistico, un camino con una gelida fiamma blu e una TV di proporzioni epiche. E se le sorprese non dovessero bastare, prova a cercare uno dei più grandi spettacoli di luci della natura dal tuo balcone. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Rodéate con el esplendor glacial del Palacio invernal del pico helado. Construido enteramente con bloques de hielo, este gélido refugio incluye una preciada obra de arte, una chimenea con fuego azul glacial y un televisor de proporciones descomunales. Si buscas un verdadero capricho, intenta observar uno de los mayores espectáculos luminosos de la naturaleza desde tu terraza. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Surround yourself in the frosty splendors of the Frozen Peak Palace. Made entirely from blocks of ice, this frosty getaway comes with a rare piece of art and an inglenook with a glacial blue flame. Reward your guests with a Frozen Peak Palace Throne item, exclusive to Frozen Peak Palace personal space. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">얼어붙은 봉우리의 아름다운 궁전에서 차가운 위엄을 느껴 보십시오. 오직 얼음으로 건축된 이 궁전은 예술품에 더욱 가까운 화로와 거대한 텔레비전을 포함하고 있습니다. 자연이 만들어낸 가장 멋진 빛의 장관을 발코니에서 구경할 수도 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Surround yourself in the frosty splendors of the Frozen Peak Palace. Made entirely from blocks of ice, this frosty getaway comes with a rare piece of art and an inglenook with a glacial blue flame. Reward your guests with a Frozen Peak Palace Throne item, exclusive to Frozen Peak Palace personal space. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">全身投入冰頂峰皇宮的冰霜魅力中。這間冰冷的度假屋全用冰塊建造，附有一件罕有的藝術品、發出冰川藍色火焰的火爐及一台大螢幕電視。如你想擁有不凡的體驗，看看你能否從露台看到大自然其中一個最大型的光影表演。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">全身投入冰頂峰皇宮的冰霜魅力中。這間冰冷的度假屋全用冰塊建造，附有一件罕有的藝術品、發出冰川藍色火焰的火爐及一台大螢幕電視。如你想擁有不凡的體驗，看看你能否從露台看到大自然其中一個最大型的光影表演。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Surround yourself in the frosty splendors of the Frozen Peak Palace. Made entirely from blocks of ice, this frosty getaway comes with a rare piece of art and an inglenook with a glacial blue flame. Reward your guests with a Frozen Peak Palace Throne item, exclusive to Frozen Peak Palace personal space. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>