<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MAG - S.V.E.R Hazard Armor Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">MAG - Pack gilet Danger S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MAG-Paket: Panzerung „Gefahr“ (S.V.E.R.)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">MAG - Pacchetto armatura Hazard S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">MAG: paquete de blindaje Hazard de S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">MAG - S.V.E.R. "위협" 방탄복 팩</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">MAG - S.V.E.R Hazard Armor Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">MAG - S.V.E.R「Hazard」裝甲包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">MAG - S.V.E.R「Hazard」裝甲包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MAG - S.V.E.R Hazard Armor Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This  S.V.E.R. Hazard Armour Pack comes with the unique Hazard Camo Pattern, Hazard Improved Ballistic Vest and the Hazard Improved Helmet. S.V.E.R. operatives live for the chance to achieve the honour they believe they deserve. The Hazard design is ideal for instilling the fear they are so used to administering on the battlefield. "The fire within fuels the true warrior." [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce pack gilet Danger S.V.E.R. est disponible dans sa version Camouflage Danger unique, avec un gilet pare-balles et un casque améliorés Danger. Les agents S.V.E.R. vivent pour avoir la chance de recevoir l'honneur qu'ils pensent mériter. Le concept Danger saura rendre la peur qu'ils ont l'habitude de susciter sur le champ de bataille. "La flamme sacrée anime le vrai guerrier." [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die S.V.E.R.-Panzerung „Gefahr“ umfasst das einzigartige „Gefahr“-Tarnmuster, die verbesserte „Gefahr“-Ballistikpanzerung und den verbesserten „Gefahr“-Helm. S.V.E.R.-Soldaten leben für den Ruhm, den sie sich in ihren Augen auch verdient haben. Das „Gefahr“-Design eignet sich ideal dafür, genau die Angst zu verbreiten, für die sie auch auf dem Schlachtfeld bekannt sind. „Den wahren Krieger treibt sein inneres Feuer.“ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il pacchetto armatura Hazard S.V.E.R. presenta un motivo mimetico originale Hazard, il giubbotto balistico potenziato Hazard e l'elmetto potenziato Hazard. I soldati S.V.E.R. combattono per conseguire la gloria che credono fermamente di meritare. Il modello Hazard è perfetto per infondere timore sul campo di battaglia. "Il vero guerriero è mosso dal fuoco interiore". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El paquete de blindaje Hazard de S.V.E.R. viene con el único diseño de camuflaje Hazard, el chaleco antibalas mejorado Hazard y el casco mejorado Hazard. Los agentes de S.V.E.R. viven por la oportunidad de lograr el honor que creen merecer. El diseño Hazard es ideal para infundir el terror que suelen inspirar en el campo de batalla. "El fuego interior alimenta al verdadero guerrero". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">S.V.E.R. 의 "위협" 방탄복 팩은 "위협" 시리즈의 방탄복 아이템을 모두 포함합니다. S.V.E.R.의 전우들은 자신들의 몫인 명예를 쟁취하기 위해 전투를 벌입니다. "위협" 라인의 방탄복은 적들에게 공포를 일으키고, "진정한 전사는 내면의 열정에 의해 움직인다"는 S.V.E.R.의 철학을 그대로 반영합니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This  S.V.E.R. Hazard Armor Pack comes with the unique Hazard Camo Pattern, Hazard Improved Ballistic Vest and the Hazard Improved Helmet. S.V.E.R. operatives live for the chance to achieve the honor they believe they deserve. The Hazard design is ideal for instilling the fear they are so used to administering on the battlefield. "The fire within fuels the true warrior." [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">S.V.E.R的「Hazard」裝甲包內含獨一無二的「Hazard」迷彩圖案、「Hazard」改良化防彈背心以及「Hazard」改良化頭盔。S.V.E.R.的人員為實現他們所堅信的榮耀而活。「Hazard」的設計滲透著恐怖的氣息，是他們最善於在戰場上讓敵方嚐到的感覺。「靈魂的火焰在真正的戰士心中熊熊燃燒。」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">S.V.E.R的「Hazard」裝甲包內含獨一無二的「Hazard」迷彩圖案、「Hazard」改良化防彈背心以及「Hazard」改良化頭盔。S.V.E.R.的人員為實現他們所堅信的榮耀而活。「Hazard」的設計滲透著恐怖的氣息，是他們最善於在戰場上讓敵方嚐到的感覺。「靈魂的火焰在真正的戰士心中熊熊燃燒。」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This  S.V.E.R. Hazard Armor Pack comes with the unique Hazard Camo Pattern, Hazard Improved Ballistic Vest and the Hazard Improved Helmet. S.V.E.R. operatives live for the chance to achieve the honor they believe they deserve. The Hazard design is ideal for instilling the fear they are so used to administering on the battlefield. "The fire within fuels the true warrior." [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>