<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Plum Tree Pavilion Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Prunier pavillon clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Pflaumenbaum-Pavillon: Clubhaus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sede del club Padiglione delle susine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sede del club Pabellón del ciruelo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Plum Tree Pavilion Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">자두나무 파빌리온 클럽하우스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Plum Tree Pavilion Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">李子樹大樓聯盟俱樂部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">李子樹大樓聯盟俱樂部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Plum Tree Pavilion Clubhouse</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take a deep breath and inhale the soft sweet aroma of the Plum Tree Pavilion. Its gentle landscaping and exquisite architecture makes this space ideal for anyone who’s a fan of fishponds and rock formations. The Plum Tree Pavilion is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Prenez une profonde respiration et inhaler l'odeur douce douce du Pavillon prunier. Son aménagement paysager doux et architecture exquise fait cet idéal d'espace pour quelqu'un qui a un fan de viviers et de formations rocheuses, de posséder. Le Pavillon du prunier est un club où chacun est invité à se joindre. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Atme tief ein und inhaliere das weiche, süße Aroma des Pflaumenbaum-Pavillons. Dank der schönen Landschaft und der herrlichen Architektur ist dieser Bereich ideal für alle Fans von Fischteichen und Felsformationen. Der Pflaumenbaum-Pavillon ist ein Clubhaus, in dem jeder Gast willkommen ist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fai un respiro profondo e lasciati inondare dal dolce aroma del Padiglione delle susine. La sua delicata e ricercata architettura del paesaggio rende questo spazio ideale per chiunque ami i laghetti con i pesci e le formazioni rocciose. Il Padiglione delle susine è una sede del club dove chiunque è il benvenuto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Respira hondo e inhala el aroma suave y dulce del Pabellón del ciruelo. Su paisaje delicado y su exquisita arquitectura convierten este espacio en ideal para todo aquel al que le guste tener estanques de peces y formaciones rocosas. El Pabellón del ciruelo es una sede del club a la que todos están invitados. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Take a deep breath and inhale the soft sweet aroma of the Plum Tree Pavilion. Its gentle landscaping and exquisite architecture makes this space ideal for anyone who’s a fan of fishponds and rock formations, to own. The Plum Tree Pavilion is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">크게 숨을 들이쉬고 자두나무 파빌리온의 부드럽고 달콤한 향기를 맡으세요. 이 장소의 아름다운 지형과 독특한 건축은 물고기가 사는 웅덩이와 신기한 돌을 좋아하는 사람이라면 누구나 어울리는 장소입니다. 자두나무 파빌리온은 누구나 환영받는 클럽하우스입니다. ※주의: 클럽하우스에 입장하려면 먼저 클럽을 구매해야 합니다.
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Take a deep breath and inhale the soft sweet aroma of the Plum Tree Pavilion. Its gentle landscaping and exquisite architecture makes this space ideal for anyone who’s a fan of fishponds and rock formations, to own. The Plum Tree Pavilion is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. *Please note, in order to access the Plum Tree Pavilion Clubhouse, you will need to have purchased the Club Slot. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在香氣芬芳的李子樹大樓內深呼吸。其平伏的地勢和獨特的建築，最適合任何喜歡魚塘石景的人。李子樹大樓聯盟俱樂部是一個歡迎任何人加入的聯盟俱樂部。※請注意，要使用李子樹大樓聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在香氣芬芳的李子樹大樓內深呼吸。其平伏的地勢和獨特的建築，最適合任何喜歡魚塘石景的人。李子樹大樓聯盟俱樂部是一個歡迎任何人加入的聯盟俱樂部。※請注意，要使用李子樹大樓聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Take a deep breath and inhale the soft sweet aroma of the Plum Tree Pavilion. Its gentle landscaping and exquisite architecture makes this space ideal for anyone who’s a fan of fishponds and rock formations, to own. The Plum Tree Pavilion is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>