<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">PlayStation®Move motion controller (Male avatar)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Manette de détection de mouvements PlayStation®Move (Avatar masculin)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">PlayStation®Move-Motion-Controller (männlicher Avatar)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Controller di movimento PlayStation®Move (avatar maschile)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mando de movimiento PlayStation®Move (avatar masculino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">PlayStation®Move 모션 컨트롤러 (남성 아바타)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">PlayStation®Move motion controller (Male avatar)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">PlayStation®Move動態控制器(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">PlayStation®Move動態控制器(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">PlayStation®Move motion controller (Male avatar)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Get your (virtual) hands on the PlayStation®Move motion controller. It changes color, just like the real motion controller coming out later this year, and is guaranteed to liven up your next Central Plaza dance party! For male avatars only.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tenez entre vos mains (virtuelles) la manette de détection de mouvements PlayStation®Move. Elle change de couleur, exactement comme la vraie manette de détection de mouvements qui sortira plus tard cette année. Effet tendance garanti pour votre prochaine fête dans la place Home ! Pour les avatars masculins seulement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nehmen Sie den PlayStation®Move-Motion-Controller in Ihre (virtuellen) Hände. Er wechselt seine Farbe wie der echte Motion-Controller, der im Laufe dieses Jahres erhältlich sein wird, und ist garantiert der Hit auf Ihrer nächsten Tanzparty auf dem Home-Platz! Nur für männliche Avatare.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Impugna (virtualmente) il controller di movimento PlayStation®Move che cambia colore, proprio come il vero controller di movimento in arrivo quest'anno, accendendo la tua prossima festa danzante in piazza Home! Solo per avatar maschili.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hazte (virtualmente) con el mando de movimiento PlayStation®Move. Cambia de color como el mando de movimiento de verdad que sale este mismo año. ¡Con él, la diversión está garantizada en tu próxima fiesta de baile en la Plaza central! Solo para avatares masculinos.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">PlayStation®Move 모션 컨트롤러를 (가상의 공간에서) 직접 소유할 수 있는 기회입니다. 진짜 모션 컨트롤러처럼 색깔을 바꾸기도 한답니다. 올해 말 출시 예정이며, 댄스 파티에 참가할 일이 있다면 필수로 챙겨가야할 물건입니다! 남성용입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Get your (virtual) hands on the PlayStation®Move motion controller. It changes color, just like the real motion controller coming out later this year. For male avatars only.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">讓您的分身角色手上拿著PlayStation®Move動態控制器吧。這可以變更顏色，就像是預定在今年下半年發售的PlayStation®Move動態控制器一樣。僅限男性分身角色使用。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">讓您的分身角色手上拿著PlayStation®Move動態控制器吧。這可以變更顏色，就像是預定在今年下半年發售的PlayStation®Move動態控制器一樣。僅限男性分身角色使用。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Get your (virtual) hands on the PlayStation®Move motion controller. It changes color, just like the real motion controller coming out later this year, and is guaranteed to liven up your next Central Plaza dance party! For male avatars only.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>