<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tycoon Furniture Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack de meubles de Magnat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tycoon – Möbelpaket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto arredamento Attico magnate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack de muebles Magnate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">タイクーン・ペントハウス家具セット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">재벌의 가구 세트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Tycoon Furniture Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">大亨家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">大亨家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Tycoon Furniture Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Tycoon Furniture Pack. Pack includes two chairs, desk, lamp, table end, bed, sofa, bookshelf and a working jacuzzi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le pack de meubles de Magnat. Le pack comprend deux chaises, un bureau, une lampe, un bout de table, un lit, un fauteuil, une étagère et un bain à remous prêt à l'emploi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Tycoon-Möbelpaket beinhaltet zwei Sessel, einen Schreibtisch, eine Lampe, einen Beistelltisch, ein Bett, ein Sofa, ein Bücherregal und ein funktionierendes Sprudelbad. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il pacchetto arredamento Attico magnate. Il pacchetto comprende due sedie, una scrivania, una lampada, un tavolino, un letto, un divano, una libreria, e una vasca a idromassaggio. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El pack de muebles Magnate. Incluye dos sillas, un escritorio, una lámpara, una mesa, una cama, un sofá, una librería y una bañera de hidromasaje. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">パーソナルスペース「タイクーン・ペントハウス」にぴったりな家具のセットです。\n\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n・オフィスチェア（タイクーン・ペントハウス）（チェア）\n・モダンチェア（タイクーン・ペントハウス）（チェア）\n・オフィスデスク（タイクーン・ペントハウス）（テーブル）\n・サイドテーブル（タイクーン・ペントハウス）（テーブル）\n・ベッド（タイクーン・ペントハウス）（ソファー）\n・モダンソファー（タイクーン・ペントハウス）（ソファー）\n・ブックシェルフ（タイクーン・ペントハウス）（収納家具）\n・ランプ（タイクーン・ペントハウス）（照明器具）\n・ジャグジー（タイクーン・ペントハウス）（装飾品）※\n購入すると、該当カテゴリーに各アイテムが追加されます。\n※このアイテムは、アニメーションや機能が追加されているアドバンスド家具です。この種類のアイテムは配置できる数に制限があります。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">재벌의 가구 세트! 의자(x2), 책상(x1), 램프(x1), 서랍장(x1), 침대(x1), 소파(x1), 책장(x1), 그리고 욕조(X1)를 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Tycoon Furniture Pack. Pack includes two chairs, desk, lamp, table end, bed, sofa, bookshelf and a working jacuzzi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這是大亨家具組合包，包括椅子(x2)、桌子(x1)、燈(x1)、茶几(x1)、床(x1)、沙發(x1)、書櫃(x1)、以及熱水浴池(X1)。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這是大亨家具組合包，包括椅子(x2)、桌子(x1)、燈(x1)、茶几(x1)、床(x1)、沙發(x1)、書櫃(x1)、以及熱水浴池(X1)。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Tycoon Furniture Pack. Pack includes two chairs, desk, lamp, table end, bed, sofa, bookshelf and a working jacuzzi. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>