<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LOOT™ Pet Basket - Yellow</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Panier animal de compagnie LOOT™ - Jaune</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LOOT™ Haustierkörbchen - Gelb</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cesta LOOT™ - Giallo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cesta para mascotas LOOT™ - Amarillo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LOOT™ Pet Basket - Yellow</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Do you share your HOME with a cute LOOT™ Schnauzer Puppy or Dragosaur? Now you can decorate your personal space for your companions with LOOT™ Animal Furnishings. Those cute critters won’t be able to interact with the items, but at least they’ll know they’re HOME. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Partagez-vous votre espace HOME avec un chiot Schnauzer LOOT™ tout mignon ou un Dragosaur ? Et bien maintenant vous pouvez décorer votre espace personnel pour vos compagnons avec le Mobilier Animalier LOOT™. Ces petites créatures ne pourront pas interagir avec les objets mais, au moins, ils sauront qu'ils sont dans HOME. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Teilst du dein HEIM mit einem niedlichen LOOT™ Schnauzer-Welpen oder einem Drachosaurus? Jetzt kannst du deine Privaträume mit LOOT™ Tierzubehör für deine Haustiere einrichten. Die süßen kleinen Viecher können vielleicht nicht damit spielen, aber zumindest fühlen sie sich wohl da HOME. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai in CASA un graziosissimo cucciolo di Schnauzer o Dragosauro LOOT™? Allieta i tuoi amici a quattro zampe con gli accessori per animali LOOT™. I tuoi animali si sentiranno A HOME! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Compartes tu CASA con un encantador cachorro Schnauzer o Dragosaurio LOOT™? Pues ya puedes decorar el espacio personal para tus compañeros con los accesorios para animales LOOT™. Estas encantadoras criaturas no pueden interactuar con los artículos, pero al menos se sentirán en HOME. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Do you share your HOME with a cute LOOT™ Schnauzer Puppy or Dragosaur? Now you can decorate your personal space for your companions with LOOT™ Animal Furnishings. Those cute critters won’t be able to interact with the items, but at least they’ll know they’re HOME. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>