<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Casino: Penthouse Suite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Casino : Suite Penthouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Kasino: Penthouse Suite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">The Casino: Penthouse Suite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Casino: Penthouse Suite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Casino: Penthouse Suite</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to our exclusive Penthouse suite strictly reserved for those in our Millionaire's Club. The concierge is on standby 24 hours a day to manage any of your needs. Enjoy your stay at the Paradise Hotel and Casino.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue dans nos exclusives suites Penthouse strictement réservées aux membres de notre Club de Millionnaires. Le concierge est à disposition 24 heures par jour pour gérer tous vos besoins. Profitez de votre séjour au Paradise and Casino Hotel.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen in unserer exklusiven Penthouse Suite ausschliesslich reserviert für die Mitglieder des Millionär-Klubs.  Der Portier ist rund um die Uhr verfügbar um sich um Ihre Bedürfnisse zu kümmern. Geniessen Sie Ihren Aufenthalt im Paradise Hotel und Kasino.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuti nella nostra esclusiva suite Penthouse, che è strettamente riservata ai soci del Club Millionaire. Il concierge è a disposizione 24/24 per soddisfare tutte le vostre necessità. Vi auguriamo un piacevole soggiorno al Paradise Hotel e Casino.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenidos a nuestro  Penthouse Suite, exclusivamente reservado por los miembros de nuestro Millionaire's Club. El conserje está listo las 24 horas para manejar cualquier necisidad que usted tenga. Disfrute su estadia en el Paradise Hotel and Casino.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome to our exclusive Penthouse suite strictly reserved for those in our Millionaire's Club. The concierge is on standby 24 hours a day to manage any of your needs. Enjoy your stay at the Paradise Hotel and Casino.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>