<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rock Reveller – Tour Bus Mega Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rock Fêtard - Super lot Tourbus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rock-Zecher – Touren-Bus-Megabündel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vizi Rock - Mega Pacchetto Bus di Giro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">ERockero – El Conjunto Mega Autobús de Gira</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rock Reveller – Tour Bus Mega Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Including: tour bus, vehicle seat, kitchen - corner unit, hob unit, oven housing, sink unit and standard unit, settee - corner piece and straight piece, stool, acoustic and electric guitar wall hangings, gold and platinum disc wall hanging, exclusive tour bus top, trousers, boots and hat for her and cardigan top, trousers, boots and hat for him! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Comprend tourbus, un siège, une cuisine (meuble d’angle, plaques chauffantes, four, évier et placards), un canapé (d’angle et standard), un pouf, des tableaux de guitare acoustique et électrique et un tableau de disques d’or et de platine. Pour les femmes, un haut de tourbus exclusif, un pantalon, des bottes et chapeau et pour les hommes, un gilet, un pantalon des bottes et Chapeau! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Einschließlich: Touren-Bus, Autositz, Küche, Eckschrank, Herd, Ofen, Spüle und Standardschrank, Sofa (Ecksitz) und Dreisitzer, Hocker, Bilder von akustischer und elektrischer Gitarre, Gold- und Platin-Schallplatten, exklusives Touren-Bus-Oberteil, Hose, Stiefel und Hut für Sie, sowie Strickjacke, Hose, Stiefel und Hut für Ihn! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Con bus di giro, sedile, cucinotto (elemento angolare, fornello, cassa per forno, elemento lavello ed elemento standard) divanetto (elemento angolare e dritto) sgabello, quadri con chitarra acustica ed elettrica, quadro con disco d’oro e disco di platino, esclusivo top tour, pantaloni, stivali e cappello per lei e cardigan, pantaloni, stivali e cappello per lui!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Incluye: autobús de gira, asiento de vehículo, cocina (unidad de esquina, unidad de cocina, mueble para el horno, unidad de fregadero y unidad standard), sofá (de esquina y recto), taburete, lienzos de guitarra acústica y eléctrica, lienzos de disco de oro y platino, techo de autobús de gira exclusivo, pantalones, botas y sombrero para ella y chaqueta, pantalones, botas y sombrero para él. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Including: tour bus, vehicle seat, kitchen - corner unit, hob unit, oven housing, sink unit and standard unit, settee - corner piece and straight piece, stool, acoustic and electric guitar wall hangings, gold and platinum disc wall hanging, exclusive tour bus top, trousers, boots and hat for her and cardigan top, trousers, boots and hat for him! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>