<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Forsaken Planet – Globe Logo (Active)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Forsaken Planet - Logo Globe (Actif)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Forsaken Planet – Globe Logo (Active)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Forsaken Planet – Logo Globe (Active)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Forsaken Planet – Logotipo del planeta (Activo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Forsaken Planet – Globe Logo (Active)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Forsaken Planet – Globe Logo (Active)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kNameTemp</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Forsaken Planet – Rewards (Active)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Forsaken Planet - Récompenses (Actives)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Forsaken Planet – Belohnungen (aktiv)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Forsaken Planet – Ricompense (attivo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Forsaken Planet – Recompensas (activo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Forsaken Planet – Rewards (Active)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Forsaken Planet – Rewards (Active)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Show off your love of Forsaken Planet™ with this sweet trophy! To retrieve your rewards, create or access your LOOT™ Entertainment account by logging in by using the Forsaken Planet globe logo in the LOOT Space Station Hub. All rewards are exclusive to PlayStation®Home users and can only be retrieved inside Home. Purchasing the following items from the LOOT™ store unlocks rewards in the Forsaken Planet game: (1) Companion unlocks a hat. The Companions bundle unlocks a Character and the hat. The Turret (Active) unlocks a gun. Purchasing the Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle unlocks the Character, the hat, the gun and a UFO.  All rewards unlock specialized gameplay perks within the Forsaken Planet videogame! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Exprimez votre amour pour Forsaken Planet™ avec ce beau trophée ! Pour récupérer vos récompenses, créez ou accédez à votre Compte LOOT™ Entertainment en vous connectant en utilisant le logo du globe Forsaken Planet dans le hall de la Station Spatiale LOOT. Toutes les récompenses sont exclusives aux utilisateurs de  PlayStation®Home et ne peuvent être récupérées que dans Home. L'achat des articles suivants dans la boutique LOOT™ libère des récompenses dans le jeu Forsaken Planet : (1) Un compagnon libère un chapeau. Le lot Compagnons libère un Personnage et un chapeau. La Tourelle (Active) libère un canon. L'achat du Lot Ultime Forsaken Planet libère un personnage, un chapeau, un canon et une soucoupe volante.  Toutes les récompenses débloquent des avantages spécifiques dans la jouabilité du jeu vidéo Forsaken Planet! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeige mit dieser herrlichen Trophäe anderen deine Liebe zu „Forsaken Planet™“! Um deine Belohnungen abzurufen, erstelle ein LOOT™ Entertainment-Konto oder greife auf dein bestehendes LOOT™ Entertainment-Konto zu, indem du dich über das Globuslogo von „Forsaken Planet“ im LOOT-Raumstationknotenpunkt anmeldest. Alle Belohnungen sind nur für PlayStation®Home-Benutzer vorgesehen und können nur innerhalb von Home abgerufen werden. Durch den Kauf der folgenden Gegenstände im LOOT™-Laden werden Belohnungen im Spiel „Forsaken Planet“ freigeschaltet: (1) Durch einen Begleiter wird ein Hut freigeschaltet. Das Paket „Begleiter“ schaltet einen Charakter und den Hut frei. Die Waffenkanzel (aktiv) schaltet eine Schusswaffe frei. Durch den Kauf des Pakets „Forsaken Planet Ultimate“ wird der Charakter, der Hut, die Schusswaffe und ein UFO freigeschaltet. Alle Belohnungen schalten spezielle Vorteile im Videospiel „Forsaken Planet“ frei! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mostra a tutti il tuo amore per Forsaken Planet™ con questo dolce trofeo! Per ricevere le tue ricompense, accedi con il tuo account LOOT™ Entertainment (o creane uno) eseguendo il login tramite il logo del pianeta di Forsaken Planet nella Stazione spaziale di LOOT. Tutte le ricompense sono riservate agli utenti PlayStation®Home e possono essere ottenute solamente all'interno di Home. Le ricompense di gioco di Forsaken Planet vengono sbloccate mediante l'acquisto dei seguenti oggetti dal negozio LOOT™: (1) Compagno sblocca un cappello. Il pacchetto Compagni sblocca un personaggio e il cappello. La torretta (attivo) sblocca una pistola. L'acquisto del pacchetto Forsaken Planet Supremo sblocca il personaggio, il cappello, la pistola e un UFO. Tutte le ricompense sbloccano extra di gioco speciali in Forsaken Planet! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Demuestra tu amor por Forsaken Planet™ con este maravilloso trofeo! Para conseguir tus premios, crea o accede a tu cuenta de LOOT™ Entertainment iniciando sesión a través del logotipo del globo de Forsaken Planet en el Hub de la estación especial LOOT. Todos los premios son exclusivos para usuarios de PlayStation®Home y solo se puede acceder a ellos desde Home. Al comprar los siguientes artículos en la tienda LOOT™ desbloquearás premios en el juego Forsaken Planet: (1) El compañero desbloquea un sombrero. El lote de compañeros desbloquea un personaje y el sombrero. La torreta (activa) desbloquea una pistola. Al comprar el Gran lote Forsaken Planet se desbloquea el personaje, el sombrero, la pistola y un OVNI. ¡Todos los premios desbloquean extras especiales en el videojuego Forsaken Planet! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Show off your love of Forsaken Planet™ with this sweet trophy! To retrieve your rewards, create or access your LOOT™ Entertainment account by logging in by using the Forsaken Planet globe logo in the LOOT Space Station Hub. All rewards are exclusive to PlayStation®Home users and can only be retrieved inside Home. Purchasing the following items from the LOOT™ store unlocks rewards in the Forsaken Planet game: (1) Companion unlocks a hat. The Companions bundle unlocks a Character and the hat. The Turret (Active) unlocks a gun. Purchasing the Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle unlocks the Character, the hat, the gun and a UFO.  All rewards unlock specialized gameplay perks within the Forsaken Planet videogame! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Show off your love of Forsaken Planet™ with this sweet trophy! To retrieve your rewards, create or access your LOOT™ Entertainment account by logging in by using the Forsaken Planet globe logo in the LOOT Space Station Hub. All rewards are exclusive to PlayStation®Home users and can only be retrieved inside Home. Purchasing the following items from the LOOT™ store unlocks rewards in the Forsaken Planet game: (1) Companion unlocks a hat. The Companions bundle unlocks a Character and the hat. The Turret (Active) unlocks a gun. Purchasing the Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle unlocks the Character, the hat, the gun and a UFO.  All rewards unlock specialized gameplay perks within the Forsaken Planet videogame! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>