<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Novus Prime Concept: The Gladius</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Concept de Novus Prime : Le Gladius</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Novus Prime Konzept: The Gladius</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Design Novus Prime: Gladius</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Concepto de Novus Prime: Gladius</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムのコンセプト：グラディアス</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임 컨셉: 글라디우스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Novus Prime Concept: The Gladius</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Novus Prime概念畫：Gladius</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Novus Prime概念畫：Gladius</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Novus Prime Concept: The Gladius</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. The Gladius fighter ship is a versatile vessel of the Earth Fleet, capable of shattering an enemy's shielding with a single hit from its powerful Charged Shot. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ornez vos murs de peintures conceptuelles de Novus Prime. Le vaisseau de combat Gladius est un vaisseau polyvalent de la flotte Terrestre, capable de briser le bouclier d'un ennemi d'un seul de ses puissants tirs chargés. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schmücke deine Wände mit den Konzeptzeichnungen von Novus Prime. Das Gladius Kriegsschiff ist ein wendiges Schiff der Erdenflotte. Mit seinem mächtigen Charge Shot kann es feindliche Schutzschilde mit nur einem einzigen Treffer zerstören. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Decora le tue pareti con il design della Novus Prime. Il caccia Gladius è una navetta versatile della Flotta Terrestre, in grado di distruggere uno scudo nemico con un solo colpo caricato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Adorna tus paredes con las pinturas conceptuales de Novus Prime. La nave de combate Gladius es un navío de la Flota de la Tierra, capaz de destruir los escudos de tus enemigos con un solo ataque de su poderoso disparo cargado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムのコンセプト絵画を壁に飾ろう。グラディアスは地球軍が誇る多目的大型船だ。その強烈なチャージショットは一撃で敵のシールドを粉砕できる。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임의 컨셉화로 벽을 장식합니다. 글라디우스 전투기는 지구 함대의 다목적 함선으로, 강력한 충전 발사 능력으로 단발에 적의 방어막을 분쇄할 수 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. The Gladius fighter ship is a versatile vessel of the Earth Fleet, capable of shattering an enemy's shielding with a single hit from its powerful Charged Shot. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用Novus Prime的概念繪畫裝飾你的牆壁。Gladius是地球艦隊一架多功能的戰鬥機，能使用能量累積射擊砲一擊粉碎敵人的防護罩。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用Novus Prime的概念繪畫裝飾你的牆壁。Gladius是地球艦隊一架多功能的戰鬥機，能使用能量累積射擊砲一擊粉碎敵人的防護罩。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. The Gladius fighter ship is a versatile vessel of the Earth Fleet, capable of shattering an enemy's shielding with a single hit from its powerful Charged Shot. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>