<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Air-Drums Sound Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Collection sonore Air-batterie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sammlung von Sounds der Air-Drums</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Collezione di suoni "Air-Drums"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Colección de sonidos "Air-Drums"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Air-Drums Sound Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A collection of 3 air-drums animations, with drum samples which can be heard by other avatars near you. You can choose between the slow loop, the fast loop, and drumsticks-tapping. Press square for the contextual menu, to choose the sound sample and its associated animation. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une collection de 3 animations d'Air-batterie, avec des effets sonores audibles par les autres utilisateurs à proximité. Appuyez sur carré pour le menu contextuel, qui vous permet de choisir entre la boucle lente, la boucle rapide, et taper les baguettes.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine Sammlung von 3 Animationen, mit Trommel Klangen, die von anderen Avataren in Ihrer Nähe zu hören ist. Sie können zwischen der schnellen Schleife, die langsame Schleife, und Drumsticks-schneidend wählen. Drücken Sie Quadrat für das Kontextmenü, um den Sound Probe und die damit verbundenen Animation zu wählen. Drücken Sie Quadrat für das Kontextmenü, um die Interaktion zu wählen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una collezione di 3 animazioni, con effetti sonori, udibili da parte di altri utenti nelle vicinanze. Premere quadrato al menu di scelta rapida che consente di scegliere tra il ciclo veloce, il ciclo lento, e bacchette intercettazioni. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una colección de 3 animaciones Air-guitar, con efectos de sonido audibles por otros usuarios cercanos. Presione cuadrado al menú contextual que le permite elegir entreel bucle rápido, el bucle lento, y baquetas-tapping. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A collection of 3 air-drums animations, with drum samples which can be heard by other avatars near you. You can choose between the fast loop, the slow loop, and drumsticks-tapping. Press square for the contextual menu, to choose the sound sample and its associated animation. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kHorn</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Drumstick-tapping</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Taper les baguettes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drumsticks-schneidend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bacchette intercettazioni</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Baquetas-tapping</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Drumstick-tapping</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kCow</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fast loop</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Boucle rapide</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schnelle Schleife</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ciclo veloce</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bucle rápido</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fast loop</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kSheep</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Slow loop</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Boucle rapide</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Langsame Schleife</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ciclo lento</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bucle lento</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Slow loop</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>