<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Somewhere Outback Dress - Off Black (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Robe Somewhere Outback - Noir mat (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Somewhere Outback  Kleid - Grau (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Somewhere Outback Vestito - Nero (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Somewhere Outback Vestido - Negro apagado (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A definite must-have party dress from our Designer's Closet collection, the Somewhere Outback dress wows with a structured, strapless bust in faux leather, making for a very cool contrast to the flowing chiffon skirt. The length hits above the knee. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Robe de fête incontournable de notre collection Designer's Closet, la robe Somewhere Outback étonne avec son buste structuré en faux cuir sans bretelles, qui contraste délicieusement avec la gracieuse jupe en mousseline. Elle tombe au-dessus du genou. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Partykleid, das in keinem Kleiderschrank fehlen darf: das schulterfreie Somewhere Outback Kleid aus unserer Kollektion Designer's Closet mit verstärktem Oberteil aus Lederimitat für den coolen Kontrast zum fließenden Rock aus Chiffon. Knappe Knielänge. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un "must" da indossare ad ogni party dalla nostra collezione Designer's Closet, il vestito Somewhere Outback presenta un corpetto strutturato in finta pelle senza bretelle, che contrasta perfettamente con l'ampia gonna in chiffon. La lunghezza è sopra il ginocchio. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un vestido de gala verdaderamente imprescindible de nuestra colección del Guardarropa de diseñadores, el vestido Somewhere Outback te deja boquiabierto con su busto y torso rígidos sin tirantes y en cuero de imitación, creando un sensacional contraste con la falda de raso suelta, cuya longitud llega hasta por encima de la rodilla. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>