<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Twin Pulse Cannons (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Canons à pulsion jumelle (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zwillingsimpulskanone (weibliche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cannoni a impulso gemelli (per donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cañones gemelos de impulsos (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ツインパルスキャノン（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Twin Pulse Cannons (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Twin Pulse Cannons (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Released on an experimental basis by Novus Prime Technologies Research, these shoulder-mounted cannons fire rapid pulses of focused disruptive force, similar to the Pulse Shot weapon employed by the Kunai fighter ship.  The current model is controlled entirely by voice commands, and a mental control system is currently in development. This item passively feeds skills and knowledge to its owner, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base experience point gains by about 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Développé de manière expérimentale par la recherche Novus Prime Technologies, ces canons montés sur épaule tirent des pulsions rapides de force disruptive concentrée, similaire au Canon à impulsion du vaisseau de combat Kunai. Le modèle actuel est contrôlé entièrement par commande vocale mais un système de contrôle mental est actuellement en cours de développement. Cet objet nourrit passivement son porteur de techniques et de connaissances, augmentant efficacement ses gains de points d'expérience de base Novus Prime d'environ 5%.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Freigegeben auf einer experimentellen Basis der Abteilung für Technologische Forschung von Novus Prime, feuert diese schultermontierte Kanone schnelle Impulse von konzentrierter zerstörerischer Energie, ähnlich der Impulswaffe, die von den Kunai Kampfschiffen verwendet wird. Das derzeitige Model wird nur allein durch Stimmkommandos aktiviert. Jedoch ist derzeit ein System zur mentalen Kontrolle in Entwicklung. Dieser Ausrüstungsgegenstand versorgt seinen Träger zusätzlich mit Fähigkeiten und Wissen und erhöht die Zufuhr von Erfahrungspunkten deiner Novus Prime Basis effektiv um ca. 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Rilasciati su base sperimentale dalla Divisione di Ricerca Tecnologica della Novus Prime, questi cannoni da spalla sparano rapidi impulsi di forza distruttiva concentrata, simili al Fuoco ad impulsi impiegato sul  caccia Kunai. Il modello attuale viene controllato interamente attraverso comandi vocali, ma è in via di sviluppo un sistema di controllo mentale. Questo oggetto fornisce a chi ne usufruisce abilità e conoscenza in modo passivo, incrementando l'acquisizione di punti esperienza della base Novus Prime di circa il 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lanzado en base experimenta por Investigación de Tecnologías Novus Prime, estos cañones de fuerzas disruptivas enfocadas de impulsos de fuego rápido sobre los hombres, son similares al arma de Disparo de Impulsos empleadas por la nave de combate Kunai.  El modelo actual es controlado completamente por comandos de voz, y un sistema de control mental está en desarrollo. Este objeto alimenta pasivamente las habilidades y los conocimientos de su dueño, incrementando efectivamente tus puntos de experiencia base Novus Prime en un 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライム技術開発部門によって実験的に発表された、これらの肩装着型キャノンはクナイ戦艦が用いるパルスショット兵器に類似している収束型妨害効果がある速射パルスを発射する。現行型は音声指示によって完全に制御され、精神制御システムは現在開発中である。\n\n※購入すると、ミニゲーム「ノーバス・プライム」内での経験値の増加量が5%上がります。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Released on an experimental basis by Novus Prime Technologies Research, these shoulder-mounted cannons fire rapid pulses of focused disruptive force, similar to the Pulse Shot weapon employed by the Kunai fighter ship.  The current model is controlled entirely by voice commands, and a mental control system is currently in development. This item passively feeds skills and knowledge to its owner, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base experience point gains by about 5%.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Released on an experimental basis by Novus Prime Technologies Research, these shoulder-mounted cannons fire rapid pulses of focused disruptive force, similar to the Pulse Shot weapon employed by the Kunai fighter ship.  The current model is controlled entirely by voice commands, and a mental control system is currently in development. This item passively feeds skills and knowledge to its owner, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base experience point gains by about 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>