<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Boba Fett Mandalorian Armor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Armure Mandalorienne Boba Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Boba Fett mandalorianische Rüstung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Armatura Mandaloriana Boba Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Armadura mandaloriana de Boba Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Female01_TorsoLegsFeet_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Female01_TorsoLegsFeet_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Boba Fett Mandalorian Armor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Female01_TorsoLegsFeet_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Female01_TorsoLegsFeet_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Boba Fett Mandalorian Armor</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">(Torso/pants/shoes) The most famous of the galactic bounty hunters, Boba Fett wore Mandalorian armor and was a clone of the famed Jango Fett. Boba Fett was one of six bounty hunters hired by Darth Vader to track and capture the Millennium Falcon. Fett was successful by setting a trap for the Millennium Falcon on Bespin.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">(Torse/pantalon/chaussures) Boba Fett, le plus célèbre chasseur de primes de la galaxie, porte une armure Mandalorienne et est un clone du non moins célèbre Jango Fett. Boba Fett est l'un des six chasseurs de primes chargés par Dark Vador de traquer et de capturer le Faucon Millenium. Fett a réussi en tendant un piège au Faucon Millenium sur Bespin.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">(Oberkörper/Hose/Schuhe) Als bekanntester der galaktischen Kopfgeldjäger trug Boba Fett eine mandalorianische Rüstung und war ein Klon des berühmten Jango Fett. Boba Fett war einer von sechs Kopfgeldjägern, die Darth Vader anheuerte, um den Millennium Falken zu finden und zu erbeuten. Fett stellte dem Millennium Falken auf Bespin erfolgreich eine Falle.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">(Torso/pantaloni/scarpe) Il più famoso dei cacciatori di taglie galattici, Boba Fett indossava un'armatura mandaloriana ed era un clone del rinomato Jargo Fett. Boba Fett era uno dei sei cacciatori di taglie assoldati da Darth Vader per rintracciare e catturare il Millenium Falcon. Fett era riuscito a tendere una trappola per il Millenium Falcon su Bespin.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">(Torso/pantalones/zapatos) El más famoso de los cazarrecompensas galácticos, Boba Fett, llevaba una armadura mandaloriana y era un clon del famoso Jango Fett. Boba Fett era uno de los seis cazarrecompensas contratados por Darth Vader para localizar y capturar el Halcón Milenario. Fett logró su objetivo poniendo una trampa al Halcón en Bespin.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Female01_TorsoLegsFeet_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Female01_TorsoLegsFeet_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">(Torso/pants/shoes) The most famous of the galactic bounty hunters, Boba Fett wore Mandalorian armor and was a clone of the famed Jango Fett. Boba Fett was one of six bounty hunters hired by Darth Vader to track and capture the Millennium Falcon. Fett was successful by setting a trap for the Millennium Falcon on Bespin.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Female01_TorsoLegsFeet_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Female01_TorsoLegsFeet_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">(Torso/pants/shoes) The most famous of the galactic bounty hunters, Boba Fett wore Mandalorian armor and was a clone of the famed Jango Fett. Boba Fett was one of six bounty hunters hired by Darth Vader to track and capture the Millennium Falcon. Fett was successful by setting a trap for the Millennium Falcon on Bespin.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>