<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Hand Car</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La Draisine à Bras</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Draisine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dresina</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Carretilla de la mano</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* Handcar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Handcar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Handcar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Handcar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Handcar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Hand Car</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Get around a lot quicker with good old fashion elbow grease.  This Handcar can get you from the main town to the mine in no time. Who needs horses to get around when you got this cart. This item increases your avatar speed.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Déplacez-vous plus rapidement en utilisant la bonne vieille huile de coude. Cette Draisine à Bras peut vous emmener de la ville principale à la mine en un rien de temps. Qui a besoin de chevaux pour se déplacer quand vous avez ça. Cet article augmente la vitesse de votre avatar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bewege dich schneller umher mit guter alter Handarbeit.  Diese Draisine bringt dich in kürzester Zeit von der Stadt zur Mine. Wer braucht Pferde, wenn man diesen Wagen hat. Dieser Artikel erhöht Ihre avatar Geschwindigkeit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vai in giro più velocemente con il buon vecchio olio di gomito. Questa Dresina può portarti dal centro della città alla miniera velocemente. Chi ha bisogno di cavalli per andare in giro quando hai questa Dresina. Questa voce la tua velocità avatar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Moverse mucho más rápido con buena grasa del codo de la moda antigua. Este Handcar puede obtener de la ciudad principal de la mina en poco tiempo. ¿Quién necesita los caballos moverse cuando tienes este carro. Este elemento aumenta la velocidad de su avatar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* Pump pump Pump [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Pump pump Pump [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Pump pump Pump [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Pump pump Pump [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Pump pump Pump [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Get around a lot quicker with good old fashion elbow grease.  This Handcar can get you from the main town to the mine in no time. Who needs horses to get around when you got this cart. This item increases your avatar speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>