<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MAG - Valor Bulldog Armor Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">MAG - Pack armure "Bulldog" Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MAG-Paket: Panzerung „Bulldog“ (Valor)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">MAG - Pacchetto armatura "Bulldog" Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">MAG: paquete de blindaje Bulldog de Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">MAG - Valor Bulldog Armor Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">MAG - Valor "불독" 방탄복 팩</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">MAG - Valor Bulldog Armor Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">MAG - Valor「Bulldog」裝甲包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">MAG - Valor「Bulldog」裝甲包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MAG - Valor Bulldog Armor Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Valor Bulldog Armour Pack comes with a unique Bulldog Camo Pattern, the Bulldog Mk 2 Reinforced Fibre and the Bulldog Mk 2 Helmet. For a Valor Company operative, donning the battle tested Bulldog uniform communicates a level of preparedness, induces intimidation in the enemy and perfectly matches their motto – "Improvise, adapt and overcome". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le pack armure "Bulldog" Valor comprend le camouflage "Bulldog", les fibres et le casque renforcés "Bulldog" Mk2. Pour un agent Valor, porter l'uniforme "Bulldog", éprouvé au combat, montre sa préparation, induit la peur chez l'ennemi et correspond parfaitement à sa devise : "Improviser. S'adapter. Vaincre." [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Valor-Panzerung „Bulldog“ umfasst das einzigartige „Bulldog“-Tarnmuster, die verstärkte Panzerung „Bulldog“ Mk 2 und den verstärkten Helm „Bulldog“ Mk 2. Für einen Soldaten der Valor Company bedeutet die kampferprobte „Bulldog“-Uniform einen hohen Grad an Sicherheit, Bedrohlichkeit und Identifikation mit dem Firmenmotto „Improvisieren. Anpassen. Siegen“. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il pachetto armatura "Bulldog" Valor presenta un motivo mimetico originale "Bulldog", l'armatura Mk 2 in fibra rinforzata "Bulldog" e l'elmetto Mk 2 "Bulldog". Per i soldati Valor, indossare le uniformi "Bulldog" collaudate in battaglia è sinonimo di preparazione e ha un potere intimidatorio sul nemico che si accompagna perfettamente al motto "Improvvisa, adattati, domina". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El paquete de blindaje Bulldog de Valor incluye el exclusivo diseño de camuflaje Bulldog, la fibra reforzada Bulldog Mk 2 y el casco Bulldog Mk 2. Para un soldado de Valor Company, enfundarse el uniforme Bulldog, probado en miles de batallas, es símbolo de preparación, intimida al enemigo y resume su lema: "Improvisa, adapta y supera". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Valor Bulldog Armor Pack comes with a unique Bulldog Camo Pattern, the Bulldog Mk 2 Reinforced Fiber and the Bulldog Mk 2 Helmet. For a Valor Company operative, donning the battle tested Bulldog uniform communicates a level of preparedness, induces intimidation in the enemy and perfectly matches their motto – "Improvise, adapt and overcome". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Valor의 "불독" 방탄복 팩은 "불독" 시리즈의 방탄복 아이템을 모두 포함합니다. Valor의 병사에게 전장에서 검증된 "불독" 방탄복이란 싸우기 위해 준비된 최상의 준비자세를 말합니다. 준비와 경험으로 제압할 수 없는 적은 존재하지 않습니다. 그럼 나가서 승리하십시오! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Valor Bulldog Armor Pack comes with a unique Bulldog Camo Pattern, the Bulldog Mk 2 Reinforced Fiber and the Bulldog Mk 2 Helmet. For a Valor Company operative, donning the battle tested Bulldog uniform communicates a level of preparedness, induces intimidation in the enemy and perfectly matches their motto – "Improvise, adapt and overcome". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Valor的「Bulldog」裝甲包內含獨一無二的「Bulldog」迷彩圖案、「Bulldog」MK 2強化纖維及「Bulldog」MK 2頭盔。作為Valor的一員，身穿起「Bulldog」軍服代表對戰鬥的決心、對敵方的威嚇，以及彰顯他們的座右銘：「就地取材、隨機應變、勇於克服」。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Valor的「Bulldog」裝甲包內含獨一無二的「Bulldog」迷彩圖案、「Bulldog」MK 2強化纖維及「Bulldog」MK 2頭盔。作為Valor的一員，身穿起「Bulldog」軍服代表對戰鬥的決心、對敵方的威嚇，以及彰顯他們的座右銘：「就地取材、隨機應變、勇於克服」。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Valor Bulldog Armor Pack comes with a unique Bulldog Camo Pattern, the Bulldog Mk 2 Reinforced Fiber and the Bulldog Mk 2 Helmet. For a Valor Company operative, donning the battle tested Bulldog uniform communicates a level of preparedness, induces intimidation in the enemy and perfectly matches their motto – "Improvise, adapt and overcome". [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>