<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Obsidian Tribus Papilio Forearm and Calf Tattoos</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tatouages Tribus papilio Obsidienne pour avant-bras et mollet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Obsidian Tribus Papilio-Tattoos für Unterarm und Wade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tatuaggi Tribus Papilio nero ossidiana per avambraccio e polpaccio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tatuaje Tribus Papilio obsidiana antebrazo y pantorrilla</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_50</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_50</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Obsidian Tribus Papilio Forearm and Calf Tattoos</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_50</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_50</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Obsidian Tribus Papilio Forearm and Calf Tattoos</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">What girl doesn't love butterflies and ink? Show off your new and unique tattoo!

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Y a-t-il une fille qui n’aime pas l’encre et les papillons ? Exhibez votre nouveau tatouage unique en son genre !

Remarque : Tous les tatouages pour torse ou jambe ne sont pas égaux. Lors de l’achat de cet accessoire de tatouage, il est possible qu’il ne soit pas adapté à tous les habits. N’hésitez pas à prendre notre article gratuit « Torse nu » pour homme ou femme afin d’afficher correctement votre nouveau tatouage ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Welches Mädchen mag nicht Schmetterlinge und Tätowierungen? Trage dein einzigartiges Tattoo voller Stolz!

Hinweis: Nicht alle Gegenstände für Oberkörper oder Beine sind gleich gestaltet. Wenn du dieses Tattoo-Zubehör kaufst, könnte es nicht mit allen Kleidungsstücken harmonieren. Gerne kannst du dir unseren kostenlosen “blanken” Oberkörper für Männer/Frauen holen, um deine neuen Tattoos angemessen zeigen zu können![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">A quale ragazza non piacerebbe farsi tatuare una farfalla? Metti in mostra il tuo nuovo e originale tatuaggio.

Nota: non tutti gli oggetti per torso o gamba sono creati allo stesso modo. Il tatuaggio che ti appresti ad acquistare potrebbe non andare bene su tutti gli articoli di abbigliamento. A questo scopo non esitare a scaricare gratuitamente l'oggetto unisex "Tela nuda" torso per visualizzare correttamente i tuoi nuovi tatuaggi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿A qué chica no le gustan los tatuajes y las mariposas? ¡Luce tu nuevo y único tatuaje!

Nota: no todos los objetos para torso y piernas se crean por igual. Cuando compres este accesorio para un tatuaje, quizá no quede bien con cualquier prenda de ropa. ¡Elige nuestro "Lienzo en blanco" de regalo para hombre o mujer y así podrás lucir tu nuevo tatuaje como se merece![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_50 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_50 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">What girl doesn't love butterflies and ink? Show off your new and unique tattoo!

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_50 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_50 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">What girl doesn't love butterflies and ink? Show off your new and unique tattoo!

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>