<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Elegant Swing Sofa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Balancelle élégante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Elegante Hollywoodschaukel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Elegante divano a dondolo </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Elegante sofá columpio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Elegant Swing Sofa</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">On this 2 person sofa swing, you can experience the joy of relaxing on a garden swing seat, gently rocking in a light breeze with a canopy shielding you from direct sun. This is an interactive active object item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">On peut se relaxer agréablement sur cette balancelle de jardin 2 places, tout en se balançant doucement, avec une brise légère et une tente de jardin pour se protéger du soleil. Il s'agit d'un objet actif interactif. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Auf dieser Hollywoodschaukel für 2 Personen kannst du erleben, wie entspannend es ist, gemütlich in einer sanften Brise im Garten zu schaukeln, während dich ein Baldachin vor direkter Sonneneinstrahlung schützt. Dies ist ein interaktiver, aktiver Gegenstand. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Su questo divano a dondolo a 2 posti, puoi goderti tutto il relax di una sedia a dondolo da giardino, cullato dolcemente da una fresca brezza e protetto dai raggi del sole grazie alla sua tenda. Questo è un oggetto attivo interattivo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con este sofá columpio para dos personas podrás sentir la alegría de relajarte en un columpio de jardín, balanceándote suavemente en una brisa ligera protegido por un toldo de la luz directa del sol. Es un artículo-objeto interactivo activo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">On this 2 person sofa swing, you can experience the joy of relaxing on a garden swing seat, gently rocking in a light breeze with a canopy shielding you from direct sun. This is an interactive active object item. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SetTargetableText</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">S'asseoir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sitzen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Siedi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sentarse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>