<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">WipEout® Pickup Hologram Viewer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">WipEout® Pickup Hologram Viewer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Afficheur holographique d'objets de WipEout®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Holografischer WipEout®-Extra-Betrachter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Visualizzatore ologramma oggetti WipEout®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Visor holográfico de objetos de WipEout®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">WipEout® 픽업 홀로그램 뷰어</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">WipEout® Pickup Hologram Viewer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">WipEout®功能道具瀏覽器</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">WipEout®功能道具瀏覽器</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">AUTO_PILOT_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Autopilot: surrender control of your ship to an automated pilot for a few seconds and admire the scenery.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pilote automatique : laissez le contrôle du vaisseau à un pilote automatique pendant quelques secondes et admirez le paysage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Autopilot: Überlasse für einige Sekunden deine Kontrolle über das Schiff einem professionellen, simulierten Piloten und genieße deine Umgebung.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pilota automatico: cedi i controlli della nave a un pilota virtuale professionista per alcuni secondi e goditi lo scenario.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Piloto automático: cede el control de tu nave durante unos instantes al piloto automático para contemplar las vistas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オートパイロット：一定時間、自動操縦になります。ワイプワールドの景観を楽しんでください。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">오토파일럿: 기체의 조종간에서 손을 놓고, 잠시 주변 경관을 감상하세요.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Autopilot: surrender control of your ship to an automated pilot for a few seconds and admire the scenery.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Autopilot(自動駕駛)：放棄您的飛船操縱，讓一個模擬職業駕駛員駕駛一段時間並一邊欣賞賽道風景。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Autopilot(自動駕駛)：放棄您的飛船操縱，讓一個模擬職業駕駛員駕駛一段時間並一邊欣賞賽道風景。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Autopilot: surrender control of your ship to an automated pilot for a few seconds and admire the scenery.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TURBO_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Activate a Turbo and boost your way through the pack, over a jump, or out of harm's way with a gratifying burst of speed.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Activez un turbo pour distancer la meute ou pour vous éloigner du danger grâce à une puissante accélération.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aktiviere den Turbo und jage mit einer unglaublichen Beschleunigung durch die Fahrzeugmeute, über eine Schanze oder aus der feindlichen Schussbahn.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Attiva il turbo e stacca i tuoi avversari, fuggi dal pericolo o risali il gruppo a tutta velocità.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Usa un turbo para adelantar a tus rivales, impulsarte en un salto o evitar una situación peligrosa con un gratificante acelerón.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ターボ：クラフトを瞬時に加速させます。ジャンプ前に使用してコースを飛び越えたり、ゴール前での一発逆転に使いましょう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">터보 부스트를 활성화하면 경쟁자들을 제치고 멋지게 달려나갈 수 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Activate a Turbo and boost your way through the pack, over a jump, or out of harm's way with a gratifying burst of speed.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在經過對手集團時、跳躍之後、或是通過損傷地帶時，啟動噴射加速來施展一個令人滿意的加速效果吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在經過對手集團時、跳躍之後、或是通過損傷地帶時，啟動噴射加速來施展一個令人滿意的加速效果吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Activate a Turbo and boost your way through the pack, over a jump, or out of harm's way with a gratifying burst of speed.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SHIELD_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Shield: become invulnerable to weapons fire or collision damage for a brief period with this protective energy field.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bouclier : le champ énergétique du bouclier protège des dégâts dus aux armes et aux collisions pendant un court laps de temps.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schild: Mit diesem schützenden Energieschild bist du für kurze Zeit gegen Waffen- und Kollisionsschäden immun.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scudo: campo di forza protettivo che per un breve periodo ti rende invulnerabile alle armi da fuoco o ai danni da collisione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Escudo: vuélvete invulnerable a los ataques de tu enemigo y a las colisiones durante un corto periodo de tiempo gracias a este campo de energía.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">シールド：ライバルからの攻撃や衝突から一定時間クラフトを保護します。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">실드: 무기의 공격이나 충돌 피해에서 잠시 동안 보호받을 수 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Shield: become invulnerable to weapons fire or collision damage for a brief period with this protective energy field.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Shield(防護罩)：施展能源防護罩可在一段固定時間內不受到武器攻擊或衝撞的損傷。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Shield(防護罩)：施展能源防護罩可在一段固定時間內不受到武器攻擊或衝撞的損傷。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Shield: become invulnerable to weapons fire or collision damage for a brief period with this protective energy field.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BOMB_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bomb: unleash this high-grade wide-radius explosive from the rear of your ship and prepare for a satisfying detonation.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bombe : lâchez ce puissant explosif au rayon d'action étendu depuis l'arrière de votre vaisseau et attendez-vous à une détonation bien jouissive.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bombe: Schieße diese hochexplosive, weitreichende Waffe aus dem Heck deines Fahrzeugs und genieße ihre unglaubliche Detonation.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bomba: sgancia dal retro della nave questo potente esplosivo ad ampio raggio e preparati a una gratificante detonazione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bomba: descarga este potente explosivo de amplio alcance desde la parte posterior de tu nave y prepárate para disfrutar de la explosión.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">バクダン：クラフト後方に爆弾を落とします。その爆発力は強烈です。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">폭탄: 고성능 광역 폭탄을 기체의 후미에서 발사합니다. 멋진 폭발이 일어납니다!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Bomb: unleash this high-grade wide-radius explosive from the rear of your ship and prepare for a satisfying detonation.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Bomb(炸彈)： 從您的飛船後方釋放高效能、廣範圍炸彈並準備進行令人滿意的爆破。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Bomb(炸彈)： 從您的飛船後方釋放高效能、廣範圍炸彈並準備進行令人滿意的爆破。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Bomb: unleash this high-grade wide-radius explosive from the rear of your ship and prepare for a satisfying detonation.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MINES_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Drop a quintet of the floating Mines to blindside your opponents with a finely-tuned trail of explosions.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Larguez cinq mines en suspension qui surprendront vos adversaires avec une explosion en chaîne.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hinterlasse deinen Gegnern fünf schwebende Minen, die sie mit einer gut abgestimmten Reihe von Explosionen überraschen werden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sgancia cinque mine fluttuanti e sorprendi gli avversari con una calibrata serie di esplosioni.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Suelta cinco minas flotantes que cegarán a tus oponentes con una serie de explosiones cuidadosamente calculadas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ジライ：クラフト後方に浮遊地雷を落とします。サーキットを覚えてライバルの不意を突いた使い方をしましょう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">허공에 부유하는 지뢰를 설치하면 아름다운 불꽃과 함께 경쟁자들을 격추할 수 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Drop a quintet of the floating Mines to blindside your opponents with a finely-tuned trail of explosions.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">可以在對戰對手的盲點之處連續施放5顆漂浮地雷，以精心設計過的爆炸路線施予痛擊。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">可以在對戰對手的盲點之處連續施放5顆漂浮地雷，以精心設計過的爆炸路線施予痛擊。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Drop a quintet of the floating Mines to blindside your opponents with a finely-tuned trail of explosions.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ROCKETS_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dependable and destructive, the Rockets are three forward-firing projectiles that practically guarantee a hit at close-range.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fiables et destructrices, ces roquettes tirées par groupe de trois sont sûres d'atteindre leur cible à courte portée.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zuverlässig und zerstörerisch: Raketen sind drei Projektile, die vorwärts geschossen werden und auf kurze Distanz einen Treffer garantieren.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Potenti e affidabili, i razzi sono tre missili sparati frontalmente; sulla corta distanza hanno probabilità di impatto pressoché totale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los cohetes son armas destructivas y muy fiables que se disparan de tres en tres. Si los disparas cerca de tu rival, casi seguro que no fallas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ロケット：破壊力抜群のロケットを前方に３本発射します。なるべくライバルクラフト達との距離を縮めて、直線コースで使用しましょう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">믿음직스러운 파괴력을 자랑하는 로켓은 근접 거리에서는 극도의 명중률을 가집니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Dependable and destructive, the Rockets are three forward-firing projectiles that practically guarantee a hit at close-range.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Rockets(火箭砲)是一種可向三方向射擊的武器，命中率高且具破壞性，保證可在特定範圍內命中敵人。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Rockets(火箭砲)是一種可向三方向射擊的武器，命中率高且具破壞性，保證可在特定範圍內命中敵人。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dependable and destructive, the Rockets are three forward-firing projectiles that practically guarantee a hit at close-range.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CANNON_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cannon: pepper your opponents with this 30 round rapid-fire barrage of high-calibre proton shells. Fire in bursts for best effect.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Canon : canardez vos adversaires avec une rafale de 30 cartouches au proton de gros calibre. Tirez par à-coups pour un effet optimal.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kanone: Verpasse deinen Gegnern eine 30-fache Schnellfeuer-Salve mit großkalibrigen Protonenhülsen. Feuere in kurzen Abständen, um die beste Wirkung zu erhalten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cannone: stuzzica gli avversari con i 30 colpi di fuoco rapido di sbarramento di questo cannone pesante a munizioni protoniche. Spara a raffica per massimizzare l'efficacia.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cañón: acribilla a tus rivales con una rápida descarga de treinta proyectiles de protones de alto calibre. Dispara ráfagas para obtener mejores resultados.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">キャノン：３０発の機関砲です。ライバルクラフトの背後から一気に浴びせると効果的です。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">대포: 대단한 연사력의 프로톤탄을 발사하는 대포로 적들을 누르십시오. 점사하면 더욱 효과적입니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Cannon: pepper your opponents with this 30 round rapid-fire barrage of high-calibre proton shells. Fire in bursts for best effect.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Cannon(加農砲)：以30發高性能陽子彈對您的敵人進行彈幕掃射。射爆敵人以達到最佳效果吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Cannon(加農砲)：以30發高性能陽子彈對您的敵人進行彈幕掃射。射爆敵人以達到最佳效果吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cannon: pepper your opponents with this 30 round rapid-fire barrage of high-calibre proton shells. Fire in bursts for best effect.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">LEECH_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Leech Beam is a pulsating electronic grapple that drains energy from your opponents and transfers it to your ship.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le faisceau sangsue absorbe l'énergie de l'adversaire et la transfère à votre vaisseau.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Sauger-Strahl ist ein pulsierender elektronischer Enterhaken, der deinen Gegnern Energie entzieht und auf dein Schiff überträgt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il raggio sanguisuga è un colpo elettronico a pulsazione che risucchia energia dagli avversari e la trasferisce nella tua nave.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El rayo sanguijuela es un gancho electrónico pulsátil que absorbe energía de tus oponentes y la transfiere a tu nave.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">リーチビーム：ロックオンしたライバルクラフトのシールドエネルギーを吸い取ります。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">리치 빔은 펄스 속성을 가진 전기장을 사용하여 적의 에너지를 흡수합니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Leech Beam is a pulsating electronic grapple that drains energy from your opponents and transfers it to your ship.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Leech Beam(吸收光束)是一種電子脈衝牽引光束，可以消耗對手的能源並轉移到自己的飛船。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Leech Beam(吸收光束)是一種電子脈衝牽引光束，可以消耗對手的能源並轉移到自己的飛船。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Leech Beam is a pulsating electronic grapple that drains energy from your opponents and transfers it to your ship.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MISSILE_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This smart Missile can be fired instantly for a ricochet effect, or locked-on for a more accurate shot at the competition.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ces missiles intelligents peuvent être tirés immédiatement pour un effet ricochet ou être verrouillés sur une cible pour un tir de précision.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese intelligente Zielrakete kann sofort abgefeuert und zu einem unberechenbaren Querschläger werden. Oder man nimmt seine Gegner ins Visier, um sie zielgenau abzuschießen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Missile intelligente che può essere sparato all'istante per un effetto rimbalzo, oppure agganciato al bersaglio per guadagnare precisione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dispara este misil inteligente para que rebote por la pista, o fíjalo en un objetivo para asegurarte de acertar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ミサイル：前方にいるライバルクラフトをロックオンし、誘導ミサイルを発射します。ロックオンカーソルが赤くなると、より命中率が高くなります。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">스마트 미사일은 즉시 발사하여 반사 효과를 작동시킬 수도 있고, 록온을 기다려 유도탄으로 사용할 수도 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This smart Missile can be fired instantly for a ricochet effect, or locked-on for a more accurate shot at the competition.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這個聰明的飛彈能搭配跳彈效果瞬間發射，或是在競賽中鎖定敵人以達到更精準的射擊。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這個聰明的飛彈能搭配跳彈效果瞬間發射，或是在競賽中鎖定敵人以達到更精準的射擊。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This smart Missile can be fired instantly for a ricochet effect, or locked-on for a more accurate shot at the competition.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PLASMA_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Plasma: this dark energy weapon surges across the track causing heavy damage to anything that crosses its path.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plasma : cette arme à l'énergie dévastatrice déferle sur la piste et inflige de terribles dégâts à tout ce qu'elle touche.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Plasma: Diese Waffe mit dunkler Energie bewegt sich über die Strecke und verursacht bei jedem, den sie trifft, beträchtlichen Schaden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Plasma: arma a energia oscura che rifluisce nel terreno causando gravi danni a tutto ciò che ne incrocia la direzione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Plasma: este arma de energía oscura recorre la pista y causa enormes daños a todo lo que se cruza en su camino.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">プラズマ：トラック前方周囲にダークエネルギーを放出し、そこを通るライバルクラフトにダメージを与えます。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">플라즈마: 트랙을 관통하는 이 강력한 에너지 무기는 접촉하는 모든 적에게 큰 피해를 입힙니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Plasma: this dark energy weapon surges across the track causing heavy damage to anything that crosses its path.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Plasma(電漿)：這個黑暗能源武器會在賽道上形成衝擊波，並對所有在它行進路徑上的物體造成極大的傷害。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Plasma(電漿)：這個黑暗能源武器會在賽道上形成衝擊波，並對所有在它行進路徑上的物體造成極大的傷害。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Plasma: this dark energy weapon surges across the track causing heavy damage to anything that crosses its path.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">QUAKE_DESC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Quake: this high-power seismic shock will blaze its way down the track with a fierce, explosive momentum.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Séisme : cette onde de choc destructrice dévale la piste en une vague d'énergie explosive.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erdbeben: Dieser äußerst starke seismische Stoß wallt mit unbändiger, explosiver Wucht über die Strecke.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Terremoto: intensa scossa sismica che si propaga lungo la pista con violenza travolgente.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Terremoto: esta potente onda sísmica arrasa la pista con un feroz impulso explosivo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">クエーク：強力な地震を発生させ、クラフト前方のコースを波立たせます。前方にいるライバルクラフトの多くにダメージを与えます。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">지진: 강력한 충격파로 대지를 흔들어 트랙을 따라 길을 냅니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Quake: this high-power seismic shock will blaze its way down the track with a fierce, explosive momentum.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Quake(震動)：這個高威力的震動波會沿著賽道引發一道強烈的爆炸波動。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Quake(震動)：這個高威力的震動波會沿著賽道引發一道強烈的爆炸波動。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Quake: this high-power seismic shock will blaze its way down the track with a fierce, explosive momentum.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CYCLE_CONTROLS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFT][RIGHT] CYCLE MODELS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFT][RIGHT] PARCOURIR LES MODÈLES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFT][RIGHT] MODELLE DURCHBLÄTTERN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFT][RIGHT] VISUALIZZA MODELLI</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFT][RIGHT] CAMBIAR DE MODELO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[LEFT][RIGHT] 모델 변경</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[LEFT][RIGHT] CYCLE MODELS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[LEFT][RIGHT] 瀏覽模型</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[LEFT][RIGHT] 瀏覽模型</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ROTATE_CONTROLS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFTSTICK] ROTATE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFTSTICK] PIVOTER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFTSTICK] DREHEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFTSTICK] RUOTA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFTSTICK] ROTAR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[LEFTSTICK] 회전</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[LEFTSTICK] ROTATE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[LEFTSTICK] 回轉</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[LEFTSTICK] 回轉</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RESET_CONTROLS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[TRIANGLE] RESET</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[TRIANGLE] RÉINITIALISER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[TRIANGLE] ZURÜCKSETZEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[TRIANGLE] RIPRISTINA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[TRIANGLE] REINICIAR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[TRIANGLE] 리셋</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[TRIANGLE] RESET</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[TRIANGLE] 重置</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[TRIANGLE] 重置</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">EXIT_CONTROLS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CIRCLE] EXIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CIRCLE] QUITTER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CIRCLE] BEENDEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CIRCLE] ESCI</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CIRCLE] SALIR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[CIRCLE] 나가기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[CIRCLE] EXIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[CIRCLE] 離開</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[CIRCLE] 離開</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>