<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">NAME</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Shellshock Figure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Figurine de Shellshock</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Shellshock-Figur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Modellino Skleroshock</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Muñeco de Psicobot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">シェルショックのフィギュア</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">쉘쇼크 피규어</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Shellshock Figure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Shellshock角色模型</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Shellshock角色模型</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Shellshock Figure</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">He was one of the four Exterminator members. His brain was destroyed by a cruise missile during the Obani Moon wars, and was replaced with a coffee machine's AI chip. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'un des quatre membres des Exterminateurs. Son cerveau a été détruit par un missile de croisière lors de la guerre des lunes d'Obani et a été remplacé par une puce de machine à café. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Er war eines der vier Exterminatoren-Mitglieder. Sein Gehirn wurde während der Obani-Mondkriege von einer Rakete zerstört und durch den KI-Chip einer Kaffeemaschine ersetzt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">È stato uno dei quattro membri degli Sterminatori. Il suo cervello è stato distrutto da un missile cruise durante le guerre delle Lune di Obani ed è stato rimpiazzato con il chip di una macchina per il caffè. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Era uno de los cuatro miembros de los Exterminadores. Su cerebro lo destruyó un misil de crucero durante las guerras de las lunas de Obani y fue reemplazado con el chip de IA de una cafetera. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">グリーマン・ヴォックスお抱えのグラディエーターのひとり。以前の戦争で脳をふきとばされたが、コーヒーメーカー用の頭脳チップを埋め込むことで生きのびたタフガイ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">오바니 달의 전쟁에서 머리에 미사일을 맞은 다음 뇌가 파괴되었습니다. 그 후 커피메이커의 AI 칩을 대신 이식받았습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">He was one of the four Exterminator members. His brain was destroyed by a cruise missile during the Obani Moon wars, and was replaced with a coffee machine's AI chip. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">他是四大毀滅者的成員之一。其大腦在歐巴尼行星大戰時被巡弋飛彈給擊毀，因而被重新換裝了咖啡機的電腦晶片。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">他是四大毀滅者的成員之一。其大腦在歐巴尼行星大戰時被巡弋飛彈給擊毀，因而被重新換裝了咖啡機的電腦晶片。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">He was one of the four Exterminator members. His brain was destroyed by a cruise missile during the Obani Moon wars, and was replaced with a coffee machine's AI chip. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>