<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - She Sells Tank - Cool Wip (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Débardeur She Sells - Crème fouettée (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - She Sells Tanktop - Cool Wip (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - She Sells Canottiera - Panna (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - She Sells Camiseta de tirantes - Color crema (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our Shine On collection radiates with fashions that are inspired by the adventure-seeker in all of us. Playful and lighthearted, each design is ready to travel the globe in search of treasures, enlightenment, and like-minded souls. This cropped muscle tee features completely open sides with front screen prints. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Notre collection Shine On rayonne avec des articles de mode inspirés par l'aventurière qui sommeille en nous. Espiègle et enjouée, chaque création est prête à traverser le monde en quête de trésors, d'éveil spirituel et d'âmes sœurs. Ce T-shirt court comporte des côtés complètement ouverts et des imprimés sérigraphiés sur le devant. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unsere Shine On Kollektion besticht durch modische Details, die die Abenteuerlust in uns allen ansprechen. Die verspielt fröhlichen Designs sind ideal für die Reise und die Suche nach Schätzen, Erleuchtung und Gleichgesinnten geeignet. Dieses bauchfreie Oberteil ist an den Seiten völlig offen und vorne attraktiv bedruckt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La nostra collezione Shine On emana uno stile ispirato all'amante dell'avventura che c'è in ognuno di noi. Sbarazzino e leggero, ogni design è pronto a viaggiare il mondo in cerca di tesori, ispirazione e anime gemelle. Questa canottiera corta con giromanica largo presenta lati completamente aperti e stampe serigrafiche sul davanti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nuestra colección Shine On brilla con estilos inspirados en la aventurera que todas llevamos dentro. Traviesos y desenfadados, cada uno de los diseños está hecho para viajar por el mundo en busca de tesoros, conocimiento y almas gemelas. Esta camiseta recortada de tipo musculación presenta amplias aberturas laterales y serigrafía frontal. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>