<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Raven Brawler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Brawler Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Raven-Brawler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Brawler Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Brawler de Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Brawler レーヴン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Raven "격투가" 장갑차</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Raven Brawler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raven「格鬥者」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raven「格鬥者」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Raven Brawler</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Brawler represents years of combat driven innovation. Complete with a 30mm canon, coaxial machinegun and resupply capabilities, this vehicle is capable of penetrating deep into enemy territory and bringing everyone safely back to base. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Brawler représente des années d'innovations militaires. Livré avec un canon de 30 mm, une mitrailleuse coaxiale et équipé pour le ravitaillement, ce véhicule est capable de pénétrer profondément les lignes ennemies et de ramener tout le monde à la base. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Brawler steht für viele Jahre Entwicklung und Kampferfahrung. Mit der 30-mm-Kanone, dem mittig angebrachten Maschinengewehr und den Lieferungsmöglichkeiten ist dieses Fahrzeug in der Lage, tief in feindliches Gebiet vorzudringen und alle Soldaten sicher wieder in die Basis zu bringen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Brawler è il prodotto di anni di studi per l'innovazione degli armamenti. Dotato di un cannone da 30 mm, mitragliatrice coassiale e capacità di rifornimento automatico, riesce a infiltrarsi facilmente in territorio nemico e riportare tutti sani e salvi alla base. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Brawler es el resultado de años de innovaciones para el combate. Completo con un cañón de 30 mm, ametralladora coaxial y funciones de reabastecimiento, este vehículo es capaz de penetrar el territorio enemigo y traer a cualquier persona de vuelta a la base sana y salva. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このBrawlerは何年にも及ぶ技術革新から生まれた。30mmの機銃にマシンガン、補給品も運ぶ能力など、優れた装甲兵員輸送車(APC)だ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Raven의 "격투가"는 오랜 시간에 거친 전투 과학의 혁신을 상징합니다. 30mm 대포와 동축기관총, 그리고 자주적인 재보급 기능까지. 전진 깊숙히 들어가, 모두를 태우고 다시 귀환할 수 있는 장갑차입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Brawler represents years of combat driven innovation. Complete with a 30mm canon, coaxial machine gun and resupply capabilities, this vehicle is capable of penetrating deep into enemy territory and bringing everyone safely back to base. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「格鬥者」代表著多年來專為戰鬥而造出的創新設計。這款載具裝有一個30mm大砲、同軸機槍和再次補給能力，能夠深入敵陣並將全部人安全送回基地。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「格鬥者」代表著多年來專為戰鬥而造出的創新設計。這款載具裝有一個30mm大砲、同軸機槍和再次補給能力，能夠深入敵陣並將全部人安全送回基地。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Brawler represents years of combat driven innovation. Complete with a 30mm cannon, coaxial machine gun and resupply capabilities, this vehicle is capable of penetrating deep into enemy territory and bringing everyone safely back to base. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>