<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Charmed SpeedWings Value Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack Économique SpeedWings de Charme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bezauberne SpeedWings Vorteilspaket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto SpeedWings Incantato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de Valor Encantado SpeedWings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">チャームド・スピードウィングス・バリューパック</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Charmed SpeedWings Value Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Charmed SpeedWings Value Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Save nearly 40% off retail price with the Charmed SpeedWings Value Pack! Pull out these wings for a major speed boost with custom animations. Includes the Sky Monarch SpeedWings, Dazzling Butterfly SpeedWings, Camellia Fairy SpeedWings, and Enchanted Fairy SpeedWings. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Économisez environ 40% du prix de vente avec le Pack Économique SpeedWings de Charme ! Sortez ces ailes pour obtenir un boost de vitesse majeur avec des animations personnalisées. Inclut les Speedwings Monarque des Cieux, les SpeedWings Papillon Éblouissant, les SpeedWings Fée Camélia et les SpeedWings Fée Enchantée. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spare fast 40% des Verkaufspreises mit dem drachischen SpeedWings Vorteilpaket! Fahre diese Flügel für einen wesentlichen Geschwindigkeitsschub mit benutzerspezifischen Animationen aus. Enthält Himmelsmonarch SpeedWings, Umwerfender Schmetterling SpeedWings, Kamelien-Elfen SpeedWings, und Verwunschene Fee SpeedWings. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Risparmia quasi il 40% sul prezzo di vendita con il Pacchetto SpeedWings Incantato! Spalanca queste ali per aumentare ulteriormente la velocità con animazioni personalizzate. In questo pacchetto sono incluse SpeedWings Monarca Celestiale, SpeedWings Farfalla Smagliante, SpeedWings Fata delle Camelie e SpeedWings Fata Incantata. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Ahorra alrededor del 40% del precio de venta con el Paquete de Valor Encantado SpeedWings! Saca estas alas para aumentar tu velocidad con animaciones personalizadas. Incluye el SpeedWings de Monarca del Cielo, la Mariposa Deslumbrante SpeedWings, las SpeedWings Hadas Camelia y el Hada Encantada SpeedWings. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">チャームド・スピードウィングス・バリューパックで値段が40%オフになります！ブーストウィングを引っ張り出して、カスタムアニメーションつきの超スピードブースト！スカイモナーク・スピードウィングス、ダズリングバタフライ・スピードウィングス、カメリアフェアリー・スピードウィングス、エンチャンテッドフェアリー・スピードウィングスが含まれます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Save nearly 40% off retail price with the Charmed SpeedWings Value Pack! Pull out these wings for a major speed boost with custom animations. Includes the Sky Monarch SpeedWings, Dazzling Butterfly SpeedWings, Camellia Fairy SpeedWings, and Enchanted Fairy SpeedWings. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Save nearly 40% off retail price with the Charmed SpeedWings Value Pack! Pull out these wings for a major speed boost with custom animations. Includes the Sky Monarch SpeedWings, Dazzling Butterfly SpeedWings, Camellia Fairy SpeedWings, and Enchanted Fairy SpeedWings. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>