<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">England Home Shirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Maillot de football - Angleterre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Trikot „England“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maglia Inghilterra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta de Inglaterra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">イングランド ホームシャツ（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">영국 홈 티셔츠 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">England Home Shirt (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">英格蘭 Home T恤 (男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">英格蘭 Home T恤 (男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">England Home Shirt</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Umbro brings together the traditional values of classic tailoring with modern fabric technology and a revolutionary design philosophy.  The new England kit is the proud result.  Wear it virtually, but always with pride. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Umbro associe les valeurs traditionnelles de la confection textile classique à une technologie de fabrication moderne et à un design révolutionnaire. Le nouveau maillot de l'Angleterre en est le parfait résultat. Portez-le virtuellement, mais toujours avec fierté. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Umbro vereint die traditionellen Werte des klassischen Schneiderns mit modernen Materialien und revolutionärer Designphilosophie. Die neue England-Ausrüstung ist das beeindruckende Ergebnis. Tragen Sie sie virtuell, aber mit Stolz. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Umbro unisce i valori tradizionali della sartoria classica con le moderne tecnologie e una rivoluzionaria idea di design. La nuova divisa inglese ne rappresenta il fiero risultato. Indossa la maglia virtualmente, ma sempre con orgoglio. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Umbro une los valores tradicionales de la confección clásica con la moderna tecnología del tejido y una filosofía de diseño revolucionaria. El gran resultado es la nueva equipación de Inglaterra. Llévala virtualmente, pero siempre con orgullo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アンブロはモダンな生地を使った伝統的な仕立てと革命的なデザイン倫理を融合した新しいイングランドのユニフォームを生み出した。誇りとともに身にまとえ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">혁신적인 디자인 철학과 신소재를 사용한 재단 기술로 탄생한 클래식 Umbro 제품입니다. 자랑스러운 노력의 결실인 해당 제품을 입고, 영국에 대한 애정을 표시하십시오. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Umbro brings together the traditional values of classic tailoring with modern fabric technology and a revolutionary design philosophy.  The new England kit is the proud result.  Wear it virtually, but always with pride. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Umbro融合傳統典雅的縫紉技術、現代布料科技及革新設計理念。讓人穿出全新型格英國風範！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Umbro融合傳統典雅的縫紉技術、現代布料科技及革新設計理念。讓人穿出全新型格英國風範！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Umbro brings together the traditional values of classic tailoring with modern fabric technology and a revolutionary design philosophy.  The new England kit is the proud result.  Wear it virtually, but always with pride. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>