<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">SeaClyff Night Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nuit club SeaClyff</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nachtclubhaus SeaClyff</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Clubhouse Notturno SeaClyff</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La Casa Club Noche SeaClyff</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">SeaClyff Night Clubhouse</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A radical nightclub space with all the essentials. Food in the fridge, tunes in the stereo and lots of space for multi-level dance floor action. State of the art everything. The doors are automatic, the appliances are interactive, even the shower and toilet work (an essential at any party). Four floors of fun in a hi-tech heaven that would make even the Great Gatsby jealous. If lavish is your lifestyle, then this is your new party pad. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un espace de boîte de nuit radicale avec tous les éléments essentiels. Le frigo regorge de nourriture, la stéréo de musiques, et il y a énormément d'espace pour danser à différents étages. Tout est dernier cri : les portes sont automatiques, les appareils sont interactifs, et même la douche et les toilettes marchent (elles sont essentielles à toute fête !). Vous avez à votre disposition quatre étages de divertissement, dans un paradis hi-tech qui ferait pâlir d'envie les plus grandes stars ! Si vous aimez ce qui est somptueux, alors voici clairement l'endroit pour vous. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein richtiger Nachtclub mit allem, was ein Club braucht: Essen im Kühlschrank, Musik aus den Lautsprechern und viel Platz für Tanz-Action auf mehreren Stockwerken. Jeder Winkel dieses Clubs ist hochmodern ausgestattet. Die Türen funktionieren automatisch, die Einrichtung ist interaktiv, sogar die Dusche und die Toilette funktionieren (äußerst wichtig auf jeder Party). Vier Stockwerke Spaß in einem HighTech-Himmel, der selbst den großen Gatsby neidisch machen würde. Wenn Luxus dein Lebensstil ist, ist das deine neue Party-Hütte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Uno notte spazio per un club con tutto l'essenziale. Cibo nel frigorifero, musica nello stereo e molto spazio per ballare su più piani. Ogni oggetto è il top della gamma. Le porte sono automatizzate, gli elettrodomestici sono interattivi, anche la doccia e il gabinetto funzionano (sono essenziali in ogni festa). Quattro piani di divertimento in un paradico high tech che farebbe ingelosire persino il Grande Gatsby. Se il lusso è il tuo stile di vita, questo è l'appartamento per le feste che fa per te. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un club noche radical con todo lo esencial. Comida en la nevera, canciones en la radio y mucho espacio para bailar en la pista de las diferentes plantas. Lo último en todo. Las puertas son automáticas y los electrodomésticos interactivos, incluyendo la ducha y el servicio (esenciales en cualquier fiesta). Cuatro plantas de diversión en un paraíso de tecnología ante el cual incluso el Gran Gatsby estaría celoso. Si tienes un estilo de vida derrochador, esta es tu nueva sala de fiestas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A radical nightclub space with all the essentials. Food in the fridge, tunes in the stereo and lots of space for multi-level dance floor action. State of the art everything. The doors are automatic, the appliances are interactive, even the shower and toilet work (an essential at any party). Four floors of fun in a hi-tech heaven that would make even the Great Gatsby jealous. If lavish is your lifestyle, then this is your new party pad. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>