<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">My Private Hideaway</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mon refuge privé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mein Privatversteck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mio rifugio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mi escondite privado</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* My Private Hideaway</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* My Private Hideaway</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* My Private Hideaway</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* My Private Hideaway</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* My Private Hideaway</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">My Private Hideaway</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Washed ashore on a solitary island in the south seas.The blazing sun, the quiet ocean, the refreshing breeze. . .  Oops! I built a house on top of a cliff and even forgot to go home. You are now able to go to the "Southern Island Hideaway" from the back door of the loghouse. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Perdu sur une île isolée des mers du Sud. Soleil étincelant, mer calme, brise rafraîchissante. Mince ! J’en ai oublié de rentrer chez moi et j’ai construit une maison sur la falaise. Vous pouvez désormais accéder au "Refuge de l'île australe” par la porte arrière du chalet. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gestrandet auf einer einsamen Insel in der Südsee. Die sengende Sonne, der ruhige Ozean, die frische Brise. /n
Oh Nein! Ich habe vergessen nach Hause zu gehen und hier auf einer Klippe ein Haus gebaut. Sie können von der Hintertür des Blockhauses zum Privatgarten der "Abgelegene Südseeinsel"-Lounge gelangen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Si trova su un'isola remota nei mari del sud su cui sono arrivato trasportato dalla corrente. Qui il sole splende, il mare è calmo e la brezza è rinfrescante. Ma perché?! Ho costruito una casa in cima a una collina e ho dimenticato di tornare a casa! Adesso puoi accedere alla sala del "Nascondiglio sull'Isola nei Mari del Sud" dal retro della capanna. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Has sido arrastrado hasta una solitaria isla en los mares del Sur. El sol abrasador, el tranquilo océano, la brisa refrescante... ¡Oh no! He construido una casa en el la cima del acantilado y hasta he olvidado regresar a casa. Ahora ya puedes ir a la sala "Retiro en la isla de los mares del Sur" desde la puerta trasera de la cabaña. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>