<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hidden Oak Retreat Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Refuge du grand chêne</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dunkeleichen-Zuflucht</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Rifugio Quercia Nascosta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Refugio del roble escondido</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Hidden Oak Retreat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">숨겨진 떡갈나무 휴양지 클럽하우스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Hidden Oak Retreat Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">秘密橡木度假屋聯盟俱樂部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">秘密橡木度假屋聯盟俱樂部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hidden Oak Retreat</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to the Hidden Oak Retreat, a clubhouse retreat tucked away in the mountains. Get away from the hustle of city life and enjoy one of the two relaxing fireplaces. Look up and and you'll notice the clubhouse lit by chandeliers made of antlers! Head out to the deck and enjoy the lakefront view while you roast some marshmallows on the campfire. Now this is the great outdoors! The Hidden Oak Retreat space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join in. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue au Refuge du grand chêne, un club-house isolé à l'abri des montagnes. Échappez au tourbillon de la vie urbaine et profitez de l'une des deux cheminées. Levez les yeux et vous remarquerez que le club-house est éclairé par un chandelier fabriqué à partir des bois d'un cerf ! Rendez-vous sur le ponton pour admirer la vue sur le lac en faisant fondre des chamallows au-dessus d'un feu de camp. Ça, c'est la belle vie ! L'espace Refuge du grand chêne est un club-house dont tout le monde peut profiter. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen in der Dunkeleichen-Zuflucht, einem Klubhaus, das versteckt in den Bergen als Rückzugsort dient. Erhole dich vom Trubel des Stadtlebens und entspanne an einem der Kamine. Wenn du nach oben schaust, wirst du bemerken, dass das Klubhaus von Geweih-Kronleuchtern erleuchtet wird! Genieße von der Veranda aus den Seeblick, während du dir über dem Lagerfeuer ein paar Marshmallows röstest. Genau so ist es in der freien Natur! Die Dunkeleichen-Zuflucht ist ein Klubhaus, in dem jeder Gast willkommen ist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuto al Rifugio Quercia Nascosta, una sede distaccata del club, nascosta tra le montagne. Allontanati dal trambusto della vita cittadina e fatti confortare da uno dei due rilassanti camini. Se alzerai la testa, noterai come la sede del club sia illuminata da lampadari di corna di cervo! Fai un giro sul terrazzo e goditi la vista sul lago mentre fai cuocere un paio di marshmallow sul fuoco. Questo è vivere la natura! Lo spazio Rifugio Quercia Nascosta è una sede del club dove chiunque è il benvenuto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te damos la bienvenida al refugio del roble escondido, un retiro exclusivo aislado en las montañas. Escapa del bullicio de la ciudad y disfruta de una de sus dos relajantes chimeneas. Si miras hacia arriba, verás que la luz del retiro viene de una lámpara de araña hecha de astas. Siéntate frente al lago y disfruta de sus vistas mientras calientas algunos malvaviscos en la fogata. ¡Qué maravilla poder disfrutar del aire libre! El refugio del roble escondido es un lugar exclusivo al que todos están invitados. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Welcome to the Hidden Oak Retreat, a clubhouse retreat tucked away in the mountains. Get away from the hustle of city life and enjoy one of the two relaxing fireplaces. Look up and and you'll notice the clubhouse lit by chandeliers made of antlers! Head out to the deck and enjoy the lakefront view while you roast some marshmallows on the campfire. Now this is the great outdoors! The Hidden Oak Retreat space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">산 중턱에 위치한 클럽하우스 휴양지인 숨겨진 떡갈나무 휴양지에 오신 것을 환영합니다. 부산한 도시의 삶을 잠시 떠나 2개의 편안한 벽난로 중 하나를 골라 쉬세요. 위를 보면 클럽하우스는 사슴뿔로 제작된 샹들리에가 있다는 것을 알 수 있습니다! 테라스로 나가 캠프 파이어에 마쉬멜로를 구우며 호수를 바라보세요. 이게 바로 진정한 자연이죠! 숨겨진 떡갈나무 휴양지는 모든 사람이 환영받는 클럽하우스입니다. *주의: 클럽하우스에 입장하려면 먼저 클럽을 구매해야 합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Welcome to the Hidden Oak Retreat, a clubhouse retreat tucked away in the mountains. Get away from the hustle of city life and enjoy one of the two relaxing fireplaces. Look up and and you'll notice the clubhouse lit by chandeliers made of antlers! Head out to the deck and enjoy the lakefront view while you roast some marshmallows on the campfire. Now this is the great outdoors! The Hidden Oak Retreat space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">歡迎來到隱藏於山中的秘密橡木度假屋。遠離都市煩囂，在兩個火爐旁放鬆休息。抬頭看看，更會發現吊燈以鹿角製成！到平台邊欣賞湖畔景色，邊在營火旁烤棉花糖，這就是最佳的戶外環境！秘密橡木度假屋空間是一個歡迎任何人加入的聯盟俱樂部。※請注意，要使用聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">歡迎來到隱藏於山中的秘密橡木度假屋。遠離都市煩囂，在兩個火爐旁放鬆休息。抬頭看看，更會發現吊燈以鹿角製成！到平台邊欣賞湖畔景色，邊在營火旁烤棉花糖，這就是最佳的戶外環境！秘密橡木度假屋空間是一個歡迎任何人加入的聯盟俱樂部。※請注意，要使用聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome to the Hidden Oak Retreat, a clubhouse retreat tucked away in the mountains. Get away from the hustle of city life and enjoy one of the two relaxing fireplaces. Look up and and you'll notice the clubhouse lit by chandeliers made of antlers! Head out to the deck and enjoy the lakefront view while you roast some marshmallows on the campfire. Now this is the great outdoors! The Hidden Oak Retreat space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>