<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Indiana Jones (Iconic) Fedora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chapeau mou Indiana Jones (iconique)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Indiana Jones (Kultfigur)-Filzhut</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cappello Indiana Jones (Iconico)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sombrero (icónico) de Indiana Jones</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Indiana Jones (Iconic) Fedora</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">(Hat) The back roads of a mountain pass flew by me as I drove down the hardly-used roadway outside Bangladesh. The wind was throwing gravel and debris against the pieces of my windshield their gunfire hadn't shattered. The rest poured into me pelting my fine leather jacket leaving me free of scars. I reached into my satchel, hoping to find the artifact the men chasing me were after. My hands glanced across the smooth silver of the small idol, and I smiled. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">(Chapeau) Les chemins de montagne défilaient devant mes yeux alors que je conduisais sur les routes peu fréquentées de la campagne du Bangladesh. Le vent projetait des graviers et des débris sur les bouts de mon pare-brise qui avaient survécus à la fusillade. Le reste retombait sur moi et bombardait ma belle veste en cuir, m'évitant ainsi les cicatrices. J'attrapai mon sac, espérant y trouver la raison pour laquelle ces hommes me poursuivaient. Mes mains passèrent sur l'argent lisse de la petite idole, et je souris. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">(Hut) Die Schotterpisten eines Bergpasses zogen an mir vorbei, als ich eine selten benutzte Straße an der Grenze zu Bangladesch entlangfuhr. Der Wind blies Kiesel und Geröll vor die Teile meiner Windschutzscheibe, die nicht vom Geschützfeuer zerstört wurden. Der Rest setzte meiner Lederjacke zu, aber ich blieb unverletzt. Ich griff in meine Tasche, in der ich das Artefakt zu finden hoffte, hinter dem die Männer her waren. Meine Hände glitten über die glatte Silberoberfläche und ich lächelte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">(Cappello) I sentieri nella gola della montagna mi sfrecciavano accanto mentre guidavo sulla strada poco frequentata alle porte del Bangledesh. Il vento gettava polvere e detriti sui frammenti del parabrezza che i loro proiettili avevano risparmiato. Il resto colpiva a raffiche la mia bella giacca di pelle che mi proteggeva dalle cicatrici. Misi la mano nel mio zaino, sperando di trovare il manufatto tanto ambito dai miei inseguitori. Le miei mani trovarono l'argento levigato del piccolo idolo, e io sorrisi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">(Sombrero) Voy dejando atrás las laderas de la montaña mientras conduzco por las poco usadas carreteras a las afueras de Bangladesh. Gravilla y restos lanzados por el viento chocan contra la luna delantera de mi coche, al menos lo que queda de ella tras el tiroteo. Mi fina chaqueta de piel me protege del resto de residuos y evita que me dejen cicatriz. Mis manos abrazan el pequeño y brillante ídolo de plata, sonrío. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">(Hat/Hair) The back roads of a mountain pass flew by me as I drove down the hardly-used roadway outside Bangledesh. The wind was throwing gravel and debris against the pieces of my windshield their gunfire hadn't shattered. The rest poured into me pelting my fine leather jacket leaving me free of scars. I reached into my satchel, hoping to find the artifact the men chasing me were after. My hands glanced across the smooth silver of the small idol, and I smiled. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>