<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LOOT™ Night - Microphone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">LOOT™ Nuit - Micro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LOOT™ Night - Mikrofon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Notturno LOOT™ - Microfono</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Micrófono - LOOT™ Noche</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LOOT™ナイト - マイク</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LOOT™ Night - Microphone</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Who needs a public access channel? Get your late night talk show career started now with the LOOT™ Night Talk Show Set for the LOOT™ Stageset Personal Space. This is an exclusive LOOT™ Bundle item! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Qui a besoin d'un canal communautaire ? Lancez votre carrière d'animateur de talk show avec le lot Talk Show LOOT™ Nuit pour votre espace personnel Décor de plateau LOOT™. C'est l'élément exclusif du lot LOOT™ ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer braucht schon einen öffentlichen Fernsehkanal? Started eure Karirere in Late Night Shows jetzt mit dem LOOT™ Night Talk Show Set für den persönlichen Raum des LOOT™ Stage Set. Diesen Artikel gibt es exklusiv nur mit dem LOOT™ Bundle! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">A chi serve una rete televisiva pubblica? Inizia la tua carriera di presentatore di talk show notturni con il Completo Talk Show Notturni per il tuo spazio personale Scenografia LOOT™.  Questo elemento è un'esclusiva del Completo LOOT™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Quién necesita un canal de acceso público? ¡Que empiece tu carrera en un programa nocturno con el conjunto de LOOT™ Programa de Noche para personalizar el estudio de LOOT™. ¡Se trata de un producto exclusivo del conjunto LOOT™!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">くだらないテレビなんてもういらない！LOOT™ナイト トーク・ショー パックでレイトナイト トーク・ショーをはじめましょう。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Who needs a public access channel? Get your late night talk show career started now with the LOOT™ Night Talk Show Set for the LOOT™ Stageset Personal Space. This is an exclusive LOOT™ Bundle item! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>