<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">USA T-shirt (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">USA T-shirt (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chemise USA (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">USA T-shirt (mann)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Camicia USA (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta USA (hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>    
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A collection for sports fans! Designed for those who experience the game as if they themselves were on the field! Kick Off is a sporty, light and comfortable brand. Perfect for playing sports or just as comfort wear, this collection includes the clothing and accessories from your favourite teams and sports. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A collection for sports fans! Designed for those who experience the game as if they themselves were on the field! Kick Off is a sporty, light and comfortable brand. Perfect for playing sports or just as comfort wear, this collection includes the clothing and accessories from your favorite teams and sports. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une collection pour les amoureux du sport! Créée pour tous ceux qui vivent le match comme s'ils étaient sur le terrain! Kick Off est une ligne de vêtements de sport, légère et confortable. Parfaite pour pratiquer un sport ou pour s'habiller confortablement, cette collection propose des vêtements et accessoires de vos équipes et de vos sports préférés. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine Kollektion für Sportliebhaber! Für all diejenigen designt, die das Spiel so erleben, als wenn sie selber auf dem Feld wären. Kick Off ist eine leichte und bequeme sportliche Linie. Ideal zum Sport treiben oder etwas bequemes zu tragen, zählt diese Linie mit Kleidung und Accessoires deiner Lieblingsmannschaften und -sportarten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una collezione per gli appassionati di sport! Creata per tutti coloro che vivono il gioco come se fossero in campo! Kick Off è una linea sportiva, leggera e confortevole. Perfetta per lo sport e comodo da indossare, questa collezione include abbigliamento e accessori delle tue squadre preferite. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Una colección para los amantes del deporte! Diseñada para todos aquellos que viven el partido como si estuviera en el campo! Kick Off es una línea deportiva, ligera y cómoda. Perfecta para practicar deporte o para vestir cómodo, esta colección tiene ropa y accesorios de tus equipos y deportes favoritos. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>