<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Round Rattan Table</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Table ronde en rotin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Runder Rattantisch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tavolo rotondo di rattan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mesa de caña redondeada</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">둥근 등나무 탁자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Round Rattan Table</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">圓形藤桌</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">圓形藤桌</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Round Rattan Table</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This hand crafted rattan Table is made of quality imported rattan palm. With it's unique shape and rich coffee colour, it will complement or complete your living space. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette table a été fabriquée à la main à partir de palmiers importés de grande qualité. Sa forme originale et sa riche couleur café en font un élément de décoration parfait. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser handgefertigte Rattantisch wurde aus hochwertigem, importiertem Rattanholz hergestellt. Mit seiner ungewöhnlichen Form und der satten Kaffeefarbe wird er jedes Zimmer verschönern. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo tavolo artigianale è realizzato con il migliore rattan di importazione. Caratterizzato da una forma unica e da un intenso color caffè, è perfetto per integrare o completare il tuo spazio abitabile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta mesa de caña está fabricada a mano con material de gran calidad. Con su forma única y su color café intenso, es ideal para complementar o completar tu salón. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">수공예로 제작한 수입산 등나무 제품입니다. 독특한 모양과 짙은 커피색이 인상적입니다. 거실에 완벽하게 어울립니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This hand crafted rattan Table is made of quality imported rattan palm. With its unique shape and rich coffee color, it will complement or complete your living space. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這張手工籐製長沙發以優質的進口省籐製成，型狀獨特，深棕色，可點綴或令客廳更完美。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這張手工籐製長沙發以優質的進口省籐製成，型狀獨特，深棕色，可點綴或令客廳更完美。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This hand crafted rattan Table is made of quality imported rattan palm. With its unique shape and rich coffee color, it will complement or complete your living space. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>