<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PAD_RIGHTSTICK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[RIGHTSTICK]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[RIGHTSTICK]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[RIGHTSTICK]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[RIGHTSTICK]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[RIGHTSTICK]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[RIGHTSTICK]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[RIGHTSTICK]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[RIGHTSTICK]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[RIGHTSTICK]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[RIGHTSTICK]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[RIGHTSTICK]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">DECLINE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Refuser</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ablehnen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Rifiuta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Rechazar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">辞退</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Decline</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">OK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">OK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">OK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">OK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aceptar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">OK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">OK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">OK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">OK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">OK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">OK</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PAD_ACCEPT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PAD_DECLINE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PAD_LEFT_RIGHT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFT][RIGHT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFT][RIGHT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFT][RIGHT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFT][RIGHT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFT][RIGHT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[LEFT][RIGHT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[LEFT][RIGHT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[LEFT][RIGHT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[LEFT][RIGHT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[LEFT][RIGHT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[LEFT][RIGHT]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ACCEPT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Accept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Accepter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Annehmen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Accetta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aceptar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">選択</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">수락</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Accept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">接受</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">接受</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Accept</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">NAVIGATE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Navigate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Naviguer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Navigieren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scorri</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Navegar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ナビゲート</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Navigate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Navigate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Navigate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Navigate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Navigate</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SCROLL_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Scroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Défiler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Scrollen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scorri</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Desplazar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スクロール</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Scroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Scroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Scroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Scroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Scroll</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PLEASE_WAIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Please Wait</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Veuillez patienter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bitte warten</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Attendere</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Espera</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">しばらくお待ちください</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Please Wait</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Please Wait</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Please Wait</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Please Wait</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Please Wait</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">LOADING</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Loading</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chargement</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lädt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caricamento in corso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cargando</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Loading</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">로딩</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Loading</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">正在載入</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">正在下載</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Loading</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sodium Teleportal: Destination Classified</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Téléportail Sodium : Destination Confidentielle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sodium-Teleporter: Ziel geheim</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Teletrasporto Sodium: destinazione classificata</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Teleportal de Sodium: destino secreto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Sodiumテレポータル：目的地はトップシークレット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium 텔레포탈: 목적지는 비밀임</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sodium Teleportal: Destination Classified</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sodium傳送站：機密目的地</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sodium傳送站：機密目的地</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sodium Teleportal: Destination Classified</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Place this mysterious teleportal in your personal space to gain access to a classified Sodium location. Warning; destination contains experimental technology. Users are advised to proceed with caution. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Placez ce mystérieux téléportail dans votre espace personnel pour accéder à une location Sodium top secrète. Attention : des technologies expérimentales y sont utilisées. Les usagers sont appelés à faire preuve de grande prudence. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Platzieren Sie diesen geheimnisvollen Teleporter in Ihrem persönlichen Apartment, um Zugang zu einem geheimen Sodium-Ort zu erhalten. Warnung: Am Zielort befindet sich experimentelle Technologie. Nutzern wird empfohlen, mit Bedacht vorzugehen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Metti questo misterioso teletrasporto nel tuo spazio personale per accedere a una destinazione Sodium classificata. Attenzione: la destinazione è dotata di tecnologia sperimentale. Si consiglia agli utenti di procedere con cautela. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Coloca este teleportal misterioso en tu espacio personal para obtener acceso a una ubicación de Sodium secreta. Advertencia: el destino contiene tecnología en fase experimental. Se recomienda a los usuarios proceder con precaución. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">あなたのパーソナルスペースに、神秘のテレポータルを設置してSodiumのシークレットプレースへのアクセスを可能にしよう。警告：実験的な場所もありますので、用心して進むようにしてください。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 신비로운 텔레포탈을 여러분의 개인공간에 설치해서 비밀로 분류된 Sodium 위치에 대한 접속권을 받으세요. 경고:목적지에서는 실험적인 기술을 적용하고 있습니다. 사용자들은 조심스럽게 이동해야 합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Place this mysterious teleportal in your personal space to gain access to a classified Sodium location. Warning; destination contains experimental technology. Users are advised to proceed with caution. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">把這個神秘傳送站放到私人空間，進入Sodium機密地帶。警告：本目的地有尚在實驗中的技術。使用者請務必小心。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">把這個神秘傳送站放到私人空間，進入Sodium機密地帶。警告：本目的地有尚在實驗中的技術。使用者請務必小心。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Place this mysterious teleportal in your personal space to gain access to a classified Sodium location. Warning; destination contains experimental technology. Users are advised to proceed with caution. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">NoPerm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You do not have clearance to access this teleportal. Please step away from the device. Officials have been informed of your activities and will respond appropriately.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous n’êtes pas autorisé à accéder à ce téléportail. Veuillez vous écarter de l'appareil. Les autorités ont été informées de vos activités et sont prêts à agir en conséquence.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie sind nicht berechtigt, auf diesen Teleporter zuzugreifen. Bitte entfernen Sie sich von dem Gerät. Die zuständigen Offiziellen wurden über Ihre Aktivitäten informiert und werden angemessen reagieren.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non hai l'autorizzazione per accedere a questo teletrasporto. Si prega di abbandonare il dispositivo. Le autorità sono state informate delle tue attività e agiranno di conseguenza.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No estás autorizado a acceder a este teleportal. Aléjate del dispositivo. Las autoridades han sido informadas de tus actividades y actuarán en consecuencia.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">あなたにはテレポータルへアクセスする認可は下りていません。デバイスから離れてください。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">당신은 이 텔레포탈에 접속하도록 인가되지 않았습니다. 그 장치에서 물러서세요. 담당직원들이 이미 당신의 행동을 인지하였으며 곧 적절한 조치를 취할 것입니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">You do not have clearance to access this teleportal. Please step away from the device. Officials have been informed of your activities and will respond appropriately.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">您未獲得使用本傳送站的許可。請離開傳送站。官方已經得知您的行為，並且會馬上展開適當的行動。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">您未獲得使用本傳送站的許可。請離開傳送站。官方已經得知您的行為，並且會馬上展開適當的行動。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You do not have clearance to access this teleportal. Please step away from the device. Officials have been informed of your activities and will respond appropriately.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Transporting</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Thank you for using this Sodium teleportal. You will now be relocated to a classified destination.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nous vous remercions d'utiliser ce Téléportail Sodium. Vous allez maintenant être envoyé vers une destination confidentielle.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Danke, dass Sie diesen Sodium-Teleporter verwenden. Sie werden nun an einen geheimen Ort befördert.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Grazie per aver utilizzato questo teletrasporto Sodium. Sarai ora teletrasportato presso la destinazione classificata.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Gracias por utilizar este teleportal de Sodium. Ahora serás teletransportado a un destino secreto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Sodiumテレポータルをご利用いただき、まことにありがとうございます。これより機密扱い場所へと移動します。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium 텔레포탈을 이용해주셔서 감사합니다. 당신은 이제 비밀로 분류된 목적지로 보내질 것입니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Thank you for using this Sodium teleportal. You will now be relocated to a classified destination.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">感謝您使用Sodium傳送站。您即將到達機密目的地。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">感謝您使用Sodium傳送站。您即將到達機密目的地。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Thank you for using this Sodium teleportal. You will now be relocated to a classified destination.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CANCEL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cancel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Annuler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Abbrechen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Annulla</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cancelar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">キャンセル</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Cancel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Cancel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Cancel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Cancel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cancel</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SODIUM2_EULA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sodium2 EULA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sodium2 EULA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sodium2 EULA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sodium2 EULA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Licencia de software de Sodium2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Sodium2利用規約</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium2 EULA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sodium2 EULA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sodium2 EULA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sodium2 EULA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sodium2 EULA</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">EULA_TEXT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">\n\nThese Terms apply to any beta trial operated by Lockwood Publishing Ltd (“Beta Trial”). Your participation in any Beta Trial and use of the trial software is subject to these Terms which form a binding agreement between you and us.

\n\n1. You must be over 18 years of age to take part in this Beta Trial and you must be a PSN Master Account Holder. 
\n\n
\n\n2. You must keep confidential all information relating to the trial software and the Beta Trials. You must not discuss the Beta Trials with anyone except us and other people taking part in the Beta Trials (“Beta Testers”). In particular, you must not discuss the Beta Trials with anyone associated with a competing videogame format or publisher, a news or information service (whether television, magazine, newspaper or otherwise) or in any online forum or chat room, other than our official Beta Trial forum. Any codes or passwords which give access to trial software or Beta Trial forums are personal to you and must not be shared with anyone else.

\n\n3. You must keep the trial software secure. You are licensed to use the trial software on a non-exclusive, revocable, non-transferable, limited basis and you must only use it for the Beta Trials. You must not copy the trial software nor give or sell it to anyone and you must not try to reverse engineer it or use it to create derivative works.

\n\n4. At all times during the Beta Trials you must act lawfully and with respect towards other Beta Testers. If the Beta Trial takes place via PSN, you must comply with the PSN Terms of Service and User Agreement (available at http://network.eu.playstation.com/tosua/index.html). You are responsible for any activity on your PSN Master Account or related sub-account during the Beta Trial. We are not responsible for the behaviour of other Beta Testers during the Beta Trial, but please let us know if you become aware of any unlawful or inappropriate behaviour by other Beta Testers. 

\n\n5. From time to time during the Beta Trials we may modify the trial software and related content and services automatically and without notice. Modifications may cause loss of data or content and loss of function or utility. You hereby authorise us to make all such modifications and agree that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we are not liable for any loss of data, content, function or utility.

\n\n6. We will use any personal information which you give us when you register or in the course of the Beta Trials to operate the Beta Trials and for research and analysis, in particular to improve the trial software and our other products and services. We will share your information with our affiliates and sub-contractors in the United Kingdom and elsewhere (including Australia, Japan and the United States of America) and they may store and use this information in their respective countries, but only for the same reasons. You agree that we may contact you in connection with the Beta Trials and to collect your feedback on the trial software.

\n\n7. You agree that your suggestions for improvements, enhancements and other changes to the trial software, and our other products and services, and any material which you provide to us during the Beta Trial, will belong to us and may be implemented by us, in whole or in part, without any payment or other compensation to you or anyone else. If your suggestions are not your own original ideas, please do not submit them.

\n\n8. We reserve the right to suspend or cancel any Beta Trial or your access to any Beta Trial at any time in our absolute discretion. If we believe that you are in breach of any of these Terms or any other relevant terms, we may terminate your participation in the Beta Trials. 

\n\n9. You agree that any products or services which you purchase in relation to the beta trial may be modified by Lockwood Publishing after purchase for the purposes of improvement and balancing. You authorize us to make all the modifications we deem necessary or desirable. You agree that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we are not liable for any loss of data, content, function or utility.

\n\n10. To the extent permitted by applicable law, these Terms shall be construed and interpreted in accordance with the laws of England and the contract between you and us shall be deemed to have been formed and performed in England. We may assign our rights and obligations under these Terms to any of our affiliates and sub-contractors without your consent provided that such assignment does not adversely affect your rights under these Terms.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">\n\nCes conditions s'appliquent à tout Test de version bêta mis en place par Lockwood Publishing Ltd (“Test de version bêta”). Votre participation à tout Test de version bêta et l'utilisation du logiciel de test sont soumises à ces conditions qui constituent un accord contraignant entre vous et nous.

\n\n1. Vous devez être âgé de plus de 18 ans pour participer à ce Test de version bêta et vous devez être titulaire d'un compte principal PSN. 
\n\n
\n\n2. Vous devez respecter la confidentialité de toute information ayant trait au logiciel de test ou aux Tests de version bêta. Vous ne devez parler à personne d'autre des Tests de version bêta excepté à nous et aux autres personnes prenant part aux Tests de version bêta ("Testeurs de version bêta"). En particulier, vous ne devez en aucun cas discuter des Tests de version bêta avec quiconque associé à un format ou un éditeur de jeux vidéo concurrent, un service d'informations (télévision, magazine, journal ou autre) ni dans des forums ou chat rooms en ligne autres que notre forum officiel de Test de version bêta. Les codes ou mots de passe donnant accès au logiciel de test ou aux forums de Test de version bêta ne peuvent être partagés avec des tiers.

\n\n3. Vous devez garder le logiciel de test en sécurité. Vous êtes autorisé à utiliser le logiciel de test sur une base non-exclusive, révocable, non-transférable, limitée et vous devez l'utiliser uniquement pour les Test de version bêta. Vous n'êtes pas autorisé à copier ni donner ou vendre le logiciel de test à quiconque , ni vous livrer à de la rétro-ingénierie ou en créer des produits dérivés.

\n\n4. À tout moment durant les Tests de version bêta vous devez agir conformément à la loi et dans le respect des autres Testeurs de version bêta. Si le Test de version bêta se déroule via PSN, vous devez vous conformer aux conditions générales d'utilisation PSN (disponibles sur http://network.eu.playstation.com/tosua/index.html). Vous êtes seul responsable de l'activité sur votre compte PSN principal ou secondaire au cours du Test de version bêta. Nous ne sommes pas responsables du comportement des autres Testeurs de version bêta au cours du Test de version bêta, mais nous vous prions de bien vouloir nous informer de tout comportement illégal ou inapproprié de la part d'autres Testeurs de version bêta. 

\n\n5. Au cours des Tests de version bêta, il est possible que nous modifiions en certaines occasions le logiciel de test ainsi que le contenu et les services relatifs de façon automatique et sans avis préalable. Les dites modifications peuvent entraîner la perte de données ou de contenu et la perte de certaines fonctions ou certains services. Vous nous autorisez par la présente à effectuer de telles modifications et consentez au fait que, dans les limites autorisées par la loi en vigueur, nous ne sommes pas responsable des éventuelles pertes de données, contenus, fonctions ou services.

\n\n6. Nous utiliserons toute information personnelle que vous nous communiquerez lors de votre inscription ou tout au long des Tests de version bêta pour mener ces mêmes Tests de version bêta et dans un objectif de recherche et d'analyse, en particulier dans le but d'améliorer le logiciel de test ainsi que nos autres produits et services. Nous partagerons vos informations avec nos filiales et sous-traitants au Royaume-Uni et ailleurs (notamment en Australie, au Japon, et aux États-Unis) qui pourront stocker ces informations dans leurs pays respectifs, mais uniquement pour les mêmes raisons. Vous nous autorisez à vous contacter dans le cadre des Tests de version bêta et à recueillir vos impressions sur le logiciel de test.

\n\n7. Vous consentez au fait que les suggestions concernant les améliorations et autres modifications du logiciel de test, de nos autres produits et services et tout autre matériel, transmises au cours du Test de version bêta, nous appartiennent et pourront être utilisées par nous en tout ou partie sans aucune rétribution ni aucune compensation pour vous ni qui ce soit. Si vos suggestions ne sont pas basées sur vos propres idées originales, veuillez ne pas les soumettre.

\n\n8. Nous nous réservons le droit de suspendre ou d'annuler tout Test de version bêta ou votre accès à un Test de version bêta à tout moment et à notre entière discrétion. Si nous avons des raisons de croire que vous commettez une infraction envers les présentes conditions ou toutes autres conditions relatives, nous mettront un terme à votre participation aux Tests de version bêta. 

\n\n9. Vous consentez au fait que les produits ou services achetés dans le cadre du Test de version bêta puissent être modifiés par Lockwood Publishing après l'achat à des fins d'amélioration et d'ajustement. Vous nous autorisez à faire toutes les modifications que nous estimons nécessaires ou souhaitables. Vous consentez au fait que, dans les limites autorisées par la loi en vigueur, nous ne sommes pas responsable des éventuelles pertes de données, contenus, fonctions ou services.

\n\n10. Dans les limites autorisées par la loi en vigueur, les présentes conditions seront régies et interprétées conformément aux lois d'Angleterre et ce contrat entre vous et nous sera considéré comme établi et exécuté en Angleterre. Nous pouvons transférer nos droits et obligations définis par les présentes conditions à nos filiales et sous-traitants sans votre consentement sous réserve qu'un tel transfert n'affecte en rien vos droits définis sous ces mêmes conditions.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">\n\nDiese Nutzungsbedingungen gelten für jeden von Lockwood Publishing Ltd durchgeführten Beta-Test (nachfolgend “Beta-Test”). Teilnahme am Beta-Test und die Nutzung der Test-Software unterliegen diesen Nutzungsbedingungen, die einen verbindlichen Vertrag zwischen Ihnen und uns darstellen.

\n\n1. Um an diesem Beta-Test teilnehmen zu können, müssen Sie mindestens 18 Jahre alt sein und über ein PSN-Hauptkonto verfügen. 
\n\n
\n\n2. Sie sind verpflichtet, alle Informationen zur Test-Software und zu den Beta-Tests vertraulich zu behandeln. Sie dürfen sich nur mit uns und anderen Teilnehmern an Beta-Tests (nachfolgend “Beta-Tester”) über die Beta-Tests austauschen. Insbesondere dürfen sie diesbezügliche Informationen nicht an Personen weitergeben, die mit konkurrierenden Videospiele-Entwicklern und -Publishern oder Nachrichtenmedien in Verbindung stehen und Sie dürfen diese Informationen nur in unserem offiziellen Beta-Test-Forum diskutieren.  Codes und Passwörter, die Ihnen Zugang zur Test-Software und den Beta-Test-Foren ermöglichen dürfen nicht weitergegeben werden.

\n\n3. Sie sind verpflichtet, die Test-Software sicher zu verwahren. Sie erhalten eine begrenzte, nicht exklusive, nicht übertragbare Lizenz für die Test-Software, die nur im Rahmen des Beta-Tests zu nutzen ist. Es ist Ihnen untersagt, eine Kopie der Test-Software anzufertigen, sie an Dritte weiterzugeben oder zu verkaufen, sie zurückzuentwickeln oder abzuwandeln.

\n\n4. Sie sind verpflichtet, während der Beta-Tests alle Regeln einzuhalten und andere Beta-Tester respektvoll zu behandeln. Wenn der Beta-Test über PSN durchgeführt wird, gelten die Nutzungsbedingungen für das PSN (einzusehen unter http://network.eu.playstation.com/tosua/index.html). Während des Beta-Tests tragen Sie die Verantwortung für alle Aktivitäten, die mit Ihrem PSN-Hauptkonto und dessen Unterkonten durchgeführt werden. Wir können für das Verhalten anderer Beta-Tester keine Verantwortung übernehmen. Teilen Sie uns bitte unverzüglich mit, wenn Sie regelwidriges oder unangemessenes Verhalten beobachten. 

\n\n5. Es kann während der Beta-Tests jederzeit vorkommen, dass wir automatisch und ohne vorherige Ankündigung Änderungen an der Test-Software vornehmen. Änderungen können zu Datenverlusten und Störungen in der Funktionalität führen. Sie nehmen zur Kenntnis, dass wir diese Änderungen durchführen und willigen ein, uns soweit gesetzlich zulässig für Datenverluste und Störungen in der Funktionalität schadlos zu halten.

\n\n6. Wir verwenden Ihre persönlichen Informationen, die Sie uns bei der Registrierung oder während des Beta-Tests mitteilen, für den Betrieb der Beta-Tests sowie für Forschung und Analyse, insbesondere zur Verbesserung der Test-Software und anderer Produkte und Dienstleistungen. Wir geben Ihre Informationen an unsere Partner in Großbritannien und weltweit (einschließlich Australien, Japan und USA) weiter. Unsere Partner sind nur dazu berechtigt, diese Informationen zu speichern und für die oben genannten Zwecke zu verwenden. Sie stimmen zu, dass wir Sie in Verbindung mit den Beta-Tests kontaktieren dürfen, um Ihre Feedback zur Test-Software zu erfragen.

\n\n7. Sie akzeptieren, dass Ihre Vorschläge zu Verbesserungen und anderen Änderungen an der Test-Software und unseren anderen Produkten und Dienstleistungen, sowie jegliches Material, dass Sie uns während des Beta-Tests zur Verfügung stellen, ohne finanzielle Vergütung für Sie oder Dritte in unseren Besitz übergehen und ganz oder teilweise von uns implementiert werden können. Wenn Vorschläge nicht Ihr eigenes geistiges Eigentum sind, sehen Sie bitte davon ab, sie uns zu schicken.

\n\n8. Wir behalten uns das Recht vor, Beta-Tests oder Ihren Zugang zu Beta-Tests jederzeit ohne Nennung von Gründen auszusetzen oder abzubrechen. Sollten Sie gegen diese Nutzungsbedingungen verstoßen, behalten wir uns vor, Sie von der Teilnahme an den Beta-Tests auszuschließen. 

\n\n9. Sie akzeptieren, dass jegliche von Ihnen in Verbindung mit dem Beta-Test bezogenen Produkte oder Dienstleistungen nach dem Bezug von Lockwood Publishing geändert werden können, um Verbesserungen und Balancierung zu implementieren. Sie erkennen unser Recht an, alle von uns als notwendig oder wünschenswert erachteten Änderungen vorzunehmen. Sie willigen ein, uns soweit gesetzlich zulässig für Datenverluste und Störungen in der Funktionalität schadlos zu halten.

\n\n10. Diese Nutzungsbedingungen sind soweit gesetzlich zulässig anhand der Rechtslage in England auszulegen und der Vertrag zwischen Ihnen und uns gilt als in England abgeschlossen und ausgeführt. Wir behalten uns vor, unsere aus diesen Nutzungsbedingungen entstehenden Rechte und Pflichten ohne Ihre Zustimmung an unsere Partner zu übertragen, insofern Ihre aus diesen Nutzungsbedingungen entstehenden Rechte dadurch nicht beeinträchtigt werden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"\n\nLe seguenti condizioni si applicano a tutte le "Beta Trial" di Lockwood Publishing Ltd. La partecipazione a tali "Beta Trial" e l'utilizzo del software di 

valutazione è soggetto all'accettazione delle seguenti condizioni.
\n\n1. Per partecipare alle "Beta Trial" è necessario avere più di 18 anni e possedere un account 

master PSN. 
\n\n
\n\n2. Non divulgare le informazioni relative al software di valutazione e alle "Beta Trial". Non parlare delle "Beta Trial con nessuno, fatta eccezione 

Lockwood Publishing Ltd e le altre persone che partecipano alle Trial (“Beta Tester”). In particolare, non discutere delle "Beta Trial" con persone associate a 

videogiochi o editori concorrenti, con servizi d'informazione (televisioni, riviste, quotidiani, ecc.) oppure in forum o chat room online, fatta eccezione per il forum 

ufficiale delle Beta Trial. Codici o password che consentono l'accesso al software di valutazione o ai forum delle Beta Trial sono personali e non devono essere 

condivise con altre persone.

\n\n3. Deve essere garantita la sicurezza del software di valutazione. Il software di valutazione è non esclusivo, revocabile, non 

trasferibile e l'utilizzo è limitato alle sole Beta Trial. Non è consentita la copia, la cessione, la vendita o le operazioni di reverse engineer sul software di 

valutazione, nè la creazione di opere da esso derivate.
\n\n4. Per tutta la durata delle Beta Trial, l'utente dovrà mantenere un atteggiamento legittimo e rispettoso nei 

confronti degli altri Beta Tester. Nel caso in cui le Beta Trial si svolgessero tramite PSN, è necessario accettare i termini di servizio e le condizioni d'uso PSN 

(disponibili su: http://network.eu.playstation.com/tosua/index.html; informazioni in lingua inglese). Durante le Beta Trial, l'utente è responsabile delle attività 

svolte con l'account master PSN o relativi account secondari. Lockwood Publishing Ltd. non è responsabile per il comportamento degli altri Beta Tester durante le Beta 

Trial ma è necessario segnalare eventuali comportamenti inappropriati di altri Beta Tester. 

\n\n5. Occasionalmente, durante le Beta Trial, il software di valutazione e 

i relativi contenuti e servizi potrebbero essere automaticamente modificati senza preavviso. Tali modifiche potrebbero provocare perdite di dati e contenuti o perdite 

di funzionalità. L'utente autorizza Lockwood Publishing Ltd. ad effettuare tali modifiche e accetta che, nei limiti consentiti dalla legge, Lockwood Publishing Ltd. 

non è responsabile per eventuali perdite di dati, contenuti o perdite di funzionalità.
\n\n6. Le informazioni personali dell'utente fornite durante la registrazione o 

nel corso dei Beta Trial, saranno utilizzate per le operazioni a esse relative e per analisi e ricerche, in particolare per il miglioramento del software di valutazione 

e dei nostri prodotti e servizi. Le informazioni saranno condivise con i nostri affiliati e sub-appaltatori nel Regno Unito e altrove (compresi Australia, Giappone e 

Stati Uniti) e potranno essere memorizzate e utilizzate nei rispettivi paesi ma solo per i medesimi scopi. L'utente acconsente di essere contattato in relazione alle 

Beta Trial per avere opinioni e pareri sul software di valutazione.

\n\n7. L'utente acconsente che i suggerimenti volti al miglioramento o a eventuali modifiche al 

software di valutazione e ai nostri prodotti e servizi e qualsiasi materiale fornito dall'utente durante le Beta Trial, appartengono a Lockwood Publishing Ltd. e 

possono essere implementate parzialmente o interamente, senza pagamento o compensazione per l'utente o per altre persone. L'utente dovrebbe fornire solo idee 

originali.
\n\n8. È facoltà di Lockwood Publishing Ltd. porre fine alla partecipazione dell'utente alle Beta Trial. Lockwood Publishing Ltd. si riserva il diritto di 

sospendere o annullare le Beta Trial o l'accesso dell'utente alle stesse in qualsiasi momento e a sua assoluta discrezione. La partecipazione dell'utente alle Beta 

Trial può essere annullata in caso di violazione di questi o altri termini e condizioni rilevanti. 

\n\n9. L'utente acconsente che i prodotti e i servizi acquistati in 

relazione alle beta trial possano essere modificate da Lockwood Publishing dopo l'acquisto. L'utente autorizza Lockwood Publishing Ltd. a eseguire le modifiche da esso 

ritenute necessarie. Accetta inoltre, nei limiti consentiti dalla legge, che Lockwood Publishing non è responsabile per perdite di dati e contenuti o perdite di 

funzionalità.\n\n10. Nei limiti consentiti dalla legge, questi termini e condizioni saranno interpretati dalle leggi dell'Inghilterra e si ritiene che il contratto tra 

Lockwood Publishing Ltd. e l'utente sia stato siglato in Inghilterra. I diritti e le obbligazioni derivanti da questi termini e condizioni potranno essere assegnati ai 

nostri affiliati o sub-appaltatori senza il consenso dell'utente, a patto che tale assegnazione non modifichi negativamente i diritti dell'utente in base a tali termini 

e condizioni. 
"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">\n\nEstos Términos se aplican a cualquier prueba beta gestionada por Lockwood Publishing Ltd (en adelante, "Prueba Beta"). Tu participación en cualquier Prueba Beta y el uso del software de prueba están sujetos a estos Términos, que constituyen un acuerdo vinculante entre tú y nosotros.

\n\n1. Debes ser mayor de 18 años para participar en esta Prueba Beta y debes ser el titular de una cuenta principal de PSN.
\n\n
\n\n2. Debes mantener el carácter confidencial de toda la información relacionada con el software de prueba y las Pruebas Beta. No debes comentar las Pruebas Beta con nadie, excepto con nosotros y otras personas que participen en las Pruebas Beta ("Evaluadores de las Pruebas Beta"). En particular, no debes comentar las Pruebas Beta con nadie relacionado con la edición o el diseño de videojuegos de la competencia, un servicio de noticias o información (ya sea televisión, prensa escrita o de otro tipo), o en cualquier foro o chat en línea que no sea nuestro foro de Pruebas Beta. Los códigos o claves que dan acceso al software de prueba o a los foros de Pruebas Beta son personales y no deben compartirse con nadie.

\n\n3. Debes proteger el software de prueba. Tienes licencia para utilizar el software de prueba de forma no exclusiva, revocable, no transferible y limitada, y sólo debes utilizarlo para las Pruebas Beta. No debes copiar el software de prueba ni cederlo o venderlo a nadie, y no debes aplicarle técnicas de ingeniería inversa o utilizarlo para crear obras derivadas.

\n\n4. En todo momento durante las Pruebas Beta debes actuar de forma legítima y respetuosa con otros Evaluadores de las Pruebas Beta. Si la Prueba Beta se lleva a cabo a través de PSN, debes cumplir con los Términos de Servicio y Acuerdo de Usuario de de PSN (disponible en http://network.eu.playstation.com/tosua/index.html). Eres responsable de cualquier actividad en tu cuenta principal de PSN o subcuenta relacionada durante la Prueba Beta. No somos responsables del comportamiento de otros Evaluadores de la Prueba Beta durante la Prueba Beta, pero por favor infórmanos si tienes conocimiento de cualquier comportamiento ilegal o inadecuado de otros Evaluadores de la Prueba Beta.

\n\n5. De vez en cuando durante las Pruebas Beta, podemos modificar el software de prueba y contenidos y servicios relacionados de forma automática y sin previo aviso. Las modificaciones pueden causar pérdida de datos o contenido y la pérdida de función o utilidad. Por la presente, nos autorizas a hacer todas las modificaciones pertinentes y estás de acuerdo en que, en la medida permitida por la legislación aplicable, no somos responsables de cualquier pérdida de datos, contenido, función o utilidad.

\n\n6. Utilizaremos cualquier información personal que nos proporciones durante el registro o en el curso de las Pruebas Beta para gestionar las Pruebas Beta y con fines de investigación y análisis, en particular para mejorar el software de prueba y otros productos y servicios. Compartiremos tu información con nuestros afiliados y subcontratistas en el Reino Unido y otros países (incluidos Australia, Japón y los Estados Unidos de América), quienes podrán almacenar y utilizar esta información en sus respectivos países, pero solo por las mismas razones. Aceptas que podamos ponernos en contacto contigo en relación con las Pruebas Beta y para conocer tu opinión sobre el software de prueba.

\n\n7. Estás de acuerdo en que tus sugerencias para mejoras, ampliaciones y otros cambios en el software de prueba, y nuestros otros productos y servicios, así como cualquier material que nos proporciones durante la Prueba Beta, nos pertenece y puede ser implementado por nosotros, en su totalidad o en parte, sin ofrecerte a cambio ningún tipo de pago u otra contraprestación a ti o a cualquier otra persona. Si tus sugerencias no son ideas originales propias, no las envíes.

\n\n8. Nos reservamos el derecho de suspender o cancelar cualquier Prueba Beta o tu acceso a cualquier Prueba Beta en cualquier momento a nuestra absoluta discreción. Si creemos que estás incumpliendo cualquiera de estos Términos o cualesquiera otros términos pertinentes, podemos poner fin a tu participación en las Pruebas Beta.

\n\n9. Estás de acuerdo en que cualquier producto o servicio que compres en relación con la Prueba Beta pueda ser modificado por Lockwood Publishing después de la compra a efectos de mejora y equilibrio. Nos autorizas a hacer todas las modificaciones que estimemos necesarias o convenientes. Convienes en que, en la medida permitida por la legislación aplicable, no somos responsables de cualquier pérdida de datos, contenido, función o utilidad.

\n\n10. En la medida permitida por la legislación aplicable, los presentes Términos se entenderán e interpretarán de conformidad con las leyes de Inglaterra y el contrato entre tú y nosotros se considerará formado y realizado en Inglaterra. Podemos ceder nuestros derechos y obligaciones bajo estos Términos a cualquiera de nuestras filiales y subcontratistas, sin tu consentimiento, siempre que dicha cesión no afecte negativamente a tus derechos bajo estos Términos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">\n\nThese Terms apply to any beta trial operated by Lockwood Publishing Ltd (“Beta Trial”). Your participation in any Beta Trial and use of the trial software is subject to these Terms which form a binding agreement between you and us.

\n\n1. You must be over 18 years of age to take part in this Beta Trial and you must be a PSN Master Account Holder. 
\n\n
\n\n2. You must keep confidential all information relating to the trial software and the Beta Trials. You must not discuss the Beta Trials with anyone except us and other people taking part in the Beta Trials (“Beta Testers”). In particular, you must not discuss the Beta Trials with anyone associated with a competing videogame format or publisher, a news or information service (whether television, magazine, newspaper or otherwise) or in any online forum or chat room, other than our official Beta Trial forum. Any codes or passwords which give access to trial software or Beta Trial forums are personal to you and must not be shared with anyone else.

\n\n3. You must keep the trial software secure. You are licensed to use the trial software on a non-exclusive, revocable, non-transferable, limited basis and you must only use it for the Beta Trials. You must not copy the trial software nor give or sell it to anyone and you must not try to reverse engineer it or use it to create derivative works.

\n\n4. At all times during the Beta Trials you must act lawfully and with respect towards other Beta Testers. If the Beta Trial takes place via PSN, you must comply with the PSN Terms of Service and User Agreement (available at http://network.eu.playstation.com/tosua/index.html). You are responsible for any activity on your PSN Master Account or related sub-account during the Beta Trial. We are not responsible for the behaviour of other Beta Testers during the Beta Trial, but please let us know if you become aware of any unlawful or inappropriate behaviour by other Beta Testers. 

\n\n5. From time to time during the Beta Trials we may modify the trial software and related content and services automatically and without notice. Modifications may cause loss of data or content and loss of function or utility. You hereby authorise us to make all such modifications and agree that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we are not liable for any loss of data, content, function or utility.

\n\n6. We will use any personal information which you give us when you register or in the course of the Beta Trials to operate the Beta Trials and for research and analysis, in particular to improve the trial software and our other products and services. We will share your information with our affiliates and sub-contractors in the United Kingdom and elsewhere (including Australia, Japan and the United States of America) and they may store and use this information in their respective countries, but only for the same reasons. You agree that we may contact you in connection with the Beta Trials and to collect your feedback on the trial software.

\n\n7. You agree that your suggestions for improvements, enhancements and other changes to the trial software, and our other products and services, and any material which you provide to us during the Beta Trial, will belong to us and may be implemented by us, in whole or in part, without any payment or other compensation to you or anyone else. If your suggestions are not your own original ideas, please do not submit them.

\n\n8. We reserve the right to suspend or cancel any Beta Trial or your access to any Beta Trial at any time in our absolute discretion. If we believe that you are in breach of any of these Terms or any other relevant terms, we may terminate your participation in the Beta Trials. 

\n\n9. You agree that any products or services which you purchase in relation to the beta trial may be modified by Lockwood Publishing after purchase for the purposes of improvement and balancing. You authorize us to make all the modifications we deem necessary or desirable. You agree that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we are not liable for any loss of data, content, function or utility.

\n\n10. To the extent permitted by applicable law, these Terms shall be construed and interpreted in accordance with the laws of England and the contract between you and us shall be deemed to have been formed and performed in England. We may assign our rights and obligations under these Terms to any of our affiliates and sub-contractors without your consent provided that such assignment does not adversely affect your rights under these Terms.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">\n\n본 약관은 Lockwood Publishing Ltd에 의해 진행되는 모든 베타 체험(이하 “베타 체험”)에 적용됩니다. 베타 체험에 참가하거나 체험판 소프트웨어를 사용하는 것은 귀하와 본사 간에 법적 구속력을 지닌 계약을 성립하는 것으로 간주합니다.

\n\n1. 베타 체험에 참가하기 위해서는 만 18세 이상이어야 하며 PSN 마스터 계정 소유자여야만 한다.
\n\n
\n\n2. 체험 소프트웨어 및 베타 체험과 관련된 모든 정보에 기밀을 유지하여야 한다. 공식 베타 체험 포럼을 통해 본사 및 베타 체험에 참가하고 있는 타인(이하 “베타 테스터”)과 논의하는 경우를 제외하고는 온라인 포럼 또는 채팅 등의 수단을 통하여 관련 사항에 대한 논의를 금지하며, 그 중에서도 경쟁 비디오 게임 종류 또는 유통사 및 업계 뉴스와 정보 제공 서비스(텔레비전, 잡지, 신문 등을 포함)의 직원과의 논의는 엄중히 금한다.  체험 소프트웨어 또는 베타 체험 포럼에 접근하기 위해 주어지는 코드 및 암호는 사용자 전용으로 주어지는 것이므로 절대 타인과 공유해서는 안 된다.

\n\n3. 사용자는 상시 체험 소프트웨어의 보안을 유지하여야 한다. 사용자에게는 취소가 가능하며 양도 불가능한 비독점적인 사용권이 베타 체험 목적으로만 제한적으로 허가된다. 사용자는 본 체험 소프트웨어의 본 체험 소프트웨어를 복제하거나, 판매하거나, 타인에게 양도하거나, 리버스 엔지니어링을 시도하거나 본 소프트웨어를 이용해 작품을 제작해서는 안 된다.

\n\n4. 사용자는 베타 체험 중 불법적인 행위를 해서는 안 되며, 다른 베타 테스터들에게 불쾌감을 주지 않아야 한다. 베타 체험이 PSN을 통해 진행되는 경우에는 PSN 이용약관(http://www.playstation.co.kr/ps_etc/etc_use.sce 참조)에 동의하여야만 한다. 사용자는 베타 체험 중 자신의 PSN 마스터 계정 및 부속 계정의 모든 활동에 대한 책임을 지게 된다. 본사는 베타 체험 중 다른 베타 테스터에 대한 사용자의 행동에 대해 책임을 지지 않으나 다른 베타 테스터의 불법적이거나 부적절한 행위에 의해 불쾌감 또는 모욕감을 느낀 경우 본사에 연락할 수 있다. 

\n\n5. 베타 체험 중 본사는 체험 소프트웨어 및 관련 콘텐츠와 서비스를 사전 통지 없이 자동으로 수정할 수 있으며, 이러한 수정은 데이터 및 콘텐츠의 손상을 유발하거나 특정 기능 및 편의성의 하락으로 이어질 수 있다. 본 약관은 사용자가 본사의 이러한 수정 행위를 법이 허용하는 최대한의 범위에서 동의하며, 본사는 데이터나 콘텐츠, 기능, 편의성의 손실이 발생하더라도 책임을 지지 않는다는 것에 동의한다.

\n\n6. 본사는 베타 체험을 진행함에 있어 사용자가 베타 체험의 참가 및 진행을 위해 제공한 개인 정보를 연구와 분석에 이용하여 체험 소프트웨어를 비롯한 본사의 제품 및 서비스 개선을 도모할 수 있다. 사용자의 정보는 영국과 기타 지역(오스트레일리아, 일본, 미합중국 포함)에 위치한 계열사 및 하도급업체와 공유되며 이러한 정보는 상기와 동일한 사유일 경우에만 해당 국가에 저장되어 사용될 수 있다. 사용자는 본사가 사용자의 베타 체험 중 사용자에게 연락하거나 체험 소프트웨어에 대한 피드백을 수집할 수 있다는 것에 동의한다.

\n\n7. 사용자는 베타 체험을 통해 본사에 제공한 개선, 개량, 변경 등의 모든 제안사항이 그에 대한 대금 지불이나 그에 상응하는 보상의 제공 없이도 체험 소프트웨어를 비롯한 본사의 제품 및 서비스에 부분적 또는 전체적으로 사용될 수 있으며, 그 권리도 본사에 귀속된다는 점에 동의한다. 사용자의 제안사항이 타인의 소유라면 본사에 전달하지 아니하여야 한다.

\n\n8. 본사는 베타 체험 중 본사의 독자적 판단에 의해 언제든지 사용자의 베타 체험 접근 권한을 정지, 취소할 수 있는 권한을 지닌다. 본사는 사용자가 약관 또는 관련 내용을 어겼다고 판단될 경우, 사용자의 베타 체험 참가권을 소멸시킬 수 있다. 

\n\n9. 사용자가 베타 체험과 관련된 제품 또는 서비스를 구입한 경우, 해당 상품이 구매 후에 개선 및 밸런스 유지를 위하여 Lockwood Publishing에 의해 수정될 수 있다는 점에 동의한다. 사용자는 본사가 필요하거나 바람직하다고 판단하는 모든 사항을 수정할 수 있는 권한을 허가한다. 사용자는 법이 허용하는 최대한의 범위 내에서 데이터나 콘텐츠, 기능, 편의성의 손실에 본사는 책임이 없다는 점에 동의한다.

\n\n10. 법이 허용하는 최대한의 범위 내에서, 본 약관은 잉글랜드 법령에 의거하여 해석되어야 하며, 본사와 사용자 간의 계약은 잉글랜드 내에서 체결되고 수행된 것으로 간주한다. 본사는 사용자의 약관상 권리에 악영향을 미치지 않는 범위 내에서 본 약관의 권리와 의무를 계열사 및 하도급업체에 사용자 동의 없이 양도할 수 있다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">\n\nThese Terms apply to any beta trial operated by Lockwood Publishing Ltd (“Beta Trial”). Your participation in any Beta Trial and use of the trial software is subject to these Terms which form a binding agreement between you and us.

\n\n1. You must be over 18 years of age to take part in this Beta Trial and you must be a PSN Master Account Holder. 
\n\n
\n\n2. You must keep confidential all information relating to the trial software and the Beta Trials. You must not discuss the Beta Trials with anyone except us and other people taking part in the Beta Trials (“Beta Testers”). In particular, you must not discuss the Beta Trials with anyone associated with a competing videogame format or publisher, a news or information service (whether television, magazine, newspaper or otherwise) or in any online forum or chat room, other than our official Beta Trial forum. Any codes or passwords which give access to trial software or Beta Trial forums are personal to you and must not be shared with anyone else.

\n\n3. You must keep the trial software secure. You are licensed to use the trial software on a non-exclusive, revocable, non-transferable, limited basis and you must only use it for the Beta Trials. You must not copy the trial software nor give or sell it to anyone and you must not try to reverse engineer it or use it to create derivative works.

\n\n4. At all times during the Beta Trials you must act lawfully and with respect towards other Beta Testers. If the Beta Trial takes place via PSN, you must comply with the PSN Terms of Service and User Agreement (available at http://www.scei.co.jp/ps3-eula/asia/index.html). You are responsible for any activity on your PSN Master Account or related sub-account during the Beta Trial. We are not responsible for the behaviour of other Beta Testers during the Beta Trial, but please let us know if you become aware of any unlawful or inappropriate behaviour by other Beta Testers. 

\n\n5. From time to time during the Beta Trials we may modify the trial software and related content and services automatically and without notice. Modifications may cause loss of data or content and loss of function or utility. You hereby authorise us to make all such modifications and agree that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we are not liable for any loss of data, content, function or utility.

\n\n6. We will use any personal information which you give us when you register or in the course of the Beta Trials to operate the Beta Trials and for research and analysis, in particular to improve the trial software and our other products and services. We will share your information with our affiliates and sub-contractors in the United Kingdom and elsewhere (including Australia, Japan and the United States of America) and they may store and use this information in their respective countries, but only for the same reasons. You agree that we may contact you in connection with the Beta Trials and to collect your feedback on the trial software.

\n\n7. You agree that your suggestions for improvements, enhancements and other changes to the trial software, and our other products and services, and any material which you provide to us during the Beta Trial, will belong to us and may be implemented by us, in whole or in part, without any payment or other compensation to you or anyone else. If your suggestions are not your own original ideas, please do not submit them.

\n\n8. We reserve the right to suspend or cancel any Beta Trial or your access to any Beta Trial at any time in our absolute discretion. If we believe that you are in breach of any of these Terms or any other relevant terms, we may terminate your participation in the Beta Trials. 

\n\n9. You agree that any products or services which you purchase in relation to the beta trial may be modified by Lockwood Publishing after purchase for the purposes of improvement and balancing. You authorize us to make all the modifications we deem necessary or desirable. You agree that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we are not liable for any loss of data, content, function or utility.

\n\n10. To the extent permitted by applicable law, these Terms shall be construed and interpreted in accordance with the laws of England and the contract between you and us shall be deemed to have been formed and performed in England. We may assign our rights and obligations under these Terms to any of our affiliates and sub-contractors without your consent provided that such assignment does not adversely affect your rights under these Terms.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">\n\n以下條款適用於任何由Lockwood Publishing Ltd提供的Beta測試(「Beta測試」)。您參與任何Beta測試及測試軟件的使用均受此等條款約束，並構成您與本公司之間的有約束力合約。

\n\n1. 您必須年滿18歲並身為PSN主帳號持有人，始可參與 Beta測試的試用。
\n\n
\n\n2. 您必須將所有與測試軟件及Beta測試有關的內容予以保密，並且不會與本公司和其他參與Beta測試（「Beta測試者」）以外的任何人士討論該等內容。特別而言，您不可與任何與競爭性電子遊戲制式或出版商、任何新聞或信息服務有關聯的人士（不論是在電視、雜誌、報章或任何其他媒體）或在我們官方測試聊天區以外的任何網上聊天區討論該等內容。任何用來存取測試軟件或Beta測試聊天區的代碼或密碼只供您個人使用，不得與他人分享。

\n\n3. 您必須確保測試軟件的安全。本公司可在非專享、可撤回、不可轉讓和有限的基礎上授權您使用測試軟件，且除試用外，不可作任何其他用途。您不可將測試軟件複製、給予或售予他人或進行反向工程或用以製作任何衍生作品。

\n\n4. 您必須在試用期間裡依法行事並尊重其他試用者。如透過PSN試用Beta測試，您必須遵守PSN使用條款及用戶合約（詳情：http://www.scei.co.jp/ps3-eula/asia/index.html）您須要對您的PSN主帳號或關聯子帳號在Beta體驗期間的任何活動負責。本公司不會就Beta測試期間其他Beta測試者的行為負責，但如果您發現任何其它Beta測試者有違法或不正當的行為，請通知本公司。 

\n\n5. 我們會不時在試用期間自動變更測試軟件和相關內容及服務而不作另行通知。有關變更可能導致數據或內容、功能或用途的損失。您在此授權本公司作出該等變更並同意在適用法律許可的範圍內，本公司毋須就任何數據、內容、功能或用途的損失承擔任何責任。

\n\n6. 我們會使用您在註冊或試用Beta測試時提供的任何個人資料進行Beta測試的運作、研究及分析，特別用以改善測試軟件和我們其他產品及服務。我們將與我們位於英國及其他地方（包括澳洲、日本及美國）的關聯公司及分承包商分享您的資料，而他們可能會在其國家儲存及使用該等資料，但只會用作相同目的。您同意我們可與您聯絡以收集關於Beta測試及測試軟件的使用意見。

\n\n7. 您同意在Beta測試期間向本公司提供有關測試軟件、其他產品及服務的改善、改進及其他變更的意見。任何該等提供的材料將屬於我們。我們可能採用全部或部份建議，並不會向您或任何人支付任何費用或補償。如不是您的原創建議，請不要提交。

\n\n8. 本公司保留權利，可按本公司的絕對酌情決定在任何時間暫停或取消測試或暫停或取消您的測試。倘若本公司認定您已違反任何使用條款或任何其他相關的條款，本公司可終止您參與Beta測試。 

\n\n9. 您同意Lockwood Publishing可能會對任何您已購買，有關Beta測試的產品或服務，在購買後為了改善和平衡進行變更。您授權我們進行一切我們認為有需要或可取的變更。您同意在適用法律許可的範圍內，我們對任何數據、內容、功能和用途的損失不負任何責任。

\n\n10. 在適用法律許可的範圍內，本使用條款根據英國法律理解和詮釋，您與本公司之間的合約視作在英國訂立和執行。本公司可將在本使用條款下的權利和義務轉讓予任何關聯公司及分承包商而毋需您的同意，但該等轉讓不會對您在本使用條款下的權利產生不利影響。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">\n\n以下條款適用於任何由Lockwood Publishing Ltd提供的Beta測試(「Beta測試」)。您參與任何Beta測試及測試軟件的使用均受此等條款約束，並構成您與本公司之間的有約束力合約。

\n\n1. 您必須年滿18歲並身為PSN主帳號持有人，始可參與 Beta測試的試用。
\n\n
\n\n2. 您必須將所有與測試軟件及Beta測試有關的內容予以保密，並且不會與本公司和其他參與Beta測試（「Beta測試者」）以外的任何人士討論該等內容。特別而言，您不可與任何與競爭性電子遊戲制式或出版商、任何新聞或信息服務有關聯的人士（不論是在電視、雜誌、報章或任何其他媒體）或在我們官方測試聊天區以外的任何網上聊天區討論該等內容。任何用來存取測試軟件或Beta測試聊天區的代碼或密碼只供您個人使用，不得與他人分享。

\n\n3. 您必須確保測試軟件的安全。本公司可在非專享、可撤回、不可轉讓和有限的基礎上授權您使用測試軟件，且除試用外，不可作任何其他用途。您不可將測試軟件複製、給予或售予他人或進行反向工程或用以製作任何衍生作品。

\n\n4. 您必須在試用期間裡依法行事並尊重其他試用者。如透過PSN試用Beta測試，您必須遵守PSN使用條款及用戶合約（詳情：http://www.scei.co.jp/ps3-eula/asia/index.html）您須要對您的PSN主帳號或關聯子帳號在Beta體驗期間的任何活動負責。本公司不會就Beta測試期間其他Beta測試者的行為負責，但如果您發現任何其它Beta測試者有違法或不正當的行為，請通知本公司。 

\n\n5. 我們會不時在試用期間自動變更測試軟件和相關內容及服務而不作另行通知。有關變更可能導致數據或內容、功能或用途的損失。您在此授權本公司作出該等變更並同意在適用法律許可的範圍內，本公司毋須就任何數據、內容、功能或用途的損失承擔任何責任。

\n\n6. 我們會使用您在註冊或試用Beta測試時提供的任何個人資料進行Beta測試的運作、研究及分析，特別用以改善測試軟件和我們其他產品及服務。我們將與我們位於英國及其他地方（包括澳洲、日本及美國）的關聯公司及分承包商分享您的資料，而他們可能會在其國家儲存及使用該等資料，但只會用作相同目的。您同意我們可與您聯絡以收集關於Beta測試及測試軟件的使用意見。

\n\n7. 您同意在Beta測試期間向本公司提供有關測試軟件、其他產品及服務的改善、改進及其他變更的意見。任何該等提供的材料將屬於我們。我們可能採用全部或部份建議，並不會向您或任何人支付任何費用或補償。如不是您的原創建議，請不要提交。

\n\n8. 本公司保留權利，可按本公司的絕對酌情決定在任何時間暫停或取消測試或暫停或取消您的測試。倘若本公司認定您已違反任何使用條款或任何其他相關的條款，本公司可終止您參與Beta測試。 

\n\n9. 您同意Lockwood Publishing可能會對任何您已購買，有關Beta測試的產品或服務，在購買後為了改善和平衡進行變更。您授權我們進行一切我們認為有需要或可取的變更。您同意在適用法律許可的範圍內，我們對任何數據、內容、功能和用途的損失不負任何責任。

\n\n10. 在適用法律許可的範圍內，本使用條款根據英國法律理解和詮釋，您與本公司之間的合約視作在英國訂立和執行。本公司可將在本使用條款下的權利和義務轉讓予任何關聯公司及分承包商而毋需您的同意，但該等轉讓不會對您在本使用條款下的權利產生不利影響。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">\n\nThese Terms apply to any beta trial operated by Lockwood Publishing Ltd (“Beta Trial”). Your participation in any Beta Trial and use of the trial software is subject to these Terms which form a binding agreement between you and us.

\n\n1. You must be over 18 years of age to take part in this Beta Trial and you must be a PSN Master Account Holder. 
\n\n
\n\n2. You must keep confidential all information relating to the trial software and the Beta Trials. You must not discuss the Beta Trials with anyone except us and other people taking part in the Beta Trials (“Beta Testers”). In particular, you must not discuss the Beta Trials with anyone associated with a competing videogame format or publisher, a news or information service (whether television, magazine, newspaper or otherwise) or in any online forum or chat room, other than our official Beta Trial forum. Any codes or passwords which give access to trial software or Beta Trial forums are personal to you and must not be shared with anyone else.

\n\n3. You must keep the trial software secure. You are licensed to use the trial software on a non-exclusive, revocable, non-transferable, limited basis and you must only use it for the Beta Trials. You must not copy the trial software nor give or sell it to anyone and you must not try to reverse engineer it or use it to create derivative works.

\n\n4. At all times during the Beta Trials you must act lawfully and with respect towards other Beta Testers. If the Beta Trial takes place via PSN, you must comply with the PSN Terms of Service and User Agreement (available at http://network.eu.playstation.com/tosua/index.html). You are responsible for any activity on your PSN Master Account or related sub-account during the Beta Trial. We are not responsible for the behaviour of other Beta Testers during the Beta Trial, but please let us know if you become aware of any unlawful or inappropriate behaviour by other Beta Testers. 

\n\n5. From time to time during the Beta Trials we may modify the trial software and related content and services automatically and without notice. Modifications may cause loss of data or content and loss of function or utility. You hereby authorise us to make all such modifications and agree that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we are not liable for any loss of data, content, function or utility.

\n\n6. We will use any personal information which you give us when you register or in the course of the Beta Trials to operate the Beta Trials and for research and analysis, in particular to improve the trial software and our other products and services. We will share your information with our affiliates and sub-contractors in the United Kingdom and elsewhere (including Australia, Japan and the United States of America) and they may store and use this information in their respective countries, but only for the same reasons. You agree that we may contact you in connection with the Beta Trials and to collect your feedback on the trial software.

\n\n7. You agree that your suggestions for improvements, enhancements and other changes to the trial software, and our other products and services, and any material which you provide to us during the Beta Trial, will belong to us and may be implemented by us, in whole or in part, without any payment or other compensation to you or anyone else. If your suggestions are not your own original ideas, please do not submit them.

\n\n8. We reserve the right to suspend or cancel any Beta Trial or your access to any Beta Trial at any time in our absolute discretion. If we believe that you are in breach of any of these Terms or any other relevant terms, we may terminate your participation in the Beta Trials. 

\n\n9. You agree that any products or services which you purchase in relation to the beta trial may be modified by Lockwood Publishing after purchase for the purposes of improvement and balancing. You authorize us to make all the modifications we deem necessary or desirable. You agree that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we are not liable for any loss of data, content, function or utility.

\n\n10. To the extent permitted by applicable law, these Terms shall be construed and interpreted in accordance with the laws of England and the contract between you and us shall be deemed to have been formed and performed in England. We may assign our rights and obligations under these Terms to any of our affiliates and sub-contractors without your consent provided that such assignment does not adversely affect your rights under these Terms.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PLEASE_RETRY_LATER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Please try again in a moment.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Réessayez dans quelques instants.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bitte versuch es noch einmal.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Riprova più tardi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Vuelve a intentarlo en unos minutos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">時間をおいてもう一度実行してください</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Please try again in a moment.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Please try again in a moment.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Please try again in a moment.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Please try again in a moment.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Please try again in a moment.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SERVER_CONNECT_FAILED</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Failed to connect to server.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Connexion au serveur échouée.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verbindung zum Server fehlgeschlagen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Impossibile connettersi al server.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fin de la partida</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">サーバーとの接続に失敗しました</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Failed to connect to server.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Failed to connect to server.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Failed to connect to server.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Failed to connect to server.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Failed to connect to server.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CONNECTION_COMM</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Communicating with data server</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Connexion au serveur de données en cours.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Datenaustausch mit dem Datenserver</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Comunicazione in corso con il server</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estableciendo una comunicación con el servidor de datos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">データサーバーと接続中です</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">데이터 서버와 통신 중</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Communicating with data server</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">與資料伺服器通訊中</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">與資料伺服器通訊中</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Communicating with data server</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>