<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cyber Side Arm (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bras Latéral Cyber ​​(mâle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Seite Pistole (männlich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Laterale del braccio (maschio)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ciber brazo lateral (masculino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cyber Side Arm (male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It's late at night.  You take a wrong turn and visit a space you've never been in before. Sometimes PlayStation®Home can be scary.  That's when you need the security that comes with the Cyber Side Arm.  Feel safe in Home, anywhere in Home! (Cyber Side Arm is meant for entertainment purposes only. Not removable from holster.)[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il est tard dans la nuit. Vous prenez un mauvais virage et de visiter un espace que vous ne l'avez jamais été auparavant. Parfois PlayStation®Home peut être effrayant. C'est quand vous avez besoin de la sécurité qui vient avec le Bras Latéral Cyber​​. Se sentir en sécurité dans Home, n'importe dans HOME! (Bras latéral Cyber ​​est destiné à des fins de divertissement seulement. Non amovibl.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es ist spät in der Nacht. Sie nehmen eine falsche Abzweigung und besuchen ein Raum, den Sie nie in vorher gewesen sind. Manchmal PlayStation®Home kann beängstigend sein. Das ist, wenn Sie die Sicherheit, dass mit der Seite Pistole kommt benötigen. Fühlen Sie sich sicher in Home, überall in Home! (Seite Pistole ist zum Zwecke der Unterhaltung gedacht. Nicht entfernbar von Holster.)[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">E 'tarda notte. Si prende una strada sbagliata e visitare uno spazio non sei mai stato prima. A volte PlayStation®Home può essere spaventoso. Questo è quando si ha bisogno la sicurezza che deriva dal braccio laterale​​. Sentirsi al sicuro in casa, ovunque in casa! (Braccio laterale ​​è destinato a scopi di intrattenimento. Non rimovibile da fondina.)[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Es tarde en la noche. Usted toma un giro equivocado y visitar un espacio que nunca has estado antes. A veces, PlayStation®Home se puede dar miedo. Eso es cuando usted necesita la seguridad que viene con el brazo lateral Cyber. Se sienten seguros en casa, en cualquier lugar de casa! (Brazo Cibernético lado es para propósitos de entretenimiento solamente. No desmontable de la funda).[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">It's late at night.  You take a wrong turn and visit a space you've never been in before. Sometimes PlayStation®Home can be scary.  That's when you need the security that comes with the Cyber Side Arm.  Feel safe in Home, anywhere in Home! (Cyber Side Arm is meant for entertainment purposes only. Not removable from holster.)[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>