<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Avalon House Alliance Furniture Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avalon alliance maison meubles paquet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Avalon Allianz Wohnmöbel Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Avalon alleanza pacchetto arredo casa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Avalon en casa paquete de muebles de la alianza</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アバロン提携家庭用家具のパッケージ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">아발론 제휴 홈 가구 패키지</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Avalon House Alliance Furniture Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">阿瓦隆联盟家家具包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">阿瓦隆联盟家家具包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Avalon House Alliance Furniture Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Can't pick which house to align yourself, or maybe you just love variety? Then get this ultimate furniture pack with all the styles from the four houses: Dumont, Raleigh, Thaon, and Grimoult. This bundle includes 56 furniture items![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Impossible de choisir lequel la maison à vous aligner, ou peut-être que vous venez de aiment la variété? Ensuite, récupérez ce pack de meubles ultime avec tous les styles des quatre maisons: Dumont, Raleigh, Thaon, et Grimoult. Cet ensemble comprend 56 éléments de mobilier![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kann nicht entscheiden, welche nach Hause, um sich anzupassen, oder vielleicht haben Sie genau wie Abwechslung? Dann bekommen diese ultimative Packung mit all den Möbeln Stile der vier Häuser: Dumont, Raleigh, Thaon und Grimoult. Dieses Set enthält 56 Möbelstücke![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non è possibile scegliere quale sede per allineare voi stessi, o forse si, proprio come varietà? Allora ottenere questo pacchetto finale con tutti gli stili di arredamento delle quattro case: Dumont, Raleigh, Thaon e Grimoult. Questo set comprende 56 pezzi di mobili![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No se puede elegir la casa de alinearse, o tal vez sólo le gusta la variedad? A continuación, obtener este paquete final con todos los estilos de los muebles de las cuatro casas: Dumont, Raleigh, Thaon y Grimoult. Este set incluye 56 piezas de mobiliario![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">自分自身を揃えるためにどの家選ぶ、または多分あなただけのさまざまなを愛していないことができますか？デュモン、ローリー、Thaon、とGrimoult：次に4つの家からすべてのスタイルでこの究極の家具のパックを入手。このバンドルは、56の家具の項目が含まれています！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">자신을 정렬하기 위해 어떤 집을 선택, 아니면 그냥 다양한 사랑하지 않을 수 있지? 뒤몽, 롤리, Thaon 및 Grimoult : 그럼 네 개의 주택에서 모든 스타일을 제공하는이 궁극적인 가구 팩을 얻을. 이 번들 56 가구 항목이 포함되어 있습니다![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Can't pick which house to align yourself, or maybe you just love variety? Then get this ultimate furniture pack with all the styles from the four houses: Dumont, Raleigh, Thaon, and Grimoult. This bundle includes 56 furniture items![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">不能挑房子对准自己，也许你只是爱品种？然后得到这个最终的家具包与所有的风格，从四个房子：杜蒙，罗利，Thaon，Grimoult。这个软件包包括56家具物品！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">不能挑房子对准自己，也许你只是爱品种？然后得到这个最终的家具包与所有的风格，从四个房子：杜蒙，罗利，Thaon，Grimoult。这个软件包包括56家具物品！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Can't pick which house to align yourself, or maybe you just love variety? Then get this ultimate furniture pack with all the styles from the four houses: Dumont, Raleigh, Thaon, and Grimoult. This bundle includes 56 furniture items![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>