<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Hands_ring_03</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Moonstone Ring (Right Middle Finger, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bague de Pierre de Lune (Majeur droit, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mondsteinring (rechter Mittelfinger, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Anello di selenite (dito medio destro, da uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Anillo de feldespato (dedo corazón, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ムーンストーンの指輪（右手中指・男性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">문스톤 반지(오른손 중지, 남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Moonstone ring (Right hand, middle finger/Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">月光石戒指（右手中指/男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">月光石戒指（右手中指/男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Moonstone Ring (Right Middle Finger, M)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Hands_ring_03_desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A ring embedded with a shimmering, pale-blue moonstone on the middle finger of the right hand. (Mohs hardness of 6)[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une bague incrustée avec une pierre de lune bleu pâle chatoyante portée au majeur de la main droite. (6 sur l'échelle de dureté de Mohs)[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Ring mit einem eingebetteten, hellblau schimmernden Mondstein, der am Mittelfinger der rechten Hand getragen wird. (Mohs Stärke 7)[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Anello con incastonato una selenite che emana una fievole luce, di color azzurro pallido, da infilarsi nel dito medio della mano destra. (durezza scala di Mohs: 6)[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un anillo con una brillante piedra de feldespato azul claro incrustada que se coloca en el dedo corazón de la mano derecha. (Dureza en escala de Mohs, 6).[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">右手の中指に輝く、独特の青白い光沢をしたムーンストーンの指輪。（モース硬度６）[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">오른손의 중지에서 아름답게 빛나는 문스톤 반지. 독특하고 창백한 광택을 가졌다.(모스 경도 6)[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A moonstone ring with a distinctive bluish-white lustre glittering on the middle finger of the right hand. (Mohs hardness = 6)[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">戴在右手中指，散發獨特的青白光澤的月光石戒指。（莫氏硬度6）[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">戴在右手中指，散發獨特的青白光澤的月光石戒指。（莫氏硬度6）[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A ring embedded with a shimmering, pale-blue moonstone on the middle finger of the right hand. (Mohs hardness of 6)[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>