<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Pajama Set (Red Checked, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set pyjama (rouge à carreaux, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Pyjama-Set (rotkariert, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set pigiama (a scacchi rossi, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de pijama (rojo a cuadros, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">パジャマセット（赤チェック・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Pajama Set (Red Checked, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 7-piece set including pajamas (top, short-length top, pants), nightcaps (regular, slightly large), slippers, and pillow.\nDefensive Strength: (None)~★\nSleepiness: ★★~★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Nightcap (Red Checked, Women) (Head Accessory)\n- Nightcap, Slightly Large (Red Checked, Women) (Head Accessory)\n- Pajama Top (Red Checked, Women) (Tops)\n- Pajama Top, Short (Red Checked, Women) (Tops)\n- Pajama Pants (Red Checked, Women) (Bottoms)\n- Pillow in Hand (Red Checked, Women) (Hand)\n- Slippers (Red Checked, Women) (Shoes)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de 7 pièces incluant des pyjamas (haut, haut court, pantalon), des bonnets de nuit (normal, un peu grand), des pantoufles et un oreiller.\nDéfense : (Sans)~★\nSommeil : ★★~★★★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Bonnet de nuit (rouge à carreaux, femme) (Accessoire de tête)\n- Bonnet de nuit, un peu grand (rouge à carreaux, femme) (Accessoire de tête)\n- Haut de pyjama (rouge à carreaux, femme) (Haut)\n- Haut de pyjama, court (rouge à carreaux, femme) (Haut)\n- Pantalon de pyjama (rouge à carreaux, femme) (Bas)\n- Oreiller en main (rouge à carreaux, femme) (Main)\n- Pantoufles (rouge à carreaux, femme) (Chaussures)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 7-teiliges Set, das einen Pyjama (Oberteil, kurzes Oberteil, Hose), Schlafmützen (normal und mittelgroß), Hausschuhe und ein Kissen enthält.\nVerteidigung: (Keine)~★\nSchläfrigkeit: ★★~★★★\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Schlafmütze (rotkariert, für Frauen) (Kopfbedeckung)\n- Schlafmütze, mittelgroß (rotkariert, für Frauen) (Kopfbedeckung)\n- Pyjama-Oberteil (rotkariert, für Frauen) (Oberteile)\n- Pyjama-Oberteil, kurz (rotkariert, für Frauen) (Oberteile)\n- Pyjamahose (rotkariert, für Frauen) (Beinkleider)\n- Kissen in der Hand (rotkariert, für Frauen) (Hand)\n- Hausschuhe (rotkariert, für Frauen) (Schuhe)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set composto da 7 elementi comprendente un pigiama (giacca, giacca corta, pantaloni), berretto da notte (normale, leggermente largo), pantofole e cuscino.\nDifesa:  (nulla)~★\nLivello sonnolenza: ★★~★★★\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Berretto da notte (a scacchi rossi, da donna) (accessorio per la testa)\n- Berretto da notte leggermente largo (a scacchi rossi, da donna) (accessorio per la testa)\n- Giacca pigiama (a scacchi rossi, da donna) (parti superiori)\n- Giacca pigiama corta (a scacchi rossi, da donna) (parti superiori)\n- Pantaloni pigiama (a scacchi rossi, da donna) (parti inferiori)\n- Cuscino in mano (a scacchi rossi, da donna) (mani)\n- Pantofole (a scacchi rossi, da donna) (scarpe)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de siete artículos que incluye pijamas (parte superior, parte superior corta y pantalón), gorro de dormir (normal y ligeramente mayor), zapatillas de andar por casa y almohada.\nDefensa: (ninguna)~★\nLetargo: ★★~★★★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Gorro de dormir (rojo a cuadros, mujer) (accesorio de cabeza)\n- Gorro de dormir, ligeramente mayor (rojo a cuadros, mujer)(Accesorio de cabeza)\n- Parte superior de pijama (roja a cuadros, mujer) (torso)\n- Parte superior corta de pijama (roja a cuadros, mujer) (torso)\n- Pantalón de pijama (rojo a cuadros, mujer) (piernas)\n- Almohada en mano (roja a cuadros, mujer) (mano)\n- Zapatillas de andar por casa (rojas a cuadros, mujer) (zapatos)\n\n* Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">パジャマ（上着・丈が短めの上着・ズボン）、ナイトキャップ（普通・大きめ）、スリッパ、枕を含む、計７点セット。\n防御力：　（なし）～★\n安眠度：　★★～★★★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・ナイトキャップ（赤チェック・女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n・ナイトキャップ・大きめサイズ（赤チェック・女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n・パジャマの上着（赤チェック・女性）/トップス\n・パジャマの上着・短（赤チェック・女性）/トップス\n・パジャマのズボン（赤チェック・女性）/ボトムス\n・手に持った枕（赤チェック・女性）/手\n・スリッパ（赤チェック・女性）/靴\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 7-piece set including pajamas (top, short-length top, pants), nightcaps (regular, slightly large), slippers, and pillow.\nDefensive Strength: (None)~★\nSleepiness: ★★~★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Nightcap (Red Checked, Women) (Head Accessory)\n- Nightcap, Slightly Large (Red Checked, Women) (Head Accessory)\n- Pajama Top (Red Checked, Women) (Tops)\n- Pajama Top, Short (Red Checked, Women) (Tops)\n- Pajama Pants (Red Checked, Women) (Bottoms)\n- Pillow in Hand (Red Checked, Women) (Hand)\n- Slippers (Red Checked, Women) (Shoes)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
