<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Lidicea's Gauntlets (Legendary Armour)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Gantelets de Lidicea (armure légendaire)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lidiceas Handschuhe (Legendäre Rüstung)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guanti d'armatura di Lidicea (Armatura leggendaria)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guanteletes de Lidicea (Armadura legendaria)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Lidicea's Gauntlets (Legendary Armor)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Legendary Armour of Lidicea, the Queen of Mercia who abdicated her throne to unite the lands, uniting the people against the shadows and forming the Guardians of Mercia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'armure légendaire de Lidicea, la reine de Mercia qui abdiqua afin de pouvoir unifier les territoires et les peuples face aux forces de l'ombres, en formant les gardiens de Mercia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die legendäre Rüstung von Lidicea, Königin von Mercia, die ihrem Thron entsagte, um die Länder und ihre Völker zu vereinen und die Wächter Mercias zu begründen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La leggendaria armatura di Lidicea, la regina di Mercia che abdicò per unire le terre e i popoli contro le ombre e diede vita ai guardiani di Mercia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La legendaria armadura de Lidicea, la Reina de Mercia que abdicó al trono para unir a las tierras, uniendo a los pueblos contra las sombras y creando los guardianes de Mercia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Legendary Armor of Lidicea, the Queen of Mercia who abdicated her throne to unite the lands, uniting the people against the shadows and forming the Guardians of Mercia. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>