<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Turning It Around Jacket - Black (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Blouson Turning It Around - Noir (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Turning It Around Jacke - Schwarz (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Giacca Turning It Around - Nero (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Turning It Around Chaqueta - Negro (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Model Alexandra Spencer is adored for her effortless sense of cool. What's more, her blog, 4th and Bleeker, is quickly becoming one of the most influential fashion reads around. Billabong has recently partnered with Alexandra on a capsule collection that reflects her jet-set lifestyle. This silky zip-up bomber jacket is a prime example of her pretty tough ways as it boldly goes to the edge with intricate embroidery across the entire back. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La mannequin Alexandra Spencer est adulée pour son sens inné de la décontraction. De plus, son blog, 4th and Bleeker, s'est rapidement imposé comme l'un des rendez-vous incontournables de la mode. Billabong s'est récemment associée à Alexandra pour créer une collection capsule reflétant son style de vie jet-set. Ce blouson aviateur zippé soyeux est un parfait exemple de ses manières un peu rudes, car il franchit allègrement les frontières avec ses broderies magnifiques recouvrant entièrement le dos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fotomodell Alexandra Spencer wird oft um ihren mühelos coolen Look beneidet. Ihr Blog "4th and Bleeker" ist außerdem auf dem besten Wege dazu, eines der einflussreichsten Modeblog des Internets zu werden. Billabong und Alexandra haben sich kürzlich zusammengetan und eine Sonderkollektion entworfen, die Alexandras Jetset-Lifestyle widerspiegelt. Diese samtseidige Bomberjacke mit Reißverschluss ist ein perfektes Beispiel dafür: robust und vielseitig, aber dennoch seidenweich und mit feinem Stickwerk auf der Rückseite. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La modella Alexandra Spencer piace molto per il suo stile semplice e rilassato. Il suo blog, 4th and Bleeker, sta rapidamente diventando uno dei punti di riferimento più seguiti per chi vuole aggiornarsi sulla moda. Billabong ha recentemente siglato un rapporto di collaborazione con Alexandra per una collezione di capi essenziali che riflettono il suo stile di vita esclusivo. Questo giubbino bomber in seta con cerniera è un ottimo esempio del modo di fare deciso di Alexandra, con il dettaglio audace del fitto ricamo che ricopre l'intera parte posteriore. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La modelo Alexandra Spencer es adorada por su innato sentido de la moda. Además, su blog, 4th and Bleeker, se está convirtiendo con rapidez en uno de los referentes más influyentes dentro de la moda. Precisamente, Billabong ha colaborado recientemente con Alexandra en una colección cápsula que refleja su estilo de vida jet-set. Esta chaqueta "bomber" con cremallera y tacto de seda es todo un ejemplo de su toque duro y su valentía, buscando los límites con un intricado bordado que cubre toda la espalda. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>