<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Pirta the Penguin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pirta le pingouin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Pirta der Pinguin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pirta il pinguino</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pirta, el pingüino</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ペンギンのぷー太君</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">펭귄 - 퍼타</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Pirta the Penguin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">波達企鵝</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">波達企鵝</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Pirta the Penguin</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Penguins are very social animals and spend most of their time in large family groups. Pirta will treat you like a member of the family, following you wherever you go. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les pingouins sont des animaux très sociables et passent la plupart de leur temps en groupes de familles. Pirta vous traitera comme un membre de sa famille et vous suivra partout. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Pinguine sind sehr gesellige Tiere, die die meiste Zeit ihres Lebens in großen Familien und Gruppen verbringen. Pirta wird dich wir ein Familienmitglied behandeln und dir überall hin folgen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I pinguini sono animali molto socievoli e passano la maggior parte del tempo in grandi gruppi familiari. Pirta ti tratterà come un membro della famiglia e ti seguirà ovunque. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los pingüinos son animales muy sociales que pasan la mayor parte del tiempo en grupos de familias. Pirta te tratará como si fueses de la familia, siguiéndote allá donde vayas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">とても懐っこいペンギンちゃんは、大所帯で過ごす時間がほとんどです。そんなぷー太君はあなたの後を追いかけるのが大好きです。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">펭귄은 아주 사회적인 동물이어서 다수의 가족 그룹들과 어울려 대부분의 시간을 보냅니다. 퍼타는 여러분을 가족의 일원으로 여기고 여러분이 어디를 가든 따라 갈 겁니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Penguins are very social animals and spend most of their time in large family groups. Pirta will treat you like a member of the family, following you wherever you go. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">企鵝是群居動物，多數時間都和一大群同類聚在一起。波達會把您當成家人，跟著到處跑。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">企鵝是群居動物，多數時間都和一大群同類聚在一起。波達會把您當成家人，跟著到處跑。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Penguins are very social animals and spend most of their time in large family groups. Pirta will treat you like a member of the family, following you wherever you go. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>