<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">BuiBui Robot Hat (women's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chapeau robot BuiBui (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">BuiBui-Roboter-Hut (Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cappello Robot BuiBui da donna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sombrero de Robot BuiBui (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブイブイロボ帽子（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">부이부이 로봇 모자(여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">BuiBui Robot Hat (women's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">布伊布伊機器人帽（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">布伊布伊機器人帽（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">BuiBui Robot Hat (women's)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Are you standing where you are through your own will, or that of the BuiBui?\n
This odd hat will have you wondering if your life is being mischievously manipulated by a BuiBui.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Es-tu à cet endroit par ta propre volonté, ou par celle des BuiBui ?\n
Ce chapeau bizarre te fera te demander si ta vie est manipulée par un BuiBui espiègle.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stehst du, wo du stehst, durch deinen Willen oder den des BuiBui?
Dieser seltsame Hut lässt dich zweifeln, ob dein Leben nicht mutwillig von einem BuiBui manipuliert wird.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ti trovi dove sei per tua volontà o per quella dei BuiBui?\n
Indossando questo strano cappello, ti chiederai se la tua vita è pilotata inconsciamente da un BuiBui.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Estás donde estás por voluntad propia o porque así lo quieren los BuiBui?\n
Este extraño sombrero hará que te preguntes si un malvado BuiBui está manipulando tu vida.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">今ここに立っているのは自分の意思なのか、ブイブイの意思なのか・・・\n
頭上で操縦桿を握るブイブイに、操られている気がする不思議な帽子。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">지금 여기에 서있는 것은 자신의 의지인가, 부이부이의 의지인가…\n
머리 위에서 조종간을 잡고 있는 부이부이에게, 조종 당하고 있는 느낌이 드는 신기한 모자.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Are you standing where you are through your own will, or that of the BuiBui?\n
This odd hat will have you wondering if your life is being mischievously manipulated by a BuiBui.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">現在站在這裡是自己的意願，還是布伊布伊的意願呢・・・\n
是頂可以感覺到被握著操作桿的布伊布伊操縱的神奇帽子。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">現在站在這裡是自己的意願，還是布伊布伊的意願呢・・・\n
是頂可以感覺到被握著操作桿的布伊布伊操縱的神奇帽子。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Am I standing here because I want to, or is it BuiBui's will?\n
BuiBui sits atop with controls in hand. Where will BuiBui take you next?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>