<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Crossfire PX Jacket - Black (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Veste Crossfire PX - Noir (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Crossfire PX Jacke - Schwarz (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Crossfire PX Giacca - Nero (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Chaqueta Crossfire PX - Negro (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">We took the same fabrication and advanced technology of our high performance boardshorts and created this revolutionary windbreaker. So no matter if you're battling wind, rain or sleet, your protection is complete. Detailed with a hood, a zip front, zip welt pockets, and a heat transfer logo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nous nous sommes inspiré du design et de la technologie de nos shorts de bain hautes performances pour créer ce coupe-vent révolutionnaire. Que vous affrontiez la pluie, le vent ou la grêle, vous serez toujours ainsi parfaitement protégé. Avec capuche, fermeture éclair à l'avant, poches passepoilées avec fermeture éclair et logo imprimé. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese revolutionäre Windjacke baut auf dem ausgefeilten Fertigungsprinzip unserer vielseitigen und robusten Boardshorts auf. Ob Regen, Schnee oder Wind - diese Jacke gewährt Schutz vor allen Unwettern. Mit Kapuze, Reißverschluss vorne, Leistentaschen mit Reißverschluss und Wärmeübertragungslogo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per creare questa rivoluzionaria giacca antivento, abbiamo utilizzato lo stesso metodo di produzione e la stessa tecnologia avanzata dei nostri shorts da mare ad alte prestazioni. Non importa se ti trovi a combattere vento, pioggia o neve, la protezione è assicurata. Comprende cappuccio, zip frontale, tasche a filetto con zip e logo traspirante. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hemos cogido la misma fabricación y la tecnología avanzada de nuestras bermudas surferas de gran resistencia y hemos creado una cazadora revolucionaria. De forma que si tienes que lidiar contra el viento, la lluvia o el granizo, estarás completamente protegido. Detalle de capucha, cremallera frontal, bolsillos de solapa con cremallera y logotipo por transferencia térmica. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>