<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ruby Suit Bundle (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack costume rubis (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rubinanzug: Paket (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto tenuta rubino (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de traje rubí (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">루비 수트 세트 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ruby Suit Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">紅寶石服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">紅寶石服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ruby Suit Bundle (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A passionate display of red and sequin fusion, this outfit has a casual appeal but with a classy finish. Bundle includes a jacket, cane, trousers, and shoes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'alliance du rouge, couleur de la passion, et des sequins rend cette tenue à la fois décontractée et sophistiquée. Le pack comprend une veste, une canne, un pantalon et des chaussures. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine heiße Kombination aus Rot und Pailletten. Dieses Outfit ist gleichzeitig alltagstauglich und mondän. Das Paket umfasst Jacke, Stock, Hose und Schuhe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa tenuta di un rosso acceso con lustrini presenta un look informale, ma con un tocco di classe. Il pacchetto include giacca, bastone, pantaloni e scarpe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con una apasionada fusión entre el rojo y las lentejuelas, este conjunto tiene un toque informal, pero con un acabado elegante. El conjunto incluye chaqueta, pantalones, zapatos y bastón. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">붉은색과 금속 재질의 열정적인 조합입니다. 자칫 캐주얼해 보일수 있는 의상에 품격을 더해 줍니다. 이 세트는 재킷, 지팡이, 바지, 그리고 구두를 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A passionate display of red and sequin fusion, this outfit has a casual appeal but with a classy finish. Bundle includes a jacket, cane, pants, and shoes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">紅色的珠片熱情澎拜。這件套裝有便服的風格，但不失大體。服裝組包括一件外套、權杖、褲子和鞋子。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">紅色的珠片熱情澎拜。這件套裝有便服的風格，但不失大體。服裝組包括一件外套、權杖、褲子和鞋子。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A passionate display of red and sequin fusion, this outfit has a casual appeal but with a classy finish. Bundle includes a jacket, cane, pants, and shoes. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>