<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Slouch Vest and Bandeau Top - Sunset</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Haut en Bandeau et Gilet ample - Crépuscule</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Slouch-Hemd mit trägerlosem Top - Sonnenuntergang</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Canottiera larga e top a fascia - Tramonto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta ancha con top de banda; Atardecer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">だるだるベスト＆トップス – サンセット（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">앞이 늘어진 조끼와 폭이 좁은 짧은 상의 - 석양 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Slouch Vest and Bandeau Top - Sunset (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">寬鬆背心和細肩帶上衣：夕陽 (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">寬鬆背心和細肩帶上衣：夕陽 (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Slouch Vest and Bandeau Top - Sunset</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Layering needn't be just a Winter thing. Keep cool and covered by throwing a loose vest over a tight bandeau top. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le multicouches ne doit pas être réservé à l'hiver. Restez au frais tout en étant couvert en mettant une veste ample par-dessus un haut en bandeau. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nicht nur im Winter sind mehrere Lagen angesagt. Schütze cool deine Haut, indem du über dem trägerlosen Top ein lockeres Slouch-Hemd trägst. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vestirsi a strati non è solo una prerogativa invernale. Alla moda, ma senza mostrare tutto grazie a questa canotta larga poggiata su un top a fascia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las capas no son solo cosa del invierno. Mantente fresco y tapado con una camiseta ancha encima de un top de banda ajustado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">重ね着は何も冬だけのものではありません。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이것 저것 걸치는 걸 겨울에만 하는 것은 아니랍니다. 달라 붙고 폭이 좁은 짧은 상의에 헐렁하게 걸치는 조끼 스타일로 시원함을 유지해 보세요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Layering needn't be just a Winter thing. Keep cool and covered by throwing a loose vest over a tight bandeau top. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">誰說多層次搭配只適合冬天的？裡面穿細肩帶上衣、外面披上一件寬鬆背心，讓您清涼又遮陽。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">誰說多層次搭配只適合冬天的？裡面穿細肩帶上衣、外面披上一件寬鬆背心，讓您清涼又遮陽。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Layering needn't be just a Winter thing. Keep cool and covered by throwing a loose vest over a tight bandeau top. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>