<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mootohn Headwear (women's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bonnet Mootohn (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mootohn-Kopfbedeckung (Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Copricapo (Mootohn) da donna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Gorro de Mootohn (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ムートンかぶりもの（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">무통 캐릭터 모자（여성）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Mootohn Headwear (women's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">慕桐角色頭套（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">慕桐角色頭套（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mootohn Headwear (women's)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Having a hard time joining the ranks of the awake?\n
Stay half-asleep with this snug-fitting Moothon Headwear\n
\n
Purchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space.\n
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tu as du mal à garder les yeux ouverts ?\n
Reste à moitié-endormi avec ce bonnet enveloppant Mootohn.\n
\n
Acheter cet objet ajoute 1 LocoRoco à ton espace personnel de l'île Loco.
Tu peux ajouter jusqu'à 20 LocoRoco à l'île Loco. Une fois le maximum atteint, tu ne peux plus ajouter d'unités.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hast du Probleme, wach zu werden?\n
Bleibe im Halbschlaf mit dieser eng sitzenden Moothon-Kopfbedeckung.\n
\n
Dieser Gegenstand fügt deinem Loco-Insel-Apartment 1 LocoRoco hinzu.
Du kannst bis zu 20 LocoRoco hinzufügen. Ist das Maximum erreicht, können keine weiteren Einheiten hinzugefügt werden.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai problemi a restare sveglio?\n
Dormi per metà con questo comodissimo copricapo raffigurante Moothon.\n
\n
Acquistando questo oggetto, aggiungerai un LocoRoco al tuo spazio personale su Loco Island.
Puoi aggiungere fino a 20 LocoRoco su Loco Island. Una volta raggiunto il numero massimo, non potrai aggiungerne altri.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Te cuesta unirte a las filas de los despiertos?\n
Quédate medio dormido con este gorro ajustado de Moothon.\n
\n
Comprar este objeto añade 1 LocoRoco a tu espacio personal en la Loco Isla.
Puedes añadir un máximo de 20 LocoRoco a la Loco Isla. Cuando hayas alcanzado este número, no podrás añadir más unidades.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">頭からスッポリかぶれるムートンのかぶりもの。\n
寝ぼすけなあなたにピッタリです！\n
\n
このアイテムを購入するとパーソナルスペース”ロコアイランド”に”ロコロコ”が１匹追加されます。
”ロコアイランド”には最大20匹まで”ロコロコ”を追加できます。最大数に達した場合は、それ以上の追加はされません。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">머리 전체를 장식할 수 있는 무통 모양의 모자\n
아직도 잠이 덜 깬 당신에게 안성맞춤이겠네요!\n
\n
이 아이템을 구입하면 퍼스널 스페이스 '로코 아일랜드'에 '로코로코'가 1마리 추가됩니다. '로코 아일랜드'에는 최대 20마리까지 '로코로코'를 추가할 수 있습니다.  최대치에 다다르면 더 이상은 추가할 수 없습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Having a hard time joining the ranks of the awake?\n
Stay half-asleep with this snug-fitting Moothon Headwear\n
\n
Purchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space.\n
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">可套住整個頭部的慕桐角色頭套。\n
最適合貪睡的你！\n
\n
購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">可套住整個頭部的慕桐角色頭套。\n
最適合貪睡的你！\n
\n
購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Having a hard time joining the ranks of the awake?\n
Stay half-asleep with this snug-fitting Moothon Headwear\n
\n
Purchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your LocoIsland personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to LocoIsland. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>