<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Green Ticket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le ticket vert</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das grüne Ticket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il biglietto verde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Boleto Verde.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">グリーンチケット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">그린 티켓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Green Ticket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">綠色票券</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">綠色票券</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Green Ticket</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is good for 50 plays in The Midway.  Play games, win fabulous prizes, impress your friends and enemies! This item can be purchased multiple times, so come back again when you run out! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un bon pour 50 parties dans The Midway. Jouez à des jeux, gagnez des prix fabuleux, impressionnez vos amis et vos ennemis ! Cet article peut être acheté plusieurs fois, donc revenez quand vous êtes à court ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gültig für 50 Spiele in "The Midway". Spielen Sie Spiele, gewinnen Sie fantastische Preise, beeindrucken Sie Ihre Freunde und Feinde! Dieser Artikel kann mehrmals gekauft werden, kommen Sie also zurück, wenn er aufgebraucht ist! [#Legal]. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">È valido per 50 partite nel Midway. Gioca, vinci premi favolosi e stupisci amici e nemici! Quest'articolo può essere acquistato più volte, quindi ritorna se ne vuoi altri! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Válido para jugar 50 partidas en The Midway. ¡Juega, gana fabulosos premios e impresiona a tus amigos y enemigos! Este objeto puede ser comprado varias veces, así que vuelve de nuevo cuando se te acabe! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アメリカン・カーニバルラウンジ内のすべてのミニゲームを50回プレイできるチケットです。\n\n各ミニゲームをクリアすると、ステキなホームリワードをゲットできます！\n残りのプレイ数がなくなったら、何度でも購入することができます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">The Midway에서 50회 게임을 할 수 있습니다. 게임을 해서 멋진 상품도 타고 친구들과 적에게 깊은 인상을 남겨 보세요! 이 아이템은 여러 번 구입할 수 있으니 떨어지면 언제라도 돌아오세요! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This is good for 50 plays in The Midway.  Play games, win fabulous prizes, impress your friends and enemies! This item can be purchased multiple times, so come back again when you run out! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">可在Midway遊戲大廳中玩50場遊戲。 玩遊戲，贏大獎，讓您的朋友和對手刮目相看！ 此物品可重複購買，用完的時候記得要回來重新購買喔！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">可在Midway遊戲大廳中玩50場遊戲。 玩遊戲，贏大獎，讓您的朋友和對手刮目相看！ 此物品可重複購買，用完的時候記得要回來重新購買喔！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This is good for 50 plays in The Midway.  Play games, win fabulous prizes, impress your friends and enemies! This item can be purchased multiple times, so come back again when you run out! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>