<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">NOOB AWAY!™ Defense Aerosol</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">NOOB AWAY!™ Aérosol de Défense</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">NOOB AWAY!™ Schutzaerosol</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">NOOB AWAY!™ Aerosol di Difesa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aerosol De Defensa NOOB AWAY!™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">NOOB AWAY!™ Defense Aerosol</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">NOOB AWAY!™ Defense Aerosol (LMO)
 
This powerful propellant allows you to deliver a temporary mist that kindly sends a pestering noob a signal that you’d rather be left alone. USE ONLY AS DIRECTED.
 
•	Unscented
•	Indoor and outdoor use
•	Jet action spray
•	CFC-free
•	Non-staining
•	Safe for use around companion pets and animals
 
DIRECTIONS FOR USE: Hold NOOB AWAY!™ firmly in your hand. Point spray nozzle at target and hold for several seconds avoiding face and eyes. Depress nozzle and wait for results (avoid laughing), repeat as necessary. FOR IN-GAME USE ONLY!

*LMO (Locomotion) is a portable item.
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">NOOB AWAY!™ Aérosol de Défense (LMO)
 
Cette puissante bombe aérosol  permet de diffuser une brume temporaire  qui envoie un message clair à un  noob harcelant qui comprendra que vous voulez rester seuls et qu’il ne s’approche plus de vous. UTILISEZ SEULEMENT VERS LA PERSONNE DESIREE.

•	Inodore
•	Utilisation à l’Intérieur et l’Extérieur
•	Jet de pulvérisation d'action
•	Sans CFC
•	Ne tâche pas
•	Sans danger pour les animaux de compagnies et domestiques

MODE D’EMPLOI: Tenir fermement  le NOOB AWAY!™ dans votre main. Pointer la buse l’aérosol vers votre cible et appuyer dessus pendant quelques secondes en évitant le visage et les yeux. Relâcher la buse et attendre le résultat (éviter de rire) ; répéter l’opération si nécessaire.  A UTILISER UNIQUEMENT POUR CE JEU!

*LMO (Locomotion) est un élément transportable.
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">NOOB AWAY!™ Schutzaerosol (LMO)
 
Dieses kraftvolle Treibmittel ermöglicht Ihnen einen temporären Dunst zu bespitzen. Damit können Sie netterweise einem belästigenden Noob Kenntnis geben, daß Sie lieber allein bleiben wollen. NUR WEISUNGSGEMÄß ZU VERWENDEN.
 
•	Parfümfrei
•	Zum äußeren und inneren Gebrauch
•	Jet-Spray Aktion
•	CFC-frei
•	Verfärbungsfrei
•	Sicher für die Gesundheit ihrer Haustiere und anderer Tiere
 
GEBRAUCHSANWEISUNG: NOOB AWAY!™ fest in der Hand halten. Die Sprühdüse auf das Ziel ausrichten und mehrere Sekunden lang drücken. Nicht direkt ins Gesicht und in die Augen sprühen. Sprühdüse loslassen und auf die Ergebnisse warten (versuchen nicht zu lachen), wiederholen falls nötig. NUR FÜR SPAß GEBRAUCHEN!

*LMO (Locomotion) ist ein tragberer Artikel.
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">NOOB AWAY!™ Aerosol di Difesa (LMO)
 
Questo propellente difensivo ti permette di spruzzare una nebbiolina temporanea che manderà gentilmente ad un fastidioso noob un chiaro segnale che preferite essere lasciato in pace. UTILIZZARE ESCLUSIVAMENTE SECONDO LE INDICAZIONI.
 
•	Inodore
•	Per uso esterno ed interno
•	Azione getto
•	Privo di CFC
•	Non macchia
•	Non nuoce ai vostri compagni domestici e agli altri animali
 
ISTRUZIONI PER L'USO: Tenere NOOB AWAY!™ saldamente in mano. Puntare l'erogatore verso l'obbiettivo e premere per alcuni secondi evitando la faccia e gli occhio. Rilasciare l'erogatore ed aspettare I risultati (evitare di ridere), ripetere se necessario. USO PER SOLI FINI LUDICI!

*LMO (Locomotion) è un articolo portatile.
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aerosol De Defensa NOOB AWAY!™ (LMO)
 
Este potente propelente le permite suministrar una rociada temporal que envía amablemente a un noob insidioso una clara señal de desea que le dejen en paz. UTILICE SOLAMENTE SEGÚN LO INDICADO.
 
•	Sin perfume
•	Para uso en interiores y al aire libre
•	jet acción aerosol
•	Libre de CFC	
•	No mancha
•	Seguro para uso cerca de animales de compañía y mascotas
 
INSTRUCCIONES DE USO: Mantenga NOOB AWAY!™ firmemente en su mano. Apunte la boquilla del spray hacia su objetivo y manténgala durante varios segundos, evitando la cara y los ojos. Presione la boquilla y espere a los resultados (evitando reírse), repita según sea necesario. ¡SOLO PARA USO EN JUEGOS!

*LMO (Locomotion) es un artículo portátil.
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">NOOB AWAY!™ Defense Aerosol (LMO)
 
This powerful propellant allows you to deliver a temporary mist that kindly sends a pestering noob a signal that you’d rather be left alone. USE ONLY AS DIRECTED.
 
•	Unscented
•	Indoor and outdoor use
•	Jet action spray
•	CFC-free
•	Non-staining
•	Safe for use around companion pets and animals
 
DIRECTIONS FOR USE: Hold NOOB AWAY!™ firmly in your hand. Point spray nozzle at target and hold for several seconds avoiding face and eyes. Depress nozzle and wait for results (avoid laughing), repeat as necessary. FOR IN-GAME USE ONLY!

*LMO (Locomotion) is a portable item.
[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>