<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rockabilly Pink Top</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Haut Rose Rockabilly</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rockabilly Rosa Spitzenc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Top Rosa Rockabilly</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Top Rosa Rockabilly</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Rockabilly line is inspired by the 1950s and is characterised by its vintage, casual and striking style.  The leather, jeans and prints are the stars of this collection. It will be impossible not to triumph on the dance floor! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La ligne Rockabilly est inspirée par les année 1950 et est caractérisée par son style vintage, décontracté et frappant. Les cuirs, jeans et imprimés sont les produits phares de cette collection. Il serait impossible de ne pas triompher sur le dance floor ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Rockabilly-Reihe ist von den 1950s Jahren inspiriert und zeichnet sich durch den trendigen, lockeren und ausgefallenen Stil aus. Leder, Jeans und Aufdrucke sind die Stars dieser Kollektion. So ist es wirklich unmöglich auf der Tanzfläche nicht zu glänzen! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La linea Rockabilly si ispira agli anni Cinquanta ed è caratterizzata da uno stile vintage e casual. Pelli, jeans e stampe sono i prodotti di punta della collezione. Il trionfo sulla pista da ballo è assicurato! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La línea Rockabilly está inspirada en los años 50 y se caracteriza por su estilo vintage, informal y llamativo. El cuero, los tejanos y los estampados son los protagonistas de esta colección; Imposible no triunfar en las pistas de baile! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Rockabilly line is inspired by the 1950s and is characterized by its vintage, casual and striking style.  The leather, jeans and prints are the stars of this collection. It will be impossible not to triumph on the dance floor! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>