<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sodium2 Decibel Headphones (for Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Casque Audio Decibel Sodium2 (pour Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sodium2 Dezibel-Kopfhörer (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sodium2 Cuffie Decibel (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Protectores Decibelios de Sodium2 (para hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Sodium2 デシベルヘッドフォン（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium2  데시벨 헤드폰 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sodium2 Decibel Headphones (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sodium2防噪耳機（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sodium2防噪耳機（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sodium2 Decibel Headphones (for Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Standing next to a roaring Velocity Racer engine without protection for any length of time is not advised. We recommend these stylish noise-cancelling headphones for whenever you're out on the Launch Grid. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rester juste à côté d'un engin Velocity Racer vrombissant sans protection pour n'importe quelle durée n'est pas conseillé. Nous recommandons l'utilisation de ce casque audio réducteur de son de grande classe  pour chaque fois que vous serez sur la Grille [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es wird davon abgeraten, ohne Hörschutz neben einem tosenden Velocity-Gleiter zu stehen. Wir empfehlen, in der Nähe des Startbereichs diese modischen Kopfhörer mit Geräuschunterdrückung zu tragen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stare accanto al motore rombante di un veicolo Project Velocity senza protezione, non è mai consigliabile. Raccomandiamo queste eleganti cuffie insonorizzanti per quelle volte in cui ti trovi sulla griglia di lancio. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No se aconseja pasar mucho tiempo junto a un motor de Corredor de velocidad en funcionamiento sin protección durante mucho tiempo. Te recomendamos estos estilosos cascos antirruido para cuando estés en la Parrilla de salida. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">すざましい音をだすVelocityレーサーエンジンに耳栓なしで近づくことはタブーです。そんなときはこのスタイリッシュなノイズキャンセリング付きのヘッドフォンで対処します。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">굉음을 내뿜는 벨로시티 레이서 엔진 옆에 잠시라도 서 있는 것은 바람직하지 않습니다. 발사대 주변에서는 소음 제거 기능을 갖춘 헤드폰을 언제나 착용해야 합니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Standing next to a roaring Velocity Racer engine without protection for any length of time is not advised. We recommend these stylish noise-cancelling headphones for whenever you're on the Launch Grid. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">只要站在極速車神怒吼的引擎旁就該戴防護設備。我們建議只要人在發射區，最好都戴上這款造型時尚的防噪音耳機。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">只要站在極速車神怒吼的引擎旁就該戴防護設備。我們建議只要人在發射區，最好都戴上這款造型時尚的防噪音耳機。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Standing next to a roaring Velocity Racer engine without protection for any length of time is not advised. We recommend these stylish noise-cancelling headphones for whenever you're on the Launch Grid. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>