<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Upgrade Bug Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack D'Améliorations Pour Insectes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Käfer-Upgrade-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Potenziamenti Insetti</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack Bicho De Mejora</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This pack gives you 15 bug health upgrades, 15 bug speed upgrades, 10 bug ability upgrades and 1 leech power power-up, allowing you to create legions of upgraded creatures that Ginger's plants will surely be unable to resist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce pack vous donne accès à 15 améliorations de santé, 15 améliorations de vitesse et 10 améliorations de compétence pour insectes ainsi qu'un power-up d'extraction d'énergie, ce qui vous permet de créer des légions de créatures améliorées auxquelles les plantes de Ginger ne pourront pas résister. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Paket enthält 15 Käfer-Gesundheits-Upgrades, 15 Käfer-Geschwindigkeits-Upgrades, 10 Käfer-Fähigkeiten-Upgrades und ein "Energie entziehen"-Power-up. Damit können unzählige verbesserte Kreaturen erschaffen werden, denen Gingers Pflanzen nichts entgegenzusetzen haben. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo pack contiene 15 potenziamenti salute, 15 potenziamenti velocità, 10 potenziamenti abilità e 1 potenziamento risucchia-energia, per creare legioni di creature potenziate pronte a sgominare le piante di Ginger. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este pack incluye 15 mejoras de salud de bicho, 15 mejoras de velocidad de bicho, 10 mejoras de habilidad de bicho y 1 potenciador de absorber energía, con lo que podrás crear legiones de criaturas mejoradas a las que no se podrán resistir las plantas de Ginger. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>