<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A glorious addition to any personal apartment, this glorious toast-popping toaster actually pops toast!

The Toast-Popping Toaster is a portable item and can be removed from your apartment and placed anywhere in PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Indispensable à tout appartement, ce magnifique grille-pain contient vraiment du pain grillé ! Le Grille-pain avec toasts est un objet portable et peut être retiré de votre appartement pour être placé n'importe où dans PlayStation®Home ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine wunderbare Ergänzung für jedes persönliche Apartment ist dieser herrliche Toast-werfende Toaster, der tatsächlich Toast auswirft! Der Toast-werfende Toaster ist ein tragbares Objekt und kann aus dem persönlichen Apartment entfernt und überall in PlayStation®Home platziert werden! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un must per qualsiasi spazio personale: un tostapane che prepara i toast e li spara fuori quando sono pronti! Il tostapane tosta-e-spara è un oggetto portatile: può essere spostato dal tuo appartamento e posizionato ovunque in PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fantástica adición a cualquier apartamento personal. Este estupendo tostador hace saltar las tostadas de verdad. ¡El tostador es un objeto portátil que puedes quitar del apartamento y colocar en cualquier lugar de PlayStation®Home! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Toast-Popping Toaster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Grille-pain avec toasts</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Toast-werfender Toaster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tostapane tosta-e-spara</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tostador</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kOffText</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Turn Off</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Désactiver</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Deaktivieren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Spegni</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apagar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kOnText</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Turn On</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Activer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aktivieren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Accendi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Encender</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kProxText</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">In Proximity</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
