<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Ranch House</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La Maison du Ranch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ranch Haus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Casa Ranch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Rancho</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Ranch House</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to your very own ranch where the sun never sets. This huge plot of land comes with an open paddock, a peaceful pond, a spacious house for you to rest at after a long day at Red Rock Springs.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue dans votre ranch personnel où le soleil ne se couche jamais. Cette grande parcelle de terre est composée d'un enclos ouvert, d'un étang paisible et d'une maison spacieuse pour vous reposer après une longue journée à Red Rock Springs.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen auf deiner ganz eigenen Ranch, wo die Sonne nie untergeht. Dieses riesige Grundstück verfügt über eine offene Pferdekoppel, einen friedlichen Teich und ein geräumiges Haus in dem du nach einem langen Tag in Red Rock Springs ausruhen kannst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuto nel tuo ranch, dove il sole non tramonta mai. Questo enorme pezzo di terreno viene con un  recinto aperto, un piacevole laghetto e una casa spaziosa per te per farti riposare dopo una lunga giornata a Red Rock Springs.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido a tu rancho donde el sol nunca se pone.Este gigante cacho de tierra viene con un paddock abierto, un estanque tranquilo y una espaciosa casa para que Descanses después de un largo día en Red Rock Springs.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome to your very own ranch where the sun never sets. This huge plot of land comes with an open paddock, a peaceful pond, a spacious house for you to rest at after a long day at Red Rock Springs.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>