<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Anime Furniture Value Pack #1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack complet meubles "Anime" 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Anime-Möbel-Paket 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto arredamento anime 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack 1 de mobiliario Anime</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Anime Furniture Value Pack #1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">애니메이션 가구 할인팩 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Anime Furniture Value Pack #1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">動漫風家具超值組合包1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">動漫風家具超值組合包1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Anime Furniture Value Pack #1</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A matching outfit is so last decade. It's all about matching furniture! Includes 8 items: Aerodynamic Chair, Camera Robot, Data Stream Table, Futuristic Room Lamp, Futuristic Slide Out Couch, Futuristic Tendril Lamp, Projection TV, and Red Crate [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La tenue assortie, c'est has been. Le top dans le futur, ce sont les meubles assortis ! Comprend 8 éléments : un fauteuil aérodynamique, un robot appareil photo, une table d'informations, une lampe futuriste, un canapé convertible futuriste, une lampe à filaments futuriste, un écran de projection et une caisse rouge. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein perfekt abgestimmtes Outfit ist so was von out. Jetzt stimmt man Möbel perfekt ab! Enthält 8 Teile: aerodynamischen Sessel, Kameraroboter, Datenstromtisch, futuristische Raumlampe, futuristische Ausziehcouch, futuristische Rankenlampe, Projektions-TV und rote Kiste. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un completo abbinato fa tanto scorso decennio. È l'arredamento che va abbinato! Include 8 oggetti: sedia aerodinamica, telecamera robotica, tavolo elettronico, lampada futuristica da camera, divano futuristico trasformabile, lampada futuristica a filamenti, TV a proiezione e cassa rossa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un conjunto a juego de la época pasada. ¡El secreto está en conjuntar  los muebles! Incluye 8 objetos: silla aerodinámica, cámara robótica, mesa de datos, lámpara futurista, sofá deslizante futurista, lámpara futurista, TV de proyección y caja roja. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">A matching outfit is so last decade. It's all about matching furniture! Includes 10 items: Aerodynamic Chair, Camera Robot, Data Stream Table, Desk Picture Frame, Futuristic Room Lamp, Futuristic Slide Out Couch, Futuristic Tendril Lamp, Projection TV, Red Crate, and Wall Picture Frame. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">복장을 통일하는 건 유치해 보일 수 있지만, 가구의 통일은 멋쟁이의 기본입니다. 아래의 10가지 아이템을 포함합니다: 공기역학 의자, 카메라 로봇, 데이터 스트림 탁자, 탁상 액자, 미래형 거실 램프, 미래형 슬라이드 소파, 미래형 촉수 램프, 프로젝션 TV, 붉은 상자, 그리고 벽걸이 액자.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A matching outfit is so last decade. It's all about matching furniture! Includes 10 items: Aerodynamic Chair, Camera Robot, Data Stream Table, Desk Picture Frame, Futuristic Room Lamp, Futuristic Slide Out Couch, Futuristic Tendril Lamp, Projection TV, Red Crate, and Wall Picture Frame. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">相配的服裝已經過時了，現在相配的家具才是潮流！包括十款道具：空氣動力學椅子、相機機械人、資料串流桌、桌上相架、未來世界房間電燈、未來世界拉出式長沙發、未來世界捲鬚狀電燈、投影電視、紅色箱子及相架。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">相配的服裝已經過時了，現在相配的家具才是潮流！包括十款道具：空氣動力學椅子、相機機械人、資料串流桌、桌上相架、未來世界房間電燈、未來世界拉出式長沙發、未來世界捲鬚狀電燈、投影電視、紅色箱子及相框。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A matching outfit is so last decade. It's all about matching furniture! Includes 10 items: Aerodynamic Chair, Camera Robot, Data Stream Table, Desk Picture Frame, Futuristic Room Lamp, Futuristic Slide Out Couch, Futuristic Tendril Lamp, Projection TV, Red Crate, and Wall Picture Frame. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>