<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Twingate Hair (for him) - White</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Twingate Coup de cheveux (pour lui) - Blanc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Twingate Frisuren (für ihn) - Weiß</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Twingate Capigliatura (per lui) - Bianco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Twingate Peinado (para él) - Blanco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Twingate Hair (for him) - White</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Every story has two sides, every day has it's night and every soul has it's dark side.  What would happen if these two sides were ever parted, if magic entered the roots of your soul and divided it into two?  The curse hung in the air filling every corner of the castle.  The splitting of a soul in two, one side to hold all that was good, great and beautiful, the other half to be filled with the darkness of evil, bitterness and hatred.  Here everything is light, the feeling of hope and happiness is palpable.  But this is Twingate Castle...[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une histoire a toujours deux versions des faits, une journée finit toujours par se transformer en nuit et chaque âme possède un côté obscur. Que se passerait-il si ces deux côtés étaient totalement indépendants ? Si la magie s'emparait de votre âme et la divisait en deux ?  La malédiction s'est infiltrée dans chaque petit recoin du château. L'âme est alors divisée en deux : un côté bienveillant, rayonnant et généreux et un côté maléfique, emplit d'aigreur et de ressentiment. Ici, tout est lumineux ; le bonheur et l'espoir sont presque palpables. Mais ici, vous êtes au château Twingate...[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jede Geschichte hat zwei Seiten, jeder Tag hat seine Nacht und jede Seele seine finstere Seite. Was würde passieren, wenn diese beiden Seiten jemals getrennt würden? Falls Magie in die Wurzeln deiner Seele eindringen und sie in zwei Teile spalten würde?  Der Fluch hing in der Luft und füllte jede Ecke des Schlosses. Das entzweispalten einer Seele, eine Seite, die das Gute, Großartige und Schöne enthält, und die andere Hälfte gefüllt mit der Finsternis des Bösen, der Bitterheit und dem Hass. Hier ist alles Licht; das Gefühl von Hoffnung und Freude ist spürbar. Aber in diesem Twingate-Schloss...[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ogni storia ha due versioni, ogni giorno ha la sua notte, ogni anima ha il suo lato oscuro. Cosa succederebbe se questi due lati venssero separarti? Se la magia si insinuasse fino alle radici della tua anima e la scindesse in due?  La maledizione era sospesa nell’aria e riempiva ogni angolo del castello. La scissione di un’anima in due, una metà che contenesse tutto ciò che in essa vi era di buono, l’altra piena fino all’orlo di buio e malvagità, crudeltà e odio. Qui, tutto è luce, si percepisce un senso di speranza e felicità. Ma questo è il castello di Twingate... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cada historia tiene dos versiones. Cada día tiene su noche y cada alma su parte oscura. ¿Qué pasaría si esas dos partes se separaran? ¿Y si la magia llegara hasta lo más profundo de tu alma y la dividiera en dos?  La maldición está en el aire y en cada rincón del castillo. La división del alma en dos partes: una con todo lo bueno, grandeza y belleza. La otra con maldad, tinieblas, rencor y odio. Aquí todo es alegría y el sentimiento de esperanza y felicidad es palpable. Pero en el castillo Twingate nunca se sabe…[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Every story has two sides, every day has it's night and every soul has it's dark side.  What would happen if these two sides were ever parted, if magic entered the roots of your soul and divided it into two?  The curse hung in the air filling every corner of the castle.  The splitting of a soul in two, one side to hold all that was good, great and beautiful, the other half to be filled with the darkness of evil, bitterness and hatred.  Here everything is light, the feeling of hope and happiness is palpable.  But this is Twingate Castle...[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>