<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Skip a Beat Rashguard - Black (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Top Skip a Beat - Noir (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Skip a Beat Rashguard - Black (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Skip a Beat Rash guard - Nero (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Top térmico Skip a Beat - Negro (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Football jersey rashguard scores major style points with its Mermaid 73 screen. But don't let its good looks fool you. As fun as it is, it doesn't mess around when it comes to protecting you from rashing and burning. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Notre top en jersey football marque des points Fashion avec son écran Mermaid 73. Mais son look fun et irréprochable ne doit pas vous leurrer. Il est aussi parfait pour vous protéger des égratignures et des brûlures. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Fußball-Rashguard mit seinem augenfälligen Mermaid 73 Aufdruck ist der absolute Treffer nicht nur für Stilikonen. Aber das Rashguard sieht nicht nur gut aus, sondern schützt auch gleichzeitig vor Hautausschlag und Sonnenbrand. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa rash guard in jersey in stile football americano segna molti punti in fatto di stile con la stampa  Mermaid 73. Ma non lasciarti ingannare dal suo aspetto; per quanto sia trendy, sa il fatto suo quando si tratta di proteggerti da abrasioni e scottature. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El top térmico de camiseta de fútbol americano anota más puntos en estilo gracias a su serigrafía Mermaid 73. Pero no dejes que su diseño espectacular te engañe. Pese a lo divertido de su look, no se anda con tonterías cuando se trata de protegerte de erupciones o quemaduras. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>