<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Cruiser Hoodie - Golden (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Sweat à capuche Cruiser - Doré (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Cruiser Kapuzenpulli - Gold (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Cruiser Felpa con cappuccio - Oro (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Cruiser Sudadera con capucha - Dorado (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Cruiser wears nice and easy with the great feel of a soft cotton fleece fabric. Styled with tonal stripes at front, the long sleeves, hood and chest pocket offer a cool contrast with solid coloring. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Cruiser se porte bien et facilement grâce au confort exceptionnel de son tissu polaire en coton doux. Agrémenté de rayures aux tons différents sur le devant, ses manches longues, sa capuche et sa poche poitrine, il offre un contraste décontracté aux couleurs unies. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Cruiser Kapuzenpulli aus kuscheligem Baumwollfleece ist wunderbar weich und bequem. Vorne gestreift mit kontrastierenden Blockfarben an den Ärmeln, der Kapuze und der Brusttasche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il pullover Cruiser è facile e comodo da indossare grazie al morbido tessuto di cotone. Con righe tono su tono sul davanti, maniche lunghe, cappuccio e tasca sul petto, questa felpa offre un fantastico contrasto con i colori a tinta unita. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La Cruiser es cómoda y agradable en el vestir, con esa genial sensación del tejido polar y su suave algodón. En un estilo a rayas con distintos tonos en la parte delantera, las mangas largas, la capucha y el bolsillo en el pecho actúan de contraste con un color sólido. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>