<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Black Stallion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'Etalon Noir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der schwarze Hengst</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lo Stallone Nero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Semental Negro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* Black Horse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Black Horse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Black Horse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Black Horse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Black Horse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Black Stallion</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB"> Ride out into the open plains and feel the wind on your face as this stallion carries you to your destination. This trusted steed will always be there when you need him, and has endless stamina. This item increases your avatar speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Galopez dans les plaines et sentez le vent caresser votre visage pendant que cet étalon vous transporte à votre destination. Cette monture de confiance sera toujours là quand vous en aurez besoin et a une endurance sans fin. Cet article augmente la vitesse de votre avatar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Reite hinaus in die weiten Ebenen und fühl den Wind im Gesicht, wenn dieser Hengst dich zu deinem Ziel trägt. Dieses vertrauenswürdige Roß wird immer da sein, wenn man es braucht, und hat endlose Ausdauer. Dieser Artikel erhöht Ihre avatar Geschwindigkeit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cavalca le pianure e senti il vento sulla tua faccia mentre questo stallone ti porta  a destinazione. Questo fidato destriero ci sarà sempre quando avrai bisogno di lui, e ha una stamina infinita. Questa voce la tua velocità avatar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Monta por las abiertas llanuras y siente el viento en tu cara mientras este semental te lleva hasta tu destino.Este fiable corcel siempre estará ahí cuando lo necesites y además tiene una energía inacabable. Este elemento aumenta la velocidad de su avatar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* The Black beauty of the ranch [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* The Black beauty of the ranch [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* The Black beauty of the ranch [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* The Black beauty of the ranch [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* The Black beauty of the ranch [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US"> Ride out into the open plains and feel the wind on your face as this stallion carries you to your destination. This trusted steed will always be there when you need him, and has endless stamina. This item increases your avatar speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>