<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nebula Air Ship Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack de meubles vaisseau nébuleux</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nebelflugschiff - Möbelpaket </LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completo arredamento aeromobile Nebula</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de muebles de aeronave Nebula</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Omitted from SCEJ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">성운 비행선 가구 세트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Nebula Air Ship Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Nebula飛船家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Nebula飛船家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Nebula Air Ship Furniture Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">These soft billowy furniture pieces are great to relax with while you are floating in the upper atmosphere. Bundle includes bed, shelf, plants, table and sofa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce mobilier au design doux et nébuleux est idéal pour vous détendre pendant que vous planez dans la stratosphère. Le pack contient un lit, une étagère, des plantes, une table et un sofa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese sanft geschwungenen Möbelstücke eignen sich großartig zum Entspannen, während man in der oberen Atmosphäre schwebt. Zum Paket gehören Bett, Regal, Pflanzen, Tisch und Sofa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Arredamento ondoso, ideale per rilassarsi quando si galleggia nell'alta atmosfera. Il completo include letto, scaffale, piante, tavolo e divano. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estos muebles suaves y ligeros son ideales para relajarte mientras flotas en las capas superiores de la atmósfera. El conjunto incluye: cama, estantería, plantas, mesa y sofá. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Omitted from SCEJ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">부드럽게 물결치는 가구들과 함께 대기권 상층에서 떠도십시오. 이 세트은 성운 비행선 - 구름 침대, 성운 비행선 - 선반, 성운 비행선 - 모형 비행선, 성운 비행선 - 식물, 성운 비행선 - 탁자, 그리고 성운 비행선 - 소파를 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">These soft billowy furniture pieces are great to relax with while you are floating in the upper atmosphere. Bundle includes the Nebula Air Ship - Cloud Bed, Nebula Air Ship - Shelf, Nebula Air Ship - Plants, Nebula Air Ship - Sofa and Nebula Air Ship - Table. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在上大氣層漂浮時，這些綿軟波動的家具最適合用來放鬆休息。組合包包括Nebula飛船-雲床、Nebula飛船-置物架、Nebula飛船-植物、Nebula飛船-沙發及Nebula飛船-桌子。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在上大氣層漂浮時，這些綿軟波動的家具最適合用來放鬆休息。組合包包括Nebula飛船-雲床、Nebula飛船-置物架、Nebula飛船-植物、Nebula飛船-沙發及Nebula飛船-桌子。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">These soft billowy furniture pieces are great to relax with while you are floating in the upper atmosphere. Bundle includes bed, shelf, plants, table and sofa. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>