<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Khul Mercali Conqueror Warshield</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bouclier de guerre conquérant Khul Mercali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Khul-Mercali-Eroberer-Kriegsschild</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scudo da guerra di Khul Mercali il conquistatore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Escudo de guerra de conquistador Khul Mercali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Khul Mercali Conqueror Warshield</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Designed for enforcing the mighty will of a Defender.\n\nThe tempered Steel of the Conqueror is famous throughout many lands, as is the unquenchable hunger for glory and adventure.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Conçu pour renforcer la puissante volonté du défenseur.\n\nL'acier trempé du conquérant est célèbre à travers les divers territoires, ainsi que sa soif insatiable de gloire et d'aventure.\n\nDÉBLOQUE DES ARTICLES DU JEU MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS – N'OFFRE PAS DE COMPOSANTS D'AVATAR POUR UN USAGE GÉNÉRAL SUR PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBLE POUR LES UTILISATEURS DU JAPON ET DE L'ASIE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zur Stärkung des mächtigen Willens der Beschützer entwickelt.\n\nDer gehärtete Stahl des Eroberers ist in vielen Ländern berühmt, genau wie sein endloser Hunger nach Ruhm und Abenteuer.\n\nZUM FREISCHALTEN VON GEGENSTÄNDEN IN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS - NICHT ZUM ERHALT VON AVATAR-KOMPONENTEN ZUR ALLGEMEINEN NUTZUNG AUF PLAYSTATION®HOME. NICHT VERFÜGBAR FÜR BENUTZER IN JAPAN UND ASIEN [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ideato per rafforzare la potente volontà del difensore.\n\nL'acciaio temperato del conquistatore è famoso in tante terre come la sua fame insaziabile di gloria e avventura.\n\nSBLOCCA OGGETTI ALL'INTERNO DEL GIOCO MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS. NON REGALA COMPONENTI PER AVATAR PER USO GENERICO CON PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBILE PER GLI UTENTI IN ASIA E GIAPPONE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Diseñado para reforzar la poderosa voluntad de un defensor.\n\nEl acero templado del conquistado es famoso en muchas tierras, como lo es también su insaciable sed de gloria y aventuras.\n\nDESBLOQUEARÁ ELEMENTOS EN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS GAME. NO REGALARÁ COMPONENTES DE AVATAR PARA EL USO GENERAL EN CASA DE PLAYSTATION. NO DISPONIBLE PARA LOS USUARIOS DE JAPÓN Y ASIA. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Designed for enforcing the mighty will of a Defender.\n\nThe tempered Steel of the Conqueror is famous throughout many lands, as is the unquenchable hunger for glory and adventure.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>