<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Baboon Butt Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cul de Babouin Ensemble</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Pavian Hintern Bündel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Culo de Babbuino Fascio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Babuino Culo Paquete</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Baboon Butt Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The De-Evolution is here . . .and it's on your buttocks.  Don't be fooled by cheap imitations, this is the real thing.  This bundle includes male and female Baboon Butts.  You're a primate, don't be afraid to show it. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La De-Evolution est la  . . . et elle est sur tes fesses. Ne soyez pas dupé par les imitations de mauvaise qualité, c'est la chose réelle. Cet ensemble comprend des Culs de Babouin pour les hommes et les femmes. Vous êtes un primate, n'ayez pas peur de le montrer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die De-Evolution ist hier  . . . und es ist auf dem gesäß. Lass dich nicht von billigen Imitaten täuschen, dies ist die reale sache. Dieses paket enthält männliche und weibliche Pavian Hintern. Du bist ein primat, keine angst zu zeigen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il De-Evolution è qui  . . . ed è su i glutei. Non fatevi ingannare dalle imitazioni a buon mercato, questa è la cosa reale. Questo fascio include maschile e femminile Culo de Babbuino. Sei un primate, non abbiate paura di mostrarlo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El De-La evolución es aquí  . . . y en las nalgas. No se deje engañar por imitaciones baratas, esto es lo real. Este paquete incluye Culos Babuino macho y hembra. Usted es un primate, no tengas miedo de demostrarlo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The De-Evolution is here . . .and it's on your buttocks.  Don't be fooled by cheap imitations, this is the real thing.  This bundle includes male and female Baboon Butts.  You're a primate, don't be afraid to show it. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>