<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Men in Black™ Headquarters</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quartier Général de Men in Black™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Men in Black™ Hauptquartier</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quartier generale Men in Black™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sede de Men in Black™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Men in Black™ Headquarters</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Get an all-access pass when you own the Men In Black™ Headquarters as your own Private Space!  Enjoy being the boss of the most top-secret organization established to monitor alien activity on Earth! Hang out with Frank the Pug in the MIB™ Offices, shop in the armory and relax in the break room! So suit up and get ready for the explosive return of Agents Kay and Jay in Men in Black™ III and the epic new video game Men in Black: Alien Crisis™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Obtenez un passe multi-accès quand vous possédez le Quartier Général Men in Black™ en tant qu'Espace Privé personnel ! Profitez d'être le chef de cette organisme top secret établi pour contrôler l'activité extraterrestre sur Terre ! Promenez-vous avec Frank le chien dans les Bureaux de MIB™, faites vos courses dans l'armurerie et relaxez-vous dans la salle de pause !  Alors en tenue et soyez prêt au retour explosif des Agents Kay et Jay dans Men in Black™ III et le nouveau jeu vidéo épique Men in Black: Alien Crisis™ ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast überall Zutritt, wenn du das Men in Black™ Hauptquartier als deinen Privatraum besitzt! Genieße deinen neuen Job als Boss der ultrageheimen Geheimorganisation für die Überwachung außerirdischer Aktivitäten auf der Erde! Häng mit Frank dem Mops ab, kauf in der Waffenkammer ein und entspanne dich im Pausenraum! Also wirf dich in Schale und bereite dich vor auf die explosive Rückkehr der Agenten Kay und Jay in Men in Black™ III und dem genialen neuen Videogame Men in Black: Alien Crisis™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Otterrai un pass universale quando avrai il Quartier generale Men In Black™ come tuo Spazio privato! Spazio privato! Gioca a fare il boss dell'organizzazione top-secret creata per il monitoraggio delle attività aliene sulla terra! Divertiti con Frank the Pug negli Uffici MIB™, fai shopping nell'armeria e prenditi una pausa nella stanza relax! Il QG MIB™ è il luogo ideale per la tua organizzazione segreta. Travestiti e preparati all'esplosivo ritorno degli agenti Kay e Jay in Men in Black™ III e nel nuovo fantastico videogioco Men in Black: Alien Crisis™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Tendrás un pase de acceso completo cuando tengas tu propio cuartel central de Men In Black™ y lo conviertas en tu propio espacio privado! ¡Disfruta siendo el jefe de la organización más clandestina creada para supervisar la actividad alienígena sobre la Tierra! ¡Podrás ver a Frank the Pug en las oficinas de MIB™,  comprar en la tienda de armas y relajarte en la sala de ocio! Vístete y prepárate para el regreso explosivo de los agentes Kay y Jay en Men in Black™ III, ¡y el nuevo y épico videojuego Men in Black: Alien Crisis™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Get an all-access pass when you own the Men In Black™ Headquarters as your own Private Space!  Enjoy being the boss of the most top-secret organization established to monitor alien activity on Earth! Hang out with Frank the Pug in the MIB™ Offices, shop in the armory and relax in the break room! So suit up and get ready for the explosive return of Agents Kay and Jay in Men in Black™ III and the epic new video game Men in Black: Alien Crisis™! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>