<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Thor DX Engine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Moteurs Thor DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Thor DX-Triebwerk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Motori Thor DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Motores Thor DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Thor DX エンジン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Thor DX 엔진</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Thor DX Engine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Thor DX 引擎</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Thor DX 引擎</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Thor DX Engine</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A Large and powerful engine to push your Sodium2 racer towards Mach 2. Don't forget to take account of the extra weight through the bends or a crash at that speed will leave nothing but a smear. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un moteur puissant et imposant qui fera atteindre Mach 2 à votre véhicule de course Sodium2. N'oubliez pas de tenir compte du surpoids dans les virages car un crash à cette vitesse vous réduirait en miettes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein großes, leistungsstarkes Triebwerk, das deinen Sodium2-Gleiter an Mach 2 heranbringt. Denk immer an das zusätzliche Gewicht des Triebwerks, sonst wird nach einem Unfall in einer Kurve nichts mehr übrig bleiben. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un motore grande e potente per consentire al tuo veicolo da corsa Sodium2 di raggiungere Mach 2. Fai attenzione alle curve: uno schianto a quella velocità con il peso ulteriore rischia di essere fatale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un enorme y potente motor para llevar a tu corredor de Sodium2 hacia el Mach2. No olvides tener en cuenta el peso adicional al tomar las curvas, un choque a esta velocidad solo dejaría una mancha como rastro. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">パワフルな大型エンジンを搭載すれば、マッハ2まで加速可能になります。車体全体の重量がかなり重くなるので、コーナーやカーブでは十分な慎重さが必要になります。高速でクラッシュしたら、車体が木っ端微塵に破壊されてしまうことでしょう。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium2 레이서를 마하 2의 속력으로 쏘아 붙이는 강력한 엔진입니다. 그러나 엔진의 무게를 감안하지 않고 코너에 진입한다면 벽과 충돌하는 불상사가 일어나기 쉽습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A Large and powerful engine to push your Sodium2 racer towards Mach 2. Don't forget to take account of the extra weight through the bends or a crash at that speed will leave nothing but a smear. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這個既巨型又強力的引擎能將你的Sodium2飛船速度推進至馬赫2。不要忘記其額外的重量，在這種速度轉彎或撞車會留下油跡。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這個既巨型又強力的引擎能將你的Sodium2飛船速度推進至馬赫2。不要忘記其額外的重量，在這種速度轉彎或撞車會留下油跡。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A Large and powerful engine to push your Sodium2 racer towards Mach 2. Don't forget to take account of the extra weight through the bends or a crash at that speed will leave nothing but a smear. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>