<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Men in Black™ Headquarters Private Space and Clubhouse Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce Lot vient avec le Club-House du Quartier Général de Men in Black™ et l'Espace Privé de Men in Black™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Men in Black™ Hauptquartier-Privatraum und Clubhaus-Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Spazio privato e Club House Quartier generale Men in Black™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lote de espacio privado y club del cuartel central de Men in Black™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Men in Black™ Headquarters Private Space and Clubhouse Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Bundle comes with the Men In Black™ Headquarters Clubhouse and Men in Black™ Private Space!  Hang out with Frank the Pug in the MIB™ Offices, shop in the armory and relax in the break room! This Bundle comes with 11 exclusive MIB™ Furniture items. So suit up and get ready for the explosive return of Agents Kay and Jay in Men in Black™ III and the epic new video game Men in Black: Alien Crisis™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce Lot vient avec le Club-House du Quartier Général de Men in Black™ et l'Espace Privé de Men in Black™ ! Promenez-vous avec Frank le chien dans les Bureaux de MIB™, faites vos courses dans l'armurerie et relaxez-vous dans la salle de pause ! Ce Lot vient avec 11 articles de mobilier exclusifs de MIB™. Alors en tenue et soyez prêts au retour explosif des Agents Kay et Jay dans Men in Black™ III et le nouveau jeu vidéo épique Men in Black: Alien Crisis™ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Bundle enthält das Men in Black™ Clubhaus und den Men in Black™ Hauptquartier-Privatraum! Häng mit Frank dem Mops im MiB™ - Büro ab, geh zum Shoppen in die Waffenkammer und entspann dich im Pausenraum! In diesem Bundle sind 11 exklusive MiB™ Einrichtungsgegenstände enthalten. Also wirf dich in Schale und sei bereit für die explosive Rückkehr der Agenten Kay und Jay in Men in Black™ III und dem genialen neuen Videospiel Men in Black: Alien Crisis™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il presente pacchetto contiene il Club House Quartier Generale Men In Black™ e lo Spazio privato Men in Black™!  Divertiti con Frank the Pug negli Uffici MIB™, fai shopping nell'armeria e prenditi una pausa nella stanza relax! Questo pacchetto contiene 11 esclusivi articoli di arredamento MIB™. Travestiti e preparati all'esplosivo ritorno degli agenti Kay e Jay in Men in Black™ III e nel nuovo fantastico videogioco Men in Black: Alien Crisis™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Este lote incluye el club del cuartel central de Men In Black™ y el espacio privado de Men in Black™!  ¡Trabaja con Frank y Pug en las oficinas de MIB™, compra en la armería y relájate en la sala de ocio! Este lote ofrece 11 exclusivos muebles de MIB™. ¡Vístete y prepárate para el retorno explosivo de los agentes Kay y Jay en Men in Black™ III, y el nuevo y épico videojuego Men in Black: Alien Crisis™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This Bundle comes with the Men In Black™ Headquarters Clubhouse and Men in Black™ Private Space!  Hang out with Frank the Pug in the MIB™ Offices, shop in the armory and relax in the break room! This Bundle comes with 11 exclusive MIB™ Furniture items. So suit up and get ready for the explosive return of Agents Kay and Jay in Men in Black™ III and the epic new video game Men in Black: Alien Crisis™! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>