<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">NAME</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Eucadian General Legs</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jambes du général d'armée eucadien</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beine eines eucadianischen Generals</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Generale Eucadiano - Gambe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Piernas de general eucadiano</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Eucadian General Legs</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The General, the highest of the high, the elitist of the elite. You have worked hard to garnish this rank, countless games, endless hours. Now, carry that rank on into your Home today. You deserve it. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Général d'armée est le grade le plus élevé qui soit ; c'est l'élite de l'élite. Vous avez travaillé dur, joué un nombre incalculable de fois et passé d'innombrables heures pour y parvenir. N'attendez donc plus pour afficher votre rang dans Home. Vous l'avez bien mérité ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der General, die höchste, elitärste Position. Für diesen Rang haben Sie hart gearbeitet – zahllose Spiele, endlose Stunden. Nehmen Sie heute diese Auszeichnung mit nach Hause, Sie haben sie sich verdient. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il generale, il grado più alto di tutti, quel che si dice l'eccellenza. Hai lavorato duro per raggiungere questo grado, ore e ore di partite infinite. Ora potrai mostrare questo grado nella tua casa. Te lo sei meritato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">General, el rango más alto, la élite de la élite. Has trabajado duro para llegar hasta aquí; innumerables partidas, innumerables horas. Lleva el rango a tu Home. Te lo mereces. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The General, the highest of the high, the elitist of the elite. You have worked hard to garnish this rank, countless games, endless hours. Now, carry that rank on into your Home today. You deserve it. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>