<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Leggings Red Flowers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Legging à fleurs rouges</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rote-Blumen-Leggings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Legging Fiori rossi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Leggings flores rojas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">レギンス - レッドフラワー（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">레깅스 붉은 꽃(여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Leggings Red Flowers (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">紅花緊身褲(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">紅花緊身褲(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Leggings Red Flowers</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">These skin-tight leggings are great for every occassion! Whether you are going to a party or you're just staying home, they will always do. They come in various colors,  prints and materials. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce legging moulant peut se porter en toutes occasions ! Que vous soyez partante pour faire la fête toute la nuit ou que décidiez simplement de passer la soirée dans votre canapé, il fera parfaitement l'affaire. Il existe même en plusieurs couleurs, motifs et matières. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese hautengen Leggings sind das perfekte Kleidungsstück für alle Gelegenheiten! Ganz gleich ob du auf einer Party glänzt oder gemütlich zu Hause bleibst: Diese Leggings sind immer goldrichtig. In verschiedenen Farben, Motiven und Materialien erhältlich. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questi legging attillati sono perfetti per ogni occasione, dalle feste alle tranquille giornate in casa. Disponibili in vari colori e materiali e con diversi motivi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Estos leggings ajustados son geniales para cualquier ocasión! Ya vayas a una fiesta o te quedes en casa, siempre te irán bien. Vienen en diversos colores, estampados y materiales. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この体にぴったりフィットするレギンスはあらゆる場面で活躍します！パーティーに行く時でも、ただ家にいる時でも、これで大丈夫。様々な色、プリントや素材からお選び頂けます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 꽉 끼는 레깅스는 모든 상황에 잘 어울립니다! 파티에서도, 혹은 집에서 쉴 때도 잘 어울리죠. 이 레깅스는 다양한 색, 무늬, 재질로 제공됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">These skin-tight leggings are great for every occassion! Whether you are going to a party or you're just staying home, they will always do. They come in various colors, prints and materials. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這些緊貼肌膚的緊身褲適合於不同場合穿著！不論你出席派對或留在家中，它們都十分適合。這緊身褲有不同顏色、圖案和質料。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這些緊貼肌膚的緊身褲適合於不同場合穿著！不論你出席派對或留在家中，它們都十分適合。這緊身褲有不同顏色、圖案和質料。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">These skin-tight leggings are great for every occassion! Whether you are going to a party or you're just staying home, they will always do. They come in various colors,  prints and materials. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>