<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Master Higgins Kanji T-shirt - [裏技] (Men's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">T-shirt Kanji du Maître - [裏技] (pour homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kanji-T-Shirt von Master Higgins – [裏技] (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maglietta del Maestro - [裏技] (da uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta con kanji del maestro - [裏技] (Hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">高橋名人の漢字Ｔシャツ「裏技」　男性用</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Master Higgins Kanji T-shirt - [裏技] (Men's)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Chinese character T-shirt hand written by Master Higgins.\n“裏技” means a secret trick to cause “useful and rare” things to occur during a game using a method not mentioned in the instruction manual.\nPut on this T-shirt and find various “裏技”![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">T-shirt à caractères chinois écrits à la main par le Maître.\n"裏技" signifie "Sort secret". Un sort secret entraîne des phénomènes "utiles et rares" en cours de jeu dont aucun manuel ne donne la recette.\nMets ce T-shirt et découvre, toi aussi, des "裏技" ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Handbeschriebenes T-Shirt mit chinesischen Zeichen von Master Higgins.\n„裏技“ steht für einen geheimen Trick, der nicht im Handbuch erwähnt wird, mit dem man „nützliche und seltene Dinge“ in einem Spiel erscheinen lässt.\nZieh dieses T-Shirt an, um viele „裏技“ zu finden![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maglietta con ideogrammi cinesi dipinti a mano dal Maestro.\n“裏技” è un trucco segreto che serve a far accadere cose "utili e rare" durante un gioco usando un metodo che non è illustrato nel manuale di istruzioni.\nIndossa questa maglietta e scopri diversi “裏技”![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta con caracteres chinos escritos por el maestro.\n“裏技” representa un truco secreto para provocar que ocurran cosas “útiles y raras” durante el juego, utilizando un método no mencionado en el manual de instrucciones.\n¡Ponte esta camiseta y encuentra varios “裏技”![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">高橋名人直筆の漢字Ｔシャツです！\n「裏技」とは、説明書などに記載されていない方法で”有用かつ珍しい現象”を意図的に起こすことが可能な操作を指します。\nあなたもこのＴシャツを着て、さまざまな裏技を見つけましょう！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Chinese character T-shirt hand written by Master Higgins.\n“裏技” means a secret trick to cause “useful and rare” things to occur during a game using a method not mentioned in the instruction manual.\nPut on this T-shirt and find various “裏技”![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>