<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LOOT™ Actives Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot de Vraies Affaires LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LOOT™ Actives Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto LOOT™ Actives</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lote LOOT™ Active</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LOOT™アクティブ・バンドル</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">LOOT™ 다이나믹 번들</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">LOOT™活躍組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">LOOT™活躍組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LOOT™ Actives Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Having a party? Then you need the LOOT™ Actives Bundle! You’ll get the Active Searchlight, Fog Machine and Grandfather clock for one LOW price. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous organisez une fête ? Alors vous avez besoin du Lot de Vraies Affaires LOOT™! Vous aurez le Vrai Projecteur, la Machine à Brouillard et l'Horloge de Grand-Père à un tout PETIT prix. Si vous possédez déjà l'Appartement Spatial LOOT™ ou le Yacht Coucher de Soleil LOOT™, vous bénéficierez carrément de 50% de rabais (Canada seulement) ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schmeißt du eine Party? Dann brauchst du das LOOT™ Actives Paket! Du erhältst den Active Scheinwerfer, Nebelmaschine und die Standuhr zu einem Supersparpreis. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dai una festa? Allora ti serve il Pacchetto LOOT™ Actives! Troverai il proiettore, la macchina del fumo e l'orologio del nonno a un prezzo davvero BASSO.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Vas a dar una fiesta? ¡Necesitas el lote LOOT™ Active! Incluye el foco, la máquina de niebla y el reloj de cuco por un precio muy BAJO.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">パーティー開催？ならLOOT™アクティブ・バンドルが必要です！アクティブ・サーチライト、フォグマシーン、グランドファーザークロックの全てがまとめて安く手に入ります！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">파티하시려고요? LOOT™ 다이나믹 번들이 딱이죠! 다이나믹 서치라이트를 써보세요, 안개 장치와 할아버지 자명종을 저렴한 가격에 제공합니다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">要辦派對嗎？那您需要LOOT™活躍組合包！您將可以透過低廉的價格獲得活躍探照燈、乾冰機以及老爺鐘。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">要辦派對嗎？那您需要LOOT™活躍組合包！您將可以透過低廉的價格獲得活躍探照燈、乾冰機以及老爺鐘。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Having a party? Then you need the LOOT™ Actives Bundle! You’ll get the Active Searchlight, Fog Machine and Grandfather clock for one LOW price. If you own the LOOT™ Space Apartment or the Sunset Yacht, you’ll get a radical 50% discount! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>