<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dolphy Breeding Guide</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guide d'élevage de Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Dolphy-Zucht“-Anleitung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guida all'allevamento di un Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guía de cría de Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィー育成ガイド</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dolphy Breeding Guide</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dolphy Room Guide</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guide du Dolphydrome</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Dolphy-Raum“-Anleitung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guida alla Stanza di Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guía del Cuarto de Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィー育成ルームのガイド</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dolphy Room Guide</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Notice</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Info</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mitteilung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Avviso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aviso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">お知らせ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Notice</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to the Dolphy Room</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue au Dolphydrome</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen im Dolphy-Raum</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuto nella Stanza di Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido/a al Cuarto de Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィー育成ルームへようこそ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome to the Dolphy Room</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Raise a Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Élever son Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Dolphy aufziehen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Alleva un Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cría a un Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィーを飼ってみましょう</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Raise a Dolphy</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Using the Dolphy Centre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utiliser le Centre Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dolphy-Zentrale benutzen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usare il Centro Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cómo usar el Centro Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィーセンターの使い方</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Using the Dolphy Center</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Feeding your Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nourrir son Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dolphy füttern</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nutrire il tuo Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cómo alimentar a tu Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">食事について</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Feeding your Dolphy</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ring Game/Test Course</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jeu des anneaux/Parcours d'essai</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ringspiel/Teststrecke</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gioco degli anelli/Circuito di prova</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de anillas/Circuito de prueba</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">リングゲームとテストコース</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ring Game/Test Course</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dolphy Races</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Courses de Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dolphy-Rennen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gare di Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Carreras de Dolphies</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィーレースについて</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dolphy Races</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_title8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Customising your Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Personnaliser son Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dolphy anpassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Personalizzare il tuo Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cómo personalizar a tu Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">カスタマイズについて</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Customizing your Dolphy</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dolphy Breeding Guide (1/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guide d'élevage de Dolphy (1/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Dolphy-Zucht“-Anleitung (1/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guida all'allevamento di un Dolphy (1/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guía de cría de Dolphy (1/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィー育成ガイド(1/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dolphy Breeding Guide (1/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dolphy Breeding Guide (2/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guide d'élevage de Dolphy (2/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Dolphy-Zucht“-Anleitung (2/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guida all'allevamento di un Dolphy (2/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guía de cría de Dolphy (2/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィー育成ガイド(2/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dolphy Breeding Guide (2/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dolphy Breeding Guide (3/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guide d'élevage de Dolphy (3/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Dolphy-Zucht“-Anleitung (3/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guida all'allevamento di un Dolphy (3/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guía de cría de Dolphy (3/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィー育成ガイド(3/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dolphy Breeding Guide (3/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dolphy Breeding Guide (4/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guide d'élevage de Dolphy (4/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Dolphy-Zucht“-Anleitung (4/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guida all'allevamento di un Dolphy (4/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guía de cría de Dolphy (4/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィー育成ガイド(4/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dolphy Breeding Guide (4/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dolphy Breeding Guide (5/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guide d'élevage de Dolphy (5/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Dolphy-Zucht“-Anleitung (5/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guida all'allevamento di un Dolphy (5/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guía de cría de Dolphy (5/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィー育成ガイド(5/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dolphy Breeding Guide (5/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dolphy Breeding Guide (6/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guide d'élevage de Dolphy (6/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Dolphy-Zucht“-Anleitung (6/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guida all'allevamento di un Dolphy (6/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guía de cría de Dolphy (6/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィー育成ガイド(6/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dolphy Breeding Guide (6/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dolphy Breeding Guide (7/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guide d'élevage de Dolphy (7/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Dolphy-Zucht“-Anleitung (7/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guida all'allevamento di un Dolphy (7/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guía de cría de Dolphy (7/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィー育成ガイド(7/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dolphy Breeding Guide (7/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_page8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dolphy Breeding Guide (8/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guide d'élevage de Dolphy (8/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Dolphy-Zucht“-Anleitung (8/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guida all'allevamento di un Dolphy (8/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guía de cría de Dolphy (8/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィー育成ガイド(8/8)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dolphy Breeding Guide (8/8)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">10.2010\nDue to its popularity, we have added new Dolphy-themed items to the Item Shop. There are also now more items you can earn in various ways that will allow you to further customise your Dolphy. Be sure to check them out!\nAdditionally, the Dolphy Race course is now called the "Challenge Course" and we have added a new "Star Course" as well. Races alternate between the two every 20 minutes. Try out the new customisation features and race courses!\n\nWe hope you have a great day with your Dolphies!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">10.2010\nVu sa popularité, nous avons ajouté de nouveaux articles sur le thème des Dolphies dans la Boutique articles. Tu peux désormais gagner encore plus d'articles de différentes façons afin de personnaliser ton Dolphy ! Alors n'hésite pas à aller voir !\nNous avons également renommé le parcours de la Course de Dolphies "course défi" et aussi ajouté la nouvelle "course étoile". Les courses alternent entre les deux toutes les 20 minutes. Essaie donc les nouvelles fonctions de personnalisation et ces courses !\n\nNous te souhaitons une bonne journée en compagnie de tes Dolphies !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">10.2010\nAufgrund seiner Popularität haben wir dem Artikel-Shop neue Dolphy-Artikel hinzugefügt. Außerdem gibt es jetzt weitere Artikel, die du auf verschiedene Arten verdienen kannst, mit denen sich dein Dolphy weiter anpassen lässt. Sieh sie dir doch mal an!\nZudem haben wir den Dolphy-Rennkurs in "Herausforderung-Kurs" umbenannt und außerdem den neuen "Stern-Kurs" hinzugefügt. Die Rennen finden alle 20 Minuten abwechselnd auf einem der beiden Kurse statt. Probier die neuen Gestaltungsfunktionen und Rennkurse aus!\n\nWir wünschen dir viel Spaß mit deinen Dolphys!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">10.2010\nVisto il successo riscosso, abbiamo messo a tua disposizione sugli scaffali del Negozio nuovi articoli ispirati a Dolphy. Abbiamo anche aggiunto nuovi premi che potrai ottenere in vari modi, e che ti permetteranno di personalizzare ulteriormente il tuo Dolphy. Ricorda di entrare a dare un'occhiata!\nIn più, il circuito della Gara di Dolphy ha cambiato nome in "Circuito sfida" , e abbiamo aggiunto un nuovo "Circuito stella". Le gare si alternano sui due percorsi ogni 20 minuti. Prova i nuovi articoli e i nuovi circuiti di gara!\n\nBuon divertimento con i tuoi Dolphy!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">10.2010\nDebido a su popularidad, hemos añadido nuevos objetos con temática Dolphy a la Tienda de Objetos. También encontrarás nuevos objetos que podrás conseguir de diferentes formas y te permitirán personalizar aún más a tu Dolphy, así que no te olvides de echarles un vistazo.\nAdemás, hemos cambiado el nombre de la carrera "Circuito Dolphy" por "Circuito Competitivo" y añadido además el nuevo "Circuito Estrella"; ambos circuitos se van alternando cada 20 minutos. ¡Prueba las nuevas características de personalización y los circuitos!\n\n¡Esperamos que pases un día genial con tus Dolphies!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">２０１０年１０月\nご好評にお応えしまして、アイテムショップに新しくドルフィーをモチーフにしたアイテムを\n入荷しました。それ以外にも、ドルフィー自体をカスタマイズできる新しいアイテムが様々な条件で手に入りますのでお楽しみに。\nまた、ハドソンゲートのドルフィーレースに新コース「スターコース」が登場。今までのコースも「チャレンジコース」と名を変えて、新コースと交互に２０分おきの開催となりました。新しいカスタマイズでチャレンジしてみましょう！\n\nこれからもドルフィーとの素敵な日々をお楽しみください。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">10.2010\nDue to its popularity, we have added new Dolphy-themed items to the Item Shop. There are also now more items you can earn in various ways that will allow you to further customize your Dolphy. Be sure to check them out!\nAdditionally, the Dolphy Race course is now called the "Challenge Course" and we have added a new "Star Course" as well. Races alternate between the two every 20 minutes. Try out the new customization features and race courses!\n\nWe hope you have a great day with your Dolphies!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Dolphy Room is your own personal area that you can use like your own room. You can decorate it with furniture, invite your friends to check it out, and take care of your pet Dolphy.\n\nWhen your Dolphy grows into an adult, you'll unlock the Ring Game and it will become able to participate in "Dolphy Races" over at the "Hudson Gate". What you do is up to you, so relax and have fun.\n\nThis guide will teach you how to take good care of your Dolphy. If you are unsure of anything while raising your Dolphy, please refer to this guide.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Dolphydrome est un espace rien qu'à toi. Tu peux le meubler à ton goût, le faire visiter à tes amis et t'y occuper de ton Dolphy.\n\nTu pourras débloquer le Jeu des anneaux lorsque ton Dolphy aura atteint l'âge adulte. Il pourra alors participer aux "Courses de Dolphy" de l'Arche d'Hudson. Tu es aux commandes, alors détends-toi et amuse-toi !\n\nCe guide t'apprendra à bien t'occuper de ton Dolphy. Si tu ne sais pas comment élever ton Dolphy, n'hésite pas à consulter ce guide.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Dolphy-Raum ist dein persönlicher Bereich, den du wie dein eigenes Zimmer benutzen kannst. Du kannst ihn mit Möbeln einrichten, Freunde einladen und dich um dein Dolphy kümmern.\n\nWenn dein Dolphy erwachsen wird, schaltest du das Ringspiel frei und kannst beim „Hudson-Tor“ am „Dolphy-Rennen“ teilnehmen. Du allein entscheidest, was du tun möchtest. Also entspann dich und viel Spaß!\n\nIn dieser Anleitung erfährst du, wie du dein Dolphy pflegen musst. Wenn du dir bei der Aufzucht deines Dolphys unsicher bist, ziehe diese Anleitung zurate.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Stanza di Dolphy è il tuo spazio personale che puoi usare come una vera e propria cameretta. La puoi decorare con nuovi mobili, invitare i tuoi amici a vederla e prenderti cura del tuo Dolphy.\n\nIl Gioco degli anelli sarà attivato quando il tuo Dolphy sarà adulto, permettendogli così di partecipare alle "Gare di Dolphy" che si tengono a "Hudson Gate". Puoi fare quello che vuoi, quindi rilassati e divertiti.\n\nQuesta guida ti insegnerà come prenderti cura del tuo Dolphy. Se hai dubbi durante l'allevamento, fai riferimento a questa guida.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Cuarto de Dolphy es tu espacio personal, y puedes disponer de él como si fuera tu propia casa: amuéblalo, invita a tus amigos a verlo y cuida de tu mascota Dolphy.\n\nCuando tu Dolphy llegue a la edad adulta, el juego de anillas quedará desbloqueado y el Dolphy podrá participar en las carreras de "Hudson Gate". La decisión está en tus manos, así que relájate y pásalo bien.\n\nEsta guía te enseñará cómo cuidar de tu Dolphy. Si tienes alguna duda sobre cómo criar a tu Dolphy, consulta esta guía.\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ここは、あなただけの特別なエリア。自分の部屋の１つとして、家具を自由に配置したりフレンドを招待することもできます。また、バーチャルペット「ドルフィー」を飼う事ができます。\n\nドルフィーが成長していくと、リングゲームが楽しめたり「ハドソンゲート」で行われている「ドルフィーレース」に参加させることもできます。もちろん、くつろぎの時間を過ごすのもいいですね。\n\nこのガイドを読めば、あなたもドルフィーの立派なパートナーとなれるでしょう。ドルフィーを飼っていて分からない事があったらこのガイドを読んでみてください。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Dolphy Room is your own personal area that you can use like your own room. You can decorate it with furniture, invite your friends to check it out, and take care of your pet Dolphy.\n\nAs your Dolphy grows into an adult, you'll unlock the Ring Game and become able to participate in "Dolphy Races" over at the "Hudson Gate". What you do is up to you, so relax and have a good time.\n\nThis guide will teach you how to take good care of your Dolphy. If you are unsure of anything while raising your Dolphy, please refer to this guide.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There are 5 devices you can use in the centre of the Dolphy Training Room to communicate and raise your Dolphy. \n\nFirst, walk up and touch the "Dolphy Centre" and select "Raise a New Dolphy" to start out.\n\nYou can name your Dolphy whatever you like. Even as children, they are smart and will immediately come if you call them from the Dolphy Centre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">5 appareils sont à ta disposition au centre du Gymnase Dolphy. Ils te permettent de communiquer avec ton Dolphy et de bien l'élever. \n\nD'abord, avance vers le "Centre Dolphy"et touche-le, puis sélectionne "Élever un nouveau Dolphy"pour commencer.\n\nChoisis librement le nom de ton Dolphy. Même jeunes, ils sont intelligents et viendront te voir si tu les appelles depuis le Centre Dolphy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In der Mitte des Dolphy-Trainingsraums gibt es 5 Geräte, die du verwenden kannst, um mit deinem Dolphy zu kommunizieren und es großzuziehen. \n\nGehe als Erstes zur „Dolphy-Zentrale“, berühre sie und wähle anschließend „Neues Dolphy großziehen“, um loszulegen.\n\nDu kannst deinem Dolphy einen beliebigen Namen geben. Auch ganz kleine Dolphys sind bereits intelligent und kommen sofort, wenn du ihre Namen in der Dolphy-Zentrale rufst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Al centro della Sala di addestramento ci sono 5 dispositivi che puoi usare per comunicare con il tuo Dolphy e farlo crescere.\n\nPer prima cosa tocca il "Centro Dolphy" e scegli "Alleva un nuovo Dolphy" per cominciare. \n\nPuoi dare al tuo Dolphy il nome che preferisci. Sin da cuccioli, i Dolphy sono molto intelligenti e accorrono non appena li chiami dal Centro Dolphy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">En el centro de la sala de entrenamiento de Dolphy hay 5 dispositivos que puedes utilizar para criar a tu Dolphy y comunicarte con él. \n\nEn primer lugar, avanza hasta el “Centro Dolphy” y tócalo para seleccionar “Criar un nuevo Dolphy”, y empezar a jugar.\n\nPon el nombre que quieras a tu Dolphy. Estos animales son inteligentes desde pequeños, y si lo llamas desde el Centro Dolphy acudirá enseguida.\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ルーム中央にある５つの装置を利用してドルフィーとの交流・育成が可能です。\n\nまず最初は「ドルフィーセンター」に触れ、「新しく飼う」を選択し、ドルフィーを飼いはじめましょう。\n\nドルフィーには自由に名前がつけられます。たとえ子供でも、ドルフィーは賢いので、ドルフィーセンターで呼ぶとすぐにあなたの元へ来てくれるでしょう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">There are 5 devices you can use in the center of the Dolphy Training Room to communicate and raise your Dolphy. \n\nFirst, walk up and touch the "Dolphy Center" and select "Raise a New Dolphy" to start out.\n\nYou can name your Dolphy whatever you like. Even as children, they are smart and will immediately come if you call them from the Dolphy Center.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Dolphy Centre is where you can communicate with your Dolphy and see their mood and stats.\n\nIf they are in a good mood, they'll be happy to participate at the Dolphy Race. If they are in a bad mood, they won't. After your Dolphy participates in a race, they'll be tired and unable to race until the next day.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Centre Dolphy te permet de communiquer avec ton Dolphy, de voir quelle est son humeur, de consulter ses statistiques.\n\nUn Dolphy de bonne humeur participera volontiers à une Course de Dolphies. Dans un mauvais jour, il ne voudra pas courir. Après une course ton Dolphy sera fatigué. Il ne pourra participer à aucune course avant le lendemain.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In der Dolphy-Zentrale kannst du mit deinem Dolphy kommunizieren und seine Stimmung sowie seine Werte ansehen.\n\nWenn es gut gelaunt ist, hat es Lust, an einem Dolphy-Rennen teilzunehmen. Wenn es schlechte Laune hat, hat es keine Lust. Nachdem dein Dolphy an einem Rennen teilgenommen hat, ist es müde und kann erst am nächsten Tag wieder für ein Rennen an den Start gehen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Centro Dolphy è la zona dove puoi comunicare con il tuo Dolphy, conoscere il suo umore e visualizzare le sue statistiche.\n\nSe è di buon umore, sarà felice di partecipare ad una Gara di Dolphy. Se è di cattivo umore, non lo farà. Dopo aver partecipato a una gara, il tuo Dolphy sarà stanco e non potrà partecipare fino al giorno dopo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Centro Dolphy es el lugar en el que puedes comunicarte con tu Dolphy y ver de qué humor está y qué características tiene.\n\nSi está de buen humor, participará encantado en la carrera; si está de mal humor, no lo hará. Después de participar en una carrera, el Dolphy estará cansado y no podrá volver a disputar otra hasta el día siguiente. \n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィーセンターは、ドルフィーとのコミュニケーションの場。ドルフィーの機嫌や能力が表示されます。\n\n機嫌が良いと、ドルフィーレースでの活躍が期待できますが、機嫌が悪いとレースへ参加してくれません。また、レースに参加したドルフィーは疲労のため、翌日までレースに参加できません。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Dolphy Center is where you can communicate with your Dolphy and see their mood and stats.\n\nIf they are in a good mood, they'll be happy to participate at the Dolphy Race. If they are in a bad mood, they won't. After your Dolphy participates in a race, they'll be tired and unable to race until the next day.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Digital fish are a Dolphy's favourite food. Use the "Dolphy Feeder" to periodically feed them. You can choose from 3 different types of digital fish to feed your Dolphy.\n\n-Speed fish: Increases swimming speed\n-Stamina fish: Increases stamina\n-Agility fish: Increase ability to swim through rings\n\nYour Dolphy's stats will increase each day according to the fish you feed it.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Dolphy adore manger du poisson numérique. Nourris-le régulièrement à l'aide de la "Mangeoire Dolphy". Tu as le choix entre 3 sortes de poissons numériques pour alimenter ton Dolphy.\n\n- Poisson de vitesse : accélère la vitesse de nage\n- Poisson d'endurance : améliore l'endurance\n- Poisson d'agilité :augmente la capacité du Dolphy à nager à travers les anneaux\n\nLes statistiques de ton Dolphy s'améliorent chaque jour en fonction du poisson que tu lui donnes à manger.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Am liebsten fressen Dolphys digitale Fische. Verwende den „Dolphy-Fütterer“, um sie regelmäßig zu füttern. Du kannst aus 3 verschiedenen digitalen Fischarten auswählen, um dein Dolphy zu füttern.\n\n- Tempofische: Erhöhen die Schwimmgeschwindigkeit.\n- Ausdauerfische: Erhöhen die Ausdauer.\n- Agilitätsfische: Verbessern die Fähigkeit, durch Ringe zu schwimmen.\n\nDie Werte deines Dolphys verbessern sich jeden Tag, abhängig von der Fischart, mit der es gefüttert wird.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il pesce digitale è il cibo preferito dai Dolphy. Usa "l'Alimentatore Dolphy" per nutrirli periodicamente. Puoi scegliere fra 3 diversi tipi di pesce digitale da dare al tuo Dolphy.\n\n- Pesce veloce: aumenta la velocità\n- Pesce resistenza: aumenta la resistenza\n- Pesce agile: aumenta l'abilità per nuotare tra gli anelli\n\nLe statistiche del tuo Dolphy aumenteranno ogni giorno a seconda del pesce con cui lo nutri.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los peces digitales son la comida favorita de los Dolphies. Usa el "alimentador de Dolphies" para darle de comer regularmente. Puedes elegir entre 3 tipos de peces digitales:\n\n-Velocipez: Incrementa la velocidad de natación\n-Resistepez: Incrementa la resistencia\n-Agilipez: Incrementa la habilidad de nadar atravesando anillas\n\nLas características de tu Dolphy mejorarán cada día según con qué peces lo alimentes.\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィーたちは「デジタルフィッシュ」が大好物。「ドルフィーフィーダー」という装置によって、定期的に与えられます。次の３種類のデジタルフィッシュが用意されていますので、好みに応じてドルフィーフィーダーからセットしてみましょう。\n\n・スピードフィッシュ…泳ぐ速度が向上します。\n・スタミナフィッシュ…持久力が向上します。\n・シャープフィッシュ…障害物（リング）を上手くクリアできるようになります。\n\n１日毎に、セットされているデジタルフィッシュに応じた能力が向上していきます。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Digital fish are a Dolphy's favorite food. Use the "Dolphy Feeder" to periodically feed them. You can choose from 3 different types of digital fish to feed your Dolphy.\n\n-Speed fish: Increases swimming speed\n-Stamina fish: Increases stamina\n-Agility fish: Increase ability to swim through rings\n\nYour Dolphy's stats will increase each day according to the fish you feed it.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There are rings set around the Dolphy Room and 2 courses you can play through; a "Test Course" and "Ring Game".\n\nThe "Test Course" is a timed, single-lap course that you can use to practice and check out your Dolphy's growth.\n\nIn the "Ring Game" you ride your Dolphy as it swims through the course. As you pass through rings, you'll need to press a button. Time it well to get a high score and make your Dolphy happy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tu verras dans le Dolphydrome des anneaux et 2 parcours de jeu : le Parcours d'essai et le Jeu des anneaux.\n\nLe Parcours d'essai est une course chronométrée d''un tour. Il te permet d'entraîner ton Dolphy et d'observer son évolution.\n\nDans le Jeu des anneaux, tu "pilotes" ton Dolphy. Après chaque anneau passé, tu dois appuyer sur une touche. Appuie au bon moment pour faire un bon score. Ton Dolphy sera content.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Um den Dolphy-Raum herum sind Ringe aufgebaut. Es gibt 2 Strecken, die du spielen kannst: Eine „Teststrecke“ und ein „Ringspiel“.\n\nDie „Teststrecke“ ist ein Zeitrennen mit einer einzigen Runde, die du verwenden kannst um zu üben und die Entwicklung deines Dolphys zu überprüfen.\n\nIm „Ringspiel“ reitest du auf deinem Dolphy, während es über die Strecke schwimmt. Wenn du durch Ringe schwimmst, musst du eine Taste drücken. Achte auf das richtige Timing, um viele Punkte zu erhalten und dein Dolphy glücklich zu machen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nella Stanza di Dolphy ci sono degli anelli e 2 circuiti sui cui puoi cimentarti: un "Circuito di prova" e un "Gioco degli anelli".\n\nIl "Circuito di prova" è una gara a tempo sulla distanza di un giro, che puoi usare per fare pratica e controllare la crescita del tuo Dolphy.\n\nNel "Gioco degli anelli" devi guidare il tuo Dolphy lungo un circuito. Ogni volta che attraversi un anello, devi premere un tasto. Scegli bene il tempo per ottenere un punteggio maggiore e rendere felice il tuo Dolphy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hay anillas alrededor del Cuarto de Dolphy y 2 circuitos por los que puedes jugar: un "Circuito de prueba" y un "Juego de anillas".\n\nEl circuito de prueba es un recorrido de una sola vuelta y cronometrado, que puedes utilizar para practicar y ver cómo mejora tu Dolphy.\n\nEn el juego de anillas tú conducirás al Dolphy mientras nada por el circuito. Al pasar por las anillas tendrás que pulsar un botón; si lo haces en el momento adecuado, obtendrás una puntuación más alta y harás feliz a tu Dolphy.\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">育成ルームにはリングがたくさん設置されておりリングでできたコースを使って「テストコース」と「リングゲーム」の２種類が楽しめます。\n\n「テストコース」では一周するまでのタイムを計ることができます。本番のレースに備え、成長を確かめるには最適です。\n\n「リングゲーム」ではドルフィーに乗って一緒にコースを回ることができます。リングをくぐる時に、タイミング良くボタンを押すことで高得点が得られます。高得点を取ると、ドルフィーの機嫌も良くなりますので頑張りましょう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">There are rings set around the Dolphy Room and 2 courses you can play through; a "Test Course" and "Ring Game".\n\nThe "Test Course" is a timed, single-lap course that you can use to practice and check out your Dolphy's growth.\n\nIn the "Ring Game" you ride your Dolphy as it swims through the course. As you pass through rings, you'll need to press a button. Time it well to get a high score and make your Dolphy happy.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dolphy races are held at "Hudson Gate". Once you raise your Dolphy into an adult, they can participate in races.\n\nOnce your Dolphy becomes an adult, "Register for a race" will become available from the Dolphy Centre menu. After you register for a race, go to the Dolphy Race Disk at Hudson Gate.\n\nIf there are too many entries for a single race, participants will be randomly decided. Also, entries will become invalid after a certain period of time. If this happens, go back to the Dolphy Centre and register for a race again.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les courses de Dolphies ont lieu à l'Arche d'Hudson. Tout Dolphy adulte peut y participer.\n\nUne fois ton Dolphy adulte, l'option "Participer à une course" apparaît dans le menu du Centre Dolphy. Après avoir inscrit ton Dolphy, dirige-toi vers la Zone de course Dolphy de l'Arche d'Hudson.\n\nSi une course compte trop d'inscrits, les participants sont tirés au sort. Les demandes de participation sont annulées au bout d'un certain temps. Si ton Dolphy n'est pas retenu, reviens au Centre Dolphy et inscris-le à une autre course.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dolphy-Rennen finden beim „Hudson-Tor“ statt. Sobald dein Dolphy erwachsen ist, kann es an Rennen teilnehmen.\n\nSobald dein Dolphy erwachsen ist, ist im Menü der Dolphy-Zentrale die Option „Für ein Rennen anmelden“ verfügbar. Gehe zur Dolphy-Rennscheibe beim Hudson-Tor, nachdem du dich für ein Rennen angemeldet hast.\n\nWenn sich zu viele Teilnehmer für ein Rennen angemeldet haben, entscheidet der Zufall, wer teilnimmt. Außerdem werden die Anmeldungen nach einer bestimmten Zeit ungültig. Gehe in diesem Fall zur Dolphy-Zentrale zurück und melde dich erneut für ein Rennen an.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le gare di Dolphy si tengono a "Hudson Gate". Quando il tuo Dolphy diventa adulto, potrà partecipare alle gare.\n\nUna volta che il tuo Dolphy è adulto, nel menu del Centro Dolphy diventerà attiva l'opzione "Iscriviti alla gara". Dopo esserti iscritto alla gara, vai sulla Zona di gara di Dolphy a Hudson Gate.\n\nSe ci sono troppe iscrizioni per una singola gara, i partecipanti verranno scelti casualmente. Inoltre le iscrizioni scadranno dopo un certo periodo di tempo. Se succede, torna al Centro Dolphy e iscriviti nuovamente a una gara.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las carreras de Dolphies se celebran en "Hudson Gate". En cuanto tu Dolphy llegue a la edad adulta podrá participar en las carreras.\n\nCuando el Dolphy se convierta en adulto podrás seleccionar “Inscribirse en una carrera” en el menú del Centro Dolphy. Después de inscribirte, ve a la pista de carreras de Hudson Gate.\n\nSi hay demasiados candidatos apuntados a una carrera, las plazas se asignarán por sorteo. Además, las inscripciones quedarán invalidadas al cabo de un cierto tiempo. Si tu inscripción queda invalidada, vuelve al Centro Dolphy e inscríbete de nuevo.\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「ハドソンゲート」ではドルフィー達のレースが開催されており、成体まで育てたドルフィーをこのレースに参加させることができます。\n\nドルフィーが成体になると、ドルフィーセンターのメニューから、「ドルフィーレース参加予約」が選択できるようになります。エントリー予約後は、ハドソンゲートにあるドルフィーレースプレートに行ってみましょう。\n\nただし、エントリー予約が多い場合は抽選となりますので、ご注意ください。また、エントリー予約は一定時間で消えてしまいます。その場合は、このルームに戻ってきて再度エントリーして下さい。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dolphy races are held at "Hudson Gate". Once you raise your Dolphy into an adult, they can participate in races.\n\nOnce your Dolphy becomes an adult, "Register for a race" will become available from the Dolphy Center menu. After you register for a race, go to the Dolphy Race Disk at Hudson Gate.\n\nIf there are too many entries for a single race, participants will be randomly decided. Also, entries will become invalid after a certain period of time. If this happens, go back to the Dolphy Center and register for a race again.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use "Customise Dolphy" to customise the colour/design, hat, and bubble effect for your Dolphy. Have fun and customise them as you like.\n\nYou'll earn new customisable items as you raise your Dolphy and compete in races.\n\nIf you buy a "Dolphy Cushion" from the store, a "Special Design" for your Dolphy will become available.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Dans "Personnaliser Dolphy", tu personnalises la couleur, le look, le chapeau et l'effet bulle de ton Dolphy. Amuse-toi bien et personnalise ton Dolphy à ton goût.\n\nTu gagneras des éléments personnalisables en élevant ton Dolphy et en le faisant participer à des courses.\n\nAchète un "Coussin Dolphy" à la boutique et tu recevras un "look spécial" pour ton Dolphy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verwende die Option „Dolphy anpassen“, um Farbe/Design, Hut und Blaseneffekt für dein Dolphy anzupassen. Viel Spaß beim Experimentieren!\n\nIndem du dein Dolphy großziehst und mit ihm bei Rennen antrittst, erhältst du neue anpassbare Gegenstände.\n\nWenn du im Geschäft ein „Dolphy-Kissen“ kaufst, wird ein „Spezialdesign“ für dein Dolphy verfügbar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usa l'opzione "Personalizza Dolphy" per personalizzare il colore, lo stile, il cappello e l'effetto-bolle del tuo Dolphy. Divertiti a personalizzarlo come più ti piace.\n\nMano a mano che il tuo Dolphy cresce e partecipa alle gare, otterrai nuovi oggetti per personalizzarlo.\n\nSe compri un "Cuscino Dolphy" dal negozio, si attiverà l'opzione "Design speciale" per il tuo Dolphy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Usa "Personalizar Dolphy" para modificar el color/diseño, sombrero y efecto de burbuja de tu Dolphy. Pásatelo bien y personalízalo como quieras.\n\nObtendrás nuevos objetos personalizables a medida que críes Dolphies y participes en carreras.\n\nSi compras un "Cojín Dolphy" en la tienda, se desbloqueará un "diseño especial" para tu Dolphy.\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィーカスタマイズでは、ドルフィーの色や柄、帽子、泡のエフェクトを変更できます。自分好みのドルフィーに見た目を変えてみましょう。\n\nこれらのドルフィー用アイテムはドルフィーが成長したり、レースに出ることで増えていきます。\n\nなお、ストアで販売中の「ドルフィークッション」を購入すると「スペシャルな柄」が追加されますのでチェックしてみてください。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Use "Customize Dolphy" to customize the color/design, hat, and bubble effect for your Dolphy. Have fun and customize them as you like.\n\nYou'll earn new customizable items as you raise your Dolphy and compete in races.\n\nIf you buy a "Dolphy Cushion" from the store, a "Special Design" for your Dolphy will become available.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">guide_legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFT][RIGHT]Switch page [CIRCLE]Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFT][RIGHT]Changer de page [CIRCLE]Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFT][RIGHT]Seite wechseln [CIRCLE]Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFT][RIGHT]Cambia pagina [CIRCLE]Abbandona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFT][RIGHT]Cambiar de página [CIRCLE]Salir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[LEFT] [RIGHT]ページ切り替え [CIRCLE]終了</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[LEFT][RIGHT]Switch page [CIRCLE]Quit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">welcome_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to the Dolphy Room</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue au Dolphydrome</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen im Dolphy-Raum</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuto nella Stanza di Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido/a al Cuarto de Dolphy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィー育成ルームへようこそ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome to the Dolphy Room</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">welcome_none</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">No news.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pas de nouvelles.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Keine Neuigkeiten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nessuna notizia.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No hay noticias.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">新しいニュースはありません。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">No news.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">welcome_news</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Dolphy Room 2010/4/17更新版です</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">welcome_dolphy_up</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB"> is growing well.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR"> grandit bien.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE"> wächst gut.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT"> sta crescendo bene.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES"> está creciendo bien.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">は順調に成長しています。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US"> is growing well.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">welcome_dolphy_noup</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB"> is fully grown.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR"> a atteint sa taille maximale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE"> ist ausgewachsen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT"> è cresciuto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES"> ha llegado al tamaño máximo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">はすっかり成長しています。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US"> is fully grown.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">welcome_dolphy_nofeed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB"> is hungry.\nGo and use the Digital Feeder.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR"> a faim.\nUtilise la Mangeoire numérique.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE"> hat Hunger.\nVerwende den digitalen Fütterer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT"> è affamato.\nUtilizza l'Alimentatore digitale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES"> tiene hambre.\nVe y usa el dispositivo alimentador digital.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">は空腹のようです。\nドルフィーフィーダーを設定しましょう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US"> is hungry.\nGo and use the Digital Feeder.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">welcome_dolphy_adult</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB"> has become an adult.\nIt can now participate in Dolphy races.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR"> a atteint l'âge adulte.\nLes courses de Dolphies lui sont désormais ouvertes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE"> ist erwachsen geworden.\nDas Dolphy kann jetzt an Rennen teilnehmen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT"> è diventato adulto.\nOra può partecipare alle Gare di Dolphy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES"> ha llegado a la edad adulta.\nAhora puede participar en carreras.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">は成体になりました。\nドルフィーレースに参加できるようになりました。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US"> has become an adult.\nIt can now participate in Dolphy races.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">welcome_dolphy_parent</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB"> has become fully grown.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR"> a atteint sa taille maximale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE"> ist voll ausgewachsen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT"> è diventato adulto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES"> ha llegado al tamaño máximo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">はすっかり成長しました。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US"> has become fully grown.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">welcome_dolphy_child</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB"> has grown fully and became a parent.\nYou can now take care of a new child Dolphy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR"> a atteint sa taille maximale et a fondé une famille.\nTu peux t'occuper d'un nouveau bébé Dolphy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE"> ist voll ausgewachsen und hat Nachwuchs bekommen.\nDu kannst dich ab sofort um ein neues Dolphy-Junges kümmern.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT"> è diventato adulto ed è genitore.\nOra puoi prenderti cura di un nuovo, piccolo Dolphy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES"> ha llegado al tamaño máximo y ha tenido una cría.\nAhora puedes cuidar de una nueva cría de Dolphy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">はすっかり成長し親になりました。\n新しく子ドルフィーを飼えるようになりました。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US"> has grown fully and became a parent.\nYou can now take care of a new child Dolphy.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">welcome_dolphy_maxspeed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB"> has already reached maximum "Speed".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR"> a déjà atteint la "Vitesse" maximum.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE"> hat bereits das maximale „Tempot" erreicht.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT"> ha già raggiunto la massima "Velocità".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES"> ya ha alcanzado la "Velocidad" máxima.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">は、これ以上「Speed」が上がらないようです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US"> has already reached maximum "Speed".</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">welcome_dolphy_maxstamina</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB"> has already reached maximum "Stamina".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR"> a déjà atteint l' "Endurance" maximum.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE"> hat bereits die maximale „Ausdauer" erreicht.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT"> ha già raggiunto la massima "Resistenza".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES"> ya ha alcanzado la "Resistencia" máxima.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">は、これ以上「Stamina」が上がらないようです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US"> has already reached maximum "Stamina".</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">welcome_dolphy_maxsharp</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB"> has already reached maximum "Agility".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR"> a déjà atteint l' "Agilité" maximum.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE"> hat bereits die maximale „Agilität" erreicht.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT"> ha già raggiunto la massima "Agilità".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES"> ya ha alcanzado la "Agilidad" máxima.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">は、これ以上「Sharp」が上がらないようです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US"> has already reached maximum "Agility".</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">welcome_update_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A new notice has arrived!\nView the "Dolphy Breeding Guide" near the entrance for details.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une nouvelle info est arrivée !\nConsulte le "Guide d'élevage de Dolphy" près \nde l'entrée pour en savoir davantage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine neue Mitteilung ist eingetroffen!\nWeitere Informationen findest du in der \n"Dolphy-Zucht"-Anleitung am Eingang.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">C'è un nuovo avviso!\nConsulta la "Guida all'allevamento di un Dolphy" \nvicino all'ingresso per conoscere tutti i dettagli.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Ha llegado un nuevo aviso!\nConsulta la "Guía de cría de Dolphy" junto \na la entrada para obtener más detalles.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">お知らせがあります!\n入り口そばの「ドルフィー育成ガイド」をご覧ください。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A new notice has arrived!\nView the "Dolphy Breeding Guide" near the entrance for details.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>