<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Luxury Glass House</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Maison de verre luxueuse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Luxuriöses Glashaus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Casa di vetro super lusso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Invernadero de lujo</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A marvel of modern architecture, this waterside property boasts an open, airy layout and an expansive view of the bayfront city's dazzling skyline. Retreat from the busyness of the business district in this posh and plush property and live the luxurious life of the PlayStation®Home elite. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Merveille d'architecture moderne, cette propriété au bord de l'eau offre un cadre vie ouvert et une vue à couper le souffle sur la baie permettant d'observer la ville au loin. Offrez-vous une pause loin de l'agitation du monde des affaires dans cette propriété chic et chère et vivez la vie de palace de l'élite PlayStation®Home. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Wunderwerk der modernen Architektur. Dieses Anwesen am Wasser trumpft mit einem offenen und luftigen Grundriss und einer großzügigen Aussicht auf die bezaubernde Skyline der Stadt an der Küste auf. Ziehe dich aus der Hektik des Geschäftsviertels zurück in dieses noble und vornehme Anwesen und genieße das luxuriöse Leben der PlayStation®Home-Elite. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un gioiello di architettura moderna: questa proprietà affacciata sul litorale vanta una struttura aperta e ariosa e un'ampia vista sulla baia di fronte, con il meraviglioso profilo della città. Fuggi dalla frenesia della zona commerciale e rifugiati in questa sontuosa ed elegante proprietà: vivi la lussuosa vita dell'élite di PlayStation®Home. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Maravilla de la arquitectura moderna, esta propiedad junto al agua presume de una disposición abierta y espaciosa, y disfruta de una amplia vista de la deslumbrante silueta de la ciudad sobre la bahía. Escapa de la ajetreada vida del distrito empresarial y refúgiate en este remanso de paz y buen gusto para vivir la suntuosa vida de la élite de PlayStation®Home. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>