<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Junk Guy Ladies Xmas Boots</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Junk Guy Noël bottes (femelle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Junk Guy Christmas Stiefel (weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Junk Guy natale stivali (femmina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Junk Guy navidad botas (hembra)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Junk Guy Ladies Xmas Boots</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Junk Guy Ladies Xmas Boots</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Metallic red and snowflakes add a Christmas touch to these fashion-forward ladies boots from the Junk Guy. Paired with the Xmas shorts, 2-ball hat and Ladies Xmas top (sold seperately), these boots are sure to add an attractive edge to your holiday spirit. \n \n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Métallique rouge et flocons de neige ajoutent une touche de Noël pour ces dames avant-gardistes bottes de Junk Guy. Jumelé avec le short de Noël, 2-ball chapeau et Mesdames Xmas top (vendu séparément), ces bottes sont sûrs d'ajouter un certain attrait énervé à votre look de vacances. \n \n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Metallic rot und Schneeflocken fügen Sie einen Hauch Weihnachten diesen fashion-forward Damen Stiefel vom Junk Guy. Gepaart mit der Weihnachts-Shorts, 2-Ball Damen Hut und Weihnachten top (separat erhältlich), sind diese Stiefel sicher, eine bestimmte edgy Appell an Ihren Urlaub Look. \n \n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Metallizzato rosso e fiocchi di neve aggiungono un tocco di Natale per queste signore stivali moda-forward dal Junk Guy. Accoppiato con il pantaloncini Xmas, 2-ball cappello e signore Xmas top (venduto separatamente), questi stivali sono sicuro di aggiungere un certo fascino spigoloso al tuo look vacanza. \n \n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Rojo y copos de nieve metálicos añaden un toque navideño a estas señoras de moda dirigida a las botas del Junk Guy. Junto con los cortos de Navidad, 2-ball sombrero y señoras Xmas superior (se vende por separado), estas botas están seguros de añadir un cierto atractivo vanguardista a tu look de fiesta. \n \n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Metallic red and snowflakes add a Christmas touch to these fashion-forward ladies boots from the Junk Guy. Paired with the Xmas shorts, 2-ball hat and Ladies Xmas top (sold seperately), these boots are sure to add an attractive edge to your holiday spirit. \n \n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Metallic red and snowflakes add a Christmas touch to these fashion-forward ladies boots from the Junk Guy. Paired with the Xmas shorts, 2-ball hat and Ladies Xmas top (sold seperately), these boots are sure to add an attractive edge to your holiday spirit. \n \n [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>