<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Torso Trinkets Bundle (female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bibelots Torse Ensemble (femelle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Torso Schmuckstücken Bündel (weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gingillo Torso Raccolta (femmina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Baratijas Torso Paquete (femenino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Torso Trinkets Bundle (female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Discover the power of Torso Trinkets and discover a whole new you.  With Fuzzy Dice, the Bosom Box, and the Torso Ticker you're bound to say something.  Torso Trinkets aren't just the next great thing, they are the thing after that, too.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Découvrez la puissance des bibelots torse et découvrez une toute nouvelle vous. Avec les Dés Laineux, la Poitrine-Boîte, et le Torse Téléscripteur vous êtes obligé de dire quelque chose. Bibelots Torse ne sont pas simplement la chose suivante grands, ils sont la chose après cela, aussi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Entdecken Sie die Kraft der Torso Tand und entdecken Sie eine ganz neue. Mit Wuschelig Würfel, den Busen-Box, und der Torso Ticker sind sie verpflichtet, etwas zu sagen. Torso Schmuckstücken sind nicht nur das nächste große ding, sie sind das, was danach auch. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scopri il potere della Trinkets Torso e scoprire un intero nuovo voi. Con Sfocato Dadi, il Box Seno, e il Ticker Torso sei destinato a dire qualcosa. Torso Telescrivente non sono solo la prossima cosa grande, sono la cosa dopo che, anche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Descubre el poder de baratijas torso y descubre que en su conjunto nuevo. Con Dados Borrosos, Caja de Pecho, y la Pizarra del Torso que está obligado a decir algo. Baratijas Torso no son sólo la gran cosa al lado, que es lo que después, también. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Discover the power of Torso Trinkets and discover a whole new you.  With Fuzzy Dice, the Bosom Box, and the Torso Ticker you're bound to say something.  Torso Trinkets aren't just the next great thing, they are the thing after that, too.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>