<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Earth</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Terre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Terra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tierra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">地球</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Earth</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fact: Space is cool. Now LOOT™’s brought all the planets to you so you can create the solar system in your personal space. Who doesn’t love Venus with all its carbon dioxide? Don’t even get me started on the gas giant Jupiter. Sorry, Pluto, you’re no longer in the club. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C' est un fait : l'espace, c' est trop cool. Et voilà, LOOT™ vous présente toutes les planètes pour que vous puissiez créer le système solaire dans votre espace personnel. Qui n'aime pas Vénus et tout son dioxyde de carbone ? Et ne parlons pas de la géante gazeuse Jupiter. Pardon Pluton, tu ne fais plus partie du club. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tatsache: Das Weltall ist cool. LOOT™ bringt dir nun alle Planeten, damit du dir dein eigenes Sonnensystem zusammenstellen kannst. Wer mag nicht Venus mit all ihrem Kohlendioxid? Oder gar den Gasgiganten Jupiter. Sorry Pluto, du bist leider nicht mehr dabei. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Informazioni: lo spazio è un luogo fighissimo. LOOT™ ti offre la possibilità di creare il tuo personalissimo sistema solare! Chi non ama Venere e la sua anidride carbonica? Mi dispiace, Plutone, non fai più parte del club. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dato: el espacio exterior es alucinante. Y ahora, LOOT™ pone en tus manos todos los planetas para que puedas crear el sistema solar en tu propio espacio personal. ¿A quién no le gusta Venus, con todo su dióxido de carbono? Y eso por no hablar del gigante del gas, Júpiter. Lo siento, Plutón, tú ya no estás en el club. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ちょっとしたお知らせ：「宇宙」はイケてる。LOOT™の全惑星を集めて自分のパーソナル・スペースでも太陽系を造ろう。二酸化炭素だらけの金星や、ガス惑星の王である木星など、どれだって大人気！悪いけど、冥王星はもう仲間外れだ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fact: Space is cool. Now LOOT™’s brought all the planets to you so you can create the solar system in your personal space. Who doesn’t love Venus with all its carbon dioxide? Don’t even get me started on the gas giant Jupiter. Sorry, Pluto, you’re no longer in the club. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>