<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Demon Cutter Yorimitsu Sword (For Large Clothes, Men)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Sabre pourfendeur de démons Yorimitsu (vêtements amples, homme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Dämonenschlitzer Yorimitsu (für weite Kleidung, für Männer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Spada trancia-demoni Yorimitsu (per vestiti larghi, da uomo)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Espada cortademonios Yorimitsu (para ropa voluminosa, hombre)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">鬼斬り頼光の刀（大型衣装用・男性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Demon Cutter Yorimitsu Sword (For Large Clothes, Men)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Sword infused with demon-cutting power.\nAttacking Strength: ★★★-\nDemon Attacking Strength: ★★★★-\n\n* When wearing clothes with volume, it can overlap with clothes, so this type is made looser around waist for easy pairing.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Sabre recelant un pouvoir pourfendeur de démons.\nPuissance d'attaque : ★★★-\nPuissance d'attaque de démons : ★★★★-\n\n*Quand vous portez des vêtements amples, il peut dépasser des vêtements. Ce modèle est moins serré autour de la taille pour un meilleur rendu.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Schwert, das die Kraft besitzt, einen Dämonen aufzuschlitzen.\nAngriff: ★★★-\nDämonenangriff: ★★★★-\n\n* Dieses sitzt lockerer um die Hüfte, damit es einfacher mit weiter Kleidung zu tragen ist und sie nicht überdeckt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Spada intrisa di un potere che permette di tranciare i demoni.\nAttacco: ★★★-\nPotere anti-demoniaco: ★★★★-\n\n* Poiché può accadere che la spada rimanga impigliata tra il panneggio di abiti voluminosi, questo modello è stato realizzato in modo tale che cada più largo attorno alla vita, per facilitare l'estrazione.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Espada que encierra el poder de cortar a los demonios.\nAtaque: ★★★-\nAtaque demoníaco: ★★★★-\n\n* La espada podría solaparse al usar ropa voluminosa, así que este modelo se lleva más suelto para un mejor ajuste.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">鬼を斬る力を秘めた刀。\n攻撃力：　★★★-\n対鬼攻撃力：　★★★★-\n\n※ボリュームのある服だと服にめり込んでしまうため、腰から少し離して合わせやすくしたタイプです。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Sword infused with demon-cutting power.\nAttacking Strength: ★★★-\nDemon Attacking Strength: ★★★★-\n\n* When wearing clothes with volume, it can overlap with clothes, so this type is made looser around waist for easy pairing.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
