<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This payment entitles you to set up a Club. At the moment there is no ongoing charge for running a Club but, in the future, we will introduce a fee (to be determined), which will be due every 30 days. Before introducing a recurring fee, we will give you not less than 90 days prior notice. If you do not wish to pay the fee at any time, you do not have to, but you will lose your entitlement to run the Club and we may delete your Club entirely. As the person who set up the Club, you will be the Club Leader. As Leader, you can invite up to 31 other users to join your Club, and appoint up to four of them as sub-leaders. You can only lead one club at a time. However, you can join up to five clubs (leading one, and joining four others). You cannot transfer leadership of your Club to anyone else. If you wish to disband your Club at any time, you may do so by following the instructions in the PlayStation®Home Manual. Once a Club is set up its name cannot be changed and, if you disband your Club, you will not be able to reuse its name. Please see the PlayStation®Home Manual for more information pertaining to Clubs and Club membership.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce paiement vous permet de créer un Club. La gestion des Clubs est pour l'instant gratuite, mais nous mettrons prochainement en place une formule mensuelle payante, d'un montant à déterminer. Vous serez prévenu au moins 90 jours avant l'application de cette formule. Si vous décidez de ne plus payer, vous ne pourrez plus gérer votre Club et nous nous réservons le droit de le supprimer complètement. En tant que créateur du Club, vous en assumez la gestion. En votre qualité de leader, vous pouvez inviter au maximum 31 utilisateurs dans votre Club et, parmi eux, désigner jusqu'à quatre sous-leaders. Vous ne pouvez gérer qu'un Club à la fois. Vous pouvez rejoindre jusqu'à cinq Clubs (en gérez un et en rejoindre 4 autres). Vous ne pouvez pas transférer la gestion de votre Club. Pour démanteler votre Club, conformez-vous aux instructions du manuel PlayStation®Home. Une fois que vous avez créé un Club, vous ne pouvez plus en modifier le nom. Si vous démantelez votre Club, vous ne pourrez plus réutiliser son nom. Consultez le manuel PlayStation®Home pour en savoir plus sur l'adhésion et l'appartenance aux Clubs. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese Zahlung berechtigt Sie, einen Club zu gründen. Zurzeit ist das Betreiben eines Clubs kostenlos. In Zukunft wird jedoch eine noch nicht festgesetzte Gebühr erhoben, die alle 30 Tage fällig wird. Bevor wir eine wiederkehrende Gebühr erheben, werden Sie mindestens 90 Tage vorher benachrichtigt. Wenn Sie die Gebühr nicht bezahlen möchten, müssen Sie das nicht tun, Sie verlieren dann jedoch die Berechtigung, den Club zu betreiben, und der Club wird möglicherweise von uns geschlossen. Der Gründer des Clubs wird zum Leiter des Clubs. Als Leiter können Sie bis zu 31 Personen in den Club einladen und bis zu vier stellvertretende Leiter benennen. Sie können jeweils nur einen Club leiten, aber bis zu fünf Clubs beitreten (einen leiten und vier weiteren beitreten). Die Leitung des Clubs kann nicht übertragen werden. Folgen Sie den Anweisungen des PlayStation®Home-Handbuchs, falls Sie den Club auflösen möchten. Sobald ein Club gegründet wurde, kann der Name nicht mehr geändert werden. Wenn Sie Ihren Club aufgelöst haben, können Sie den Clubnamen nicht erneut verwenden. Weitere Informationen zu Clubs sowie der Clubmitgliedschaft finden Sie im PlayStation®Home-Handbuch.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo pagamento ti dà diritto a creare un Club. Al momento la gestione di un Club non ha costi periodici, ma in futuro sarà soggetta al pagamento di una quota mensile ancora da determinarsi. L'applicazione di un canone mensile, tuttavia, avverrà con un preavviso minimo di 90 giorni. Puoi anche decidere di non versare la somma, ma ciò ti precluderà il diritto a gestire il tuo Club, il quale potrebbe venire cancellato. In qualità di creatore del Club ne sarai il Leader e, come tale, potrai invitare fino a 31 utenti a diventarne membri e nominare fino a quattro di loro come vice leader. Non puoi essere il leader di più club contemporaneamente, ma puoi essere membro di cinque club in totale (come leader di uno di questi e membro di altri quattro). Non ti è possibile trasferire la leadership del tuo Club ad altri. Puoi sciogliere il tuo Club in qualsiasi momento seguendo le istruzioni contenute nel manuale di PlayStation®Home. Una volta creato un Club non puoi cambiarne il nome e non puoi riutilizzare il nome di un Club che è stato sciolto. Consulta il manuale di PlayStation®Home per maggiori informazioni sui Club e sull'adesione ai Club. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este pago te da derecho a crear un club. En estos momentos, disponer de un club es gratuito, pero en el futuro se aplicará una tarifa periódica (aún por determinar) que deberá abonarse cada 30 días. Antes de introducirla, te avisaremos con una antelación no inferior a 90 días. Si en cualquier momento decides ignorar la tarifa, podrás hacerlo, pero perderás el derecho a dirigir el club y puede que este se elimine para siempre. La persona que crea un club, se convierte en líder del mismo. Como líder, podrás invitar a un máximo de 31 usuarios más a unirse a tu club y designar a hasta cuatro de ellos como sublíderes. Solo puedes dirigir un club. No obstante, puedes unirte a un máximo de cinco clubs (uno como líder y los otros cuatro, como miembro). No puedes transferir la dirección de tu club a otra persona. Si quieres deshacer tu club, puedes hacerlo en cualquier momento siguiendo las instrucciones del manual de PlayStation®Home. Una vez hayas creado el club, no podrás cambiarle el nombre y, si decides deshacerlo, no podrás volver a utilizar ese nombre para otro. Consulta el manual de instrucciones de PlayStation®Home para obtener más información acerca de los clubs y de la pertenencia a ellos.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">クラブを購入することで、クラブを作成・運営できるようになります。\nクラブを作成すると、クラブハウス（ベーシック）を利用する事が\nできます。\nまた、別売りのクラブハウスを購入して利用することも可能です。\n\n同時に運営できるクラブは１人１つです。\nクラブを他人に譲渡する事はできません。\nクラブの名前は、既に使用されているクラブ名と同じものは使えません。\nまた、一度設定すると後から変更することはできません。\n\nクラブならびにクラブハウスの詳細については、公式Webサイトまたはヘルプをご参照下さい。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이것을 구매하시면 클럽을 만드실 수 있습니다.\n
클럽을 설립한 사람이 클럽 리더가 되어, 31명의 다른 유저를 클럽으로 초대할 수 있습니다. 그 중 4명까지 서브 리더로 추대할 수 있습니다. 클럽은 한번에 한개씩만 운영이 가능하나 가입은 5개 클럽까지 가능합니다. 클럽 하나를 소유하면 4개의 다른 클럽에 가입하실 수 있습니다. 클럽의 리더쉽은 다른 유저에게 양도할 수 없으며 클럽을 해체하시려면 홈 내의 온라인 매뉴얼을 참고해 주시기 바랍니다. 클럽 이름은 고유하기 때문에, 한번 클럽을 생성하면 클럽명을 바꿀 수 없으며 클럽을 해체할 경우 그 클럽명은 다시 사용하실 수 없습니다.\n
클럽 하우스와 클럽 멤버쉽에 대해서는 홈 내의 온라인 매뉴얼을 참고해 주시기 바랍니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This payment entitles you to set up a Club.\n
As the person who set up the Club, you will be the Club leader. As Leader, you can invite up to 31 other users to join your Club and appoint up to 4 of them as sub-leaders. You can only lead one Club at a time. You can join up to 5 Clubs though so, if you lead one, you can join 4 others. You cannot transfer leadership of your Club to anyone else. If you wish to disband your Club at any time, you can do so following the instructions in the online manual within PlayStation®Home. Club names are unique. Once you set up a Club you cannot change the Club name and, if you disband your Club, you cannot reuse the Club name.\n
Please see the online manual within PlayStation®Home for more information about use of Clubhouses and Club membership. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">本次購買可以讓您建立一個聯盟。\n
建立聯盟的人便是該聯盟的隊長。隊長可以邀請另外31位使用者參加該聯盟，並且可以指派最多4位的副隊長。您一次只能營運一個聯盟。您最多可以同時參加5個聯盟。但如果您已建立1個聯盟，您就只能最多參加另外4個聯盟。您不能轉讓您的聯盟領導權給任何其他人。如果任何時候您想要解散聯盟，您可以依照線上說明內的步驟進行解散。聯盟名稱只能使用一次，一但確定就無法進行更改，而即使在解散聯盟後也不能再度使用同一聯盟名稱。\n
關於聯盟俱樂部以及聯盟成員的詳細內容，請參閱PlayStation®Home內的線上說明。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">本次購買可以讓您建立一個聯盟。\n
建立聯盟的人便是該聯盟的團長。團長可以邀請另外31位使用者參加該聯盟，並且可以指派最多4位的副團長。您一次只能營運一個聯盟。您最多可以同時參加5個聯盟。但如果您已建立1個聯盟，您就只能最多參加另外4個聯盟。您不能轉讓您的聯盟領導權給任何其他人。如果任何時候您想要解散聯盟，您可以依照線上說明內的步驟進行解散。聯盟名稱只能使用一次，一但確定就無法進行更改，而即使在解散聯盟後也不能再度使用同一聯盟名稱。\n
關於聯盟俱樂部以及聯盟成員的詳細內容，請參閱PlayStation®Home內的線上說明。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This payment entitles you to set up a Club. At the moment there is no ongoing charge for running a Club but, in the future, we will introduce a fee (to be determined), which will be due every 30 days. Before introducing a recurring fee, we will give you not less than 90 days prior notice. If you do not wish to pay the fee at any time, you do not have to, but you will lose your entitlement to run the Club and we may delete your Club entirely. As the person who set up the Club, you will be the Club Leader. As Leader, you can invite up to 31 other users to join your Club, and appoint up to four of them as sub-leaders. You can only lead one club at a time. However, you can join up to five clubs (leading one, and joining four others). You cannot transfer leadership of your Club to anyone else. If you wish to disband your Club at any time, you may do so by following the instructions in the PlayStation(R)Home Manual. Once a Club is set up its name cannot be changed and, if you disband your Club, you will not be able to reuse its name. Please see the PlayStation(R)Home Manual for more information pertaining to Clubs and Club membership.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Club</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Club</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Club</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Club</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Club</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">クラブ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">클럽</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Club</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">聯盟</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">聯盟</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Club</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
