<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Slackers Chino Pants - Charcoal (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Pantalon style chino Slackers - Fusain (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Slackers Chinohose - Dunkelgrau (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Slackers Pantaloni Chino - Grigio antracite (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Slackers Pantalones chinos - Color carbón (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A laid-back vibe comes easy to the Slacker chinos. Designed in a slim fit, its retro colorways are shaded in earth greens and browns. Designed in a soft brushed cotton, style points include 5 pockets, a leather logo patch, contrast taping, and embroidered details. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une ambiance décontractée va à merveille au chino Slacker. Coupe étroite, ses couleurs rétro sont nuancées de tons verts et bruns évoquant la terre. Confectionné en coton brossé doux, son style comporte 5 poches, un patch logo en cuir, un surpiquage contrasté et des détails brodés. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Relaxt und cool aussehen - die Slacker Hose im Chinostil macht's einfach. Die Hose aus gebürsteter Baumwolle ist eng geschnitten und in klassischen Erdfarben wie Grün und Braun erhältlich. Mit fünf Taschen, Lederlogoflicken, Kontraststreifen und Stickdetails. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I pantaloni Slacker in stile chino offrono un look casual e rilassato. Questi pantaloni tal taglio aderente presentano tonalità del verde scuro e del marrone. In morbido cotone spazzolato, a completare lo stile sono 5 tasche, toppa in pelle con logo, bordatura a contrasto e dettagli ricamati. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Es fácil lograr un toque distendido con los chinos Slacker. Diseñados con un corte ajustado, presentan unas tonalidades retro matizadas con verde y marrón terrosos. Elaborados en suave algodón peinado, los rasgos de estilo incluyen un diseño de 5 bolsillos, parche de cuero con el logotipo,  cintas en contraste y detalles de bordado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A laid-back vibe comes easy to the Slacker chinos. Designed in a slim fit, its retro colourways are shaded in earth greens and browns. Designed in a soft brushed cotton, style points include 5 pockets, a leather logo patch, contrast taping, and embroidered details. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>