<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Scheme Walkshorts - Military Camo (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Short de randonnée Scheme - Camouflage militaire (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Scheme Wandershorts - Militär-Tarnfarbe (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Scheme Pantaloncini - Verde mimetico (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Scheme Pantalón corto - Camuflaje militar (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Add modern styling to the mix with a touch of the classics. Made with an enzyme stone washing, which gives it a broken-in look and feel. Includes side pockets, flap cargo pockets and a Billabong woven label above the back pocket. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ajoutez du modernisme à votre style avec une touche de classique. Son lavage à la pierre et aux enzymes lui confère un look et un sentiment d'assurance. Avec des poches latérales, des poches plaquées à rabat et une étiquette Billabong tissée au-dessus de la poche arrière. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Modisches Stiling mit einem Hauch von Klassik. Steingewaschen für den leicht abgetragenen Look und bequemen Sitz. Mit Seitentaschen, Pattentaschen und einem gewebten Billabong Logo über der Gesäßtasche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aggiungi lo stile moderno a questo mix con un tocco di classicità. Lo speciale trattamento di lavaggio con pietra pomice crea questo look comodo e dimesso.  Comprende tasche laterali, tasche stile cargo con pattina ed etichetta Billabong in tessuto sulla tasca posteriore. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Añade a la mezcla un estilo moderno con un toque clásico. Fabricado con efecto lavado a la piedra con enzimas, que le da un aspecto y tacto de ya usado. Incluye bolsillos laterales y bolsillos amplios con solapa, así como la etiqueta cosida con el logotipo de Billabong encima del bolsillo trasero. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>