<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Red Poster 2 Anakin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Poster rouge 2 Anakin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rotes Poster 2 Anakin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Poster Rosso 2 Anakin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Póster rojo 2 Anakin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Red Poster 2 Anakin</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Senate is always a busy place, especially during times like this. The corridors are filled with people of importance wandering from hallway to hallway and room to room. Their dealings kept secret behind closed doors, but I have learned that with a watchful eye you can notice things others miss - simply by watching for long enough. Take the great Jedi Anakin Skywalker. He doesn't realize that even with the Force someone like myself can see where he is betrayed by his emotions. It's not difficult. After all, I'm almost certain a poster like this hangs in the private quarters of the Senate somewhere. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Sénat grouille d'activité, surtout par les tmps qui courent. Les couloirs sont remplis de gens importants passant de hall en hall et de salle en salle. Ils cachent leurs agissements derrière des portes closes. Mais j'ai appris qu'avec un œil exercé, on peut voir des choses que les autres ne voient pas : simplement en observant assez longtemps. Prenez le grand Jedi Anakin Skywalker, par exemple. Il ne réalise pas que même avec la Force, quelqu'un comme moi peut voir où ses émotions le trahissent. C'est facile. Après tout, je suis presque certain qu'un poster comme celui-ci est affiché dans les salles privées du Sénat. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Im Senat wird immer viel gearbeitet, besonders in Zeiten wie diesen. Die Korridore sind mit wichtigen Leuten gefüllt, die von Gang zu Gang und Zimmer zu Zimmer gehen. Ihre Geschäfte werden hinter geschlossenen Türen betrieben, aber ich habe erfahren, dass man, wenn man aufpasst, Dinge bemerken kann, die andere übersehen - wenn man nur lange genug zusieht. Zum Beispiel der große Jedi Anakin Skywalker. Ihm ist nicht klar, dass selbst mit der Macht jemand wie ich sehen kann, wenn seine Gefühle ihn verraten. Es ist nicht schwer. Immerhin bin ich fast sicher, dass ein Poster wie dieses irgendwo in den Privatquartieren des Senats hängt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Senato è sempre un luogo affollato, specialmente in tempi come questi. I corridoi sono pieni di persone importanti che vanno di stanza in stanza, di sala in sala. I loro affari vengono mantenuti segreti e avvengono a porte chiuse, ma ho imparato che se hai l'occhio attento e molta pazienza, puoi notare cose che sfuggono ai più. Prendiamo ad esempio il grande Jedi Anakin Skywalker. Egli non si rende conto che, nonostante la Forza, anche uno come me capisce che le sue emozioni lo tradiscono. Non è difficile. Dopotutto, sono quasi sicuro che un poster come questo sia appeso da qualche parte nei quartieri privati del Senato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Senado siempre es un lugar de ajetreo, sobre todo en tiempos como este. Los pasillos están llenos de personas importantes que vagan de ala en ala y de sala en sala. Sus asuntos permanecen en secreto tras las puertas cerradas, pero he aprendido que, si eres observador e inviertes el tiempo suficiente, puedes percibir cosas que otros pasan por alto. Piensa en el gran Jedi Anakin Skywalker. Él no se da cuenta de que, incluso con la Fuerza, alguien como yo puede ver cuándo es traicionado por sus emociones. No es difícil. Al fin y al cabo, estoy casi seguro de que hay un póster como este colgado en las dependencias privadas del Senado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Senate is always a busy place, especially during times like this. The corridors are filled with people of importance wandering from hallway to hallway and room to room. Their dealings kept secret behind closed doors, but I have learned that with a watchful eye you can notice things others miss - simply by watching for long enough. Take the great Jedi Anakin Skywalker. He doesn't realize that  even with the Force someone like myself can see where he is betrayed by his emotions.  It's not difficult. After all, I'm almost certain a poster like this hangs in the  private quarters of the Senate somewhere. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>