<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Red Poster Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble poster rouge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rotes Poster-Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Poster Rosso Pacchetto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Póster rojo Conjunto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Red Poster Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">(Bundle) The explosion was hours ago, yet my children and I were gathered in the corner of our small apartment on Coruscant still. This war had been going for too long, The council seems powerless to stop it, and the Separatists grow stronger by the day. But we can do our part - we know this. We support the war effort by purchasing the Playstation Home Poster Bundle, which supports the Jedi and Clones in their fight. Includes Red Poster 1, 2 and 3. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">(Ensemble) L'explosion s'était produite il y a plusieurs heures, mais mes enfants et moi étions toujours prostrés dans un coin de notre petit appartement sur Coruscant. Cette guerre durait depuis trop longtemps. Le Conseil semblait incapable de l'arrêter. Et les Séparatistes devenaient plus forts de jour en jour. Mais nous avons un rôle à jouer, nous le savons. Nous pouvons soutenir l'effort de guerre en achetant l'ensemble de posters Playstation, ce qui aide les Jedi et les Clones dans leurs efforts. Comprend les posters rouges 1, 2 et 3. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">(Pack) Die Explosion war bereits Stunden her, aber meine Kinder und ich befanden uns immer noch in der Ecke unserer kleinen Wohnung auf Coruscant. Dieser Krieg wütete bereits für zu lange, der Rat scheint nicht in der Lage ihn zu beenden und die Separatisten gewinnen täglich an Macht. Aber wir können unseren Teil beitragen - das wissen wir. Wir unterstützen den Krieg, indem wir das Playstation Home Poster-Pack kaufen, das die Jedi und Klone in ihrem Kampf unterstützt. Beinhaltet Rotes Poster 1, 2 und 3. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">(Pacchetto) L'esplosione era avvenuta ore prima, ma io e i miei bambini eravamo ancora radunati immobili in un angolo del nostro piccolo appartamento su Coruscant. Questa guerra va avanti da troppo tempo. Il consiglio sembra non essere in grado di fermarla, e i Separatisti diventano più forti ogni giorno che passa. Ma noi possiamo fare la nostra parte - e lo sappiamo. Sosteniamo lo sforzo bellico acquistando il Pacchetto di Poster Playstation Home, che aiuta i Jedi e i Cloni nella loro battaglia. Include Poster Rosso 1, 2 e 3. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">(Conjunto) La explosión fue ya hace horas, pero mis hijos y yo continuamos inmóviles en la esquina de nuestro pequeño apartamento en Coruscant. Esta guerra está durando demasiado. El Consejo parece incapaz de detenerla, y los Separatistas se hacen más fuertes cada día. Pero podemos contribuir - lo sabemos. Apoyamos el esfuerzo bélico al comprar el conjunto de pósters de Playstation, que apoya a los Jedi y a los Clones en su lucha. Incluye los pósters rojos 1, 2 y 3. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">(Bundle) The explosion was hours ago, yet my children and I were gathered in the corner of our small apartment on Coruscant still. This war had been going for too long, The council seems powerless to stop it, and the Separatists grow stronger by the day. But we can do our part - we know this. We support the war effort by purchasing the Playstation Home Poster Bundle, which supports the Jedi and Clones in their fight. Includes Red Poster 1, 2 and 3. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>