<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wrangler - Off-White Crew Sweater</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Wrangler — Pull ras-de-cou blanc cassé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wrangler - Pullover mit Rundhalsausschnitt in Offwhite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Wrangler - Maglione a scollo tondo bianco sporco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Wrangler - Suéter de Cuello Redondo Color Hueso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Wrangler - Off-White Crew Sweater (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Wrangler - Off-White Crew Sweater (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Wrangler - Off-White Crew Sweater (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Wrangler - Off-White Crew Sweater (Women)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Ellie sweat top comes in an off white shade with blue striped detail throughout. With ribbing at the crew neckline, cuffs and hemline, this top also features button detail at the right shoulder. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce pull Ellie est proposé dans une teinte banc cassé avec des rayures bleues sur l'ensemble. Avec des côtes au col ras-de-cou, aux poignets et à la taille, ce haut présente également des boutons sur l'épaule gauche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser Ellie-Pullover in einem Offwhite-Ton hat durchweg blau gestreifte Details. Gerippt an Rundhalsausschnitt, Manschetten und Saum. Dieser Pullover hat außerdem Knöpfe an der rechten Schulter. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo maglione stile Ellie ha una colorazione bianco sporco e presenta un design generale a strisce blu. Lavorato a costine nel girocollo tondo, ai polsini e all'orlo, questo top utilizza anche bottoni decorativi sulla spalla destra. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este suéter Ellie en tono blanco hueso a rayas azules en su conjunto, tiene textura elástica en el cuello, puños y bajo, y presenta un adorno con botón en el hombro derecho. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>