<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sodium Robo-Cobra - Zlato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Robot-cobra Sodium - Zlato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sodium-Robo-Kobra - Zlato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Robo-Cobra Sodium - Zlato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sodium Robocobra - Zlato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Sodium　ロボコブラ – Zlato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium 로보-코브라 - 즐라토</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sodium Robo-Cobra - Zlato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sodium機器眼鏡蛇：Zlato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sodium機器眼鏡蛇：Zlato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sodium Robo-Cobra - Zlato</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sodium's top scientists have designed, engineered and manufactured this sleek Robo-Cobra. What's more, you don't have to feed him any mice, because he's robotic! Limited Edition Lockwood item exclusive to E3®![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les meilleurs scientifiques de Sodium ont conçu, élaboré et fabriqué cet élégant Robot-cobra. Le meilleur, c'est qu'il n'y a même pas besoin de lui donner des souris à manger, puisque c'est un robot ! Article Lockwood en édition limitée et exclusif à E3® ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese coole Robo-Kobra wurde von Sodiums besten Wissenschaftlern entworfen und hergestellt. Und das Gute ist, dass du ihn nicht mit Mäusen füttern musst, weil er ein Roboter ist! Limitierter Lockwood-Gegenstand exklusiv für die E3®![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I più eminenti scienziati di Sodium hanno ideato, progettato e realizzato questo sinuoso Robo-Cobra. E non dovrai neanche preoccuparti di dargli da mangiare topolini… è un robot! Oggetto Lockwood in edizione limitata in esclusiva per l'E3®![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los mejores científicos de Sodium han diseñado y fabricado este elegante robocobra. Y lo mejor de todo es que, ¡no tienes que darle ratones para comer porque es un robot! ¡Objeto Lockwood de edición limitada, exclusivo de E3®![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Sodiumのトップエンジニアが設計したロボコブラ。ロボットだから餌いらず！E3限定Lockwoodアイテム。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium 최고의 과학자들이 설계하고 기술 검토를 거쳐 제작한 이 날렵한 로보-코브라. 더 좋은 것은, 이 녀석에게는 생쥐 먹이를 줄 필요가 없다는 거죠, 로봇이니까요! E3® 전용 Lockwood 의 한정판 아이템![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sodium's top scientists have designed, engineered and manufactured this sleek Robo-Cobra. What's more, you don't have to feed him any mice, because he's robotic! Limited Edition Lockwood item exclusive to E3®![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sodium的一流科學家經過苦心設計，終於製造出時髦的機器眼鏡蛇。更厲害的是你用不著餵它老鼠，因為這是機器做的！E3®展獨家限量版Lockwood周邊商品！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sodium的一流科學家經過苦心設計，終於製造出時髦的機器眼鏡蛇。更厲害的是你用不著餵它老鼠，因為這是機器做的！E3®展獨家限量版Lockwood周邊商品！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sodium's top scientists have designed, engineered and manufactured this sleek Robo-Cobra. What's more, you don't have to feed him any mice, because he's robotic! Limited Edition Lockwood item exclusive to E3®![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>