<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Octopoot Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot de Octopoot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Oktopups Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Octopoot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bloque Octopoot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オクトプートセット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Octopoot Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There are too many Octopoots clogging up the ‘intertubes’ of the Interwebz!  They’re slowing down our gameplay! Here at LOOT™, in order to get rid of as many pesky Octopoots as possible, we’ve shoved them into a pretty little bundle: The Octopoot Poster, Male and Female Hoodie, Hat and Skateboard! Out of the interwebz and into your (virtual) hands. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il y a trop d’Octopoots qui bouchent les “intertubes” de l’Interwebz ! Ils ralentissent  notre jouabilité !  Ici à LOOT™, pour éliminer le plus possible de ces agaçants Octopoots, nous les avons fourrés dans un joli petit lot : Le Poster Octopoot, les sweats à capuche, chapeaux et skateboards Homme et Femme ! Plus rien dans l’Interweb mais tout dans vos mains (virtuelles). Nous sommes comme des plombiers…si les plombiers revendaient le magma répugnant qu’ils trouvent dans les tubes….beurk. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es gibt zu viele Oktopupse, die die Interrohre des Internetz' vermüllen. Sie bremsen das Gameplay aus! Um so viele dieser lästigen Oktopupse wie möglich loszuwerden, haben wir von LOOT™ sie zu einem hübschen Bundle geschnürt: Das Oktopups-Poster, Kapuzenpulli für Männer und Frauen, Mütze und Skateboard! Direkt aus dem Internetz in deine (virtuelle) Hand! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ci sono troppi Octopoot che stanno intasando gli "intercavi" di Internet rallentando il tuo gameplay! Qui a LOOT™ ci occupiamo di questi fastidiosi esserini e li abbiamo in un succulento pacchetto: il Poster Octopoot, le Felpe con cappuccio per uomo e donna e lo Skate! Direttamente dal web nelle tue mani (virtuali). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Hay demasiados Octopoots atascando los "intertubos" de la Interwebz, y el nuestro juego va demasiado lento! Por eso, para deshacernos del mayor número posible de estos fastidiosos Octopoots, los empleados de LOOT™ los hemos metido en un bloque pequeño y muy aseado: ¡póster Octopoot, sudadera de chico y de chica, sombrero y monopatín! Recién sacados de la interwebz y directamente a tus manos (virtuales). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">沢山のOctopootsがインターウェブのインターチューブを詰まらせている! 私達のゲームプレイをも遅らせているぞ! ここ、LOOT™では、厄介なOctopootsを出来るだけ沢山取り除くために綺麗な固まりに丸めこんだら、Octopoot ポスター、男の子と女の子のパーカー、帽子とスケートボードになったよ!　インターウェブ発信、君の仮想の手の中に。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">There are too many Octopoots clogging up the ‘intertubes’ of the Interwebz!  They’re slowing down our gameplay! Here at LOOT™, in order to get rid of as many pesky Octopoots as possible, we’ve shoved them into a pretty little bundle: The Octopoot Poster, Male and Female Hoodie, Hat and Skateboard! Out of the interwebz and into your (virtual) hands. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>