<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Yukata Bottom (Hagoita, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bas de Yukata (Hagoita, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Yukata-Unterteil (Hagoita, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Yukata parte inferiore (Hagoita, U)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Parte inferior de Yukata (Hagoita, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">浴衣・下（男性・羽子板）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">유카타 하의 (남성, 부채)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Yukata Bottom (Men/Hagoita)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">日式浴衣 下 (男用／羽子板）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">日式浴衣 下 (男用／羽子板）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Yukata Bottom (Hagoita, M)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A single-layer kimono dyed a light turquoise, with a motif commonly found on hagoita (ornamental New Year's paddles) featured on the hem. This is only the bottom half, below the obi belt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un kimono composé d'une seule couche teint en turquoise clair et orné d'un motif typique des hagoita (raquettes en bois ornementales). C'est seulement le bas, au-dessous de la ceinture obi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein einfacher, helltürkis eingefärbter Kimono aus Baumwolle mit einem Hagoita-Motiv auf dem Saum. So wie man es von einem Hagoita (dekorierter Neujahrsfächer) kennt. Dies ist nur die untere Hälfte, die sich unterhalb des Obigürtels befindet.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un kimono leggero tinto in turchese pallido e decorato con un motivo tradizionale degli hagoita (racchette da volano usate durante il Capodanno). Solo la parte inferiore, dalla cintola (obi) in giù.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un kimono de algodón de una sola capa teñido de color turquesa claro con un motivo que se suele encontrar en los hagoita (paletas decorativas del Año Nuevo) en el dobladillo. Esto solo es la parte inferior, por debajo del cinturón obi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">淡い緑色に染めた浴衣の裾に、羽子板（はごいた）が描かれている、ひとえの着物。帯から下の半身。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">희미한 녹색에 물들인 유카타의 옷자락에 부채가 그려져 있는 전통 복장. 허리띠 아래의 하의.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">An unlined kimono bottom with light green dyed hemming and a hagoita (Japanese battledore) drawn on it.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在染成淺綠色的下擺印上羽子板的一重和服。腰帶之下的下半身部份。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在染成淺綠色的下擺印上羽子板的一重和服。腰帶之下的下半身部份。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A single-layer kimono dyed a light turquoise, with a motif commonly found on hagoita (ornamental New Year's paddles) featured on the hem. This is only the bottom half, below the obi belt.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>