<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Luau Woven Shirt - Washed Blue (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Chemise tissée Luau - Bleu délavé (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Luau Hemd - Ausgewaschenes Blau (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Luau Camicia - Blu effetto sbiadito (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Luau Camisa - Azul efecto lavado (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Hawaiian floral print brings aloha to the cool look of the Luau woven shirt. Distinct details include a single left chest pocket, wooden buttons and a woven flag label for added detail. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'imprimé floral hawaïen ajoute une touche aloha au look décontracté de cette chemise tissée Luau. Parmi les détails distinctifs figurent une poche poitrine unique placée à gauche, des boutons en bois et une étiquette-drapeau tissée rapportée. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das mit Blumen bedruckte Luau Hawaii-Hemd verbindet Aloha mit einem modisch-coolen Look. Zu besonderen Details zählen eine Brusttasche auf der linken Seite, Holzknöpfe und ein gewebtes Flaggenetikett. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La stampa floreale hawaiana dona un tocco di aloha al look intrigante della camicia Luau. I dettagli esclusivi comprendono una tasca unica a sinistra sul petto, bottoni di legno e un'etichetta in tessuto con la bandiera. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El estampado floral hawaiano le da ese plus de "aloha" a la imagen de por sí moderna de la camisa Luau. Entre los detalles distintivos se cuentan un bolsillo individual a la izquierda del pecho, botones de madera y detalle de etiqueta cosida por un lado. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>