<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Space Station Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Station Spatiale clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Raumstation Clubhaus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stazione Spaziale Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estación Espacial Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Space Station Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Space Station Clubhouse</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Space Station needs a crew, and you've been selected to take part in an all new out-of-this-world experience. Your Space Station adventure will have you defending your new home against incoming asteroids in the fully interactive Station Defense turret center. On top of defending the station your tasks will also include lowering and raising the external shutters so you don't  get blinded by the sun and you'll even have to evacuate the garbage you produce in to the vaccum of space. Your shuttle is cleared for arrival.

The Space Station space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La Station Spatiale a besoin d'un équipage, et vous avez été choisi pour prendre part à une nouvelle expérience hors de ce monde. Dans votre aventure à la Station Spatiale, vous défendrez votre nouvelle maison contre les astéroïdes entrants depuis votre tourelle entièrement interactive de Défense de la Station. En plus de défendre la station, vos tâches incluront aussi l'ouverture et la fermeture des volets externes pour ne pas être aveuglé par le soleil et vous devrez même vider dans l'espace les ordures que vous produisez. Le Station spatiale clubhouse est un espace où chacun est invité à se joindre.

Votre navette est parée pour le lancement et attend votre autorisation. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Raumstation braucht eine neue Besatzung, und du wirst mit von der Partie sein. Halte dich bereit für ein Abenteuer, das deine Vorstellungskraft sprengen wird. Dein neues Zuhause muss verteidigt, und gefährliche Asteroiden müssen zerstört werden. Dazu gibt es eigens die interaktive und Abwehrzentrale der Station, die dir dabei helfen wird. Außerdem bist du verantwortlich für die äußeren Deckklappen, die dich vor zu starker Sonnenstrahlung und Blendung schützen. Und auch die einfachen Arbeiten, wie Müllentsorgung in den Weiten des Alls, gehören zu deinen Aufgaben.  Die Raumstation ist ein Clubhaus, wo jeder zur Teilnahme eingeladen wird.

Dein Raumtransporter ist bereit zum Abheben und wartet nur noch auf dein Kommando. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Stazione Spaziale ha bisogno di un equipaggio, e tu sei stato scelto per partecipare a questa nuova esperienza fuori dal mondo. Nella tua avventura alla Stazione dovrai difendere la tua nuova casa dalla minaccia degli asteroidi in arrivo, dal tuo posto nella torre difensiva interattiva della Stazione. I tuoi compiti includeranno l'apertura e la chiusura delle saracinesche esterne, così da non rimanere accecato dalla luce solare, e portare la spazzatura fuori, nell'immenso vuoto spaziale.

Lo Stazione Spaziale è un club in cui tutti sono invitati a partecipare.

Il tuo shuttle è pronto al lancio, aspetta solo il tuo Ok. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La Estación Espacial necesita una tripulación, y tú has sido elegido para formar parte de una experiencia totalmente fuera de este mundo. Tu aventura en la Estación Espacial te tendrá defendiendo tu nuevo hogar de asteroides entrantes en la totalmente interactiva central de cúpulas de la Estación de Defensa. Además de defender tu estación, tus tareas también incluirán bajar y subir las persianas exteriores para evitar ser cegado por el sol e incluso tendrás que desechar la basura que produzcas hacia el vacío del espacio.

La Estación Espacial es un club donde todo el mundo está invitado a unirse.

Tu transbordador está listo para el despegue, esperando tu autorización. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Space Station needs a crew, and you've been selected to take part in an all new out-of-this-world experience. Your Space Station adventure will have you defending your new home against incoming asteroids in the fully interactive Station Defense turret center. On top of defending the station your tasks will also include lowering and raising the external shutters so you don't  get blinded by the sun and you'll even have to evacuate the garbage you produce in to the vaccum of space. Your shuttle is cleared for arrival.

The Space Station space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Space Station needs a crew, and you've been selected to take part in an all new out-of-this-world experience. Your Space Station adventure will have you defending your new home against incoming asteroids in the fully interactive Station Defense turret center. On top of defending the station your tasks will also include lowering and raising the external shutters so you don't  get blinded by the sun and you'll even have to evacuate the garbage you produce in to the vaccum of space. Your shuttle is cleared for arrival.

The Space Station space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>