<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">TACC Assault Rifle - Male</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fusil d'assaut TACC - Homme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">TACC Sturmgewehr - Für Ihn </LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">TACC Assault Rifle - Uomo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">TACC Assault Rifle - Hombre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">TACC Assault Rifle - Male</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Show the beasts and outlaws of the Badlands that Human weapons development is going strong by gearing up with the TACC Assault Rifle.  Assault rifles combine precision targeting with rapid fire and are a vital component of an ark hunter's arsenal! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Équipez-vous de ce fusil d'assaut TACC et montrez aux monstres et aux parias des badlands que la recherche et le développement d'armes d'origine humaine se porte bien. Alliant un ciblage précis à un tir rapide, les fusils d'assaut constituent un élément essentiel de l'arsenal de tout Pillarche ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeig den Gesetzlosen und den Kreaturen der Badlands, dass von Menschen entwickelte Waffen sich nicht zu verstecken brauchen und rüste dich mit dem TACC Sturmgewehr aus. Sturmgewehre kombinieren das präzise Anvisieren mit einer schnellen Feuerrate und sind ein unerlässlicher Bestandteil im Waffenarsenal eines Archenjägers. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fai vedere alle bestie e agli umani delle  Badlands che lo sviluppo delle armi degli Human sta andando a gonfie vele sfoggiando un TACC Assault Rifle.  Quest'arma combina un puntamento di precisione con un alto rateo di fuoco e rappresenta un elemento vitale nell'arsenale di ogni ark hunter. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Equípate con el TACC Assault Rifle para demostrar a las bestias y forajidos de Badlands la fortaleza de las armas Human. Los fusiles de asalto combinan precisión y rapidez de disparo y son una parte fundamental del arsenal de los ark hunter. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Show the beasts and outlaws of the Badlands that Human weapons development is going strong by gearing up with the TACC Assault Rifle.  Assault rifles combine precision targeting with rapid fire and are a vital component of an ark hunter's arsenal! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>