<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Obsidian Reigning Blades Lower Back and Calf Tattoos</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tatouages Lames reines Obsidienne bas du dos et mollet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Obsidian Reigning Blades-Tattoos für den unteren Rücken und Wade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tatuaggi Lame regnanti nero ossidiana per la parte inferiore della schiena e polpaccio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tatuajes Cuchillos reinantes obsidiana parte baja de la espalda y pantorrilla</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_35</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_35</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Obsidian Reigning Blades Lower Back and Calf Tattoos</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_35</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_35</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Obsidian Reigning Blades Lower Back and Calf Tattoos</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Reigning Blades tattoos let everyone know that you are not messing around. You're in the danger zone.

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les tatouages Lames reines permettent à tout le monde de savoir que vous ne plaisantez pas. Vous êtes dans la zone dangereuse.

Remarque : Tous les tatouages pour torse ou jambe ne sont pas égaux. Lors de l’achat de cet accessoire de tatouage, il est possible qu’il ne soit pas adapté à tous les habits. N’hésitez pas à prendre notre article gratuit « Torse nu » pour homme ou femme afin d’afficher correctement votre nouveau tatouage ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Reigning Blades-Tattoos zeigt allen, dass mit dir nicht zu spaßen ist. Du bist eine Gefahrenzone.

Hinweis: Nicht alle Gegenstände für Oberkörper oder Beine sind gleich gestaltet. Wenn du dieses Tattoo-Zubehör kaufst, könnte es nicht mit allen Kleidungsstücken harmonieren. Gerne kannst du dir unseren kostenlosen “blanken” Oberkörper für Männer/Frauen holen, um deine neuen Tattoos angemessen zeigen zu können![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scegliendo i tatuaggi Lame regnanti comunichi a tutti che sei un tipo col quale non si scherza.

Nota: non tutti gli oggetti per torso o gamba sono creati allo stesso modo. Il tatuaggio che ti appresti ad acquistare potrebbe non andare bene su tutti gli articoli di abbigliamento. A questo scopo non esitare a scaricare gratuitamente l'oggetto unisex "Tela nuda" torso per visualizzare correttamente i tuoi nuovi tatuaggi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con los tatuajes Cuchillos reinantes, todos sabrán que no bromeas. Estás en zona de peligro.

Nota: no todos los objetos para torso y piernas se crean por igual. Cuando compres este accesorio para un tatuaje, quizá no quede bien con cualquier prenda de ropa. ¡Elige nuestro "Lienzo en blanco" de regalo para hombre o mujer y así podrás lucir tu nuevo tatuaje como se merece![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_35 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_35 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Reigning Blades tattoos let everyone know that you are not messing around. You're in the danger zone.

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_35 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_35 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Reigning Blades tattoos let everyone know that you are not messing around. You're in the danger zone.

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>