<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">80" Color Moodlight LED TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">TV LED ambianceur couleur 80"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">80" Moodlight Farb-LED-TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">TV LED 80" a colori con luci d'atmosfera</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Televisión LED con luz de color 80"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">80"カラームードライトLED TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">80 인치 무드라이트 LED TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">80" Color Moodlight LED TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">80吋氣氛燈光液晶電視</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">80吋氣氛燈光液晶電視</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">80" Color Moodlight LED TV</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The latest model in LED TVs now comes with moodlighting that changes color in time! This TV will create the best possible ambience in your apartment. It comes in various sizes! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce tout dernier modèle de téléviseur LED est désormais équipé d'un ambianceur qui change de couleur en temps réel ! Il saura proposer l'ambiance adéquate dans votre appartement. Ce téléviseur existe en plusieurs tailles ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das neueste LED-TV-Modell gibt es jetzt mit Stimmungslicht, dessen Farben sich mit der Zeit verändern. Dieser Fernseher verbreitet die schönste nur mögliche Atmosphäre in deiner Wohnung. In unterschiedlichen Größen erhältlich! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo televisore LED di ultima generazione dotato di luci d'atmosfera che cambiano colore nel tempo per creare un'atmosfera da sogno nel tuo appartamento. Disponibile in varie dimensioni. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡El último modelo en televisión LED ahora viene con una luz que cambia de color con el tiempo! Esta tele creará el mejor ambiente en tu apartamento. ¡La hay de varios tamaños! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LED TVの最新モデルには、時間と共に色が変化するムードライトがついてきます！このTVはお部屋に最高の雰囲気を創り出します。他にも様々なサイズがございます！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">최신 LED TV는 이제 시간과 함께 색이 바뀌는 무드라이팅 기술이 적용되어 제공됩니다! 이 TV로 최고의 분위기를 연출할 수 있습니다. 다양한 크기로 제공됩니다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The latest model in LED TVs now comes with moodlighting that changes color in time! This TV will create the best possible ambience in your apartment. It comes in various sizes! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">最新款的LED電影現附有氣氛燈，會隨時間改變顏色！這款電視機會為你的居所製造出最好的氣氛。這電視有不同尺寸！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">最新款的LED電影現附有氣氛燈，會隨時間改變顏色！這款電視機會為你的居所製造出最好的氣氛。這電視有不同尺寸！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The latest model in LED TVs now comes with moodlighting that changes color in time! This TV will create the best possible ambience in your apartment. It comes in various sizes! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>