<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Playstation®Home Mansion - Infinity Pool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Manoir PlayStation®Home - Piscine panoramique</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Playstation®Home-Villa: Infinity Pool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Villa PlayStation®Home - Piscina infinita</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mansión de PlayStation®Home: piscina infinita</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">PlayStation®Home 맨션 - 영원의 풀장</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">PlayStation®Home Mansion - Infinity Pool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">PlayStation®Home豪華別墅 －無邊際泳池</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">PlayStation®Home豪華別墅 －無邊際泳池</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">PlayStation®Home Mansion - Infinity Pool</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Boasting a generous outdoor patio, this lavish waterfront backyard comes complete with two fireplaces, a marble bar, and gold statues overlooking your own private wishing fountain. Combine this with a large, glass-walled, infinity pool that looks out into the ocean’s horizon and you have the perfect backyard for any social get-together or simply a relaxing afternoon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En plus de son sublime patio, ce jardin sur front de mer somptueux comprend deux cheminées, un bar en marbre et des statues en or surplombant votre propre fontaine à souhaits. Ajoutez à cela une grande piscine panoramique aux parois de verre avec pour seul horizon le bleu infini de l'océan et vous obtenez le lieu idéal pour organiser une fête ou, tout simplement, pour vous détendre. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser opulente Garten am Wasser glänzt mit einer großzügigen Außenterrasse und verfügt über zwei offene Feuerstellen, eine Marmorbar und Goldstatuen, die Ihren privaten Wunschbrunnen überblicken. Zusammen mit dem großen Infinity-Pool mit Glaswandung, der direkt mit dem Horizont über dem Ozean verschmilzt, bietet sich hier die perfekte Kulisse, um sich mit Freunden zu treffen oder einfach einen entspannten Nachmittag zu verbringen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Arricchito da uno splendido patio, questo sontuoso spazio aperto sul mare vanta due camini, un bar in marmo e delle statue d'oro che vegliano sulla tua personale fontana dei desideri. Se aggiungi anche una grande piscina infinita con pareti in vetro, affacciata direttamente sull'oceano, hai l'ambiente perfetto per qualsiasi evento sociale o per un tranquillo pomeriggio di relax. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este magnífico patio de jardín trasero con piscina incorpora dos chimeneas, una barra de bar de mármol y estatuas de oro que presiden tu propia fuente de los deseos. Si le sumas la piscina infinita, con muro de cristal y enrasada al nivel del océano, tendrás el escenario perfecto para tus reuniones de sociedad o para disfrutar plácidamente de una tarde de relax. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">넓은 야외 테라스를 자랑하는 이 뒷뜰은 두 개의 벽난로와 대리석 바, 그리고 개인 소유의 분수를 바라보는 황금 조각상들로 이루어져 있습니다. 거기에 바다의 수평선이 보이도록 유리벽을 두른 야외 수영장이 포함되면, 친구들을 초대하거나, 편안한 오후의 휴식을 취할수 있는 완벽한 공간이 됩니다. 또한 추가 보너스로는 PlayStation®Home 맨션을 방문하는 친구들에게 최대 6개의 황금 리워드를 각기 선물할 수 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Boasting a generous outdoor patio, this lavish waterfront backyard comes complete with two fireplaces, a marble bar, and gold statues overlooking your own private wishing fountain. Combine this with a large, glass-walled, infinity pool that looks out into the ocean’s horizon and you have the perfect backyard for any social get-together or simply a relaxing afternoon. And for an added bonus the PlayStation®Home Mansion also includes up to 6 unique gold rewards for each of your guests. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">奢華的河畔後園擁有倘大的室外中庭，並備有兩座火爐、一個大理石酒吧及黃金雕像，能俯瞰你的私人許願噴泉。還有大型玻璃牆的無邊際泳池，能眺望大海的地平線。這是一個最適合用作任何社交場合或享受悠閒下午的後院。此外，PlayStation®Home豪華別墅還包括最多6種額外黃金獎品道具給你和你的賓客。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">奢華的河畔後園擁有倘大的室外中庭，並備有兩座火爐、一個大理石酒吧及黃金雕像，能俯瞰你的私人許願噴泉。還有大型玻璃牆的無邊際泳池，能眺望大海的地平線。這是一個最適合用作任何社交場合或享受悠閒下午的後院。此外，PlayStation®Home豪華別墅還包括最多6種額外黃金獎品道具給你和你的賓客。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Boasting a generous outdoor patio, this lavish waterfront backyard comes complete with two fireplaces, a marble bar, and gold statues overlooking your own private wishing fountain. Combine this with a large, glass-walled, infinity pool that looks out into the ocean’s horizon and you have the perfect backyard for any social get-together or simply a relaxing afternoon. And for an added bonus the PlayStation®Home Mansion also includes up to 5 unique gold rewards for each of your guests. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>