<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dynamite DX Fuel Additive x26</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Additif pour carburant Dynamite DX x26</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dynamite DX- Treibstoffzusatz x26</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Additivo al carburante Dynamite DX x26</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aditivo de combustible Dynamite DX x26</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Dynamite DX 燃料添加物 x26</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Dynamite DX연료 첨가제 x26</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Dynamite DX Fuel Additive x26</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Dynamite DX 燃料添加物 x26</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Dynamite DX 燃料添加物 x26</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dynamite DX Fuel Additive x26</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A highly unstable and powerful fuel additive for your Sodium2 racer that supplements your fuel to increase your top speed. This is a 26 use item that will be used automatically in a race if equipped. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un additif de carburant instable et hautement explosif pour votre engin Sodium2 qui améliorera votre vitesse de pointe. Il s'agit d'un objet d'utilité 26 qui sera automatiquement utilisé lors d'une course s'il est équipé. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein sehr instabiler Treibstoffzusatz für deinen Sodium2-Gleiter, der deine Höchstgeschwindigkeit erhöht. Dies ist ein Gegenstand, mit 26 Anwendungen, der automatisch in einem Rennen benutzt wird, wenn er ausgerüstet wurde. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un additivo per il carburante altamente instabile e potente per il tuo veicolo Sodium2 che integra il carburante per aumentare la velocità massima. Quest'oggetto può essere usato 26 volta(e). Dopo averlo equipaggiato, sarà utilizzato automaticamente in gara. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un aditivo de gasolina muy inestable y potente para tu corredor de Sodium2 que complementa el combustible para aumentar la velocidad máxima. Este es un objeto de 26 uso(s) que se utilizará automáticamente en carrera cuando esté equipado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">あなたのSodium2 レーサーに必要な強力だが不安定な燃料。最高速の限界を超える為のサプリメント。このアイテム26は装備する事によりレースで自動的に使用されます。\n26回使用可能です。\n\n※本アイテムは消費型アイテムです。追加購入が可能です。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">여러분의 최고 속력을 최대로 증가시키기 위해 연료를 보완해주는 Sodium2 레이서를 위한 아주 불안정하지만 강력한 연료첨가제.이것이 일단 갖추게 되면 경주에서 자동으로 적용될 26 사용 아이템입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A highly unstable and powerful fuel additive for your Sodium2 racer that supplements your fuel to increase your top speed. This is a 26 use item that will be used automatically in a race if equipped. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sodium2賽車專用強效燃料添加物，非常不穩定，但能讓極速往上飆。本物品只能使用26次，裝上後就會在出賽時自動啟用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sodium2賽車專用強效燃料添加物，非常不穩定，但能讓極速往上飆。本物品只能使用26次，裝上後就會在出賽時自動啟用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A highly unstable and powerful fuel additive for your Sodium2 racer that supplements your fuel to increase your top speed. This is a 26 use item that will be used automatically in a race if equipped. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>