<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Personal Casino Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Casino Personnel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Persönliches Casino Gesamtpaket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Casinò Personale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Casino personal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Personal Casino Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Personal Casino Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Personal Casino Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Personal Casino Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Personal Casino Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Personal Casino Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Now you can take on the roll of being a casino boss. This bundle include all of your favorite casino games, Poker, War, Blackjack, Big Six, Craps, Roulette, Video Poker, Video Blackjack, and Slots. Not only will you get all of these fantastic games but you'll also get your own Casino Personal Space. It'll be like you're running a mini version of Paradise Springs for you and your friends.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Soyez excité à l'idée de devenir le patron du casino. Ce pack inclus tous vos jeux préférés du casino, Poker, Bataille Royale, Blackjack, Roue de la Fortune, Craps, Roulette, Vidéo Poker, Vidéo Blackjack, et Machines à Sous. En plus de tous ces jeux fantastiques vous aurez votre Espace Casino Personnel. C'est comme si vous aviez une version réduite de Paradise Springs pour vous et vos amis. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nun können Sie die Rolle des Casino Bosses übernehmen. Dieses Gesamtpaket beinhaltet  Ihre gesamten und beliebtesten Casino-Spiele; Poker, War, Blackjack, Big Six, Craps, Roulette, Video Poker, Video Blackjack und Slots. Sie erhalten nicht nur diese tollen Spiele, sondern auch Ihren persönlichen Casino-Raum. Sie werden das Gefühl haben,  als hätten Sie das Paradise Springs für sich und Ihre Freunde im Kleinformat geschaffen.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ora potrai diventare il capo di un casinò. Questo pacchetto include tutti i tuoi giochi preferiti del casinò: Poker, War, Blackjack, Big Six, Craps, Roulette, Video Poker, Video Blackjack, e Slot. Non otterrai soltanto tutti questi giochi fantastici, ma otterrai anche il tuo Appartamento Casinò Personale. Sarà come avere una piccola versione del Paradise Springs per e i tuoi amici [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ahora puedes tirarte el rollo y ser un jefe de casino. Este pack incluye todos tus juegos de casino favoritos, Póker, War, Blackjack, Big Six, Dados, Ruleta, Videopóker, Videoblackjack y tragaperras. No sólo conseguirás todos estos juegos sino también tu propio Casino personal. Será como una mini versión del Paradise Springs para ti y tus amigos. Lia a tus amigos a una noche de diversión y juego en tu propio casino. Aquí tu eres el jefe. Lo que tú digas se hará. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Personal Casino Bundle [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Personal Casino Bundle [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Personal Casino Bundle [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Personal Casino Bundle [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Personal Casino Bundle [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Now you can take on the roll of being a casino boss. This bundle include all of your favorite casino games, Poker, War, Blackjack, Big Six, Craps, Roulette, Video Poker, Video Blackjack, and Slots. Not only will you get all of these fantastic games but you'll also get your own Casino Personal Space. It'll be like you're running a mini version of Paradise Springs for you and your friends.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>