<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Five Leafed Clover Seat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fauteuil Trèfle à cinq feuilles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fünfblättriges Kleeblatt-Seat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sedia Quadrifoglio a cinque foglie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Asiento de trébol de cinco hojas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">五つ葉クローバーシート</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">다섯 잎 클로버 시트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Five Leafed Clover Seat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">五葉草座椅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">五葉草座椅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Five Leafed Clover Seat</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If you thought a four leafed clover was lucky you haven't seen anything yet! This Five Leafed Clover Seat not only looks amazing and offers you a comfy seat, but it also greatly increases your chances of winning a reward in the OMG Trap-O-Matic found in Aurora. Note - You will eventually trap all the items without the Five Leafed Clover Seat, but with it you will catch all items a lot quicker. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si vous pensiez que les trèfles à quatre feuilles étaient synonymes de chance, vous n’avez encore rien vu ! Ce fauteuil Trèfle à cinq feuilles en jette et améliore votre confort, mais augmente aussi largement vos chances d’obtenir une récompense dans le Trp-O-Matic d’Aurora. Remarque - vous finirez par attraper tous les objets sans le fauteuil Trèfle à cinq feuilles, mais il vous permettra d'y parvenir beaucoup plus rapidement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn du gedacht hast, dass ein vierblättriges Kleeblatt Glück bringt, steht dir eine Überraschung bevor! Dieses Fünfblättrige Kleeblatt-Set sieht nicht nur toll aus und ist eine komfortable Sitzgelegenheit, es steigert auch deine Chance erheblich, beim OMG Trap-O-Matic in Aurora zu gewinnen. Hinweis - Du kannst auch ohne Fünfblättriges Kleeblatt-Set irgendwann alle Gegenstände bekommen, doch mit dem Set geht das sehr viel schneller.
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se pensavi che il quadrifoglio portasse fortuna, non hai visto ancora niente! Questa sedia Quadrifoglio a cinque foglie non è solo bellissima e confortevole, ma aumenta in maniera considerevole le tue possibilità di vincere un premio in Trap-O-Matic in Aurora. Nota: potrai intrappolare tutti gli oggetti anche senza la sedia Quadrifoglio a cinque foglie, ma con questa catturerai tutti gli oggetti molto più velocemente. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si pensabas que un trébol de cuatro hojas daba suerte, ¡aún no has visto nada! Este asiento de trébol de cinco hojas no solo es chulísimo y muy cómodo, sino que, además, incrementa enormemente las probabilidades de conseguir un premio en el juego de Tramp-a-mática que encontrarás en Aurora. Nota: conseguirás atrapar todos los objetos sin ayuda de este asiento de trébol de cinco hojas, pero con él conseguirás atrapar todos los objetos mucho más rápido.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">四つ葉のクローバーがラッキーアイテム? そんなの序の口! この五つ葉クローバーシートは見た目がステキなだけじゃなく、座り心地も抜群。おまけにオーロラにあるトラップ大作戦で賞品を獲得するチャンスまで高めてくれます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">네 잎 클로버가 행운을 상징한다고 생각했다면 큰 오산입니다! 이 다섯 잎 클로버 시트는 겉모습도 멋지고 안락한 좌석도 제공할 뿐만 아니라 Aurora에서 찾을 수 있는 트랩-오-마틱의 리워드를 얻을 확률을 크게 높여주기도 합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">If you thought a four leafed clover was lucky you haven't seen anything yet! This Five Leafed Clover Seat not only looks amazing and offers you a comfy seat, but it also greatly increases your chances of winning a reward in the OMG Trap-O-Matic found in Aurora. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">如果您認為四葉草是您見過的幸運之物，那就看看這個吧！這「五葉草座椅」不僅看起來令人驚訝，為您提供舒適的座位，而且還會極大地增加您在極光群島中遊玩「超級陷阱」時贏得獎品道具的幾率。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">如果您認為四葉草是您見過的幸運之物，那就看看這個吧！這「五葉草座椅」不僅看起來令人驚訝，為您提供舒適的座位，而且還會極大地增加您在極光群島中遊玩「超級陷阱」時贏得獎品道具的幾率。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">If you thought a four leafed clover was lucky you haven't seen anything yet! This Five Leafed Clover Seat not only looks amazing and offers you a comfy seat, but it also greatly increases your chances of winning a reward in the OMG Trap-O-Matic found in Aurora. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>