<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Mirage Trophy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mirage Trophy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Trophée Mirage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mirage-Trophäe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Trofeo Mirage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Trofeo de Mirage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Mirage Trophy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Mirage 트로피</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Mirage Trophy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Mirage 獎盃</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Mirage 獎盃</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mirage Trophy</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Usually it whizzes past in a green blur! Finally you get the chance to study this crazy ship design in detail. Mirage are delighted to offer this model trophy to adorn your home. It shouldn’t work but it does!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Usually it whizzes past in a green blur! Finally you get the chance to study this crazy ship design in detail. Mirage are delighted to offer this model trophy to adorn your home. It shouldn’t work but it does! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Habituellement, vous le voyez passer dans un éclair vert ! Vous avez enfin l'occasion d'étudier l'incroyable design de ce vaisseau dans les moindres détails. Mirage est ravie de vous proposer ce modèle réduit, un véritable trophée pour votre maison. Il ne devrait pas fonctionner, et pourtant...! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Normalerweise flitzt es als grüner Blitz vorbei! Nun hat man endlich die Gelegenheit, das irre Design dieses Schiffes genauer zu begutachten. Mirage freut sich, dieses Modell als Zierde für jedes Heim anbieten zu können. Klingt wie ein gewagtes Vorhaben – aber es funktioniert tatsächlich! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Finora avete visto solamente la sua scia verde, ma finalmente potrete ammirare nel dettaglio il design originale di questa nave. La Mirage è lieta di presentare questo modellino con il quale adornare le vostre case... ed è perfettamente funzionante! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Normalmente no es más que una mancha borrosa verde. Ahora, por fin podrás examinar su extravagante diseño en detalle. Mirage se complace en ofrecerte este trofeo, una réplica de su nave, para tu hogar. No debería funcionar, ¡pero lo hace! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Usually it whizzes past in a green blur! Finally you get the chance to study this crazy ship design in detail. Mirage are delighted to offer this model trophy to adorn your home. It shouldn’t work but it does! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">레이스 트랙에서라면 형체를 알아볼 수 없는 녹색 환영으로 보이겠지만, 이제 구입할 수 있는 이 모델 트로피와 함께라면 Mirage의 최신 기체를 구석구석 뜯어볼 수 있습니다. 거실을 장식할 수 있는 물건들 중, 단연 최고입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Usually it whizzes past in a green blur! Finally you get the chance to study this crazy ship design in detail. Mirage are delighted to offer this model trophy to adorn your home. It shouldn’t work but it does! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">通常您只能在賽道上看到這款賽車飛馳而過的綠色影子，現在您終於有機會可以仔細欣賞它的絕妙設計了！Mirage專誠為您獻上這個模型獎盃，為您的家居錦上添花。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">通常您只能在賽道上看到這款賽車飛馳而過的綠色影子，現在您終於有機會可以仔細欣賞它的絕妙設計了！Mirage專誠為您獻上這個模型獎盃，為您的家居錦上添花。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Usually it whizzes past in a green blur! Finally you get the chance to study this crazy ship design in detail. Mirage are delighted to offer this model trophy to adorn your home. It shouldn’t work but it does! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>