<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Hawaiian Crackle Woven Shirt - Burnt Coral (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Chemise tissée Hawaiian Crackle - Corail brûlé (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Hawaiian Crackle Hemd - Korallenrot (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Camicia in tessuto Hawaiian Crackle - Corallo bruciato (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Hawaiian Crackle Camisa de vestir - Coral quemado (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Life isn't always t-shirts and boardshorts. And for those times when you need to step it up, our woven shirts will never let you down. Their upscale details and top quality construction offer incredible durability for a lifetime of wear. Featuring ultra fine fabrics and a dominant air of surf authority, polished performances don't get any better than this. You'll experience this with the tailored fit of the Hawaiian Crackle, along with its floral print and tonal cracked background and single chest pocket. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La vie ne se résume pas toujours aux T-shirts et aux shorts de planchistes. Et pour les moments où vous avez besoin de passer à la classe supérieure, nos chemises tissées ne vous laisseront jamais tomber. Leurs détails et leur fabrication haut de gamme leur confèrent une incroyable résistance au temps. Fabriquées dans des tissus ultrafins, donnant de l'autorité, leurs performances impeccables ne pourraient être meilleures. Vous y goûterez avec la coupe sur mesure de l'Hawaiian Crackle, avec son imprimé floral sur fond tonal craquelé et sa poche poitrine. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Man kann nicht immer nur T-Shirts und Boardshorts tragen. Manchmal erfordert die Situation einfach etwas mehr. Zum Glück liegen Sie mit einem Hawaiian Crackle Hemd nie falsch. Die hochwertige Verarbeitung, robuste Konstruktion und optimale Passform garantieren langjährige Zufriedenheit. Nicht zuletzt besticht das Hawaiian Crackle Hemd durch seinen besonders weichen Stoff mit augenfälligen Surfdetails, die einzelne Brusttasche, das Blumenmuster und den farblich abgesetzten Hintergrund. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nella vita non ci sono solo shorts da mare e t-shirt. E per le occasioni che richiedono un po' di eleganza, le nostre camicie in tessuto non ti deluderanno. I particolari esclusivi e il taglio di ottima qualità rendono questi capi resistenti e durevoli. Grazie ai loro tessuti pregiati, danno a chi le indossa un'aria da surfista esperto dall'eleganza ricercata. E tu ti sentirai così, indossando lo stile sartoriale delle camice Hawaiian Crackle, con motivi floreali su sfondo in gradazione a effetto marmorizzato e un taschino. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">En la vida no todo va a ser camisetas y bermudas. Y para las ocasiones en que tengas que subir el nivel, nuestras camisas nunca te decepcionarán. Sus detalles exclusivos y su elaboración de alta calidad ofrecen una increíble durabilidad de uso.  Hecha de tejidos ultra delicados y con la impronta de una jerarquía surfera, su carácter refinado es insuperable. Es lo que sentirás con el corte a medida de la Hawaiian Crackle, que presenta estampado floral sobre fondo uniforme agrietado y cuenta con bolsillo en el pecho. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>