<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Juggernaut Steampunk Adventure Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble steampunk Juggernaut</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Juggernaut Steampunk-Abenteuerpaket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto avventura Fantasy antico Juggernaut</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de aventuras de steampunk Juggernaut</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Juggernaut Steampunk Adventure Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">For the discerning neo-victorian! Join the adventure with this collection of steampunk inspired clothing and furniture. Bundle includes: Bundle Includes: Steampunk Jacket (Male), Steampunk Goggles (Male), Steampunk Gloves (Male), Steampunk Pants (Male), Steampunk Top Hat (Male), Steampunk Corset (Female), Steampunk Goggles (Female), Steampunk Pants (Female), Steampunk Hair (Female), Steampunk Boots (Female), Robotic Spider, Steampunk Table, Steampunk Chair, Steampunk Lamp, Steampunk Clock, Steampunk Picture Frame. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour le néo-victorien avisé ! Joignez l'aventure avec cette collection de vêtements et d'éléments de mobilier d'inspiration steampunk. L'ensemble inclut : Veste steampunk (homme), Lunettes steampunk (homme), Gants steampunk (homme), Pantalon steampunk (homme), Haut-de-forme steampunk (homme), L'ensemble inclut : Corset steampunk (femme), Lunettes steampunk (femme), Pantalon steampunk (femme), Cheveux steampunk (femme), Bottes steampunk (femme), Araignée robotique, Table steampunk, Chaise steampunk, Lampe steampunk, Cadre steampunk, Horloge steampunk. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Für den Wählerischen Neo-Viktorianer! Auf ins Abenteuer – mit dieser Sammlung Steampunk-inspirierter Kleidungs- und Möbelstücke. Das Bundle enthält: Steampunk-Jacke (Männliche), Steampunk-Brille (Männliche), Steampunk-Handschuhe (Männliche), Steampunk-Hose  (Männliche), Steampunk-Zylinder (Männliche), Steampunk-Korsett (Weiblich), Steampunk-Brille (Weiblich), Steampunk-Hose (Weiblich), Steampunk-Haar (Weiblich), Steampunk-Stiefel (Weiblich), Roboterspinne, Steampunk-Tisch, Steampunk-Stuhl, Steampunk-Lampe, Steampunk-Bilderrahmen, Steampunk-Uhr. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per il brillante neovittoriano che c'è in te! Unisca l'avventura con questa raccolta di abiti e arredi in stile fantasy antico. Il pacchetto include: Giacca Fantasy antico (uomo), Lenti Fantasy antico (uomo), Guanti Fantasy antico (uomo), Pantaloni Fantasy antico (uomo), Cilindro Fantasy antico (uomo), Corsetto Fantasy antico (donna), Lenti Fantasy antico (donna), Pantaloni Fantasy antico (donna), Capelli Fantasy antico (donna), Stivali Fantasy antico (donna), Ragno robot, Tavolo Fantasy antico, Sedia Fantasy antico, Lampada Fantasy antico, Cornice quadrata, Fantasy antico, Orologio Fantasy antico. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Para el neo-victoriano más exquisito! Únete a la aventura con esta colección de ropa y muebles inspirados en el movimiento steampunk. El paquete incluye: Chaqueta steampunk (masculino), Gafas steampunk (masculino), Guantes steampunk (masculino), Pantalones steampunk (masculino), Gorro steampunk (masculino), Corsé steampunk (femenino), Gafas steampunk (femenino), Pantalones steampunk (femenino), Cabello steampunk (femenino), Botas steampunk (femenino), El paquete incluye: Araña robótica, Mesa steampunk, Silla steampunk, Lámpara steampunk, Marco de imagen steampunk, Reloj  steampunk. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">For the discerning neo-victorian! Join the adventure with this collection of steampunk inspired clothing and furniture. Bundle includes: Bundle Includes: Steampunk Jacket (Male), Steampunk Goggles (Male), Steampunk Gloves (Male), Steampunk Pants (Male), Steampunk Top Hat (Male), Steampunk Corset (Female), Steampunk Goggles (Female), Steampunk Pants (Female), Steampunk Hair (Female), Steampunk Boots (Female), Robotic Spider, Steampunk Table, Steampunk Chair, Steampunk Lamp, Steampunk Clock, Steampunk Picture Frame. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>