<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cannon Coolant Upgrade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Refroidisseur Fusils</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kanonenkühlmittel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Raffreddamento cannoni</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mejora del refrigerante del cañón</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">大砲冷却アップグレード</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">캐논 냉각제 업그레이드</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Cannon Coolant Upgrade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">火炮冷卻劑升級組件</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">火炮冷卻劑升級組件</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cannon Coolant Upgrade</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You might be keeping your cool in the Aurora Island Defence game, but are your cannons? This rare Coolant will vastly improve your cannons thermal performance and prevent them from overheating so readily.  It also makes for a great bespoke table when the need arises.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Peut-être gardez-vous la tête froide dans le jeu de défense d’Aurora, mais qu’en est-il de vos canons ? Ce liquide de refroidissement rare améliorera grandement les performances thermiques de vos canons et les empêchera de surchauffer trop rapidement. Il fait également office de table sur mesure au besoin.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du behältst bei der Verteidigung Auroras vielleicht einen kühlen Kopf, aber wie sieht es mit deinen Kanonen aus? Dieses seltene Kühlmittel verbessert die Hitzebeständigkeit deiner Kanonen und schützt sie vor allzu schnellem Überhitzen. Lässt sich notfalls auch hübsch als Tisch verwenden.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Magari tu riuscirai a tenere il sangue freddo nel gioco della difesa dell'isola di Aurora, ma sarà lo stesso per i tuoi cannoni? Questo raro fluido refrigerante migliorerà enormemente le prestazioni termiche dei tuoi cannoni e impedirà che si surriscaldino facilmente. Fa anche da tavolo personalizzato quando la necessità incombe.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Puede que nunca te acalores al defender la Isla de Aurora, ¿pero qué tal andan tus cañones? Este extraño refrigerante mejorará enormemente el rendimiento térmico de tus cañones, y evitará que se sobrecalienten tan rápido. También puede funcionar como una mesa a medida cuando lo necesites.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラ島防衛ミニゲームでいくらあなたがクールでいても、大砲を冷やさないと生き延びることはできません。この珍しい冷却装置を使えば、大砲の性能をあげることができ、大砲のオーバーヒートも避けられます。また、大きなテーブルとしても使えます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Aurora 섬 방어 게임을 하면 시원할 지 모르지만 캐논도 과연 시원할까요? 이 희귀한 냉각제는 캐논의 열 성능을 크게 높여주며 쉽게 과열되지 않도록 예방합니다. 필요한 경우 훌륭한 맞춤 제작 테이블이 되기도 합니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">You might be keeping your cool in the Aurora Island Defence game, but are your cannons? This rare Coolant will vastly improve your cannons thermal performance and prevent them from overheating so readily.  It also makes for a great bespoke table when the need arises.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">你或許能在極光島嶼守衛戰遊戲中保持冷靜，但是你的火炮能嗎？這種稀有的冷卻劑將大大改進火炮的耐熱性能，輕鬆防止它們過熱。當有需要時，該冷卻劑還能充當一張多用途的大桌。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">你或許能在極光島嶼守衛戰遊戲中保持冷靜，但是你的火炮能嗎？這種稀有的冷卻劑將大大改進火炮的耐熱性能，輕鬆防止它們過熱。當有需要時，該冷卻劑還能充當一張多用途的大桌。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You might be keeping your cool in the Aurora Island Defense game, but are your cannons? This rare Coolant will vastly improve your cannons thermal performance and prevent them from overheating so readily.  It also makes for a great bespoke table when the need arises.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>