<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Crypt Keeper (Red)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Gradien de la crypte (Rouge)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Grabwächter (rot)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guardiano della cripta (rosso)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guardián de la cripta (rojo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">地下室の門番（赤）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">크립트 키퍼 (빨간색)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Crypt Keeper (Red)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">地下聖堂守護者（紅色）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">地下聖堂守護者（紅色）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Crypt Keeper (Red)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Crypt Keeper ensures your safety from the evil creatures that lurk within. However, this does not stop your apartment from filling with an eerie red fog and the sound of the horrific creatures imprisoned within the crypt below.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce gardien de la crypte vous protège des créatures abominables tapies dans les ténèbres. Toutefois, votre appartement s'emplit quand même d'un étrange brouillard rouge et du son des créatures horribles prisonnières de la crypte souterraine.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser Grabwächter beschützt dich vor den bösen Kreaturen, die dir drinnen auflauern. Aber deine Wohnung wird sich mit einem unheimlichen roten Nebel füllen, und man kann die Schreie der schrecklichen Kreaturen hören, die unten gefangen sind.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo Guardiano della cripta fa sì che le creature diaboliche che la infestano non ti assalgano. Comunque, ciò non ti impedisce di riempire il tuo appartamento di una spaventosa nebbia rossa e dei lamenti delle orribili creature imprigionate nella cripta.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Guardián de la cripta te protege de las criaturas diabólicas que están al acecho. Sin embargo, esto no quita que no puedas llenar el apartamento de espeluznante niebla roja y con sonidos de criaturas terroríficas presas en la cripta que hay bajo tierra.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">地下室の門番はあなたを闇や邪悪な存在から守ってくれる者だ。ただ、赤い霧が立ち込めたり地下室から恐ろしげな叫び声が聞こえてくるのはどうしようもないらしい。.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 크립트 키퍼는 숨어있는 악의 생물로부터 당신의 안전을 보장합니다. 하지만, 이것은 당신의 아파트가 기분 나쁜 붉은 안개와 지하실에 갖힌 무서운 생물들의 소리로 가득차는 것을 막을 순 없습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This Crypt Keeper ensures your safety from the evil creatures that lurk within. However, this does not stop your apartment from filling with an eerie red fog and the sound of the horrific creatures imprisoned within the crypt below.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這個地下聖堂守護者確保你不會受潛伏其中的邪惡生物傷害。但是，這不會防止你的個人空間被注滿可怕的紅霧和被囚禁在地下聖堂內恐怖生物的叫聲。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這個地下聖堂守護者確保你不會受潛伏其中的邪惡生物傷害。但是，這不會防止你的個人空間被注滿可怕的紅霧和被囚禁在地下聖堂內恐怖生物的叫聲。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This Crypt Keeper ensures your safety from the evil creatures that lurk within. However, this does not stop your apartment from filling with an eerie red fog and the sound of the horrific creatures imprisoned within the crypt below.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>