<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Draped Silk Tapered Hem Top</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tunique En Soie Drapée Evasée</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drapiertes, enganliegendes Seidentop mit schrägem Saum</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Top A Drappo Di Seta Con Orlo Affusolato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Top de Seda Drapeado con Dobladillo Desigual</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_33</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_33</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_33</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_33</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_33</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Draped Silk Tapered Hem Top</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The finest haute couture top drapes you in cream and tan silk flatteringly and cinches around your waist with a simple chocolate brown belt. The tapered hem makes this top more flowing and dramatic.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce splendide haut digne des plus grands défilés vous enveloppe dans la douceur de la soie. De couleur crème, il met votre taille en valeur avec sa ceinture couleur chocolat. Sa forme en fuseau lui donne un air fluide et aérien.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses edle Haute-Couture-Top hüllt die Trägerin in creme- und hautfarbene Seide und umschmeichelt ihre Hüfte mit einem einfachen, schokoladenbraunen Gürtel. Der schräge Saum sorgt für einen fließenden und dramatischen Effekt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un top d'alta moda che ti avvolge in maniera lusinghiera con seta panna e marrone chiaro e che si stringe attorno alla vita con una semplice cintura cioccolato. L'orlo affusolato rende questo top più mosso e teatrale.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lo mejor de la alta costura te envuelve en seda color crema oscuro de forma favorecedora y se ciñe a tu cintura con un sencillo cinturón marrón. El borde recortado hace que el top tenga mayor fluidez y dramatismo.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_33 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_33 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_33 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_33 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_33 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The finest haute couture top drapes you in cream and tan silk flatteringly and cinches around your waist with a simple chocolate brown belt. The tapered hem makes this top more flowing and dramatic.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>