<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Drey Wicked White Woven Trilby</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chapeau décalé en feutre tressé Drey blanc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weißer gewobener Drey Fedora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Capello floscio in tessuto Drey bianco sporco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sombrero tejido color blanco neutro de Drey</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">【Drey】編み帽子　（ホワイト）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"드레이" 위키드 화이트 중절모 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Drey Wicked White Woven Trilby (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Drey暗灰白針織呢帽  (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Drey暗灰白針織呢帽  (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Drey Wicked White Woven Trilby</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The modern woven trilby serves as homage to relaxed city chic. Set against beautiful soft waves this style is the ultimate complement to any outfit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le feutre tressé moderne sert d'hommage au chic citadin décontracté. Associé à de belles ondulations, ce style apporte un complément parfait à n'importe quelle tenue. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der moderne, gewobene Fedora ist eine Hommage an den lässigen Stadt-Chic. Sie weichen Linien dieses Hutes machen ihn zur perfekten Ergänzung jedes Outfits. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il cappello floscio in tessuto è un omaggio all'atmosfera chic e rilassata tipica della città. Morbide onde di tessuto e quadretti, questo stile dà il tocco finale a qualunque capo indossato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El moderno sombrero tejido es todo un homenaje al look chic relajado de ciudad. Colocado sobre unas ondas suaves, este estilo es el complemento definitivo para cualquier conjunto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このモダンな帽子は都会派女子に大人気！この帽子はどんな服装にも合います！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">현대적인 중절모는 시크한 도시 스타일의 정점을 표현합니다. 아름다운 웨이브 머리와 함께라면 어떤 의상과도 완벽하게 어울립니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The modern woven trilby serves as homage to relaxed city chic. Set against beautiful soft waves this style is the ultimate complement to any outfit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">充滿現代感的針織呢帽，向輕鬆城市派風尚致敬。這種風格適合波浪捲髮，容易搭配各種服飾。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">充滿現代感的針織呢帽，向輕鬆城市派風尚致敬。這種風格適合波浪捲髮，容易搭配各種服飾。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The modern woven trilby serves as homage to relaxed city chic. Set against beautiful soft waves this style is the ultimate complement to any outfit. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>