<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Nis_Dots_No015</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Personnage 2D: Tink</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドットオブジェ　ジェントルメンな厄介ガエル　ティンク</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">도트 오브제 젠틀맨 민폐 개구리 팅크</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Tink: Gentlefrog" Sprite Statue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">像素雕像 麻煩紳士青蛙TINK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">像素雕像 麻煩紳士青蛙TINK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">2D Character Objects: Tink</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nis_Dots_No015</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Untitled</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La statuette d'un personnage que tu peux mettre dans ta chambre pour décorer.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">『魔界戦記ディスガイア２』のヒロイン・ロザリンドの幼馴染。とある理由で今はカエルの姿に変えられています。元の姿は美少年である（本人談）、かは実際に目撃した方々にお任せします。２重人格持ちというハタ迷惑なカエル。凶暴＆エロスな性格が出る時は姿が赤く染まる。「さぁ遠慮なく抱きしめてトゥナイト！」こちらのセリフに対する苦情はドットオブジェにぶちまけてください。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">『마계전기 디스가이아2』의 히로인 로자린드의 소꿉친구. 어떤 이유로 지금은 개구리의 모습으로 변해있습니다. 원래 모습은 미소년(본인 왈), 인지는 실제로 목격한 분들께 맡기겠습니다. 이중인격을 가진 민폐 개구리. 흉폭&amp;에로스한 성격이 나올 때는 빨개진다.「자, 사양하지 말고 껴안아 줘 오늘밤!」이 대사에 대한 불만은 도트 오브제에 다 털어놓아 주세요.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Tink is a childhood friend of Rozalin, the heroine in "Disgaea 2". And for some unknown reason, he's been changed into a frog. He was originally quite a handsome young man (according to his own account), but it's better to trust someone who actually saw him back then. He has dual personalities which can make him quite an annoying young frog. When he turns red, he is vulgar and violent, saying things like "Come on! You know you want it!" Please direct all complaints to this Sprite Statue. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">他是『魔界戰記 Disgaea 2』の女主角Rozalin的青梅竹馬，因為某種緣故而變身成為青蛙。他原本是美少年（本人說的），至於是真是假就留給見過他本人的目擊者作判斷；是隻有著雙重人格的煩人青蛙，當凶暴與好色的性格出現時會全身變紅。「來吧！不要猶豫了，今晚抱緊我吧！」若對這句話有任何不滿，請向像素雕像提出抗議。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">他是『魔界戰記 Disgaea 2』の女主角Rozalin的青梅竹馬，因為某種緣故而變身成為青蛙。他原本是美少年（本人說的），至於是真是假就留給見過他本人的目擊者作判斷；是隻有著雙重人格的煩人青蛙，當凶暴與好色的性格出現時會全身變紅。「來吧！不要猶豫了，今晚抱緊我吧！」若對這句話有任何不滿，請向像素雕像提出抗議。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A small character statue that you can place to decorate your own room.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>