<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nebulon-interweave power suit (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Costume de puissance tressé au Nebulon (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verwobener Nebulon-Power-Anzug (weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Armatura potenziata ad intecci di nebule (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de poder Nebulon-entretejido (femenino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ネブロン―インターウェーブパワースーツ（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">네브론 - 인터웨이브파워슈트(여성용)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Nebulon-interweave power suit (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">尼布隆織法能量套裝 (女性用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">尼布隆織法能量套裝 (女性用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Nebulon-interweave power suit (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Brainchild of Novus Prime defense technology researcher, Dr. Dimitri Andros, the Nebulon-interweave power suit can be worn under the standard armored gear used by the Earth
Fleet’s fighter pilots.  The power suit is skin-tight, channeling cascades of energy to and from a miraculously tiny Nebulon reactor. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Idée brillante que l'on doit au chercheur Dimitri Andros du 
secteur technologie de défense de Novus Prime, le costume de puissance
 tressé au Nébulon peut se porter sous  les armures strandard qu'utilisaient les pilotes de la flotte terrienne. Le costume de force est moulant, et l'on peut ressentir les afflux d'énergie allant et venant d'un réacteur à Nébulon miraculeusement petit.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dank der genialen Erfindung vom Top-Entwickler von Novus Prime für Verteidigungstechnologoie, Dr. Dimitri Andros, kann der Nebulon-Power-Anzug unter der Standardausrüstung getragen werden, die von Piloten der Erdflotte verwendet wird. Der Power-Anzug ist hauchdünn und bündelt Kaskaden von Energie von und zu einem merkwürdigen, kleinen Nebulon Reaktor. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Frutto del genio del ricercatore sulla tecnologia
della difesa della Novus Prime, Dott. Dimitri Andros,
l'Armatura potenziata ad intrecci di Nebule può
esser indossata sotto l'equipaggiamento di difesa
standard usato dai piloti dei caccia della flotta terrestre.
L'Armatura potenziata è aderente alla pelle, e fa in
modo che si accumulino cascate di energia da e per
gli estremamente minuscoli reattori a nebule. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Obra del investigador de tecnología de defensa Novus Prime, Dr. Dimitri Andros, el traje de poder Nebulon-entretejido puede ser llevado debajo del equipo de armadura estándar usado por los pilotos de combate de la flota de la Tierra. El traje de poder es ajustado, canalizando cascadas de energía desde y hace el milagroso diminuto reactor Nebulon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライム防衛技術開発者、デミトリ・アンドロス博士による大発明、ネブロン―インターウェーブパワースーツは、地球艦隊の戦闘機パイロットに支給される標準的なアーマーギアの下に着ることができる。このタイトなスーツは、奇跡的なサイズにまで小さくなったネブロンリアクターでエネルギーを管理しています。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노버스·프라임 방위기술개발자 -데미토리·앤드로스 박사- 에 의한 대발명, 네브론 - 인터웨이브파워슈트는, 지구함대의 전투기 파일럿에게 지급되는 표준적인 아마기어 밑에 입을 수 있다. 이 타이트한 슈트는, 기적적인 사이즈에까지 작아진 네브론리액터에서 에너지를 관리하고 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Brainchild of Novus Prime defense technology researcher, Dr. Dimitri Andros, the Nebulon-interweave power suit can be worn under the standard armored gear used by the Earth Fleet’s fighter pilots.  The power suit is skin-tight, channeling cascades of energy to and from a miraculously tiny Nebulon reactor. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">由诺凡斯．布莱姆防卫技术研究者，迪米崔．安卓斯博士所发明，这个尼布伦织法的能量套装可以让地球舰队战斗机的驾驶员，穿在一般防护装备里面。这套能量衣轻薄如羽翼，衣服上面的能源电路管布满了微小的尼布伦接收装置。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">由诺凡斯．布莱姆防卫技术研究者，迪米崔．安卓斯博士所发明，这个尼布伦织法的能量套装可以让地球舰队战斗机的驾驶员，穿在一般防护装备里面。这套能量衣轻薄如羽翼，衣服上面的能源电路管布满了微小的尼布伦接收装置。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Brainchild of Novus Prime defense technology researcher, Dr. Dimitri Andros, the Nebulon-interweave power suit can be worn under the standard armored gear used by the Earth Fleet’s fighter pilots.  The power suit is skin-tight, channeling cascades of energy to and from a miraculously tiny Nebulon reactor. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>