<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ethnic Beaded Flower Ring &amp; Bracelet (For Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bague et bracelet floraux ethniques garnis de perles (pour femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blumenring und -armband aus Trachtenperlen (für Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Braccialetto e anello floreale etnico con perline (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de anillo y pulsera de abalorios étnico (para mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ethnic Beaded Flower Ring &amp; Bracelet (For Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A ring and bracelet made of ethnic-style beads. The ring goes on the right hand, and the bracelet on the left. Perfect for those who want to enjoy a look with rustic charm that starts with their hands! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bracelet et bague de perles au style ethnique. La bague se porte à la main droite et le bracelet, à la gauche. Parfaits pour celles qui souhaitent donner à leurs mains un charme rustique ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ring und Armband aus Perlen im Trachtenstil. Der Ring wird an der rechten Hand getragen und das Armband gehört an den linken Arm. Für alle, die einen ländlichen Look bevorzugen und auch die Hände entsprechend kleiden möchten! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Anello e bracciale di perline in stile etnico. L'anello va indossato sulla mano destra, mentre il braccialetto sulla sinistra. Ideale per chi vuole un look semplice a partire dalle mani! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un conjunto de pulsera y anillo hecho con abalorios de estilo étnico. El anillo va en la mano derecha y la pulsera, en la muñeca izquierda. ¡Ideal para quienes buscan un estilo étnico que empiece por las manos! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A ring and bracelet made of ethnic-style beads. The ring goes on the right hand, and the bracelet on the left. Perfect for those who want to enjoy a look with rustic charm that starts with their hands! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>