<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Space Cubes (4) - Glass - White</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cubes de l'Espace (4) - En Verre - Blanc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Space-Cubes (4) - Glas - weiß</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cubi spaziali (4) - vetro - bianchi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cubos espaciales (4) - Cristal - Blanco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Space Cubes (4) - Glass - White</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Space Cubes (4), as in four compartments, are a great way to decorate your Space Apartment. Each Space Cubes (4) set comes with the open, closed and glass versions of your colour choice. Check out the awesome Space Cubes (4) Bundle for more colourful stack ‘em and mismatch ‘em possibilities. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les Cubes de l'Espace (4), avec 4 compartiments, sont une façon formidable de décorer votre Appartement Spatial. Chaque ensemble de Cubes de l'Espace (4) est proposé en version ouverte, fermée ou en verre et vous avez le choix de la couleur. Jetez un oeil sur le super lot Cubes de l'Espace (4) pour plus de possibilités d'agencements multicolores. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Space-Cubes (4), die Viererpackung, eignet sich hervorragend als Dekoration deines Space-Apartments. Jedes Space-Cubes (4) Set enthält eine offene, eine geschlossene und eine Glasvariante in der Farbe deiner Wahl. Beachte auch das geniale Space-Cubes (4) Bundle, mit noch mehr Stapelbarkeit und schrillen Farbkombinationen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I Cubi spaziali (4) sono quattro scaffali perfetti per arredare il tuo Space Apartment. Ogni set è disponibile in una varietà di colori e in versione aperta, chiusa e di vetro. Scopri il meraviglioso pacchetto Cubi spaziali (4) per realizzare abbinamenti variopinti e infiniti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los cubos espaciales (4), con cuatro compartimentos, son una forma fantástica de decorar tu apartamento espacial. Cada lote "cubos espaciales" (4) viene con las versiones abierto, cerrado y cristal, y el color que elijas. No te pierdas el fabuloso lote "cubos espaciales" (4) y descubre nuevas y coloridas posibilidades de apilados y combinados. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Space Cubes (4), as in four compartments, are a great way to decorate your Space Apartment. Each Space Cubes (4) set comes with the open, closed and glass versions of your color choice. Check out the awesome Space Cubes (4) Bundle for more colorful stack ‘em and mismatch ‘em possibilities. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>