<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Sailor-style Summer School Uniform Set (White with Red Scarf, Navy, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set uniforme d'École Marinière d'Été (blanc avec foulard rouge, marine, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Sommerschuluniform Set (weiß mit rotem Schal, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set divise scolastiche estive alla marinaretta (bianche con foulard rosso e gonne blu scuro, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de uniforme escolar de verano estilo marinero (blanco con pañuelo rojo, azul marino, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">夏用セーラー服セット（白＆赤スカーフ，紺・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Sailor-style Summer School Uniform Set (White with Red Scarf, Navy, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">3-item set with white short sleeve sailor-style uniform and navy blue thin pleated skirt, and combination of both. \nYouth Level: ★★★-★★★★\nDefensive Strength: ★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Sailor-style Summer School Uniform (White with Red Scarf, Women) (Tops)\n- Summer School Skirt (Navy, Women) (Bottom)\n- Sailor-style Summer School Uniform, Top &amp; Bottom (White with Red Scarf, Navy, Women) (Combination)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set 3 pièces avec un uniforme blanc style marinière à manches courtes et une jupe plissée légère bleu marine, et une combinaison des deux. \nNiveau de Jeunesse : ★★★-★★★★\nDéfense : ★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Uniforme d'École Marinière d'Été (blanc avec foulard rouge, femme) (Haut)\n- Jupe d'École d'Été (marine, femme) (Bas)\n- Uniforme d'École Marinière d'Été, Haut &amp; Bas (blanc avec foulard rouge, marine, femme) (Combinaison)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">3-teiliges Set bestehend aus einer weißen kurzärmlige Matrosenschuluniform mit einem marineblauen dünngefalteten Rock und eine Kombination aus beidem. \nYouth Level: ★★★-★★★★\nVerteidigung: ★\nDas Set beinhaltet die folgenden Kleidungsstücke:\n\n- Sommerschuluniform (weiß mit rotem Schal, für Frauen) (Oberteil)\n- Sommerschulrock (marineblau, für Frauen) (Unterteil)\n- Sommerschuluniform, Ober- und Unterteil (weiß mit rotem Schal, marineblau, für Frauen) (Kombination)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der enstprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set composto da 3 elementi: una divisa alla marinaretta con camicia a maniche corte e gonna blu scuro, più un completo comprendente entrambi gli oggetti citati.\nLivello giovinezza: ★★★-★★★★\nDifesa: ★\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Divisa scolastica estiva alla marinaretta (bianca con foulard rosso, da donna) (parti superiori)\n- Gonna divisa scolastica estiva (blu scuro, da donna) (parti inferiori)\n- Divisa scolastica estiva alla marinaretta - parte superiore e inferiore (bianca e blu con foulard rosso, da donna) (completo)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de tres artículos con el uniforme estilo marinero de manga corta, la falda plisada azul marino y la combinación de ambos. \nNivel de juventud: ★★★-★★★★\nDefensa: ★\nEste conjunto incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Uniforme escolar de verano estilo marinero (blanco con pañuelo rojo, mujer) (torso)\n- Falda escolar de verano (azul marino, mujer) (piernas)\n- Conjunto de uniforme escolar de verano estilo marinero (blanco con pañuelo rojo, azul marino, mujer)(combinación)\n\n*Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">白い半袖セーラー服と、紺の薄手のプリーツスカートと、その２つの組み合わせの３点セット。\n青春度　: ★★★～★★★★\n防御力　: ★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・夏用セーラー服（白＆赤スカーフ・女性）/ トップス\n・夏用スクールスカート（紺・女性）/ボトムス\n・夏用セーラー服・トップス＋ボトムズ（白＆赤スカーフ，紺・女性）/組み合わせ\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">3-item set with white short sleeve sailor-style uniform and navy blue thin pleated skirt, and combination of both. \nYouth Level: ★★★-★★★★\nDefensive Strength: ★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Sailor-style Summer School Uniform (White with Red Scarf, Women) (Tops)\n- Summer School Skirt (Navy, Women) (Bottom)\n- Sailor-style Summer School Uniform, Top &amp; Bottom (White with Red Scarf, Navy, Women) (Combination)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category. [#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
