<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Weapon Pad – Mechanite Reaper</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plateforme d'arme – Faucheuse en mechanite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">WWaffenpad – Mechanitschnitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pedana armi - Mietitore di mechanite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Panel de armas – Segadora de mechanite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Weapon Pad – Mechanite Reaper</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Place this item in your MiniBots Training Facility to allow Mechanite Reapers to be equipped. Anyone who owns the Mechanite Reaper hand item can equip the Mechanite Reaper at this pad during a multiplayer game. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Placez cet élément dans votre centre d'entraînement MiniBots pour qu'il soit possible de s'équiper avec les faucheuses en mechanite. N'importe qui peut s'équiper avec la faucheuse en mechanit de cette plateforme pendant une partie multijoueur s'il possède l'élément de main faucheuse en mechanite. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Platzieren Sie dieses Objekt in Ihre MiniBots-Trainingsanlage, damit Mechanitschnitter damit ausgestattet werden kann. Jeder der das Mechanitschnitter-Handobjekt besitzt, kann das Mechanitschnitter in diesem Pad in einem Multiplayer-Spiel bestücken.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Colloca questo elemento nella struttura di addestramento Minibot per consentire l'equipaggiamento con Mietitore del mechanite. Chiunque possieda l'elemento Mietitore del mechanite può dotarsene in questa pedana durante una partita in modalità multigiocatore. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Coloca este artículo en tus instalaciones de entrenamiento de MiniBots para permitir que las Segadoras de mechanite estén equipados. Cualquier propietario del artículo de mano Segadora de mechanit puede equipar la Segadora de mechanite en este panel durante una partida para varios jugadores. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Place this item in your MiniBots Training Facility to allow Mechanite Reapers to be equipped. Anyone who owns the Mechanite Reaper hand item can equip the Mechanite Reaper at this pad during a multiplayer game. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>