<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hollyridge Estate – Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Hollyridge Estate – club-house</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hollyridge Estate – Clubhaus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hollyridge Estate - sedi di club</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hollyridge Estate - sedes de clubes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Hollyridge Estate – Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hollyridge Estate – Clubhouse</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Hollyridge Estate is the  perfect setting for an elegant winter soiree! This personal space features classic Victorian architecture and design and also features built-in decorating options which allow you to create a festive atmosphere without taking up any furniture slots! Includes customizable wallpaper, a snowball fight minigame and much more! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Hollyridge Estate est le lieu idéal pour une soirée d'hiver raffinée ! Cet club-house présente une architecture et un design victoriens classiques, ainsi que des options de décoration intégrées vous permettant de créer une atmosphère festivesans prendre les emplacements de meubles. Comprend fond d'écran personnalisable, un combat mini-jeu de boule de neige et beaucoup plus! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Hollyridge Estate ist die perfekte Umgebung für einen eleganten Winterabend! Diese Clubhaus Note beruhen auf klassischer viktorianischer Architektur und Design, und sie beinhalten auch eingebaute Dekorationsoptionen, mit denen Slots Möbel. Beinhaltet anpassbare Tapeten, eine Schneeballschlacht Minispiel und vieles mehr! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La tenuta Hollyridge è l'ambiente perfetto per un'elegante serata invernale! Questo sedi di club presenta un design e un'architettura in classico stile vittoriano, nonché opzioni integrate decorative che ti permettono di creare un'atmosfera festosa senza occupare spazio sui mobili! Comprende uno sfondo personalizzabile, un minigioco con battaglia a palle di neve e molto altro ancora! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Hollyridge Estate es el escenario perfecto para una elegante velada de invierno! Este sedes de clubes cuenta con una arquitectura y un diseño de estilo clásico victoriano, así como opciones de decoración integradas que permiten crear un ambiente festivo sin ocupar espacio con muebles. ¡Incluye fondos de escritorio personalizables, un minijuego de batalla de bolas de nieve y mucho más! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Hollyridge Estate is the  perfect setting for an elegant winter soiree! This personal space features classic Victorian architecture and design and also features built-in decorating options which allow you to create a festive atmosphere without taking up any furniture slots! Includes customizable wallpaper, a snowball fight minigame and much more! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Hollyridge Estate is the  perfect setting for an elegant winter soiree! This personal space features classic Victorian architecture and design and also features built-in decorating options which allow you to create a festive atmosphere without taking up any furniture slots! Includes customizable wallpaper, a snowball fight minigame and much more! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>