<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Fossil Collection Plates Set (for coral)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set plateaux de collection de fossiles (pour coraux)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Eine Tafel zur Fossiliensammlung (für Korallen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set di tavole per la collezione di fossili (per coralli)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego placas de colección de fósiles (para coral)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">化石収集プレートセット（サンゴ用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">화석수집 플레이트 세트(산호용)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Fossil Collection Plates Set (for corals)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">化石收集盤組合包（用於珊瑚）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">化石收集盤組合包（用於珊瑚）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Fossil Collection Plates Set (for coral)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 2-piece set of collection plates for displaying coral fossils.\nThis set contains the following items:\n\n- Old Fossil Collection Plate (for coral)(Decoration)\n- Brand New Fossil Collection Plate (for coral)(Decoration)\n\n * Upon purchase, each item in the applicable category will be added. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de deux pièces de plateaus de collection pour exposer les fossiles de coraux.\nCe set contient les objets suivants:\n\n- Ancienne plateau de collection de fossiles (pour coraux)(Décoration)\n- plateau de collection de fossiles toute neuve (pour coraux)(Décoration)\n\n * Après l’achat chaque article sera ajouté à leur catégorie respective. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein zweitteiliger Satz aus Sammeltellern, mit dem Korallenfossilien zur Schau gestellt werden können.\nDieser Satz enthält die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Alte Tafel zur Fossiliensammlung (für Korallen)(Dekoration)\n- Brandneue Tafel zur Fossiliensammlung (für Korallen)(Dekoration)\n\n * Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand in entsprechender Kategorie hinzugefügt. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set di 2 tavole per la collezione e l'esposizione di fossili di corallo.\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Vecchia tavola per la collezione di fossili (per coralli)(decorazione)\n-Ultimo modello di tavola per la collezione di fossili (per coralli)(decorazione)\n\n*Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce\nsopra elencata nella specifica categoria. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Un juego 2 piezas de placas para exhibición de fósiles de coral.\nEste juego contiene los siguientes objetos:\n\n- Placa antigua de colección de fósiles (para coral) (adorno)\n- Placa nueva de colección de fósiles (para coral) (adorno)\n\n * Después de la compra, cada objeto será agregado a la categoría a la que aplica. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">サンゴの化石をピッタリ収めて飾ることが出来る収集プレートの2枚セット。\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・古めかしい化石収集プレート（サンゴ用）（装飾品）\n・真新しい化石収集プレート（サンゴ用）（装飾品）\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">산호 화석을 딱 맞게 끼워 장식할 수 있는 수집 플레이트의 2매 세트. \n본 세트에는, 하기의 아이템이 포함되어 있습니다.\n\n●고풍스러운 화석 수집 플레이트(산호용)(장식품)\n●최신의 화석 수집 플레이트(산호용)(장식품)\n\n※구입하면, 해당 카테고리에 각 아이템이 추가됩니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">A set of 2 plates that is perfectly suited to mounting and displaying coral fossils. \n This set includes the following items: \n\n・Antiquated Fossil Collection Plate (for corals) (Ornament)\n・Brand-new Fossil Collection Plate (for corals) (Ornament)\n\n Upon purchase, all items will be placed into their respective categories.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">適合用來收納和裝飾珊瑚化石的收集盤，一套兩件。\n本組合包包括以下道具。\n\n●古舊的化石收集盤（用於珊瑚）（裝飾品）\n●全新的化石收集盤（用於珊瑚）（裝飾品）\n\n※購買後，各道具將被加進相對類別內。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">適合用來收納和裝飾珊瑚化石的收集盤，一套兩件。\n本組合包包括以下道具。\n\n●古舊的化石收集盤（用於珊瑚）（裝飾品）\n●全新的化石收集盤（用於珊瑚）（裝飾品）\n\n※購買後，各道具將被加進相對類別內。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 2-piece set of collection plates for displaying coral fossils.\nThis set contains the following items:\n\n- Old Fossil Collection Plate (for coral)(Decoration)\n- Brand New Fossil Collection Plate (for coral)(Decoration)\n\n * Upon purchase, each item in the applicable category will be added. [#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
