<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Khul Mercali Raider's Shield</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bouclier de soldat Khul Mercali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Khul-Mercali-Räuberschild</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scudo del razziatore Khul Mercali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Escudo de asaltante Khul Mercali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Khul Mercali Raider's Shield</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Built for close-quarters combat style of a Mercian Fighter.\n\nMade from mighty oak and adorned with the horns of fierce creatures, this shield can withstand the onslaught of battle but is light enough for a Warrior to charge into the fray.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Conçu pour le style de combat rapproché du guerrier mercian.\n\nFabriqué à partir d'un solide chêne et orné de cornes de créatures féroces, ce bouclier peut résister à la fureur des assauts mais est suffisamment léger pour permettre au guerrier de charger.\n\nDÉBLOQUE DES ARTICLES DU JEU MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS – N'OFFRE PAS DE COMPOSANTS D'AVATAR POUR UN USAGE GÉNÉRAL SUR PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBLE POUR LES UTILISATEURS DU JAPON ET DE L'ASIE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Speziell auf den Nahkampf-Stil der Mercia-Kämpfer ausgelegt.\n\nDieser Schild ist aus dem Holz einer mächtigen Eiche gefertigt und mit Hörnern wilder Kreaturen verziert. Er kann starken Angriffen standhalten, doch ist leicht genug, dass der Krieger sich in der Schlacht mühelos bewegen kann.\n\nZUM FREISCHALTEN VON GEGENSTÄNDEN IN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS - NICHT ZUM ERHALT VON AVATAR-KOMPONENTEN ZUR ALLGEMEINEN NUTZUNG AUF PLAYSTATION®HOME. NICHT VERFÜGBAR FÜR BENUTZER IN JAPAN UND ASIEN [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Perfetto per il combattimento corpo a corpo del guerriero Mercian.\n\nFatto di potente legno di quercia e decorato con le corna di feroci creature, questo scudo resiste ai colpi della battaglia, ma è abbastanza leggero per permettere al guerriero di caricare in mischia.\n\nSBLOCCA OGGETTI ALL'INTERNO DEL GIOCO MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS. NON REGALA COMPONENTI PER AVATAR PER USO GENERICO CON PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBILE PER GLI UTENTI IN ASIA E GIAPPONE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Creado para el estilo de combate cuerpo a cuerpo de un luchador de Mercia.\n\nFabricado con un fuerte roble y adornado con los cuernos de feroces criaturas, este escudo puede soportar el embate de la batalla pero es lo suficientemente ligero para que un guerrero cargue en el fragor del combate.\n\nDESBLOQUEARÁ ELEMENTOS EN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS GAME. NO REGALARÁ COMPONENTES DE AVATAR PARA EL USO GENERAL EN CASA DE PLAYSTATION. NO DISPONIBLE PARA LOS USUARIOS DE JAPÓN Y ASIA. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Built for close-quarters combat style of a Mercian Fighter.\n\nMade from mighty oak and adorned with the horns of fierce creatures, this shield can withstand the onslaught of battle but is light enough for a Warrior to charge into the fray.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>