<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Starter Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Débutants emballer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Starter-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto iniziale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de inicio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* Starter Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Starter Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Starter Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Starter Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Starter Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Starter Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The starter pack comes with both fish and decorations included. The fish included are: Neon Tetra, Guppy, Fantail, Electric Yellow Cichlid. Decorations included: Blue Brush Coral, Purple Ludwigia, Purple Hygrophylia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Débutants emballer est livré avec les poissons et les décorations incluses. Les poissons sont inclus: Neon Tetra, Guppy, Fantail, Electric Yellow Cichlid. Décorations inclus: Blue Brush Coral, Ludwigia - Pourpre, Hygrophylia - Pourpre.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Starter-Paket kommt mit beiden Fische und Dekorationen enthalten. Der Fisch enthalten sind: Neon Tetra, Guppy, Fantail, Electric Yellow Cichlid. Dekorationen enthalten: Blue Brush Coral, Ludwigia - lila, Hygrophylia - lila. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il pacchetto iniziale viene fornita sia con pesci e decorazioni inclusi. I pesci sono inclusi: Neon Tetra, Guppy, Fantail, Electric Yellow Cichlid. Decorazioni incluso: Blue Brush Coral, Ludwigia - Porpora, Hygrophylia - Porpora. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El paquete de inicio incluye tanto a los peces y decoraciones incluidos. El pescado se incluyen: Neon Tetra, Guppy, Fantail, Electric Yellow Cichlid. Decoraciones incluido: Blue Brush Coral, Ludwigia - Púrpura, Hygrophylia - Púrpura.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The starter pack comes with both fish and decorations included. The fish included are: Neon Tetra, Guppy, Fantail, Electric Yellow Cichlid. Decorations included: Blue Brush Coral, Purple Ludwigia, Purple Hygrophylia. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>