<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mahjong apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appartement Mahjong</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mahjong-Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Appartamento di Mahjong</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apartamento Mahjong</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オリエントハウス</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">마종 솔리테르 퍼스널 스페이스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Mahjong Solitaire Personal Space</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">麻將接龍個人空間</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">麻將接龍個人空間</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mahjong apartment</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Looking for a nice and tranquil place to stay? The Mahjong apartment is just the place! This walled apartment in an busy Orient city is an oasis of rest with blossom trees and koi carps. If you are looking for something more lively you can try the Mahjong Attack game that comes with the apartment. Mahjong Attack is a challenging variant of Mahjong Solitaire which is all about speed! You play the game alone (single player), together with your friends (co-op) or against your friends (multiplayer)! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous cherchez un logement agréable et tranquille ? L'appartement Mahjong est fait pour vous ! Cet appartement clos, situé dans une ville animée d'Orient, est une oasis de paix entourée d'arbres et peuplée de carpes koï. Si vous recherchez quelque chose plus vivant, essayez le jeu Mahjong Attack qui accompagne l'appartement. Mahjong Attack est une nouvelle variante du Mahjong Solitaire basée sur la rapidité ! Vous pouvez jouer seul, faire équipe avec vos amis (co-op) ou encore les affronter (multijoueur) ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Auf der Suche nach einem schönen, ruhigen Ort? Dann ist das Mahjong-Apartment genau das Richtige! Dieser von Mauern umgebene Bereich in einer lebhaften, asiatischen Stadt ist eine Oase der Ruhe mit blühenden Bäumen und Koi-Karpfen. Wer auf der Suche nach etwas Rasanterem ist, der kann "Mahjong Attack" spielen, das im Apartment verfügbar ist. "Mahjong Attack" ist eine anspruchsvolle Variante von "Solitair Mahjong", in der es um Schnelligkeit geht! Das Spiel kann alleine (Einzelspieler), zusammen mit Freunden (Koop) oder gegen Freunde (Multiplayer) gespielt werden. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stai cercando un posto bello e tranquillo? Allora l'appartamento di Mahjong fa al caso tuo! Questo appartamento recintato si trova in una trafficata città orientale ma è un'oasi di pace con alberi in fiore e carpe Koi. Se vuoi qualcosa di più vivace, prova il gioco Mahjong Attack disponibile insieme all'appartamento. Mahjong Attack è una entusiasmante variante del classico gioco in solitario in cui il fattore determinante è la velocità! Puoi giocare da solo (partita in solitario), insieme ai tuoi amici (partita cooperativa) oppure contro i tuoi amici (partita in multigiocatore)! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Necesitas un lugar tranquilo y agradable para quedarte? ¡El apartamento Mahjong es lo que estabas buscando! El apartamento vallado situado en una concurrida ciudad oriental es un oasis de descanso decorado con cerezos en flor y carpas koi. Si buscas algo un poco más movidito, puedes echar una partida al juego Mahjong Attack que viene con el apartamento. Mahjong Attack es una variante desafiante del solitario Mahjong tradicional, que se basa sobre todo en la rapidez. ¡Puedes jugar solo (un jugador), con tus amigos (modo cooperativo) o contra ellos (multijugador)! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">素敵で落ち着きのある場所をお探しでしたら、オリエントハウスはまさに最適！花が咲き、鯉が回遊するこのパーソナルスペースは、都市の喧騒から隔てられた憩いの場です。より刺激的なものをお求めでしたら、このパーソナルスペースにある「麻雀アタック」をプレイしてみてはいかがでしょう。「麻雀アタック」には一人用のシングルプレイモード、友人と協力するCO-OPモード、友人と競うマルチプレイモードの３つのゲームモードが楽しめます！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">고요하고 아름다운 휴식처를 찾고 있나요? 마종 솔리테르 퍼스널 스페이스를 만나 보십시오! 바쁘게 움직이는 동양의 어느 도시에 자리잡은, 담장이 둘러진 아파트입니다. 아파트에는 마종 어택 게임이 포함되어 있으며, 언제든 플레이할 수 있습니다. 마종 어택은 마종 솔리테르에서 변형된 게임이며, 속도를 중시합니다. 혼자 플레이하거나, 친구들과 협동 모드 또는 경쟁 모드에서 멀티플레이를 즐길 수 있습니다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Looking for a nice and tranquil place to stay? The Mahjong Solitaire Personal Space is just the place! This walled apartment in an busy Orient city is an oasis of rest with blossom trees and koi carps. If you are looking for something more lively you can try the Mahjong Attack game that comes with the apartment. Mahjong Attack is a challenging variant of Mahjong Solitaire which is all about speed! You play the game alone (single player), together with your friends (co-op) or against your friends (multiplayer)! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">尋找一個好的寧靜停留地點？這個麻將接龍個人空間正是您需要的地方！這個位於繁忙的東方城市圍牆中的公寓，是一個擁有花開樹木和錦鯉魚池的休閒綠洲。如果您正在尋找更生動的東西，你可以嘗試公寓內的麻將襲擊遊戲。麻將襲擊是一個具有挑戰性的變種麻將接龍遊戲，遊戲特徵在於速度！你可以自己遊玩遊戲（單人），跟你的朋友一起遊玩（協力），或跟你的朋友對戰（多人）！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">尋找一個好的寧靜停留地點？這個麻將接龍個人空間正是您需要的地方！這個位於繁忙的東方城市圍牆中的公寓，是一個擁有花開樹木和錦鯉魚池的休閒綠洲。如果您正在尋找更生動的東西，你可以嘗試公寓內的麻將襲擊遊戲。麻將襲擊是一個具有挑戰性的變種麻將接龍遊戲，遊戲特徵在於速度！你可以自己遊玩遊戲（單人），跟你的朋友一起遊玩（協力），或跟你的朋友對戰（多人）！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Looking for a nice and tranquil place to stay? The Mahjong apartment is just the place! This walled apartment in an busy Orient city is an oasis of rest with blossom trees and koi carps. If you are looking for something more lively you can try the Mahjong Attack game that comes with the apartment. Mahjong Attack is a challenging variant of Mahjong Solitaire which is all about speed! You play the game alone (single player), together with your friends (co-op) or against your friends (multiplayer)! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>