<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Spacewalk Blaster Pistol (bundle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pistolet à impulsion pour escapade spatiale (lot)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blasterpistole für den Weltraumspaziergang (paket)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pistola blaster per attività extraveicolari (pacchetto)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pistola explosiva de paseo espacial (paquete)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スペースウォークブラスターピストルセット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">우주 유영용 블래스터 권총 세트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Spacewalk Blaster Pistol (bundle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">太空漫步激光槍組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">太空漫步激光槍組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Spacewalk Blaster Pistol (bundle)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This state-of-the-art laser pistol allows Space-walkers to defend the station by destroying bot crawlers. It can function under all gravity levels, including zero-G. This pistol is worn as a hand item. This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce pistolet laser dernier cri permet aux personnes effectuant des sorties dans l'espace de défendre la station contre les droïdes de récolte. Il peut fonctionner dans tous les niveaux de gravité, y compris en apesanteur. Ce pistolet laser est un objet à tenir en main. Ce lot comprend les versions homme et femme. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese supermoderne Laserpistole erlaubt es Weltraumspaziergängern, die Station durch das Vernichten von Bot-Crawlern zu verteidigen. Sie funktioniert auf allen Schwerkraft-Ebenen, einschließlich Schwerelosigkeit. Diese Pistole wird als Ausrüstungsgegenstand in der Hand getragen. Dieses Paket enthält sowohl männliche als auch weibliche Versionen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una moderna pistola laser atta a difendere la stazione dai bot che vi strisciano sopra. È efficace a qualsiasi livello di gravità, anche a zero-G. Deve essere impugnata come arma da mano. Il pacchetto comprende sia la versione femminile sia quella maschile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta innovadora pistola láser permite a los caminantes espaciales defender la estación destruyendo rastreadores robot. Puede funcionar en todos los niveles de gravedad, incluida la fuerza G cero. Esta pistola se lleva como artículo de mano. Este paquete incluye las versiones masculina y femenina. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この最新鋭レーザーピストルなら、ボットクローラーを破壊してステーションを守ることができる。無重力を含むどんな重力条件下でも機能する。\n※身につけると、ミニゲーム「スペースウォーク」内でクローラーを撃つことができます。\n\n本セットには、アバターのカスタマイズ用の以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n・「スペースウォークブラスターピストル（男性用）」（手）\n・「スペースウォークブラスターピストル（女性用）」（手）\n※購入すると、「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">최첨단 레이저 권총으로 우주유영 중에 봇 크롤러를 파괴하고 정거장을 지키는 데 유용합니다. 어떤 중력 하에서도 작동하며, 심지어 무중력 상태에서도 사용할 수 있습니다. 이 권총은 손에 쥐는 물건으로 장착됩니다. 이 번들에는 남성용과 여성용이 모두 포함되어 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This state-of-the-art laser pistol allows Space-walkers to defend the station by destroying bot crawlers. It can function under all gravity levels, including zero-G. This pistol is worn as a hand item. This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這支高科技的激光槍讓太空漫步者擊倒機械爬行獸，保護太空站。這款手部道具能在所有重力環境（包括零重力）下運作。本組合包包括男用及女用。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這支高科技的激光槍讓太空漫步者擊倒機械爬行獸，保護太空站。這款手部道具能在所有重力環境（包括零重力）下運作。本組合包包括男用及女用。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This state-of-the-art laser pistol allows Space-walkers to defend the station by destroying bot crawlers. It can function under all gravity levels, including zero-G. This pistol is worn as a hand item. This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>