<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Venice Stroll Dress - Black (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Robe Venice Stroll - Noir (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Venice Stroll Kleid - Schwarz (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Venice Stroll Vestito - Nero (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Venice Stroll Vestido - Negro (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This dress is the most iconic piece of Alex Spencer’s 4th and Bleeker for Billabong collection. It has a striking silhouette with cut out sides and back. A stand out piece for every fashionista’s wardrobe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette robe est la pièce la plus emblématique d'Alex Spencer’s 4th et Bleeker pour la collection Billabong. Elle dessine une silhouette saisissante avec ses côtés et son dos ajourés. Une pièce incontournable de toute garde-robe branchée. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Venice Stroll Kleid ist das ikonische Kleid von 4th and Bleekers Alex Spencer für die Billabong Kollektion. Mit seiner augenfälligen Silhouette mit Seitenschlitzen und Rückenausschnitten ist dieses Kleid das Stück, das im Kleiderschrank keiner modebewussten Frau fehlen darf. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo vestito è il pezzo più emblematico della collezione 4th and Bleeker di Alex Spencer per Billabong. Presenta una silhouette di effetto con ritagli sui lati e sulla schiena. Un capo imperdibile per ogni vera fashionista. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este vestido es la prenda más icónica del 4th and Bleeker de Alex Spencer, diseñada para la colección de Billabong. Presenta una imponente silueta con espalda y lados recortados. Una prenda a destacar en el armario de cualquier amante de la moda. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>