<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Yukata Top (Shishimai, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Haut de Yukata (Shishimai, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Yukata-Oberteil (Shishimai, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Yukata parte superiore (Shishimai, U)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Parte superior de Yukata (Shishimai, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">浴衣・上（男性・獅子舞）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">유카타 상의(남성, 사자 춤)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Yukata Top (Men/Lion dance)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">日式浴衣 上 (男用／獅子舞）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">日式浴衣 上 (男用／獅子舞）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Yukata Top (Shishimai, M)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A single-layer kimono dyed a light blue, with a shishimai (lion dance) motif featured on the hem. This is only the top half, above the obi belt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un kimono composé d'une seule couche teint en bleu clair et orné de motifs de shishimai (danse du lion). C'est seulement le haut, au-dessus de la ceinture obi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein einfacher, hellblau eingefärbter Kimono aus Baumwolle mit einem Shishimai-Motiv (Löwentanz) auf dem Saum. Dies ist nur die obere Hälfte, die sich oberhalb des Obigürtels befindet.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un kimono leggero tinto in blu pallido e decorato con uno Shishimai (leone cinese danzante). Solo la parte superiore, dalla cintola (obi) in su.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un kimono de algodón de una sola capa teñido de color azul claro con un motivo shishimai (baile de león) en el dobladillo. Esto solo es la parte superior, por encima del cinturón obi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">淡い青色に染めた浴衣の裾に、獅子頭（ししがしら）が描かれている、ひとえの着物。帯より上の半身。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">희미한 청색으로 물들인 유카타의 옷자락에 사자의 탈이 그려져 있는 전통 복장. 허리띠 위의 상의.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">An unlined kimono top with baby blue dyed hemming and a lion mask drawn on it.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在染成淺藍色的下擺印上獅子頭的一重和服。腰帶之上的上半身部份。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在染成淺藍色的下擺印上獅子頭的一重和服。腰帶之上的上半身部份。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A single-layer kimono dyed a light blue, with a shishimai (lion dance) motif featured on the hem. This is only the top half, above the obi belt.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>