<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tattoo and Lace Corset Bundle (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack corsets et tatouages (pour Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tattoo und Schnürkorsett-Paket (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Tatuaggi e corsetti di pizzo (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de tatuajes y corsés (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">문신과 레이스 코르셋 번들 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Tattoo and Lace Corset Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">紋身及花邊緊身上衣組合包（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">紋身及花邊緊身上衣組合包（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Tattoo and Lace Corset Bundle (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">These corsets will be a great addition to your wardrobe. Bundle includes the Butterfly Tattoo and Lace Corset, Rose Tattoo and Lace Corset, and Angel Wings Tattoo and Lace Corset. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ces corsets trouveront naturellement leur place dans votre garde-robe. Le pack comprend le corset et tatouage papillon, le corset et tatouage rose et le corset et tatouage ailes d'ange. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese Korsetts machen sich in deinem Kleiderschrank wunderbar. Im Paket enthalten sind Schmetterling-Tattoo und Schnürkorsett, Rosen-Tattoo und Schnürkorsett sowie Engelsflügel-Tattoo und Schnürkorsett. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dei corsetti per arricchire alla grande il tuo guardaroba. Il pacchetto include tre tatuaggi (farfalla, rosa e ali d'angelo) e tre corsetti di pizzo abbinati. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estos corsés serán una magnífica incorporación para tu fondo de armario. El conjunto incluye el tatuaje de mariposa y corsé de encaje, el tatuaje de rosa y corsé de encaje y el tatuaje de alas de ángel y corsé de encaje. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">당신의 옷장을 멋지게 채워 주는 세 종류의 탱크탑입니다. 이 번들은 나비 문신과 레이스 코르셋, 장미 문신과 레이스 코르셋, 그리고 천사 날개 문신과 레이스 코르셋을 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">These three tank tops will be a great addition to your wardrobe. Bundle includes the Butterfly Tattoo and Lace Corset, Rose Tattoo and Lace Corset, and Angel Wings Tattoo and Lace Corset. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這三款緊身上衣能為你的衣帽間錦上添花。組合包包括蝴蝶紋身及花邊緊身上衣、玫瑰紋身及花邊緊身上衣及天使翅膀紋身及花邊緊身上衣。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這三款緊身上衣能為你的更衣室錦上添花。組合包包括蝴蝶紋身及花邊緊身上衣、玫瑰紋身及花邊緊身上衣及天使翅膀紋身及花邊緊身上衣。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">These three corsets will be a great addition to your wardrobe. Bundle includes the Butterfly Tattoo and Lace Corset, Rose Tattoo and Lace Corset, and Angel Wings Tattoo and Lace Corset. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>