<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gothic Lolita Dress - Starry</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gothic Lolita Dress - Starry</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Gothic Lolita Dress - Starry</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Vestido Gothic Lolita - Estrellado</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Robe Gothic Lolita - Étoilée</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gothic Lolita Kleid – Sternenhimmel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Abito Gothic Lolita - Stellato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴシックロリータドレス - スターリー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">고딕 로리타 드레스 - 스타리</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">哥德蘿莉塔洋裝 - 星空款</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">哥德蘿莉塔連身裙 - 星夜款</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Step into a midnight fairytale with this elegant navy dress, dusted in delicate stars. Lace trim and a velvet bow complete the celestial Lolita charm. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Step into a midnight fairytale with this elegant navy dress, dusted in delicate stars. Lace trim and a velvet bow complete the celestial Lolita charm. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Step into a midnight fairytale with this elegant navy dress, dusted in delicate stars. Lace trim and a velvet bow complete the celestial Lolita charm. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Entra en un cuento de hadas nocturno con este elegante vestido azul marino, adornado con delicadas estrellas. Encaje y un lazo de terciopelo completan su encanto celestial estilo Lolita. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plonge dans un conte de fées nocturne avec cette élégante robe bleu marine parsemée d’étoiles délicates. Finitions en dentelle et nœud en velours pour un charme Lolita céleste. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Betritt ein Mitternachtsmärchen in diesem eleganten marineblauen Kleid, bestäubt mit feinen Sternen. Spitzenbesatz und eine Samtschleife vollenden den himmlischen Lolita-Charme. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vivi una favola di mezzanotte con questo elegante abito blu navy, cosparso di stelline delicate. Rifinito con pizzo e un fiocco di velluto per un incanto Lolita celestiale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">繊細な星々がきらめくエレガントなネイビードレスで、真夜中の童話の世界へ。レースの縁取りとベルベットのリボンがロリータの天体的な魅力を引き立てます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">섬세한 별빛이 흩뿌려진 우아한 네이비 드레스로 한밤중의 동화 속으로. 레이스 장식과 벨벳 리본이 고딕 로리타의 천상 매력을 완성합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">穿上這件優雅的藏青色洋裝，踏入星夜童話。點綴細緻星星、蕾絲滾邊與絲絨蝴蝶結，完美展現哥德蘿莉塔的星辰魅力。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">穿上這條優雅的深藍色連身裙，彷彿走進午夜童話。細緻星星點綴、蕾絲滾邊與天鵝絨蝴蝶結，展現星空系哥德蘿莉塔風格。 [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>