<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sony internet tv</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sony internet tv</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sony-Internetfernsehen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Sony internet TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sony internet tv</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">To celebrate the launch of Sony internet tv you can download this model of the TV for your personal space. Sony internet tv brings you the best of the Internet straight to your TV screen by seamlessly streaming online content through your broadband connection. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour fêter le lancement du service Sony internet tv, vous pouvez télécharger ce modèle de téléviseur pour votre espace personnel. Sony internet tv vous offre le meilleur du web directement sur votre écran de télé, grâce à un flux de streaming continu passant par votre connexion haut-débit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Um die Veröffentlichung des Sony-Internetfernsehens zu feiern, können Sie dieses Fernsehermodell für Ihr persönliches Apartment herunterladen. Sony-Internetfernsehen bringt Ihnen durch nahtloses Streaming von Online-Inhalten über Ihre Breitbandverbindung das Beste, was das Internet zu bieten hat, direkt auf Ihren Fernsehbildschirm. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per celebrare il lancio della Sony internet TV è possibile scaricare questo modello di TV per il tuo spazio personale. La Sony internet TV ti fornisce il meglio della rete direttamente sul tuo schermo televisivo tramite contenuti streaming online grazie alla tua connessione a banda larga. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Para celebrar el lanzamiento de Sony internet tv, ahora puedes descargar este modelo de televisor para tu espacio personal. Sony internet tv te trae lo mejor de Internet directamente a la pantalla de tu televisor. Disfruta de todo el contenido en línea sin cortes a través de tu conexión de banda ancha. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>