<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Caserne Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Raven-Kaserne</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caserma Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Barracones de Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">兵舎 レーヴン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Raven 병영</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raven軍營</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raven軍營</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Raven Barracks</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Situées dans une forêt équatoriale, les casernes Raven seront votre petit coin de paradis. Vous aimerez les ruines anciennes, les oiseaux endémiques et la merveilleuse flore, protégés par des barricades en fibres composites, un sismographe et un détachement de gardes Raven.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Raven-Kaserne liegt im Regenwald am Äquator und ist Ihr kleines Stück vom Paradies. Genießen Sie die antiken Ruinen, exotischen Vögel und wunderschönen Pflanzen und natürlich die Kompositfaser-Barrikaden, seismischen Sensornetze und Ihren Elite-Wachposten.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caserma Raven - Situata nella foresta equatoriale, la caserma Raven è un pezzetto di paradiso. Le rovine antiche, la fauna locale e la flora rigogliosa sono protette da barricate in fibra composita, una griglia di sensori sismici e un distaccamento di guardie d'élite della Raven.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Barracones de Raven - Situados en la selva ecuatoriana, los barracones de Raven son todo un paraíso. Puedes disfrutar de las antiguas ruinas, las aves autóctonas y la hermosa vegetación decorada con barricadas de fibra compuesta, una red de sensores sísmicos y los centinelas de élite de Raven.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">レーヴンの兵舎　―　熱帯雨林の中にあるレーヴンの兵舎では楽園を味わうことができる。廃墟と化した遺跡や、美しく珍しい鳥類、合成ファイバーで強化されたバリケードに生える神秘的な植物。エリート集団であるレーヴンに相応しい兵舎である。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">적도 지역의 다우림에 위치한 Raven 병영은 조그만 천국과도 같습니다. 고대의 유적과 이름 모르는 새들, 아름다운 식물 등이 강화 합성 저지대와 지표탐지기, 그리고 정예 Raven 정찰병들에 의해 지켜지고 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">位於熱帶雨林的Ravan軍營，著實是你一嘗身處天堂滋味的地方。在這裡，你可找到古代遺址、原生雀鳥和美麗的植物群，並由複合纖維街壘、地震感測網格和Raven的精英支隊哨兵加以防禦。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">位於熱帶雨林的Ravan軍營，著實是你一嘗身處天堂滋味的地方。在這裡，你可找到古代遺址、原生雀鳥和美麗的植物群，並由複合纖維街壘、地震感測網格和Raven的精英支隊哨兵加以防禦。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Located in an equatorial rain forest, the Raven barracks is your little slice of paradise. You’ll enjoy the ancient ruins, native birds, and beautiful flora fortified by composite fiber barricades, a seismic sensor grid and your elite Raven sentry detachment.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>