<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Crossfire Shorts - Military Camo (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Short Crossfire - Camouflage militaire (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Crossfire Shorts - Militärfarbe (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Crossfire Shorts - Mimetico Militare (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Crossfire Pantalón corto - Camuflaje militar (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There's no denying the Crossfire Solid's impressive look and style. This walkshort is fully submersible, clean and totally versatile. Features include chino styling, new welded wave labels, a zippered back pocket, and internal pocket print. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C'est indéniable : Crossfire Solid a un look stylé. Ce short de rue résiste à l'eau : il est donc élégant et totalement versatile. Avec poches chinos, nouveaux motifs vagues, poche arrière à fermeture éclair et poche interne imprimée. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kein Zweifel: die Crossfire Solid Chino-Shorts imponieren durch Stil und Aussehen. Zudem können die vielseitigen Wandershorts auch als Badeshorts dienen. Zu besonderen Eigenschaften zählen die neuen geschweißten Wellenlogos, eine Gesäßtasche mit Reißverschluss und die innen bedruckten Taschen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non c'è dubbio che gli shorts Crossfire Solid hanno un look e uno stile impressionante. Il capo è perfetto in acqua, pulito e completamente versatile. Presentano taglio in stile chino, nuove etichette dell'onda, tasca posteriore con zip e tasca interna. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Es innegable el impresionante aspecto y estilo del Crossfire Solid. Este pantalón corto es totalmente sumergible, sencillo y versátil. Entre sus características está el estilo "chino", nuevas etiquetas con la imagen de la ola, un bolsillo trasero de cremallera y estampado en bolsillo interno. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>