<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ninjutsu Warrior - Assassin 暗殺者 (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guerrier Ninjutsu - Assassin 暗殺者 (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ninjutsu-Krieger - Assassine 暗殺者 (Mann)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guerriero Ninjutsu - Assassino 暗殺者 (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guerrero Ninjutsu: asesino 暗殺者 (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">忍者・暗殺者（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">닌자 워리어 - 암살자 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ninjutsu Warrior - Assassin (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">忍者 — 暗殺忍者（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">忍者 — 暗殺忍者（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ninjutsu Warrior - Assassin 暗殺者 (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Transform into a ninja assassin and carve your place in history. Creep silently in the shadows or back flip out in the open - either way everyone will know to treat you with respect. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Transformez-vous en ninja assassin et gravez votre nom dans l’histoire. Faufilez-vous dans l’ombre en silence, ou faites un salto arrière en pleine lumière – quel que soit votre choix, chacun vous devra le respect. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verwandle dich in einen Ninja-Assassinen und schreibe Geschichte. Schleiche stumm durch die Schatten oder  katapultiere dich mit einem Rückwärtssalto aus ihnen heraus– was du auch machst, alle werden dich mit Respekt behandeln.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Trasformati in un ninja assassino e ritagliati il tuo posto nella storia. Stai silenziosamente nell'ombra o esci allo scoperto - in entrambi i casi tutti sapranno trattarti col dovuto rispetto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Transfórmate en un asesino ninja y ocupa tu lugar en la historia. Muévete sigilosamente por entre las sombras o aparece de un salto ante tu enemigo. Sea lo que sea, todos te respetarán. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">忍者となり、歴史に名を刻もう。影の中を静かに忍び寄る姿やバク転をしながら移動している姿に誰もが憧れるだろう。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">닌자 암살자로 변신하고 자신의 이름을 역사에 남기세요. 그림자 속에서 소리 없이 살며시 다가가거나 트인 공간에서 뒤로 공중제비를 도세요. 어떤 방식으로 접근하든 사람들은 당신을 존중해야 할 것입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Transform into a ninja assassin and carve your place in history. Creep silently in the shadows or back flip out in the open - either way everyone will know to treat you with respect. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">成為忍者刺客，您將載入史冊名流千古。在黑暗中無影無聲地穿梭，亦或在光天化日下猝不及防地現身殺敵。任您來去無蹤，世人無不敬佩。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">成為忍者刺客，您將載入史冊名流千古。在黑暗中無影無聲地穿梭，亦或在光天化日下猝不及防地現身殺敵。任您來去無蹤，世人無不敬佩。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Transform into a ninja assassin and carve your place in history. Creep silently in the shadows or back flip out in the open - either way everyone will know to treat you with respect. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>