<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Miss Behave - Camouflage Knuckle Duster Shoes (without stockings)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Miss Behave – Camouflage Talons Poing Américain (sans chaussures)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Miss Behave - Tarnfarben Schlagring-Schuhe (ohne strümpfen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Miss Behave - Mimetico Scarpe Tirapugni (senza calze)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Miss Behave – Camuflaje Zapatos Puño Americano (sin medias)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Miss Behave - Camouflage Knuckle Duster Shoes (without stockings)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">With this collection you will show you mean business, the family business! Ladies can be super sassy and sexy while the gents can be dapper and dashing! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Grâce à cette collection, vous montrerez qu'être dur en affaires est une histoire de famille ! Les demoiselles sont branchées et sexy, et les hommes, élégants et stylés ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit dieser Kollektion zeigst du, dass du Geschäft meinst, das Familien-Geschäft! Die Damen können super aufregend und sexy auftreten während die Herren elegant und gut aussehen! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Con questa colezione farai vedere a tutti che fai sul serio, sono affari di famiglia! Le signore sonoe super sexy e piene di stile, i signori, eleganti e raffinati! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con esta colección vas a mostrar a todos lo que son los negocios: ¡los negocios de la familia! Las mujeres son sexy y atrevidas mientras que los hombres son elegantes y sofisticados! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">With this collection you will show you mean business, the family business! Ladies can be super sassy and sexy while the gents can be dapper and dashing! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>