<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ratchet Figure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Figurine de Ratchet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ratchet-Figur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Modellino Ratchet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Muñeco de Ratchet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ラチェットのフィギュア</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">라쳇 피규어</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ratchet Figure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">拉捷特角色模型</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">拉捷特角色模型</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ratchet Figure</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The friendly Lombax that everyone knows and loves. Now depicted in a rare material from the Shadow Sector and handcrafted to exact likeness. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le gentil Lombax préféré des dames! Représenté dans un matériau rare tout droit sorti du Secteur de l'Ombre et travaillé à la main pour une ressemblance frappante. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der freundliche Lombax, den jedermann kennt und liebt. Jetzt in einem seltenen Material aus dem Schatten-Sektor von Hand exakt nach seinem Ebenbild geformt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il simpatico Lombax che tutti conoscono e amano. Raffigurato in un prezioso materiale proveniente dal Settore Ombra e fatto a mano per riprodurne fedelmente le fattezze. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El amistoso Lombax al que todos conocen y adoran. Tallado a mano con precisión en un raro material del sector Sombrío. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">みんなが大好きな人気者のロンバックス。シャドー・セクターのレア素材を使ったハンドメイド作品で本人そっくりの仕上がり ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">모두가 사랑하는 우리의 롬백스입니다. 최고급 원재로 만들어 더욱 실물 같습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The friendly Lombax that everyone knows and loves. Now depicted in a rare material from the Shadow Sector and handcrafted to exact likeness. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">眾所周知受眾人愛戴的友善隆巴克斯。現在由暗影象限稀有材料所繪製並手工打造的精製角色模型上市囉。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">眾所周知受眾人愛戴的友善隆巴克斯。現在由暗影象限稀有材料所繪製並手工打造的精製角色模型上市囉。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The friendly Lombax that everyone knows and loves. Now depicted in a rare material from the Shadow Sector  and handcrafted to exact likeness. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>