<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ethnic Beaded Flower Earrings Set (For Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Boucles d'oreilles florales ethniques garnies de perles (pour femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blumenohrringe aus Trachtenperlen (für Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set di orecchini etnici a fiore con perline (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de pendientes de flor de abalorios étnico (para mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ethnic Beaded Flower Earrings Set (For Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Flower earrings made of ethnic-style beads perfect for anyone looking for a rustically fashionable look!\nSometimes even earrings can make a whole outfit fun!\n\nThis set includes the following items for customizing avatars.\nEthnic Beaded Flower Earring - Left Ear (For Female) (Jewelry)\nEthnic Beaded Flower Earring - Right Ear (For Female) (Jewelry)\n\n*Upon purchase, all items will be added to their corresponding categories. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Boucles d'oreilles en perles de style ethnique, idéales pour toutes celles qui souhaitent avoir l'air branchées et rustiques !\nParfois, une paire de boucles d'oreilles suffit à donner de la gaieté à une tenue !\n\nCet ensemble comprend les éléments de personnalisation d'avatar suivants :\nBoucle d'oreille à perles ethniques - Oreille gauche (pour femme) (bijou)\nBoucle d'oreille à perles ethniques - Oreille droite (pour femme) (bijou)\n\n*À l’achat, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie correspondante. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blumenohrringe aus Perlen im Trachtenstil für alle, die ländliche Mode bevorzugen!\nManchmal erhält ein Outfit erst durch die Ohrringe den letzten Schliff!\n\nZu diesem Set gehören folgende Objekte, mit denen du Avatare ausstatten kannst.\nBlumenohrring aus Trachtenperlen – linkes Ohr (für Frauen) (Schmuck)\nBlumenohrring aus Trachtenperlen – rechtes Ohr (für Frauen) (Schmuck)\n\n*Nach dem Kauf erscheinen alle Gegenstände in ihren entsprechenden Kategorien.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Orecchini a fiore in stile etnico fatti di perline, per un look semplice e alla moda!\nSpesso, gli orecchini possono cambiare un intero completo!\n\nIl set include i seguenti elementi per la personalizzazione dell'avatar.\nOrecchino etnico a fiore con perline - Sinistro (donna) (gioielleria)\nOrecchino etnico a fiore con perline - Destro (donna) (gioielleria)\n\n*All'acquisto, tutti gli oggetti verranno aggiunti alle rispettive categorie. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pendientes de flores hechos con abalorios de estilo étnico perfectos si buscas un estilo elegante a la par que rústico.\n¡A veces, unos pendientes pueden darle el toque divertido a todo el atuendo!\n\nEste conjunto incluye los siguientes elementos para personalizar avatares.\nPendiente de flor de abalorios étnico: oreja izquierda (para mujer) (joyas)\nPendiente de flor de abalorios étnico: oreja derecha (para mujer) (joyas)\n\n*Los objetos se añadirán a las categorías correspondientes una vez que los hayas comprado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Flower earrings made of ethnic-style beads perfect for anyone looking for a rustically fashionable look!\nSometimes even earrings can make a whole outfit fun!\n\nThis set includes the following items for customizing avatars.\nEthnic Beaded Flower Earring - Left Ear (For Female) (Jewelry)\nEthnic Beaded Flower Earring - Right Ear (For Female) (Jewelry)\n\n*Upon purchase, all items will be added to their corresponding categories. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>