<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Everything Empire Strikes Back 30th Anniversary Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le pack complet 30e anniversaire de L'Empire contre-attaque</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Komplettpaket zum 30-jährigen Jubiläum von Das Imperium schlägt zurück</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set completo di tutto - 30º Anniversario de L'Impero colpisce ancora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Paquete con todo del Treinta Aniversario de El imperio contraataca</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* The Everything Empire Strikes Back 30th Anniversary Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* The Everything Empire Strikes Back 30th Anniversary Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Everything Empire Strikes Back 30th Anniversary Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* The Everything Empire Strikes Back 30th Anniversary Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* The Everything Empire Strikes Back 30th Anniversary Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Everything Empire Strikes Back 30th Anniversary Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Everything Empire Strike's Back?  Yes, this massive bundle has everything from the Empire Strike's Back release being sold in the store. This means 51 items in total. This bundle includes all 22 male and all 19 female costume items (including Yoda's lightsaber), plus all 10 furniture items.  You get everything from the Empire Strike's Back release being sold in the store with this bundle.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tout est Empire contre-attaque ? Oui cet énorme paquet a tout de l’Empire contre-attaque que l’on trouve en magasin. Ce qui veut dire 51 objets au total. Ce paquet contient les 22 costumes masculins et les 19 costumes féminins (incluant le sabre laser de Yoda), en plus de 10 objets meublés. Vous aurez tout de l’Empire contre-attaque que l’on trouve en magasin dans ce paquet. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ist wirklich alles drin aus Das Imperium schlägt zurück?  Ja, dieses riesige Paket enthält alles aus der Das Imperium schlägt zurück-Serie, was auch im Laden erhältlich ist. Insgesamt sind es 51 Teile. Dieses Paket enthält alle 22 männlichen Kostümteile und alle 19 weiblichen Kostümteile (inklusive Yodas Lichtschwert) sowie alle zehn Möbelteile. Du erhältst alles aus der Das Imperium schlägt zurück-Serie, was auch im Laden erhältlich ist.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tutto Empire Strikes Back?  Sì, questo pacchetto enorme ha tutto dall'uscita di Empire Strikes Back venduta in negozio. Questo vuol dire 51 articoli in totale. Questo pacchetto include tutti e 22 gli articoli di costume maschili e tutti i 19 femminili (compresa la spada laser di Yoda), più tutti i 10 articoli di accessori. Avrete tutto dall'uscita di Empire Strikes Back venduta in negozio con questo pacchetto.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Todo lo de El imperio contraataca?  Sí, este enorme paquete contiene todo lo que venden en las tiendas del estreno de El imperio contraataca. Son 51 objetos en total. El paquete incluye todos los trajes completos, 22 de hombre y 19 de mujer (incluyendo el sable láser de Yoda), más 10 muebles.  Este paquete incluye todos los objetos que se venden en las tiendas del estreno de El imperio contraataca.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Everything Empire Strike's Back?  Yes, this massive bundle has everything from the Empire Strike's Back release being sold in the store. This means 51 items in total. This bundle includes all 22 male and all 19 female costume items (including Yoda's lightsaber), plus all 10 furniture items.  You get everything from the Empire Strike's Back release being sold in the store with this bundle.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Everything Empire Strike's Back?  Yes, this massive bundle has everything from the Empire Strike's Back release being sold in the store. This means 51 items in total. This bundle includes all 22 male and all 19 female costume items (including Yoda's lightsaber), plus all 10 furniture items.  You get everything from the Empire Strike's Back release being sold in the store with this bundle.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>