<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Before Me Crop Top - Peacoat (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Top court Before Me - Bleu foncé (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Before Me Bauchfreies Oberteil - Blaugrau (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Before Me Top - Marinara (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Camiseta corta Before Me - Marinero (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The unique, irresistible looks from our Designer's Closet offer a distinct street edge with hints of ocean inspiration. Simple yet defiant, romantic but slightly sophisticated, each piece offers a glimpse of your yet-to-be-determined style evolution. This short sleeve knit top is gathered at center with a knot detail. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce haut unique et irrésistible, sorti tout droit de notre Designer's Closet, offre un look street d'inspiration maritime. Simple mais original, romantique mais sophistiqué, chaque élément offre un aperçu de l'évolution de votre style vraiment très personnel. Ce haut à manches courtes est resserré au centre avec un motif de nœud. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unsere einzigartige, unwiderstehliche Designer's Closet Kollektion bietet einen modischen, vom Meer inspirierten Look. Schlicht, aber dennoch frech, und mit einem Hauch von Romantik und Eleganz - die Kreationen von Designer's Closet lassen bereits die Stilevolution von morgen erahnen. Dieses kurzärmelige Strickoberteil wird in der Mitte durch einen attraktiven Knoten zusammengehalten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il look unico e irresistibile della nostra collezione Designer's Closet offre un tocco distintamente urbano con accenni ispirati all'oceano. Semplice ma ribelle, romantico ma leggermente sofisticato, ogni capo offre uno sguardo al tuo stile in evoluzione e non ancora definito. Questo top in maglia a maniche corte è raccolto al centro con un dettaglio annodato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los diseños únicos e irresistibles de Designer's Closet ofrecen un acabado callejero distinto con inspiración marina. Simple y, a su vez, rebelde y romántico con un toque de sofisticación. Cada pieza deja entrever una evolución de tu estilo aún por perfilar. Este top de punto de manga corta está fruncido en el centro con un detalle de nudo. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>