<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Infused Interweave Suit (Black)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Costume Tressé Impregné (Noir)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verwobener Bindungsanzug (Schwarz)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Armatura intrecciata a infusione (Nero)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de poder Nebulon-entretejido (Negro)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Infused Interweave Suit (Black)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Infused Interweave Suit (Black)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Brainchild of Novus Prime defense technology researcher, Dr. Dimitri Andros, the Nebulon-interweave power suit can be worn under the standard armored gear used by the Earth Fleet’s fighter pilots.  The power suit is skin-tight, channeling cascades of energy to and from a miraculously tiny Nebulon reactor. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Idée brillante que l'on doit au chercheur Dimitri Andros du  secteur technologie de défense de Novus Prime, le costume de puissance  tressé au Nébulon peut se porter sous  les armures strandard qu'utilisaient les pilotes de la flotte terrienne. Le costume de force est moulant, et l'on peut ressentir les afflux d'énergie allant et venant d'un réacteur à Nébulon miraculeusement petit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dank der genialen Erfindung vom Top-Entwickler von Novus Prime für Verteidigungstechnologoie, Dr. Dimitri Andros, kann der Nebulon-Power-Anzug unter der Standardausrüstung getragen werden, die von Piloten der Erdflotte verwendet wird. Der Power-Anzug ist hauchdünn und bündelt Kaskaden von Energie von und zu einem merkwürdigen, kleinen Nebulon Reaktor. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Frutto del genio del ricercatore sulla tecnologia della difesa della Novus Prime, Dott. Dimitri Andros, l'Armatura potenziata ad intrecci di Nebule può esser indossata sotto l'equipaggiamento di difesa standard usato dai piloti dei caccia della flotta terrestre. L'Armatura potenziata è aderente alla pelle, e fa in modo che si accumulino cascate di energia da e per gli estremamente minuscoli reattori a nebule. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Obra del investigador de tecnología de defensa Novus Prime, Dr. Dimitri Andros, el traje de poder Nebulon-entretejido puede ser llevado debajo del equipo de armadura estándar usado por los pilotos de combate de la flota de la Tierra. El traje de poder es ajustado, canalizando cascadas de energía desde y hace el milagroso diminuto reactor Nebulon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Brainchild of Novus Prime defense technology researcher, Dr. Dimitri Andros, the Nebulon-interweave power suit can be worn under the standard armored gear used by the Earth Fleet’s fighter pilots.  The power suit is skin-tight, channeling cascades of energy to and from a miraculously tiny Nebulon reactor. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Brainchild of Novus Prime defense technology researcher, Dr. Dimitri Andros, the Nebulon-interweave power suit can be worn under the standard armored gear used by the Earth Fleet’s fighter pilots.  The power suit is skin-tight, channeling cascades of energy to and from a miraculously tiny Nebulon reactor. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>