<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Step Outside Shorts - Black Multi (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Short Step Outside - Noir Multi (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Step Outside Shorts - Black/Mehrfarbig (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Step Outside Shorts - Nero Multicolore (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Step Outside Pantalón corto - Multinegro (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stand out with these high waisted, perfectly fitted shorts offered in a beautiful jacquard ethnic striped fabric. Side seam zipper and darts give this funky short a tailored look. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Démarquez-vous avec ces shorts taille haute parfaitement coupés proposés dans un très beau tissu jacquard à rayures ethnique. La fermeture zippée sur la couture latérale et les fléchettes donnent à ce short stylé un look personnalisé. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Setzen Sie sich ab von der Menge mit dieser hochtaillierten, perfekt angepassten Shorts aus wunderschönem Jacquardstoff mit Folklorestreifen. Der Seitenreißverschluss und die Abnäher verleihen dieser ausgefallenen Shorts den maßgeschneiderten Look. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Distinguiti con questi short a vita alta e perfettamente aderenti in uno splendido tessuto jacquard con motivo etnico a strisce. La zip laterale con cucitura e il motivo a freccette offrono a questi short stravaganti un look sartoriale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hazte ver con este pantalón corto de talle alto y perfectamente ajustado, elaborado en hermoso Jacquard a rayas con motivos étnicos. La cremallera a un lado y las flechas le dan un aspecto "funk" y hacen que parezca hecho a medida. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>