<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">BuiBui Mittens (women's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Moufles BuiBui (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">BuiBui-Fäustlinge (Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Muffole BuiBui da donna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Manoplas de BuiBui (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブイブイグローブ（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">부이부이 장갑(여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">BuiBui Mittens (women's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">布伊布伊手套（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">布伊布伊手套（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">BuiBui Mittens (women's)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Slip these BuiBui Mittens on, and let the little things lend\n
you a hand! Wave your hands, and the BuiBui seem to\n
wave, too! Startle friends with the threat of BuiBui mischief!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Enfile ces moufles BuiBui à la fois chaudes et jolies !\n
Agite tes mains, on dirait que les BuiBui s'agitent aussi ! \n
Effraie tes amis avec les terribles BuiBui !\n
\n
Acheter cet objet ajoute 1 LocoRoco à ton espace personnel de l'île Loco.
Tu peux ajouter jusqu'à 20 LocoRoco à l'île Loco. Une fois le maximum atteint, tu ne peux plus ajouter d'unités.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zieh die BuiBui-Fäustlinge an, damit die kleinen Kerle ihre Hand im\n
Spiel haben! Winke mit den Händen, und die BuiBui winken ebenfalls!\n
Erschrecke deine Freunde, indem du ihnen BuiBui-Schabernack androhst!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Indossa queste muffole BuiBui e lascia che ti diano\n
una mano! Agita le mani: sembrerà che anche il BuiBui\n
si muova! Fai trasalire gli amici servendoti della perfidia dei BuiBui!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Ponte estas manoplas de BuiBui y deja que estos pequeños te echen una mano! ¡Mueve las manos y parecerá que los BuiBui también se mueven! ¡Asusta a tus amigos con la amenaza de los malvados BuiBui!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブイブイがあなたの両手をいたずらっぽく演出してくれるグローブ。\n
手を振ると、ブイブイも手を振っているように見えるよ！\n
周囲がドキッとすること間違いなし！\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">당신의 두 손을 장난스럽게 연출해줄 인상쓰는 부이부이 장갑.\n
손을 흔들면 부이부이도 손을 흔들고 있는 것처럼 보여!\n
주변 분위기를 험악하게 만들어 줄 거야!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Slip these BuiBui Mittens on, and let the little things lend\n
you a hand! Wave your hands, and the BuiBui seem to\n
wave, too! Startle friends with the threat of BuiBui mischief!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">布伊布伊手套將你的雙手點綴出惡作劇般的感覺。\n
一揮手看起來就像布伊布伊也在揮手喔！\n
周遭的人一定會嚇一跳吧！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">布伊布伊手套將你的雙手點綴出惡作劇般的感覺。\n
一揮手看起來就像布伊布伊也在揮手喔！\n
周遭的人一定會嚇一跳吧！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Slip these BuiBui Mittens on, and let the little things lend\n
you a hand! Wave your hands, and the BuiBui seem to\n
wave, too! Startle friends with the threat of BuiBui mischief!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>