<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Silly walk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Marche ridicule</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dumme Bewegung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Passeggiata ridicola</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paseo tonto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Silly walk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Silly walk</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is probably the most ridiculous locomotion you can buy in Home. This hilarious walk consists of one impossibly long step, followed by two little skips. Be warned, you will look like a fool walking around like this![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Voici probablement la démarche la plus débile disponible sur Home. Cette mache désopilante consiste en un premier pas gigantesque, suivi de deux petits sautillements. Vous êtes prévenus: vous aurez l'air ridicule!   [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dies ist wahrscheinlich die meisten lächerlich Fortbewegung Sie in Haushalt kaufen kann. Diese lustigen Spaziergang besteht aus einem unglaublich langen Schritt, durch zwei kleine Sprünge folgten. Seien Sie gewarnt, werden Sie wie ein Narr herum so aussehen![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa è probabilmente la più stupida passeggiata disponibili su Home. Questo movimento esilarante è un passo enorme per primo, seguito da due piccoli salti. Siete stati avvertiti: si ridicolo!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este es probablemente el más tonto paseo disponible en Home. Esto paseo hilarante es un gran paso primero, seguido por dos pequeños saltos. Usted ha sido advertido: que se verá ridículo![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This is probably the most ridiculous locomotion you can buy in Home. This hilarious walk consists of one impossibly long step, followed by two little skips. Be warned, you will look like a fool walking around like this! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This is probably the most ridiculous locomotion you can buy in Home. This hilarious walk consists of one impossibly long step, followed by two little skips. Be warned, you will look like a fool walking around like this! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>