<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Female01_Hat_bi_soldier_Re</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Black Irem Brigade Mask (Replica, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Masque de la Brigade Noire Irem (Réplique, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Black Irem Brigade"-Maske (Replik, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maschera della Brigata Black Irem (replica, da donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Máscara del Escuadrón Irem Negro (réplica, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブラックアイレム団戦闘員　マスク（レプリカ・女性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블랙 아이렘단 전투원 마스크（레플리카, 여성）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Combatant of the Black Irem Brigade - Mask (Replica/Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">黑色Irem團戰鬥員 面罩（複製品/女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">黑色Irem團戰鬥員 面罩（複製品/女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Black Irem Brigade Mask (Replica, F)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Female01_Hat_bi_soldier_Re_description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A mask worn by combatants in the Black Irem Brigade to hide their faces. Large auditory devices attached to the ear areas allow combatants to listen to the orders of their colonel without fail; however, they also have the unfortunate side effect of making it difficult to listen to sounds coming from behind.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un masque porté par les combattants de la Brigade Noire Irem pour cacher leur visage. Le large dispositif auditif attaché au niveau des oreilles permet aux combattants de suivre les ordres du Colonel sans échouer; cependant, il y a un malheureux effet secondaire qui empêche de bien entendre les sons provenant de l'arrière. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine Maske, die von den Kämpfern der Black Irem Brigade getragen wird, um ihre Gesichter zu bedecken. Große Kommunikationsgeräte, die im Ohrbereich befestigt sind, ermöglichen es den Kämpfern, die Anweisungen des Colonels stets zu hören. Leider lassen sich Geräusche, die von hinten kommen, dadurch schlechter wahrnehmen.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una maschera indossata dai combattenti della Brigata Black Irem, per nascondere i propri lineamenti. Apparecchi acustici di grandi dimensioni applicati alle zone auricolari, permettono di ricevere senza alcun errore gli ordini del Colonnello: il problematico effetto collaterale, però, è che non si riescono a sentire bene i suoi che provengono da dietro.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una máscara utilizada por los combatientes del Escuadrón Irem Negro para ocultar su rostro. Incluye grandes dispositivos auditivos acoplados a la zona del oído para que los combatientes oigan las órdenes del coronel de forma clara. Sin embargo, tienen el inconveniente de que dificultan la audición de sonidos procedentes de la retaguardia.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブラックアイレム団の戦闘員たちが顔を隠すために着用するマスク。前方より発せられる大佐からの指示を聞き漏らさないように、大型の特殊耳殻が取り付けられている。後方からの音が聞き取りにくいなどの弱点がある。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블랙 아이렘단의 전투원들이 얼굴을 숨기기 위해 착용한 마스크. 전방에서 들려오는 대령의 지시를 놓치지 않도록, 대형 특수 귓바퀴가 붙어 있다. 후방에서 발생하는 소리는 잘 들을 수 없다는 약점이 있다.[#Legal]
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The mask used by Combatants of the Black Irem Brigade to cover their faces. Characteristic large ears have been stuck on in order to hear their leader's orders from up front, but it's hard to hear sounds from behind.[#Legal]
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">黑色Irem團的戰鬥員們用來隱藏面貌的面罩。為了不漏聽在前方指揮的上校指令，配置了大型的特殊耳罩。但是缺點是聽不太清楚由後方傳來的聲音。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">黑色Irem團的戰鬥員們用來隱藏面貌的面罩。為了不漏聽在前方指揮的上校指令，配置了大型的特殊耳罩。但是缺點是聽不太清楚由後方傳來的聲音。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A mask worn by combatants in the Black Irem Brigade to hide their faces. Large auditory devices attached to the ear areas allow combatants to listen to the orders of their colonel without fail; however, they also have the unfortunate side effect of making it difficult to listen to sounds coming from behind.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>