<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Drey Blush Pink Lace Top with Envelope Satchel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Haut en dentelle rose Drey avec une Sacoche Enveloppe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zartrosa Drey Spitzenoberteil mit Handtäschchen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Top di pizzo rosa pallido con borsetta a busta Drey</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Top de encaje rosa con bolso maletín de Drey</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">【Drey】カバン付きレーストップ（ピンク・女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">봉투형 작은 가방에 받혀 입는 "드레이" 발그레한 핑크 레이스 탑 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Drey Blush Pink Lace Top with Envelope Satchel (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Drey粉紅色蕾絲上衣含小包包 （女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Drey粉紅色蕾絲上衣含小包包 （女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Drey Blush Pink Lace Top with Envelope Satchel</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Add a touch of vintage elegance with this little lace number. The perfect day-to-evening top with fluted sleeves and fitted bodice. Add the subtle charms of the distressed leather satchel  to create the ultimate in class and style.\n\n Fit: Snug\n Fabric: Vintage Lace\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ajoutez une touche d'élégance vintage avec ce petit haut en dentelle. Le haut parfait pour la journée comme pour le soir avec des manches retroussées et un corsage ajusté. Ajoutez le charme subtil de la sacoche en cuir pour créer un must de classe et de style. \n\n Coupe: confortable\n Tissu: Dentelle vintage\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hol dir etwas Retro-Chic mit diesem Spitzenoberteil. Das Oberteil mit seinen kurzen Ärmeln und dem taillierten Mieder ist perfekt für jeden Anlass. Mit dem Lederhandtäschchen rundest du das ultimative Outfit stilvoll ab.\n\n Passform: Eng anliegend\n  Stoff: Retro-Spitze\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aggiungi un tocco di eleganza vintage con questo gioiellino di pizzo. Il top perfetto dalla mattina alla sera con maniche a tubo e corpetto aderente. Aggiungi il fascino sottile della borsetta in pelle invecchiata per creare lo stile e la classe definitivi.\n\n Vestibilità: Confortevole\n Tessuto: Pizzo vintage\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Vístete con un toque vintage y a la par elegante con este conjunto de encaje. Un top ideal para llevar a todas horas con mangas onduladas y entallado al busto que se combina con un coqueto bolso en cuero para crear estilo y distinción.\n\n Talle: ceñido.\n Tejido: encaje vintage.\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">レースシリーズでヴィンテージ・エレガンスを着こなそう。 フィット：ぴったりめ\n 素材：ヴィンテージレース\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 자그마한 레이스 탑으로 빈티지적인 우아함을 더해 보세요. 둥근 홈 주름이 잡힌 소매와 몸에 딱 맞춘 보디스는 낮부터 밤까지 완벽한 탑이죠. 궁극적인 클래스와 스타일의 창조를 위해 오래된 가죽가방의 미묘한 매력을 추가하는 것도 괜찮죠.\n\n 사이즈: 꼭 낌\n 직물: 빈티지 레이스\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Add a touch of vintage elegance with this little lace number. The perfect day-to-evening top with fluted sleeves and fitted bodice. Add the subtle charms of the distressed leather satchel  to create the ultimate in class and style.\n\n Fit: Snug\n Fabric: Vintage Lace\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這套簡單的蕾絲衣服，增添些許復古的優雅美感。這件短袖、合身上衣適合白天和晚上穿著。仿舊皮包帶來的幽微魅力，創造極致古典風格。\n\n 合身：舒適\n 布料：復古蕾絲\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這套簡單的蕾絲衣服，增添些許復古的優雅美感。這件短袖、合身上衣適合白天和晚上穿著。仿舊皮包帶來的幽微魅力，創造極致古典風格。\n\n 合身：舒適\n 布料：復古蕾絲\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Add a touch of vintage elegance with this little lace number. The perfect day-to-evening top with fluted sleeves and fitted bodice. Add the subtle charms of the distressed leather satchel  to create the ultimate in class and style.\n\n Fit: Snug\n Fabric: Vintage Lace\n [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>