<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ObjectName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">PAC-MAN™ T-Shirt1(Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">T-shirt 1 PAC-MAN™ (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">PAC-MAN™-T-Shirt1 (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">T-Shirt1 PAC-MAN™ (Per donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta 1 PAC-MAN™ (Femenina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">女性用パックマンTシャツ1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">팩맨 티셔츠 1 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">PAC-MAN T-Shirt1(Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">PAC-MAN T恤 1（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">PAC-MAN T恤 1（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">PAC-MAN® Collection T-Shirt</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ObjectDescription</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A T-shirt featuring a new color. This item cannot be obtained as a Home Reward in Namco Museum. Wear this to stand out from the crowd! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un T-shirt présentant une nouvelle couleur. Cet article ne peut être obtenu comme récompense Home dans Namco Museum. Portez-le pour vous démarquer des autres ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein T-Shirt mit brandneuer Farbe. Dieser Artikel kann nicht als Home-Gewinn im Namco Museum erworben werden. Tragen Sie ihn, um sich von anderen abzuheben! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una T-shirt di un colore nuovo. Questa maglietta non può essere vinta in Namco Museum. Indossala e distinguiti dalla folla! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta con un color nuevo. Este artículo no se puede obtener como premio Home en Namco Museum. ¡Póntelo para llamar la atención! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ナムコミュージアムリワードアイテムのニューカラーTシャツです。これを着用して他の人と差をつけよう！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">남코뮤지엄의 리워드 아이템인 뉴 컬러 티셔츠입니다. 남들하고는 달라야죠! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A T-shirt featuring a new color. This item cannot be obtained as a Home Reward in Namco Museum. Wear this to stand out from the crowd! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Namco Museum獎品的新色T恤，只可在這裡拿到。穿起它讓自己與別不同吧！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Namco Museum獎品的新色T恤，只能在這裡得到。穿起它讓自己與眾不同吧！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">All your childhood memories will come flooding back when you wear this T-shirt, bearing all the trademark symbols of everyone's favorite arcade classic. The cherry emblem on the sleeve gives it that extra burst of sweetness![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>