<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">My Private Hideaway</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mon Nid Secret</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mein geheimes Versteck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mio rifugio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mi propio escondite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">私だけの隠れ家</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">나만의 숨겨진 집</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">My Private Hideaway</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">我的私人秘密樂園</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">我的私人秘密樂園</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">My Private Hideaway</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Washed ashore on a solitary island in the south seas. The blazing sun, the quiet ocean, the refreshing breeze, crap!  I built a house on top of a cliff and even forgot to go home.  You are now able to go to the "Southern Island Hideaway" lounge from the back door of the loghouse. Also, there are plans to add many different things to this personal space in the future. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Perdu sur une île isolée des mers du Sud.  Soleil étincelant, mer calme, brise rafraîchissante.  Mince ! J’en ai oublié de rentrer chez moi et j’ai construit une maison sur la falaise.   Vous pouvez désormais accéder au jardin privé de votre “Nid Secret des Mers du Sud” par la porte arrière du chalet.  Par la suite de nombreuses autres options seront ajoutées à cet espace personnel. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gestrandet auf einer einsamen Insel in der Südsee. Die sengende Sonne, der ruhige Ozean, die frische Brise. Oh Nein! Ich habe vergessen nach Hause zu gehen und hier auf einer Klippe ein Haus gebaut .  Sie können von der Hintertür des Blockhauses zum Privatgarten der "geheimes Versteck auf der Südseeinsel"-Lounge gelangen. Desweiteren ist geplant, dass diesem persönlichen Raum viele verschiedene Elemente hinzugefügt werden. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Si trova su un'isola remota nei mari del sud su cui sono arrivato trasportato dalla corrente. Qui il sole splende, il mare è calmo e la brezza è rinfrescante.  Ma perché?! Ho costruito una casa, ma io mi dimentico sempre di tornare a casa!   Adesso puoi accedere al giardino privato della sala del "Rifugio dell'isola del sud" dal retro della capanna.  In futuro, inoltre, verranno aggiunti altri elementi a questo spazio personale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Has sido arrastrado hasta una solitaria isla en las islas del sur. El sol abrasador, el tranquilo océano, la brisa refrescante. ¡Oh no! He construido una casa en el la cima del acantilado y hasta he olvidado regresar a casa.   Ahora ya puedes ir a la sala "El Escondite de la Isla del Sur" desde la puerta trasera de la cabaña.  También, hay muchos planes para agregar muchas cosas diferentes a este espacio personal en el futuro. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">流れ着いた南海の孤島。 照りつける太陽、静かな海、爽やかな風、 しまった！　帰るのも忘れ崖の上に家を建ててしまった・・・  ログハウスの裏口から、ラウンジ「南の島の隠れ家」のプライベートガーデンに行けるようになります。 また、本パーソナルスペースは今後様々な要素が追加される予定です。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">남해의 고도로 표류한 당신.

내리쬐는 태양, 조용한 바다, 상쾌한 바람이 있습니다. 절벽 위에 집을 짓고는, 섬을 탈출하는 것마저 잊었군요!

통나무집 후문에서 "남쪽 섬의 숨겨진 집" 라운지로 이동할 수 있습니다. 또한 향후 다양한 요소가 이 퍼스널 스페이스에 추가될 예정입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Washed ashore on a solitary island in the south seas. The blazing sun, the quiet ocean, the refreshing breeze, crap!  I built a house on top of a cliff and even forgot to go home.  You are now able to go to the "Southern Island Hideaway" lounge from the back door of the loghouse. Also, there are plans to add many different things to this personal space in the future. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">漂流至南洋的孤島。
熾熱的陽光、寧靜的海洋、清新的潮風，糟了，我竟然在懸崖上建造了一個房子，並忘記回家了…。

從小木屋後門可以前往「南島秘密樂園」的私人花園。
此外，本個人空間今後將預定陸續追加新要素。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">漂流至南洋的孤島。
熾熱的陽光、寧靜的海洋、清新的潮風，糟了，我竟然在懸崖上建造了一個房子，並忘記回家了…。

從小木屋後門可以前往「南島秘密樂園」的私人花園。
此外，本個人空間今後將預定陸續追加新要素。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Washed ashore on a solitary island in the south seas. The blazing sun, the quiet ocean, the refreshing breeze, crap!  I built a house on top of a cliff and even forgot to go home.  You are now able to go to the "Southern Island Hideaway" lounge from the back door of the loghouse. Also, there are plans to add many different things to this personal space in the future. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>