<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Painted Bare Accessory Bundle (female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Kit d’accessoires Painted Bare (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Pack Accessoires Bemalung (weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Painted Kit di accessori Bare (femmina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de accesorios Painted Bare (Mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Painted Bare Accessory Bundle (female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Painted Bare Accessory Bundle (female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Enjoy all these picture perfect accessories whether with the paint or an outfit of your choice.  Includes two Madame Flutterby hair accessories, the Lady Purrfect ears and the Mistress Multi-Coloured hairstyle, plus a bonus hair style! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Profitez de tous ces accessoires au look parfait que ce soit avec la peinture ou une tenue de votre choix. Comprend deux accessoires Madame Butterfly pour les cheveux, les oreilles de Madame Parfaite et la coiffure de Madame Multicolore, plus une coiffure bonus. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Viel Spaß mit all diesen tollen Accessoires, kombinierte mit einer Bemalung oder einem Outfit deiner Wahl. Das Pack beinhaltet zwei Madame Schmetterlings-Accessoires für die Haare, Lady Schnurrkatze-Ohren und die Meisterin Multicolor-Frisur, und außerdem eine Bonus-Frisur! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Godetevi questi accessori immagine perfetta sia con vernice o un gruppo di loro scelta. Include due accessori per capelli di Madame Butterfly, orecchie e capelli perfetti Multicolor Padrona signora, oltre a uno stile di capelli bonus! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Disfruta de todos estos accesorios de imagen perfecta ya sea con la pintura o un equipo de su elección. Incluye dos Madame Butterfly accesorios para el pelo, las orejas y la dama perfecta peinado Mistress Multicolor, además de un bono de estilo de pelo!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Enjoy all these picture perfect accessories whether with the paint or an outfit of your choice.  Includes two Madame Flutterby hair accessories, the Lady Purrfect ears and the Mistress Multi-Coloured hairstyle, plus a bonus hair style! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Enjoy all these picture perfect accessories whether with the paint or an outfit of your choice.  Includes two Madame Flutterby hair accessories, the Lady Purrfect ears and the Mistress Multi-Colored hairstyle, plus a bonus hair style! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>