<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Obsidian Throwing Star (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Etoile de lancer obsidienne (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Obsidian-Wurfstern (männliche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Shuriken Obsidian (per uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estrella Obsidiana (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オブシディアン手裏剣（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Obsidian Throwing Star (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Obsidian Throwing Star (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Weighing in at a mere two kilograms, this massive throwing star slices through the strongest metals found on Earth.  Obsidian infantry have been known to use these blades as shields, as well, and their own armor protects them from the razor edges of the star itself. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pesant seulement un petit deux kilogrammes, cette étoile de lancer massive tranche tous les métaux que l'on peut trouver sur Terre.  L'infanterie obsidienne est aussi connue pour utiliser ces lames comme boucliers alors que leurs propres armures les protègent des tranchants effilés des étoiles elles-mêmes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit einem Gewicht von nur  zwei Kilogramm schneidet dieser massive Wurfstein durch die stärksten Metalle, die auf der Erde gefunden werden können. Die Obsidian-Infanterie ist dafür bekannt, diese Klingen auch als Schilder zu benutzen. Ihre eigene Rüstung schützt sie vor den rasierklingenscharfen Kanten der Sterne.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Del peso di soli due chilogrammi, quest'enorme shuriken perfora i più resistenti metalli terrestri come fossero burro. La fanteria Obsidian era famosa per l'utilizzo di quest'arma anche come scudo, con l'armatura a protezione del corpo dalle affilate lame dello shuriken stesso. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con un peso de tan solo dos kilogramos, estas masivas estrellas cortan a través de los metales más fuertes de la Tierra.  La infantería Obsidiana es famosa por usar estas cuchillas como escudos, además, sus propias armaduras los protegen de los bordes filosos de la estrella misma. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">手裏剣は地球上に存在する最強の金属を切り裂く。オブシディアン歩兵ユニットはこの手裏剣を盾として使うことでも知られており、彼らの鎧は手裏剣の鋭利な刃から身を守る役目を果たしている。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* kDesc [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Weighing in at a mere two kilograms, this massive throwing star slices through the strongest metals found on Earth.  Obsidian infantry have been known to use these blades as shields, as well, and their own armor protects them from the razor edges of the star itself. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* kDesc [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* kDesc [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Weighing in at a mere two kilograms, this massive throwing star slices through the strongest metals found on Earth.  Obsidian infantry have been known to use these blades as shields, as well, and their own armor protects them from the razor edges of the star itself. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>