<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sodium Robo-Jerboa - Blago</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Robot-gerboise Sodium - Blago</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sodium-Robo-Jerboa - Blago</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Robo-Jerboa Sodium - Blago</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sodium Robojerboa - Blago</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Sodium　ロボねずみ – Blago</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium 로보-저보아 - 블라고</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sodium Robo-Jerboa - Blago</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sodium機器跳鼠：Blago</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sodium機器跳鼠：Blago</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sodium Robo-Jerboa - Blago</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Originally designed as a children's toy by Sodium scientists, the Robo-Jerboa turned out to be very useful for hopping across the desert sands carrying important data and messages. Limited Edition Lockwood item exclusive to E3®![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Initialement conçu par les scientifiques de Sodium comme un jouet pour enfant, le Robot-gerboise s'est avéré très utile pour traverser les sables du désert en sautillant pour transmettre d'importants messages et autres données. Article Lockwood en édition limitée et exclusif à E3® ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Wissenschaftler von Sodium hatten den Robo-Jerboa ursprünglich nur als Kinderspielzeug konzipiert, doch er konnte sehr gut über den Wüstensand hüpfen, um wichtige Daten und Nachrichten zu überbringen. Limitierter Lockwood-Gegenstand exklusiv für die E3®![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ideato originariamente come giocattolo per bambini dagli scienziati di Sodium, il Robo-Jerboa si è dimostrato molto utile per saltellare tra le sabbie del deserto e consegnare informazioni e messaggi importanti. Oggetto Lockwood in edizione limitata in esclusiva per l'E3®![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Originalmente, Sodium lo diseñó como un juguete para niños. Pero robojerboa terminó siendo muy útil para saltar por el desierto llevando datos importantes y mensajes. ¡Objeto Lockwood de edición limitada, exclusivo de E3®![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Sodiumのエンジニアが設計した砂漠地帯で力をいかんなく発揮するロボットです。E3限定Lockwoodアイテム。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">원래는 Sodium 의 과학자들이 아이들 장난감으로 설계한 로보-저보아는 중요한 자료와 메시지를 지니고 모래 사막 위를 뛰어 다닐 수 있어서 아주 유용하다는 걸 알게 되었답니다. E3® 전용 Lockwood 의 한정판 아이템![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Originally designed as a children's toy by Sodium scientists, the Robo-Jerboa turned out to be very useful for hopping across the desert sands carrying important data and messages. Limited Edition Lockwood item exclusive to E3®![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sodium的科學家原來是要設計兒童玩具，結果這個機器跳鼠實用性強，能攜帶重要資料和訊息橫跨沙漠。E3®展獨家限量版Lockwood周邊商品！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sodium的科學家原來是要設計兒童玩具，結果這個機器跳鼠實用性強，能攜帶重要資料和訊息橫跨沙漠。E3®展獨家限量版Lockwood周邊商品！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Originally designed as a children's toy by Sodium scientists, the Robo-Jerboa turned out to be very useful for hopping across the desert sands carrying important data and messages. Limited Edition Lockwood item exclusive to E3®![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>