<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">What would you do if you found this?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Que feriez-vous si vous trouviez ça ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Was macht man mit einem solchen Fund?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cosa faresti se trovassi uno di questi?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Qué harías si te encontraras esto?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">We strongly advise that you do NOT, under ANY circumstance, EVEN if threatened to death and EVEN if the entire worlds survival depended on it: do NOT use this to buy classical music. The internet would burst its tubes, and you wouldn’t be able to logon to your social network. Ever again. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nous vous recommandons fortement de ne PAS faire ce qui suit, en AUCUN cas, MÊME sous menace de mort et MÊME si la survie du monde entier en dépend : ne PAS utiliser cette musique classique d'achat. Les tubes d'Internet exploseraient et vous ne pourriez plus vous connecter à votre réseau social. Plus jamais. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es wird dringend empfohlen, unter KEINEN Umständen, AUCH bei Todesandrohung und selbst, wenn das Überleben der GANZEN Welt davon abhinge, NIEMALS damit Klassik-CDs zu kaufen. Das würde das Internet sprengen und die sozialen Netzwerke wären nicht mehr zugänglich. Nie wieder. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Consigliamo di NON usarlo per acquistare musica classica, in NESSUN caso, NEMMENO dietro minaccia di morte e NEPPURE se la sopravvivenza di interi mondi dipendesse da questo. In caso contrario, Internet brucerebbe le valvole e voi non potreste più connettervi al vostro social network. Mai più. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Recomendamos que, bajo NINGÚN concepto, NI aunque te amenacen de muerte e INCLUSO si la supervivencia del universo dependiera de ello: uses ESTO para comprar música clásica. Internet saltaría por los aires y no podrías volver a entrar en tu red social. Nunca jamás. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>