<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Small White Wing Set (Men / Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de petites ailes blanches (homme, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Kleine weiße Flügel-Set (für Frauen und Männer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set piccole ali bianche (da uomo/donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de pequeñas alas blancas (hombre y mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">小さな白い羽セット（男女）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Small White Wing Set (Men / Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 10-piece Locomotion set, including 6 types of Small White Wings, Halos (Men / Women) and Hand-held Bow &amp; Arrows (Men / Women).\n
Locomotion Speed: ★★★~★★★★★\n
Sense of Justice: ★★★\n
* Locomotion is a portable item.\n
This set includes the following items:\n
\n
- Halo (Men) (Head Accessory)\n
- Hand-held Bow &amp; Arrow (Men) (Hands)\n
- Halo (Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Hand-held Bow &amp; Arrow (Women) (Hands)\n
- Locomotion - Small White Wings, Head, Near (Portables)\n
- Locomotion - Small White Wings, Head, Mid (Portables)\n
- Locomotion - Small White Wings, Head, Far (Portables)\n
- Locomotion - Small White Wings, Back, Near (Portables)\n
- Locomotion - Small White Wings, Back, Mid (Portables)\n
- Locomotion - Small White Wings, Back, Far (Portables)\n
\n
* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 10 pièces d'objets de locomotion, contenant 6 types de petites ailes blanches, des auréoles (homme/femme) et des arcs en main avec flèche (homme/femme).\n
Vitesse : ★★★~★★★★★\n
Droiture : ★★★\n
* Un objet de locomotion est un objet portable.\n
Ce set inclut les objets suivants :\n
\n
- Auréole (homme) (Accessoire de tête)\n
- Arc en main et flèche (homme) (Mains)\n
- Auréole (femme) (Accessoire de tête)\n
- Arc en main et flèche (femme) (Mains)\n
- Locomotion - Petites ailes blanches, tête, proches (Objets portables)\n
- Locomotion - Petites ailes blanches, tête, moyennes (Objets portables)\n
- Locomotion - Petites ailes blanches, tête, éloignées (Objets portables)\n
- Locomotion - Petites ailes blanches, dos, proches (Objets portables)\n
- Locomotion - Petites ailes blanches, dos, moyennes (Objets portables)\n
- Locomotion - Petites ailes blanches, dos, éloignées (Objets portables)\n
\n
* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 10-teiliges Set von Bewegungsgegenständen, das 6 Arten von kleinen weißen Flügeln, Heiligenscheine (für Frauen und Männer) und Pfeil und Bogen in der Hand (für Frauen und Männer) enthält.\n
Geschwindigkeit: ★★★~★★★★★\n
Sinn für Gerechtigkeit: ★★★\n
* Bewegungsgegenstände sind tragbare Gegenstände.\n
Dieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n
\n
- Heiligenschein (für Männer) (Kopfbedeckung)\n
- Pfeil und Bogen in der Hand (für Männer) (Hände)\n
- Heiligenschein (für Frauen) (Kopfbedeckung)\n
- Pfeil und Bogen in der Hand (für Frauen) (Hände)\n
- Bewegungsgegenstand - Kleine weiße Flügel am Kopf, nah (Tragbare Objekte)\n
- Bewegungsgegenstand - Kleine weiße Flügel am Kopf, mittel (Tragbare Objekte)\n
- Bewegungsgegenstand - Kleine weiße Flügel am Kopf, entfernt (Tragbare Objekte)\n
- Bewegungsgegenstand - Kleine weiße Flügel am Rücken, nah (Tragbare Objekte)\n
- Bewegungsgegenstand - Kleine weiße Flügel am Rücken, mittel (Tragbare Objekte)\n
- Bewegungsgegenstand - Kleine weiße Flügel am Rücken, entfernt(Tragbare Objekte)\n
\n
* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set Locomotion composto da 10 elementi, comprendente 6 tipi di piccole ali bianche, aureole (da uomo/donna) e archi e frecce (da uomo/donna).\n
Velocità di spostamento: ★★★~★★★★★\n
Senso della giustizia: ★★★\n
* Gli oggetti Locomotion sono oggetti portatili.\n
Nel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n
\n
- Aureola (da uomo) (Accessorio per la testa)\n
- Arco e freccia tenuti in mano (da uomo) (Mani)\n
- Aureola (da donna) (Accessorio per la testa)\n
- Arco e freccia tenuti in mano (da donna) (Mani)\n
- Locomotion - Piccole ali bianche vicine alla testa (Oggetti portatili)\n
- Locomotion - Piccole ali bianche sopra la testa (Oggetti portatili)\n
- Locomotion - Piccole ali bianche lontane dalla testa (Oggetti portatili)\n
- Locomotion - Piccole ali bianche vicine alla schiena (Oggetti portatili)\n
- Locomotion - Piccole ali bianche sulla schiena (Oggetti portatili)\n
- Locomotion - Piccole ali bianche lontane dalla schiena (Oggetti portatili)\n
\n
* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de 10 artículos de locomoción, incluyendo seis tipos de pequeñas alas blancas, aureolas (para hombre y mujer), y arco y flecha en mano (hombre y mujer).\n
Velocidad de locomoción: ★★★-★★★★★\n
Sentido de la justicia: ★★★\n
* Locomoción es un artículo portátil.\n
Este juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n
\n
- Aureola (hombre) (Accesorio de cabeza)\n
- Arco y flecha en mano (hombre) (Manos)\n
- Aureola (mujer) (Accesorio de cabeza)\n
- Arco y flecha en mano (mujer) (Manos)\n
- Locomoción - Pequeñas alas blancas, cabeza, cerca (Portátiles)\n
- Locomoción - Pequeñas alas blancas, cabeza, a media distancia (Portátiles)\n
- Locomoción - Pequeñas alas blancas, cabeza, lejos (Portátiles)\n
- Locomoción - Pequeñas alas blancas, espalda, cerca (Portátiles)\n
- Locomoción - Pequeñas alas blancas, espalda, a media distancia (Portátiles)\n
- Locomoción - Pequeñas alas blancas, espalda, lejos (Portátiles)\n
\n
* Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ロコモーションの小さな白い羽6タイプ、頭の上の輪（男性用／女性用）、手に持った弓矢（男性用／女性用）を含んだ、計10点セット。\n
ロコモーションの移動速度：　◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆\n
正義感：　★★★\n
※LMO(ロコモーション)はポータブルアイテムです。\n
本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n
\n
・頭の上の輪（男性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n
・手に持った弓矢（男性）/手\n
・頭の上の輪（女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n
・手に持った弓矢（女性）/手\n
・LMO-小さな白い羽・頭・近/ポータブルアイテム\n
・LMO-小さな白い羽・頭・中/ポータブルアイテム\n
・LMO-小さな白い羽・頭・遠/ポータブルアイテム\n
・LMO-小さな白い羽・背中・近/ポータブルアイテム\n
・LMO-小さな白い羽・背中・中/ポータブルアイテム\n
・LMO-小さな白い羽・背中・遠/ポータブルアイテム\n
\n
※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 10-piece Locomotion set, including 6 types of Small White Wings, Halos (Men / Women) and Hand-held Bow &amp; Arrows (Men / Women).\n
Locomotion Speed: ★★★~★★★★★\n
Sense of Justice: ★★★\n
* Locomotion is a portable item.\n
This set includes the following items:\n
\n
- Halo (Men) (Head Accessory)\n
- Hand-held Bow &amp; Arrow (Men) (Hands)\n
- Halo (Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Hand-held Bow &amp; Arrow (Women) (Hands)\n
- Locomotion - Small White Wings, Head, Near (Portables)\n
- Locomotion - Small White Wings, Head, Mid (Portables)\n
- Locomotion - Small White Wings, Head, Far (Portables)\n
- Locomotion - Small White Wings, Back, Near (Portables)\n
- Locomotion - Small White Wings, Back, Mid (Portables)\n
- Locomotion - Small White Wings, Back, Far (Portables)\n
\n
* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
