<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Big Time Woven Shirt - Black (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Chemise tissée Big Time - Noir (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Big Time Stoffhemd - Schwarz (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Big Time Camicia - Nero (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Big Time Camisa - Negro (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Big Time woven says it with style. This yarn dye check woven button-up with dual chest pockets will have you leading the pack in no time. Details include contrast piecing and a woven Billabong label at top of pocket. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Dites-le avec classe grâce à la chemise tissée Big Time. Cette chemise en fil tissé teint boutonnée avec deux poches poitrine vous permettra de briller en un instant. Pièces contrastées et étiquette Billabong tissée sur le haut de la poche figurent parmi les détails caractéristiques de cette chemise. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Setzen Sie sich ab von der Menge - mit diesem garngefärbten, karierten Big Time Stoffhemd mit Knopfleiste, zwei Brusttaschen, farblich abgesetzten Details und einem Billabong Stoffetikett oben an der Tasche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La camicia Big Time la sa lunga in fatto di stile. Con questa camicia in tessuto a quadri tinto in filo con bottoncini e due tasche sul petto, sarai subito il leader del gruppo. Comprende dettagli a contrasto e un'etichetta Billabong in tessuto sopra la tasca. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La camisa de vestir Big Time transmite estilo por sí misma. De botones y a cuadros, de hilo teñido y con dos bolsillos en el pecho, esta prenda te hará el cabecilla del grupo en menos de ya. Entre los detalles se incluye ensamblado de colores en contraste y etiqueta Billabong cosida en la parte superior del bolsillo. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>