<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mola Ram Head Piece</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chapeau Mola Ram</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mola Ram-Kopfteil</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cappello Mola Ram</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sombrero de Mola Ram</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mola Ram Head Piece</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">(Head Piece) The heat from the lava pits has been getting stronger lately. As I step out of my private quarters and out into the view of the chanting thugees who I can bend to my will, it brushes against my skin; the burn feels like it is just beginning to form. As I step forward, a terrified man from the village is being shackled and sacrificed to Kali in a pit of molten rock. I suppose it is time I address my servants and Kali. I raise my fists in the air, and the men cheer. I guess it was a good thing I chose to purchase the Mola Ram avatar outfit for this occasion. Anything else would seem underdressed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">(Chapeau) La chaleur provenant des fosses de lave devient de plus en plus insoutenable en ce moment. Je sors de mes quartiers, en pleine vue des voyous que je commande à mon gré, la chaleur me colle à la peau. Ça commence à brûler. Je m'avance, on est en train d'attacher et de sacrifier un homme du village, terrifié, dans une fosse de lave en fusion. Je suppose qu'il est temps que je m'adresse à mes serviteurs et à Kali. Je lève les poings dans les airs, et les hommes m'acclament. Heureusement que j'ai choisi d'acheter la tenue de Mola Ram pour l'occasion. Toute autre tenue n'aurait pas fait l'affaire. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">(Kopfteil) Die Hitze aus den Lavagruben ist stärker geworden. Ich spüre, wie sie auf der Haut zu brennen beginnt, während ich mein Privatquartier verlasse und mich den skandierenden Thuggees zeige, die sich stets meinem Willen beugen. Als ich hervortrete, sehe ich, wie ein verängstigter Mann aus dem Dorf gefesselt, und Kali in einer Grube aus geschmolzenem Gestein geopfert wird. Es ist wohl Zeit, mich an meine Untergebenen und Kali zu wenden. Ich strecke meine Fäuste gen Himmel und die Männer jubeln. Es war eine weise Entscheidung, die Mola-Ram-Avatar-Ausstattung für diese Gelegenheit zu erwerben. Alles andere wäre hier nicht angemessen gewesen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">(Cappello) Il calore delle pozze di lava si è fatto più intenso, ultimamente. Uscendo dal mio alloggio e davanti ai miei salmodianti e obbedienti sudditi, mi accarezza la pelle; sento la bruciatura che si forma. Mentre faccio un passo avanti, un uomo del villaggio terrorizzato viene messo in catene e sacrificato a Kali in un fosso pieno di roccia fusa. Suppongo sia arrivato il momento di rivolgermi ai miei servitori e a Kali. Alzo i pugni al cielo, e gli uomini esultano. Immagino sia stato un bene comprare il completo avatar di Mola Ram per questa occasione. Qualsiasi altra cosa non sarebbe sembrata all'altezza. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">(Accesorio de cabeza) El calor del magma de lava se hace insoportable. Salgo de mis aposentos privados y oigo los cánticos Thugs, a quienes puedo dominar a mi voluntad, esa melodía golpea mi piel. Empiezo a notar el calor. Doy un paso y veo como arrastran a un hombre aterrorizado y lo sacrifican en una pila de rocas ardientes en honor a la diosa Kali. Supongo que es el momento idóneo para dirigirme a mis sirvientes y a Kali. Levanto mis puños y la muchedumbre grita. Fue una buena idea comprar el conjunto avatar de Mola Ram para esta ocasión. Con cualquier otra cosa no hubiese dado la talla. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">(Head Piece) The heat from the lava pits has been getting stronger lately. As I step out of my private quarters and out into the view of the chanting thugees who I can bend to my will, it brushes against my skin; the burn feels like it is just beginning to form. As I step forward, a terrified man from the village is being shackled and sacrificed to Kali in a pit of molten rock. I suppose it is time I address my servants and Kali. I raise my fists in the air, and the men cheer. I guess it was a good thing I chose to purchase the Mola Ram avatar outfit for this occasion. Anything else would seem underdressed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>