<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Energy Helmet (female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Casque d'énergie (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Energie Helm (frau)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Casco di Energia (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Casco de Energia (mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Get ready for an exciting adventure!
It's time to stop dreaming and write your own story! Create a fantasy world where you are the protagonist. Designed exclusively for you, we give you the opportunity to become your favourite character. Get ready for an exciting adventure ...And have a happy ending![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Get ready for an exciting adventure!
It's time to stop dreaming and write your own story! Create a fantasy world where you are the protagonist. Designed exclusively for you, we give you the opportunity to become your favorite character. Get ready for an exciting adventure ...And have a happy ending![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Préparez-vous pour une aventure passionnante ! 
Il est temps d’arrêter de rêver et d’écrire votre histoire ! Créez un monde imaginaire dont vous êtes le héros ! Conçu spécialement pour vous, nous vous donnons l’opportunité de devenir votre personnage favori.  Préparez-vous pour une aventure passionnante……  avec une fin heureuse ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Machen Sie sich bereit für ein aufregendes Abenteuer! 
Hören Sie auf zu Träumen und schreiben Sie Ihre eigene Geschichte! Erschaffen Sie eine Fantasy-Welt mit Ihnen als Helden. Nur für Sie entworfen, um Ihnen die Möglichkeit zu geben Ihr eigener Lieblingscharakter zu werden. Machen Sie sich bereit für ein aufregendes Abenteuer… und ein tolles Happy-End! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Preparati per un'avventura emozionante! 
Basta sognare e inizia a scrivere la tua storia! Crea un mondo di fantasia in cui tu sei il protagonista. Solo a te diamo la possibilità di diventare il tuo personaggio preferito. Preparati per un'avventura emozionante... dal lieto fine! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Prepárate a vivir una fascinante aventura! 
¡Ha llegado el momento de dejar de soñar, para poder escribir tu propia historia!  Con esta nueva colección podrás crear un mundo de fantasía en el que ser el protagonista. Diseñado exclusivamente para ti, te damos la oportunidad de convertirte en tu personaje favorito. Decide qué camino quieres tomar, ¿seguirás la senda del bien, o serás el primer villano en salir victorioso? Prepárate para una emocionante aventura... ¡Y que tengas un final feliz! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>