<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Moonlight Room</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chamber clair de lune</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mondschein-Zimmer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Camera chiaro di luna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Habitación luz de luna</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">When the sun sets, darkness reigns the night and only the magic of the moon lights up the streets. At that precise moment, the "Moonlight Room" comes to life. Its dark tones and silver trims are full with beauty, class and distinction. This is a shelter for lovers of the night.


\n

[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Au couché du soleil, l'obscurité reigne dans la nuit et seule la magie de la lune illumine les rues. A ce moment précis la "Chamber clair de lune" prend vie. Ses tons foncés et argentés sont pleins de charme, classe et distinction. C'est un refuge pour les amoureux de la nuit.
\n

[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn die Sonne untergeht, regiert die Dunkelheit die Nacht und nur das magische Mondlicht erhellt die Straßen. Genau in diesem Moment erwacht der „Moonlight Room“ zum Leben. Seine dunklen Töne mit silbernen Details sind vornehm und voller Schönheit und Klasse. Ein nächtlicher Unterschlupf für Liebespaare. 
\n

[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quando il sole tramonta, l'oscurità regna la notte e solo la magia della luna illumina le strade. In quel preciso momento, la "Camera chiaro di luna" prende vita. I suoi toni scuri e finiture in argento sono pieni di bellezza, classe e distinzione. Questo è un rifugio per gli amanti della notte.
\n

[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuando el sol se esconde, la oscuridad reina en la noche y sólo la magia de la luna ilumina las calles. En ese preciso instante, la “Habitación de luz de luna” cobra vida. Sus tonos oscuros y remates plateados están llenos de belleza, clase y distinción. Este es un refugio para los enamorados de la noche.  
\n

[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>