<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">retreat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Retreat to the Diner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Battre en retraite vers le café-restaurant</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Ziehen Sie sich ins Diner zurück.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Torna al Diner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Volver al restaurante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Retreat to the Diner</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Resistance 3™ Scavenger</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chasse au trésor Resistance 3™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Resistance 3™"-Plünderer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ricerca di Resistance 3™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Búsqueda de Resistance 3™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Resistance 3™ Scavenger</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Explore these war torn streets to find valuable equipment and earn great rewards. But keep an eye out for the feral Chimera, they are hungry and will spare no one. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Explorez ces rues dévastées par la guerre pour trouver des équipements de valeur et gagner de grandes récompenses. Mais gardez les yeux ouverts pour repérer les Chimères sauvages : elles ont faim et n'épargneront personne. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erkunden Sie die vom Krieg verwüsteten Straßen, um wertvolle Ausrüstung zu finden und tolle Belohnungen zu verdienen. Aber halten Sie die Augen nach den barbarischen Bestien offen – sie sind hungrig und verschonen niemanden. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Perlustra queste strade devastate dalla guerra per cercare equipaggiamenti e ricompense di valore. Attenzione ai Chimera selvaggi: sono affamati e non avranno pietà! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Explora estas calles devastadas por la guerra para encontrar equipamiento valioso y lograr grandes recompensas. Pero ten cuidado con las quimeras salvajes, están hambrientas y no hacen excepciones. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Explore these war torn streets to find valuable equipment and earn great rewards. But keep an eye out for the feral Chimera, they are hungry and will spare no one. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Journal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Journal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tagebuch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Diario</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Diario</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Journal</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Close Journal    [L2]/[R2] Turn Page</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Fermer [L2]/[R2] Tourner la page</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE] Schließen   [L2]/[R2] Seite umblättern</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE] Chiudi   [L2]/[R2] Volta pagina</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] Cerrar   [L2]/[R2] Pasar página</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE] Close Journal    [L2]/[R2] Turn Page</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page1_text1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This journal holds the key to survival! Within it is the location of five key items that could be invaluable to whomever possesses them.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce journal peut vous permettre de survivre ! Vous y trouverez une liste d'endroits où trouver cinq objets clés dont la valeur sera sûrement inestimable pour tous ceux qui les possèdent.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Tagebuch enthält den Schlüssel zum Überleben! Es verrät, wo sich fünf wichtige Gegenstände befinden, die sich als unbezahlbar erweisen könnten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo diario è la chiave per la sopravvivenza! Al suo interno sono indicate le posizioni di cinque oggetti dal valore inestimabile per chiunque li possieda.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Este diario contiene la clave para sobrevivir! Contiene las posiciones de cinco objetos clave que pueden ser valiosísimos para quien los posea.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This journal holds the key to survival! Within it is the location of five key items that could be invaluable to whomever possesses them.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page1_text2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A lot of blood has been spilt trying to recover these items, including my own if you are reading this.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Des litres de sang ont été versés pour tenter de retrouver ces objets, et si vous lisez ceci, c'est que j'ai fait don du mien également.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Viel Blut ist bei der Suche nach diesen Gegenständen vergossen worden – einschließlich meines, wenn Sie dies hier lesen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Litri e litri di sangue sono stati versati nel tentativo di recuperare questi oggetti. Compreso il mio, se stai leggendo queste righe.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Se ha derramado mucha sangre para intentar recuperar estos objetos, incluida la mía si estás leyendo esto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A lot of blood has been spilt trying to recover these items, including my own if you are reading this.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page1_text3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">To whomever has found this journal, I wish you luck and hope that you manage to find the items described within its pages. They may be the only chance you will have of surviving these dark days.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">À quiconque trouve ce journal : je vous souhaite bonne chance et j'espère que vous parviendrez à retrouver les objets décrits dans ces pages. C'est peut-être là votre seule chance de survivre à cette guerre sordide.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer auch immer dieses Tagebuch findet: Ich wünsche Ihnen Glück und hoffe, Sie finden die Gegenstände, die auf diesen Seiten beschrieben sind. Sie könnten Ihre einzige Chance sein, diese finsteren Tage zu überleben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Auguro fortuna a chiunque trovi questo diario, con la speranza che riesca a recuperare gli oggetti descritti in queste pagine. Potrebbero essere l'unica speranza di sopravvivenza in questi giorni bui.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">A quien haya encontrado este diario, te deseo suerte y espero que logres encontrar los objetos descritos en sus páginas. Pueden ser tu única posibilidad de sobrevivir en estos tiempos oscuros.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">To whomever has found this journal, I wish you luck and hope that you manage to find the items described within its pages. They may be the only chance you will have of surviving these dark days.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page1_text4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If you see my son, please tell him to be strong, that I love him and that Daddy is sorry.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si vous croisez mon fils, je vous en prie, dites-lui d'être fort, dites-lui que je l'aime et que son papa est désolé.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn Sie meinem Sohn begegnen, sagen Sie ihm, er soll stark sein, dass ich ihn liebe und dass es seinem Daddy leidtut.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se mai incontrassi mio figlio, ti prego di dirgli di essere forte, che papà gli vuole bene e che gli dispiace tanto per ciò che è successo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si ves a mi hijo, por favor, dile que sea fuerte, que le quiero y que papá lo siente.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">If you see my son, please tell him to be strong, that I love him and that Daddy is sorry.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page2_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">October 12th</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le 12 octobre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">12. Oktober</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">12 ottobre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">12 de octubre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">October 12th</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page2_text</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Managed to pluck up the courage to leave the safety of the Diner today, I need to begin my search for supplies and get back to my boy soon, I hate leaving him alone. Think I will search the back of the building opposite the diner first.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aujourd'hui, j'ai réussi à prendre mon courage à deux mains et à quitter ce havre de paix qu'est le café-restaurant. Je dois chercher des vivres et retourner au plus vite auprès de mon fils. Je n'aime pas le laisser seul. Je pense commencer par fouiller l'arrière du bâtiment en face du café-restaurant.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Habe heute den Mut aufgebracht, die Sicherheit des Diners zu verlassen. Ich muss Vorräte suchen und bald wieder zu meinem Jungen zurück. Es ist furchtbar, ihn allein zu lassen. Zuerst werde ich die Rückseite des Gebäudes gegenüber des Diners untersuchen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Oggi sono riuscito a trovare il coraggio di lasciare il Diner. Devo iniziare la ricerca di oggetti utili e tornare al più presto da mio figlio. Odio lasciarlo da solo. Penso che prima inizierò a cercare dal retro dell'edificio di fronte al Diner.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hoy he logrado reunir valor suficiente para dejar la seguridad del restaurante. Tengo que empezar mi búsqueda de suministros y volver pronto con mi hijo. No me gusta dejarlo solo. Creo que primero registraré detrás del edificio frente al restaurante.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Managed to pluck up the courage to leave the safety of the Diner today, I need to begin my search for supplies and get back to my boy soon, I hate leaving him alone. Think I will search the back of the building opposite the diner first.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page3_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">October 13th</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le 13 octobre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">13. Oktober</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">13 ottobre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">13 de octubre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">October 13th</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page3_text</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">I have seen a radio in the middle of the park, but I couldn't get to it because of the feral Chimera patrolling the area. It could be our best chance of finding other survivors.Will try again tomorrow.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">J'ai vu une radio au milieu du parc mais je n'ai pas pu l'atteindre à cause des Chimères sauvages qui patrouillent dans la zone. C'est peut-être notre meilleure chance de retrouver d'autres survivants. Je réessaierai demain.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mitten im Park habe ich ein Funkgerät entdeckt, ich kam jedoch nicht ran, weil die wilden Bestien das Gebiet patrouillieren. Das könnte unsere Chance sein, andere Überlebende zu finden. Ich versuche es morgen wieder.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ho visto una radio al centro del parco, ma non sono riuscito a raccoglierla per via dei Chimera selvaggi che si aggirano nell'area. Potrebbe essere la nostra più grande possibilità di trovare altri sopravvissuti. Domani farò un altro tentativo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">He visto una radio en mitad del parque, pero no pude llegar hasta ella por las quimeras salvajes que patrullan por la zona. Podría ser nuestra mejor opción para encontrar a otros supervivientes. Volveré a intentarlo mañana.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">I have seen a radio in the middle of the park, but I couldn't get to it because of the feral Chimera patrolling the area. It could be our best chance of finding other survivors.Will try again tomorrow.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page4_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">October 14th</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le 14 octobre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">14. Oktober</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">14 ottobre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">14 de octubre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">October 14th</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page4_text</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">I have managed to cover some ground today, I saw a feral Chimera rummaging around in the garbage areas behind the surrounding buildings, I wonder if there's something useful back there.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">J'ai réussi à couvrir une bonne distance aujourd'hui. J'ai vu une Chimère sauvage fouiller les poubelles des bâtiments environnants. Je me demande s'il y a quelque chose d'utile dans ces endroits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Heute konnte ich ein ziemlich großes Gebiet untersuchen. Dabei habe ich eine Bestie entdeckt, die auf den Müllplätzen hinter den Gebäuden der Umgebung herumgewühlt hat. Ob es da wohl etwas Nützliches gibt?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sono riuscito a esplorare un po' la zona, oggi. Ho visto un Chimera selvaggio frugare fra la spazzatura dietro gli edifici circostanti. Mi chiedo se possa esserci qualcosa di utile, là.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hoy he logrado cubrir bastante terreno. Vi una quimera salvaje rebuscando en las áreas de basura detrás de los edificios circundantes. Me pregunto si habrá algo útil allí.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">I have managed to cover some ground today, I saw a feral Chimera rummaging around in the garbage areas behind the surrounding buildings, I wonder if there's something useful back there.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page5_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">October 15th</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le 15 octobre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">15. Oktober</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">15 ottobre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">15 de octubre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">October 15th</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page5_text</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There must be some weapons around here somewhere! I thought I saw a gun in one of the cars but those damn feral Chimera showed up before I got a chance to investigate further.I will keep trying.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il doit y avoir des armes dans les parages ! Je crois avoir vu un pistolet dans une voiture, mais ces foutues Chimères sauvages se sont pointées avant que j'aie eu la possibilité de m'approcher. Je réessaierai.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Irgendwo hier muss es Waffen geben! Ich dachte, ich hätte eine in einem der Autos gesehen, aber diese verdammten Bestien sind aufgetaucht, bevor ich es mir näher ansehen konnte. Ich versuche es weiter.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Devono pur esserci delle armi da qualche parte! Penso di aver visto una pistola dietro a una delle auto, ma quel maledetto Chimera selvaggio è saltato fuori prima ancora che mi avvicinassi. Continuerò a cercare.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Tiene que haber armas en alguna parte! Creí ver un arma en uno de los coches pero esas malditas quimeras salvajes aparecieron antes de que pudiera investigarlo. Seguiré intentándolo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">There must be some weapons around here somewhere! I thought I saw a gun in one of the cars but those damn feral Chimera showed up before I got a chance to investigate further.I will keep trying.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page6_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">October 16th</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le 16 octobre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">16. Oktober</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">16 ottobre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">16 de octubre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">October 16th</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_page6_text</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">I have discovered a decent size locker, there must be something of use inside it. I need to find a key to open the pad lock though. I saw a body lying in the street, but I didn't get a chance to see if it was alive.Most likely not. The feral Chimera increase in numbers by the day and the death squads are still sweeping the area regularly.I must get that equipment and get back to my boy today whatever the risks.Too much time has already passed.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">J'ai découvert un coffre de belle taille. Il doit y avoir quelque chose d'utile à l'intérieur. Mais je dois trouver la clé pour ouvrir le cadenas. J'ai vu un corps dans la rue mais je n'ai pas pu vérifier si la personne était vivante. Sans doute pas. Les Chimères sauvages sont plus nombreuses chaque jour et les escadrons de la mort quadrillent la zone. Je dois trouver cet équipement et revenir auprès de mon fils, coûte que coûte. Je n'ai que trop tardé.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ich habe eine ziemlich große Kiste gefunden, da muss etwas Nützliches drin sein. Aber ich brauche einen Schlüssel, um das Schloss zu öffnen. Auf der Straße lag ein Mensch, aber ich konnte nicht nachsehen, ob er noch gelebt hat ... wahrscheinlich eher nicht. Die Bestien werden jeden Tag mehr und die Todesschwadronen kontrollieren das Gebiet regelmäßig. Ich muss diese Ausrüstung holen und noch heute zu meinem Jungen zurück, egal, wie hoch das Risiko ist. Es ist schon zu viel Zeit vergangen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ho scoperto un baule di medie dimensioni, dovrà pur contenere qualcosa. Devo trovare la chiave per aprire il lucchetto. Ho visto un corpo in strada, ma non ho potuto avvicinarmi per verificare se fosse ancora vivo. Probabilmente no. I Chimera selvaggi aumentano giorno dopo giorno e le squadre d'assalto continuano a perlustrare l'area. Devo recuperare quelle cose e tornare da mio figlio oggi stesso, costi quel che costi. È passato troppo tempo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">He descubierto un cofre bastante grande, debe de contener algo útil. Pero tengo que encontrar una llave para abrir el candado. Vi un cuerpo tirado en la calle, pero no tuve ocasión de ver si estaba vivo. Seguramente no. Las quimeras salvajes aumentan de número día tras día y los escuadrones de la muerte siguen barriendo la zona con regularidad. Tengo que encontrar ese equipamiento y volver con mi hijo hoy mismo, cueste lo que cueste. Ha pasado demasiado tiempo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">I have discovered a decent size locker, there must be something of use inside it. I need to find a key to open the pad lock though. I saw a body lying in the street, but I didn't get a chance to see if it was alive.Most likely not. The feral Chimera increase in numbers by the day and the death squads are still sweeping the area regularly.I must get that equipment and get back to my boy today whatever the risks.Too much time has already passed.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">journal_recovered</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Recovered</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Retrouvé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Geborgen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Recuperato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Recuperado</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Recovered</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ladder_prompt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Climb</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Grimper</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Klettern</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Sali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Trepar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Climb</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">crawl_prompt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Crawl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Ramper</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Kriechen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Striscia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Arrastrarse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Crawl</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">fence_prompt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Force Open</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Forcer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Aufbrechen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Forza</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Forzar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Force Open</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Caution - Feral Approaching!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Attention : Chimère en approche !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Achtung: Bestie nähert sich!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Attenzione: Chimera selvaggi in avvicinamento!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Atención: ¡Salvaje aproximándose!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Caution - Feral Approaching!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">intro_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Resistance 3™ Scavenger</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chasse au trésor Resistance 3™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Resistance 3™"-Plünderer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ricerca di Resistance 3™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Búsqueda de Resistance 3™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Resistance 3™ Scavenger</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">intro_text1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Explore these war torn streets to find valuable equipment and earn great rewards. But keep an eye out for the feral Chimera, they are hungry and will spare no one.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Explorez ces rues dévastées par la guerre pour trouver des équipements de valeur et gagner de grandes récompenses. Mais gardez les yeux ouverts pour repérer les Chimères sauvages : elles ont faim et n'épargneront personne.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erkunden Sie die vom Krieg verwüsteten Straßen, um wertvolle Ausrüstung zu finden und tolle Belohnungen zu verdienen. Aber halten Sie die Augen nach den barbarischen Bestien offen – sie sind hungrig und verschonen niemanden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esplora queste strade devastate dalla guerra alla ricerca di equipaggiamenti e ricompense di valore. Attenzione ai Chimera selvaggi: sono affamati e non avranno pietà!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Explora estas calles devastadas por la guerra para encontrar equipamiento valioso y lograr grandes recompensas. Pero ten cuidado con las quimeras salvajes, están hambrientas y no hacen excepciones.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Explore these war torn streets to find valuable equipment and earn great rewards. But keep an eye out for the feral Chimera, they are hungry and will spare no one.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">intro_text2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">To earn rewards you must successfully collect the items and escape safely. If you get spotted by the Chimera or run out of time, it will be game over and you will lose any items you have collected on the current run.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour gagner des récompenses, vous devez retrouver les objets et vous échapper. Si vous vous faites repérer par les Chimères ou que vous dépassez le temps imparti, vous perdrez la partie ainsi que tous les objets que vous aurez réunis.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Um Belohnungen zu erhalten, müssen Sie die Gegenstände einsammeln und sich in Sicherheit bringen. Wenn die Bestien Sie entdecken oder die Zeit abläuft, ist das Spiel vorbei und Sie verlieren alle Gegenstände, die Sie beim aktuellen Versuch gesammelt haben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per ottenere le ricompense, devi recuperare gli oggetti e metterti in salvo. Se vieni scoperto dai Chimera o il tempo a tua disposizione si esaurisce, la partita terminerà e perderai qualsiasi oggetto recuperato nel corso della tua ricerca.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Para conseguir recompensas debes recoger los objetos y huir a un lugar seguro. Si las quimeras te ven o se te acaba el tiempo, se terminará la partida y perderás los objetos que hayas recogido en ese intento.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">To earn rewards you must successfully collect the items and escape safely. If you get spotted by the Chimera or run out of time, it will be game over and you will lose any items you have collected on the current run.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">intro_legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Begin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Commencer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Starten</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Inizia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Empezar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Begin</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">caught_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Game Over</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez perdu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spiel vorbei</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il gioco è finito</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fin de la partida</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Game Over</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">caught_text1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You did not escape safely, any supplies you may have collected on this run have been lost!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous ne vous êtes pas échappé(e) et tous les vivres que vous avez collectés ont été perdus !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie konnten nicht fliehen, deshalb sind alle Gegenstände, die Sie bei diesem Versuch gesammelt haben, verloren!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non sei riuscito a metterti in salvo! Tutti gli oggetti recuperati durante questa ricerca sono andati perduti!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡No has logrado escapar y has perdido los suministros que habías recogido en este intento!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You did not escape safely, any supplies you may have collected on this run have been lost!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">caught_text2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">To earn rewards you must successfully collect the items and escape safely.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour gagner des récompenses, vous devez retrouver les objets et vous échapper.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Um Belohnungen zu erhalten, müssen Sie die Gegenstände einsammeln und sich in Sicherheit bringen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per ottenere le ricompense, devi recuperare gli oggetti e metterti in salvo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Para conseguir recompensas debes recoger los objetos y huir a un lugar seguro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">To earn rewards you must successfully collect the items and escape safely.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">squad_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Chimeran death squad have entered the area!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'escadron de la mort chimérien a pénétré dans la zone !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Todesschwadron der Bestien hat das Gebiet betreten!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La squadra d'assalto Chimera è entrata nell'area!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡El escuadrón de la muerte quimera ha entrado en la zona!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Chimeran death squad have entered the area!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">squad_text1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You were forced to abandon your supplies and escape to avoid capture.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez dû abandonner vos vivres et vous échapper pour éviter d'être capturé(e) !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie mussten die Gegenstände zurücklassen und fliehen, um nicht erwischt zu werden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sei stato costretto ad abbandonare le tue risorse e a fuggire per evitare la cattura.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te has visto obligado a abandonar los suministros y huir para evitar que te capturen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You were forced to abandon your supplies and escape to avoid capture.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">squad_legend1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Play Again</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Rejouer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Erneut spielen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Gioca ancora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Volver a jugar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Play Again</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">squad_legend2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Exit to Diner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Sortir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE] Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE] Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] Salir del restaurante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE] Exit to Diner</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">safe_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You Escaped to Safety</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez réussi à vous échapper</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie konnten sich in Sicherheit bringen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sei salvo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Has huido a lugar seguro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You Escaped to Safety</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">safe_text1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Congratulations, you managed to avoid the Feral Chimera and escaped safely.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Félicitations, vous avez évité les Chimères sauvages et vous vous êtes échappé(e).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Glückwunsch, Sie konnten den Bestien ausweichen und sich in Sicherheit bringen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Congratulazioni! Sei riuscito a evitare i Chimera selvaggi e a metterti in salvo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Enhorabuena, has logrado evitar a las quimeras salvajes y has huido a un lugar seguro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Congratulations, you managed to avoid the Feral Chimera and escaped safely.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">safe_text2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dare you venture back outside to earn all 5 rewards?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Oserez-vous vous aventurer dehors pour gagner les 5 récompenses ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wagen Sie sich wieder nach draußen, um alle 5 Belohnungen zu verdienen?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai il fegato di avventurarti all'esterno per ottenere le 5 ricompense?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Te atreverás a salir de nuevo para conseguir las 5 recompensas?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dare you venture back outside to earn all 5 rewards?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">safe_legend1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Play Again</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Rejouer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Erneut spielen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Gioca ancora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Volver a jugar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Play Again</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">safe_legend2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Exit to Diner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Sortir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE] Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE] Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] Salir del restaurante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE] Exit to Diner</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">squad_alert</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Death squad Alert!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Escadron de la mort !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Todesschwadron-Alarm!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Squadra d'assalto! Attenzione!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Alerta de escuadrón de la muerte!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Death squad Alert!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">crowbar_find</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have discovered a crowbar!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez découvert un pied de biche !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben ein Brecheisen gefunden!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai trovato un piede di porco!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has encontrado una palanca!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You have discovered a crowbar!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">pickup</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Pick Up</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Ramasser</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Aufheben</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Raccogli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Recoger</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Pick Up</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">key_find</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You search the unfortunate man for something of use and find a small silver key!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez fouillé le corps de ce pauvre homme et vous avez trouvé une petite clé en argent !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie durchsuchen den Pechvogel nach etwas Nützlichem und finden einen kleinen Silberschlüssel!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai ispezionato lo sfortunato e hai trovato una piccola chiave d'argento!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Registras al desafortunado por si lleva algo útil y encuentras una pequeña llave plateada!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You search the unfortunate man for something of use and find a small silver key!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">locker_deny</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The container is locked. You will need to find a key to open it!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le coffre est fermé à clé. Vous devez trouver la clé pour l'ouvrir !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Kiste ist verschlossen. Sie brauchen einen Schlüssel, um sie zu öffnen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il baule è chiuso. Ti serve una chiave per aprirlo!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El contenedor está cerrado. Necesitarás una llave para abrirlo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The container is locked. You will need to find a key to open it!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">locker_open</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You open the container and find a valuable item inside.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez ouvert le coffre et trouvé un objet de valeur à l'intérieur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie öffnen die Kiste und finden darin einen wertvollen Gegenstand.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai aperto il baule e trovato un oggetto di valore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Abres el contenedor y encuentras dentro un objeto valioso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You open the container and find a valuable item inside.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">car_deny</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It is locked. You will need to find something to force it open.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C'est fermé à clé. Vous devez trouver quelque chose pour forcer la serrure.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verschlossen. Sie müssen etwas zum Aufbrechen finden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">È chiuso. Ti serve qualcosa per forzare la serratura.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Está cerrado. Necesitarás algo para forzarlo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">It is locked. You will need to find something to force it open.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">You break the lock, but find nothing of value inside.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Vous avez forcé la serrure mais vous n'avez rien trouvé à l'intérieur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sie brechen das Schloss auf, im Inneren finden Sie aber nichts Wertvolles.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hai forzato il lucchetto, ma non hai rinvenuto nulla di valore all'interno.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Rompes el cerrojo, pero no encuentras nada valioso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You break the lock, but find nothing of value inside.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">car_open</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You break the lock and find a valuable item.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez forcé la serrure et trouvé un objet de valeur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie brechen das Schloss auf und finden einen wertvollen Gegenstand.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai forzato il lucchetto e trovato un oggetto di valore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Rompes el cerrojo y encuentras dentro un objeto valioso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You break the lock and find a valuable item.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">mag_find</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have found a Magnum! Make it back to the diner safely with this item to keep it.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez trouvé un Magnum ! Retournez discrètement au café-restaurant avec cet objet pour pouvoir le garder.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben eine Magnum gefunden! Schaffen Sie es damit sicher zurück zum Diner, um sie zu behalten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai trovato una Magnum! Torna sano e salvo al Diner per assicurarti questo oggetto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has encontrado una Magnum! Vuelve sano y salvo al restaurante con este objeto para conservarlo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You have found a Magnum! Make it back to the diner safely with this item to keep it.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">chimerawep_find</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have found a Chimera weapon! Make it back to the diner safely with this item to keep it.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez trouvé une arme chimérienne ! Retournez discrètement au café-restaurant avec cet objet pour pouvoir le garder.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben eine Waffe der Bestien gefunden! Schaffen Sie es damit sicher zurück zum Diner, um sie zu behalten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai trovato un'arma Chimera! Torna sano e salvo al Diner per assicurarti questo oggetto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has encontrado un arma quimera! Vuelve sano y salvo al restaurante con este objeto para conservarlo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You have found a Chimera weapon! Make it back to the diner safely with this item to keep it.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">map_find</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have found a Map! Make it back to the diner safely with this item to keep it.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez trouvé une carte ! Retournez discrètement au café-restaurant avec cet objet pour pouvoir le garder.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben eine Karte gefunden! Schaffen Sie es damit sicher zurück zum Diner, um sie zu behalten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai trovato una mappa! Torna sano e salvo al Diner per assicurarti questo oggetto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has encontrado un mapa! Vuelve sano y salvo al restaurante con este objeto para conservarlo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You have found a Map! Make it back to the diner safely with this item to keep it.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">radio_find</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have found a Radio! Make it back to the diner safely with this item to keep it.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez trouvé une radio ! Retournez discrètement au café-restaurant avec cet objet pour pouvoir le garder.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben ein Funkgerät gefunden! Schaffen Sie es damit sicher zurück zum Diner, um es zu behalten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai trovato una radio! Torna sano e salvo al Diner per assicurarti questo oggetto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has encontrado una radio! Vuelve sano y salvo al restaurante con este objeto para conservarlo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You have found a Radio! Make it back to the diner safely with this item to keep it.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">jacket_find</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have found a Jacket! Make it back to the diner safely with this item to keep it.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez trouvé une veste ! Retournez discrètement au café-restaurant avec cet objet pour pouvoir le garder.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben eine Jacke gefunden! Schaffen Sie es damit sicher zurück zum Diner, um sie zu behalten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai trovato una giacca! Torna sano e salvo al Diner per assicurarti questo oggetto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has encontrado una chaqueta! Vuelve sano y salvo al restaurante con este objeto para conservarlo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You have found a Jacket! Make it back to the diner safely with this item to keep it.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">investigate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Investigate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Enquêter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Untersuchen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Ispeziona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Investigar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Investigate</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">abandon_legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[L2] Abandon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[L2] Abandonner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[L2] Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[L2] Annulla</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[L2] Salir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[L2] Abandon</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kick_legend1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rapidly Press [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyer rapidement sur [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücken Sie schnell [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi rapidamente [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa rápidamente [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rapidly Press [ACCEPT]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kick_legend2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Kick</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Donner un coup de pied</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE] Treten</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE] Calcia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] Patada</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE] Kick</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">[DECLINE] Force Open</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Forcer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Aufbrechen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE] Forza</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE] Forzar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE] Force Open</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">press_circle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyer sur [DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücken Sie [DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi [DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa [DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Press [DECLINE]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">press_x</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyer sur [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücken Sie [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Press [ACCEPT]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">square</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[SQUARE]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">square_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[SQUARE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[SQUARE]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>