<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ghostbusters™ Costume Female</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Costume S.O.S. Fantômes™ pour femme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ghostbusters™-Kostüm für Frauen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Costume da donna Ghostbusters™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Disfraz femenino de Cazafantasmas™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">女性用 ゴーストバスターズ™ コスチューム</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ghostbusters™ Costume Female</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Ghostbusters™ Limited Edition Boiler Suit Female Costume features a Proton Pack, Elbow Pads, Black Combat Boots, Black Chemical Resistant Gloves and a stylish Ghostbusters Hat for your PlayStation®Home Female avatar. Get the most unique and desirable unlicensed nuclear particle accelerator today. It will only be available for a limited time! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un Costume bleu de travail S.O.S. Fantômes™ pour femme édition limitée avec Pack à protons, Coudières, Bottes noires de combat, Gants noirs hyper-résistants et Casquette élégante S.O.S. Fantômes pour votre avatar féminin PlayStation®Home. Procurez-vous dès aujourd'hui l'accélérateur de particules nucléaires, un accessoire exclusif et unique. Cette offre n'est valable que pour une période limitée! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese limitierte Auflage des Ghostbusters™-Overalls für Frauen enthält ein Proton-Pack, Ellbogenschützer, schwarze Kampfstiefel, schwarze, gegen Chemikalien resistente Handschuhe und einen schicken Ghostbusters-Hut für Ihre PlayStation®Home Female avatar. Kaufen Sie noch heute den einzigartigen und wünschenswerten, unlizenzierten Nuklear-Beschleuniger. Begrenzt erhältlich! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa tuta da lavoro da donna Ghostbusters™ in edizione limitata include uno zaino protonico, dei paragomiti, degli stivali neri da combattimento, dei guanti neri resistenti agli acidi e un cappellino alla moda Ghostbusters per il tuo avatar femminile di PlayStation®Home. Acquista oggi l'acceleratore di particelle nucleari, un accessorio unico ed esclusivo. Sarà disponibile solo per un tempo limitato! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta edición limitada del disfraz femenino de  Cazafantasmas™ incluye un pack de protones, coderas, botas negras de combate, guantes negros resistentes a productos químicos y un elegante sombrero de cazafantasmas para tu personaje femenino de PlayStation®Home. Consigue hoy mismo el exclusivo y solicitado acelerador de partículas ilegal. Solo estará disponible un tiempo limitado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴーストバスターズ™女性用コスチューム（つなぎ）セット\n
PlayStation®Homeの女性アバター用ゴーストバスターズ™ のコスチュームです。最高にユニークで魅力的な「無許可の原子力パワー装置」を今すぐ手に入れましょう。\n
\n
本セットには、アバターカスタマイズ用の以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n
\n
「女性用 ゴーストバスターズ™ コスチューム　胴体部分」（トップス）\n
「女性用 ゴーストバスターズ™ コスチューム　脚部分」（ボトムズ）\n
「女性用 ゴーストバスターズ™ コスチューム　ブーツ」（靴）\n
「女性用 ゴーストバスターズ™ コスチューム　帽子」（頭）\n
「女性用 ゴーストバスターズ™ コスチューム　手袋」（手）\n

※購入すると、「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This Ghostbusters™ Limited Edition Boiler Suit Female Costume features a Proton Pack, Elbow Pads, Black Combat Boots, Black Chemical Resistant Gloves and a stylish Ghostbusters Hat for your PlayStation®Home Female avatar. Get the most unique and desirable unlicensed nuclear particle accelerator today. It will only be available for a limited time! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>