<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sammy the Skunk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sammy le sconse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sammy das Stinktier</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sammy la moffetta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mauro, la mofeta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スカンクのサミー君</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">스컹크 - 새미</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sammy the Skunk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">薩米臭鼬</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">薩米臭鼬</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sammy the Skunk</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hey Sammy, nice to see ya. Aww, look at that big bushy tail waving in the air! Are you glad to see me? Wait a minute…. PEEE-EUW! That is some smelly skunk stink right there. You're still cute though, so it's okay. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Salut Sammy, content de te voir. Ouah, regarde cette grande queue touffue qui s'agite ! Tu es content de me voir ? Attends… BEURK ! Voilà une odeur de sconse bien nauséabonde. Mais tu es mignon, alors on te pardonne. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hey Sammy, schön dich zu sehen. Ui, was für einen großen buschigen Schwanz du da hast! Freust du dich auch, mich zu sehen? Moment mal ... I-GITT! Mein Gott, stinkst du! Na ja, ist schon okay, du bist trotzdem süß. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ehi Sammy, felice di vederti. Aww, guarda quella coda pelosa che scodinzola nell'aria! Ti fa piacere vedermi? Aspetta un attimo…. PEEE-EUW! Sento proprio odore di moffetta puzzolente qui. Nonostante tutto sei graziosa, perciò tutto ok. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Hombre, Mauro! ¡Pero cuánto tiempo sin verte! ¿Mueves la cola porque te alegras de verme? Yo también estoy… ¡Puaj, qué peste! Bueno, vale, te lo perdono porque somos amigos… [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">サミー君にうかつに近づくと危険。しかしそんなリスクがあろうと近づきたくなるのがサミー君です。
\n※このアイテムはポータブルアイテムです。  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">헤이 새미, 만나서 반가워. 와우, 그 커다란 털복숭이 꼬리를 흔들어 대는 걸 봐! 나를 보니까 반가워?  잠시만…. 피-유! 정말 고약한 스컹크 냄새구나. 그래도 귀여우니까, 괜찮아. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Hey Sammy, nice to see ya. Aww, look at that big bushy tail waving in the air! Are you glad to see me? Wait a minute…. PEEE-EUW! That is some smelly skunk stink right there. You're still cute though, so it's okay. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">嘿，薩米，很高興見到你。 瞧牠那毛茸茸的大尾巴搖擺的樣子！你好可愛喔～等一下…噁 ! 牠又放臭屁了。不過你超可愛的，所以沒關係啦。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">嘿，薩米，很高興見到你。 瞧牠那毛茸茸的大尾巴搖擺的樣子！你好可愛喔～等一下…噁 ! 牠又放臭屁了。不過你超可愛的，所以沒關係啦。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hey Sammy, nice to see ya. Aww, look at that big bushy tail waving in the air! Are you glad to see me? Wait a minute…. PEEE-EUW! That is some smelly skunk stink right there. You're still cute though, so it's okay. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>