<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Daffodil Ikebana 2-piece Set</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de 2 pièces d'Ikebana de Narcisses</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">2-teiliges Set von Narzissen-Ikebana</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set 2 ikebana con narcisi</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos artículos ikebana de narcisos</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">水仙の生け花２点セット</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Daffodil Ikebana 2-piece Set</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 2-piece set that includes daffodils arranged in bamboo and ceramic vases.\nThis set includes the following items for private lounge customization.\n\n- Daffodils Arranged in Bamboo (Ornaments)\n- Daffodils Arranged in Ceramic (Ornaments)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category in "Private Lounge Customization".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 2 pièces incluant des narcisses arrangés dans des vases en bambou et en céramique.\nCe set inclut les objets suivants, pour personnaliser votre espace personnel :\n\n- Narcisses arrangés dans un bambou (Décoration)\n- Narcisses arrangés dans une céramique (Décoration)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective dans "Personnalisation de l'espace privé".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 2-teiliges Set, das Narzissen-Blumenarrangements in einer Bambusvase und einer Keramikvase enthält.\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände zur Bearbeitung des persönlichen Raumes.\n\n- Bambusvase mit Narzissen-Blumenarrangement (Verzierungen)\n- Keramikvase mit Narzissen-Blumenarrangement (Verzierungen)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie in "Bearbeitung des persönlichen Raumes" hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set composto da 2 elementi comprendente dei narcisi disposti in un vaso di bambù e in un vaso di ceramica.\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti per la personalizzazione della stanza privata.\n\n- Vaso di bambù con composizione di narcisi (Decorazioni)\n- Vaso di ceramica con composizione di narcisi (Decorazioni)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettiva categoria in "Personalizzazione stanza privata".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos artículos que incluye arreglos de narcisos en jarrones de bambú y cerámica.\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos para la personalizar la sala.\n\n- Arreglo de narcisos en recipiente de bambú (Adornos)\n- Arreglo de narcisos en recipiente de cerámica (Adornos)\n\n* Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría en "Personalización de la sala privada".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">水仙の、竹の器に生けたものと陶器に生けたものの２点セット。\n
本セットには、プライベートラウンジのカスタマイズ用の下記アイテムが含まれています。\n
\n
・竹の器に生けた水仙/装飾品\n
・陶器に生けた水仙/装飾品\n
\n
※購入すると、「プライベートラウンジのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 2-piece set that includes daffodils arranged in bamboo and ceramic vases.\nThis set includes the following items for private lounge customization.\n\n- Daffodils Arranged in Bamboo (Ornaments)\n- Daffodils Arranged in Ceramic (Ornaments)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category in "Private Lounge Customization".[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
