<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">neotopia sandwichboard LMO</LANG>
	<LANG ID="de-DE">neotopia Umhänge-Werbetafeln LMO</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-US">neotopia sandwichboard LMO</LANG>
	<LANG ID="es-ES">Cartel neotopia LMO</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Pancarte neotopia LMO</LANG>
	<LANG ID="it-IT">Pettorale pubblicitario neotopia LMO</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Show your support for neotopia, the new virtual world coming to PlayStation®4 with this awesome sandwichboard #EmbraceTomorrow. By equipping this Locomotion Item, your avatar's run speed will be faster. LMO (Locomotion) is a Portable Item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeige mit diesen fantastischen Umhänge-Werbetafeln deine Unterstützung für neotopia, die neue virtuelle Welt, welche auf die PlayStation®4 kommen wird #EmbraceTomorrow. Wenn Sie sich mit einem Bewegungsobjekt ausrüsten, wird die Laufgeschwindigkeit Ihres Avatars schneller. Bewegungsobjekte sind tragbare Gegenstände. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Show your support for neotopia, the new virtual world coming to PlayStation®4 with this awesome sandwichboard #EmbraceTomorrow. By equipping this Locomotion Item, your avatar's run speed will be faster. LMO (Locomotion) is a Portable Item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apoya neotopia, el nuevo mundo virtual que llegará a PlayStation®4, con este fabuloso cartel #Embrace Tomorrow. Al equipar este objeto de locomoción, la velocidad de carrera de tu avatar aumentará. LMO (locomoción) es un objeto portátil. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Soutenez neotopia, le nouveau monde virtuel sur PlayStation®4, grâce à cette super pancarte #EmbraceTomorrow. La vitesse de déplacement de votre avatar sera bien plus importante si vous équipez cet objet de locomotion. LMO (Locomotion) è un oggetto portatile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mostra il tuo sostegno per neotopia, il nuovo mondo virtuale in arrivo su PlayStation®4, con questo fantastico pettorale pubblicitario #EmbraceTomorrow. Equipaggiando questo accessorio di movimento, la velocità di corsa del tuo avatar aumenterà. LMO (Locomotion) è un oggetto portatile. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>