<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Enchanted Toadstool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Champignon Vénéneux Enchanté</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verzauberter Fliegenpilz</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fungo incantato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Taburete encantado</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">魔法にかけられた毒キノコ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">마법에 걸린 독버섯</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Enchanted Toadstool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">被施加魔法的毒菇</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">被施加魔法的毒菇</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Enchanted Toadstool</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">An accident with the Cauldron of the Sunless Kingdom caused this giant coloured mushroom to sprout. Experiment with ingredients and see what you can discover. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un accident avec le Chaudron du Royaume Sans-Soleil a permis à ce champignon Coloré de germer. Expérimentez avec les différents ingrédients pour voir ce que vous pourrez découvrir. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nach einem Missgeschick mit dem Kessel des Sonnenlosen Königreichs ist dieser farbenfrohe Riesenpilz gewachsen. Experimentiere mit Zutaten und sieh, was du entdecken kannst. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un incidente con il Calderone del Regno Tetro ha causato la crescita di questo gigantesco fungo Colorato. Prova i diversi ingredienti alla ricerca di nuove scoperte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un accidente con el Caldero del Reino sin sol provocó el nacimiento de esta gigantesca seta de Colores. Experimenta con los ingredientes a ver qué puedes descubrir. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">太陽無き王国の大釜の事故により、巨大な色付きキノコが出現。色々な材料で実験し、たくさんのことを発見しよう。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">망자의 왕국 가마솥에서 발생한 어떤 사고가 이같이 거대하고 화려한 색상의 버섯을 싹트게 했지요. 성분을 실험해서 무엇을 발견할 수 있는지 찾아봐요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">An accident with the Cauldron of the Sunless Kingdom caused this giant coloured mushroom to sprout. Experiment with ingredients and see what you can discover. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">蔽日王國神鼎發生的意外，讓這顆巨大的彩色蘑菇開始生長。用各種食材做實驗，看看能發現什麼。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">蔽日王國神鼎發生的意外，讓這顆巨大的彩色蘑菇開始生長。用各種食材做實驗，看看能發現什麼。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">An accident with the Cauldron of the Sunless Kingdom caused this giant colored mushroom to sprout. Experiment with ingredients and see what you can discover. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>