<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Salvador the Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Salvador le dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Salvador der Drache</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Salvador il Dragone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salvador el dragón</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドラゴンのサルバトール</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">용 - 살바도르</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Salvador the Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">沙瓦多龍</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">沙瓦多龍</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Salvador the Dragon</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Once known as the Ancient Roamer, these days Salvador enjoys a few more home comforts. A warm place to sleep and regular walks take priority over wreaking fiery vengeance on peasants. There are still a few tricks in the old dragon yet, though! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Autrefois connu sous le nom d'Ancien vagabond, Salvador est plus enclin au confort de la maison ces derniers temps. Un endroit chaud où dormir et de banales promenades ont pris le pas sur les ravages d'une vengeance féroce sur les paysans. Le vieux garde cependant plus d'un tour dans son sac ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Einst als der "Alte Rastlose" bekannt, genießt Salvador heute die Vorzüge eines gemütlichen Zuhauses. Ein warmer Schlafplatz und regelmäßige Spaziergänge sind ihm wichtiger als die Bauern mit seinem Feueratem in Angst und Schrecken zu versetzen. Doch in dem alten Drachen stecken immer noch genug Tricks! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se un tempo era noto come il Vecchio Vagabondo, oggi Salvador preferisce le comodità di casa. Piuttosto che scatenare la sua vendetta sui contadini, preferisce un posto caldo dove dormire e quotidiane passeggiate. Tuttavia, il dragone non ha perso ancora tutte le sue vecchie abitudini! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conocido antiguamente como el Viejo Hormero, Salvador disfruta, hoy en día, de mayor comodidad. Un sitio cálido para dormir y paseos regular son más importantes que vengarse fieramente de los campesinos. ¡Sin embargo, este viejo dragón aún se guarda algún as en la manga! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">かつては世界中を恐怖に陥れたサルバトールだが、最近はリラックスモード。暖かい寝床と軽い散歩が日課。ただし油断は禁物。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">전에는 고대의 유랑자로 알려졌던 살바도르는 요즘 편하게 쉬고 있어요. 농민들에게 불타는 파괴를 일삼는 것 보다, 따스하게 잠을 잘 수 있고 그냥 산보하는 것을 더 좋아하니까요. 하지만 아직 이 나이든 용이 물러진 것은 아닙니다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Once known as the Ancient Roamer, these days Salvador enjoys a few more home comforts. A warm place to sleep and regular walks take priority over wreaking fiery vengeance on peasants. There are still a few tricks in the old dragon yet, though! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">以前人叫牠流浪惡龍，最近只想在家賦閒。現在的牠寧願睡覺、散步，也不想出去荼毒農夫。不過這隻老龍還是有兩把刷子的！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">以前人叫牠流浪惡龍，最近只想在家賦閒。現在的牠寧願睡覺、散步，也不想出去荼毒農夫。不過這隻老龍還是有兩把刷子的！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Once known as the Ancient Roamer, these days Salvador enjoys a few more home comforts. A warm place to sleep and regular walks take priority over wreaking fiery vengeance on peasants. There are still a few tricks in the old dragon yet, though! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>