<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Torso_spelunker_14</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Green Spelunking Jumpsuit Top (M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Haut de combinaison de spéléologie verte (H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Grünes Oberteil für Spelunker-Overall (M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Parte superiore tuta da speleologo verde (U)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camisa de espeleólogo verde (M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">洞窟探険用トップス（緑・男性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">동굴 탐험용 상의(그린, 남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Green Spelunking Jumpsuit Top (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">洞窟探險用上衣（綠色/男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">洞窟探險用上衣（綠色/男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Green Spelunking Jumpsuit Top (M)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Torso_spelunker_14_description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The top half of a green jumpsuit with sleeves rolled back to give the arms more freedom. Comes with a brown backpack.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le haut d'une combinaison verte avec les manches retroussées pour donner plus de liberté aux bras. Accompagné d'un sac à dos marron.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Oberteil eines grünen Overalls mit hochgerollten Ärmeln für bessere Beweglichkeit der Arme. Brauner Rucksack inklusive.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La parte superiore di una tuta da speleologo verde. Le maniche sono arrotolate per lasciare una maggiore libertà di movimento. È corredata da uno zaino marrone.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Parte superior de un traje del espeleólogo verde con las mangas remangadas para tener mayor libertad de movimiento. Incluye una mochila marrón.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">動きやすいように袖を折り曲げた、緑の「つなぎ」の上半身部分。黒いリュックサックとのセット。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">움직이기 쉽게 소매를 접어 구부린 그린 탐험용 상의. 브라운 칼라의 배낭과 세트를 이룬다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The top half of a green jumpsuit with sleeves rolled back to give the arms more freedom. Comes with a black backpack.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">綠色連身服的上半身部份。為了便於活動，特別把袖子捲了起來。附贈咖色背包。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">綠色連身服的上半身部份。為了便於活動，特別把袖子捲了起來。附贈褐色背包。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The top half of a green jumpsuit with sleeves rolled back to give the arms more freedom. Comes with a brown backpack.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>