<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Transit Snapback Cap - Military Camo (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Casquette snapback Transit Camouflage militaire (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Transit Snapback-Kappe - Tarnfarbe (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Transit Cappello Snapback - Mimetico Militare (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Transit Gorra con cierre trasero - Camuflaje militar (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Transit hat is as tough and dependable as they come. Completely covered in a high quality woven fabric, its snap back design allows you to adjust the fit for perfect comfort. Our iconic wave logo is embroidered at front. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La casquette Transit est solide et l'on peut compter dessus. Complètement recouverte de tissu, sa conception snapback vous permet de l'ajuster pour un confort parfait. Notre logo iconique en forme de vague est brodé sur le front. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese robuste Transit Stoffkappe macht einfach alles mit. Aus hochwertigem Material und mit Snapbackdesign für perfekten Sitz und höchsten Komfort. Vorne auf der Kappe ist unser ikonisches Wellenlogo aufgestickt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il cappello Transit è estremamente forte e sicuro. Interamente ricoperto di tessuto di alta qualità, il design snapback ti consente di regolare la larghezza per il massimo comfort. Il nostro caratteristico logo in tessuto è ricamato sulla parte frontale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La gorra Transit es tan dura y fiable como ninguna. Revestida enteramente  con una tela cosida de alta calidad, su diseño de cierre trasero te permite ajustarla para una comodidad total. Nuestro icónico logotipo con la ola está bordado por delante. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>