<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Crush</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Crush</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Crush</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Crush</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Crush</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Crush, a charming and romantic companion who can encourage love with only the beating of his wings. He graduated with honors at the school of love, he is an adventurer ready to melt the heart of anyone who gets in his way. Crush knows that love always wins! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Crush, un compagnon à la fois charmant et romantique qui sait inviter à l'amour par le seul battement de ses ailes. Il a obtenu son diplôme avec les honneurs à l'école de l'Amour, c'est un aventurier prêt à faire fondre le cœur de quiconque croise son chemin. Crush sait que l'Amour gagne toujours ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Crush, ein charmanter und romantischer Begleiter, der die Liebe nur mit dem Schlagen seiner Flügel ermutigen kann. Er hat sein Studium an der Schule der Liebe mit Auszeichnung abgeschlossen, ist ein Abenteurer, bereit, das Herz eines jeden, der ihm über den Weg läuft, zum Schmelzen zu bringen. Crush weiß, dass die Liebe immer gewinnt![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Crush, un compagno affascinante e romantico che incoraggia l’amore con il semplice battito delle sue ali. Ha conseguito una laurea con lode alla scuola dell’amore ed è un avventuriero pronto a sciogliere il cuore di chiunque si trovi sulla sua strada. Crush sa bene che l’amore vince sempre![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Crush, un compañero encantador y romántico capaz de enamorar con solo el batir de sus alas. Licenciado con honores en la escuela del amor, es un aventurero dispuesto a derretir el corazón de cualquiera que se ponga a su alcance. Crush sabe que el amor siempre vence! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kCompanionName1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Crush</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Crush</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Crush</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Crush</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Crush</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>