<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Interceptor DX Aerofoils</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Profil Interceptor DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Interceptor DX Frontspoiler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Profilo alare Interceptor DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Perfiles aerodinámicos Interceptor DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Interceptor DX エアロフォイル</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Interceptor DX 날개</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Interceptor DX Aerofoils</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Interceptor DX 機翼</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Interceptor DX 機翼</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Interceptor DX Aerofoils</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A more streamlined design for your Sodium2 racer to produce exceptional straight line speed and turning power. Turn too tightly though and you'll lose momentum. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un profil plus caréné pour votre véhicule de course Sodium2 pour une puissance accrue dans les virages et une vitesse exceptionnelle en ligne droite. Cependant, si vous effectuez des virages trop secs, vous perdrez votre élan. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein aerodynamischeres Design, das deinem Sodium2-Gleiter ein herausragendes Kurvenverhalten und sehr hohe Geschwindigkeiten auf Geraden ermöglicht. Doch wenn du zu eine Kurve zu eng fliegst, verlierst du an Geschwindigkeit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un design aerodinamico migliorato consente al tuo veicolo da corsa Sodium2 di raggiungere un'eccezionale velocità lineare e maggiore potenza in curva. Attenzione a non tagliare troppo in curva o rischierai di perdere velocità. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un diseño más aerodinámico para que tu corredor de Sodium2 obtenga una velocidad en línea recta y una potencia de giro excepcionales. Pero si haces un giro demasiado cerrado, perderás impulso. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">流線型のデザインで、並外れた直線スピードとカーブ操作力を誇ります。ただし、あまり急に曲がりすぎると、運動量を失ってしまいます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium2 레이서를 위해 더욱 다듬어진 디자인입니다. 주행 성능의 경이로운 향상과 회전 속도를 가져옵니다. 그러나 너무 빠듯한 각도의 코너링은 역시 타이밍을 놓치는 결과를 가져옵니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A more streamlined design for your Sodium2 racer to produce exceptional straight line speed and turning power. Turn too tightly though and you'll lose momentum. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">讓你的Sodium2飛船有更加流線型的設計，達到出色的直路速度和轉彎能量。但如果過急地轉彎，便會失去動力。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">讓你的Sodium2飛船有更加流線型的設計，達到出色的直路速度和轉彎能量。但如果過急地轉彎，便會失去動力。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A more streamlined design for your Sodium2 racer to produce exceptional straight line speed and turning power. Turn too tightly though and you'll lose momentum. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>