<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Loco Sofa (Kulche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fauteuil Loco (Kulche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Loco-Sofa (Kulche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sofà dei Loco (Kulche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LocoSofá (Kulche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ロコソファ（クルチェ）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">로코 소파(크루체)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Loco Sofa (Kulche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">樂克沙發（克魯傑）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">樂克沙發（克魯傑）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Loco Sofa (Kulche)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This striking sofa is covered with a LocoRoco design. Only a professional interior designer could arrange a room around this!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space. Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce sublime fauteuil est recouvert d'un motif LocoRoco.
Seul un décorateur d'intérieur professionnel pourrait organiser une pièce autour de ça !\n\nAcheter cet objet ajoute 1 LocoRoco à ton espace personnel de l'île Loco.
Tu peux ajouter jusqu'à 20 LocoRoco à l'île Loco. Une fois le maximum atteint, tu ne peux plus ajouter d'unités.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses auffällige Sofa ist mit einem LocoRoco-Design bezogen. Nur ein professioneller Innenarchitekt könnte einen Raum darum herum gestalten!\n\nDieser Gegenstand fügt deinem Loco-Insel-Apartment 1 LocoRoco hinzu. Du kannst bis zu 20 LocoRoco hinzufügen. Ist das Maximum erreicht, können keine weiteren Einheiten hinzugefügt werden.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una singolare poltrona in stile LocoRoco.\n
Solo un arredatore d'interni professionista è in grado di arredare una stanza partendo da questo pezzo!\n\nAcquistando questo oggetto, aggiungerai un LocoRoco al tuo spazio personale su Loco Island. Puoi aggiungere fino a 20 LocoRoco su Loco Island. Una volta raggiunto il numero massimo, non potrai aggiungerne altri.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este llamativo sofá está forrado con un diseño de LocoRoco.  ¡Solo un diseñador de interiores profesional podría decorar una habitación con esto!\n\nComprar este objeto añade 1 LocoRoco a tu espacio personal en la Loco Isla. Puedes añadir un máximo de 20 LocoRoco a la Loco Isla. Cuando hayas alcanzado este número, no podrás añadir más unidades.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">”ロコロコ”が全面的にデザインされたインパクト抜群のソファ。\nこれを部屋にマッチさせられるようならインテリアの達人！\n\nこのアイテムを購入するとパーソナルスペース”ロコアイランド”に\n”ロコロコ”が１匹追加されます。”ロコアイランド”には最大20匹まで”ロコロコ”を追加できます。最大数に達した場合は、それ以上の追加はされません。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">로코로코'가 전면에 디자인된 임팩트 있는 소파. 이것을 방에 잘 매치시킬 수 있다면 당신은 인테리어의 달인!\n\n이 아이템을 구입하면 퍼스널 스페이스 '로코 아일랜드'에 '로코로코'가 1마리 추가됩니다. '로코 아일랜드'에는 최대 20마리까지 '로코로코'를 추가할 수 있습니다.  최대치에 다다르면 더 이상은 추가할 수 없습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This striking sofa is covered with a LocoRoco design. Only a professional interior designer could arrange a room around this!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space. Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">以”樂克樂克”為主題所設計的超醒目沙發。若將此沙發完美融入個人房間，你就是個擺設高手！\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">以”樂克樂克”為主題所設計的超醒目沙發。若將此沙發完美融入個人房間，你就是個擺設高手！\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A sofa that screams "LocoRoco" all over it. If you can blend this sofa into your room, you must have a degree in interior design!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your LocoIsland personal space. Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to LocoIsland. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>