<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Xiong Mao the Baby Panda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Xiong Mao le bébé panda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Xiong das Pandababy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Xiong Mao il baby panda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Xiong Mao, el bebé panda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">パンダのマオ君</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">아기 팬다 - 청 마오</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Xiong Mao the Baby Panda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">胖達寶貝熊貓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">胖達寶貝熊貓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Xiong Mao the Baby Panda</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">As you probably already know, pandas are very rare due to their specialist dietary requirements. Virtual pandas like Xiong Mao are much hardier than their real life counterparts and can thrive in any virtual environment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Comme vous le savez, les pandas sont très rares en raison de leur régime alimentaire bien particulier. Les pandas virtuels comme Xiong Mao sont bien plus résistants que leurs homologues de la vraie vie et peuvent s'épanouir dans n'importe quel environnement virtuel. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du weißt sicher schon, dass Pandas auf Grund ihres speziellen Fressverhaltens sehr selten sind. Virtuelle Pandas wie Xiong Mao sind weitaus robuster als ihre echten Artgenossen und fühlen sich in jeder virtuellen Umgebung wohl. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Come probabilmente già sai, i panda sono molto rari a causa delle loro particolari abitudini alimentari. I panda virtuali come Xiong Mao sono molto meno delicati della loro controparte reale e possono sopravvivere in qualunque contesto virtuale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Como probablemente ya sabréis, los osos panda requieren una dieta bastante estricta. Los pandas virtuales, como Xiong Mao, son mucho más duros que sus homólogos reales y pueden habitar en cualquier hábitat virtual. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ご存知のようにパンダはとてもデリケートな生き物です。でもご安心下さい、このヴァーチャルパンダならいかなる環境にも適応できます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">벌써 알고 계시겠지만, 팬다는 식단이 독특해서 아주 희귀한 동물입니다. 청 마오 같은 가상 팬다는 살아있는 팬다보다 아주 강인해서 어떤 가상의 환경에서도 살아 남을 수 있답니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">As you probably already know, pandas are very rare due to their specialist dietary requirements. Virtual pandas like Xiong Mao are much hardier than their real life counterparts and can thrive in any virtual environment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">您可能知道熊貓因為食物特殊，所以非常稀少。胖達這些虛擬熊貓和真熊貓比起來強太多了，能夠在任何虛擬環境下頭好壯壯。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">您可能知道熊貓因為食物特殊，所以非常稀少。胖達這些虛擬熊貓和真熊貓比起來強太多了，能夠在任何虛擬環境下頭好壯壯。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">As you probably already know, pandas are very rare due to their specialist dietary requirements. Virtual pandas like Xiong Mao are much hardier than their real life counterparts and can thrive in any virtual environment. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>