<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Inflatable Whale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Baleine gonflable</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aufblasbarer Wal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Balena Gonfiabile</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ballena hinchable</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴムのクジラ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Inflatable Whale</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">We know when you stare at this glittering blue whale you can’t help but say, ‘Oooh, shiny!” But when you purchase this piece you’ll unlock whale sea-life for LOOT’s Amaterasu Experience (if you own it, that is.) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">On sait bien qu'en regardant cette belle baleine scintillante, vous ne pouvez vous empêcher de dire "Ohhh, ça brille !". En achetant cet élément vous libérez une vraie baleine de l'Expérience Amaterasu de Loot (si vous l'avez, bien sûr).  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wir wissen, was du sagen wirst, sobald du ein Auge auf diesen funkelnden blauen Wal wirfst: "Oooh, wie der glänzt!"
Aber, wenn du dieses Stück kaufst, fügst du dem Ökosystem in LOOT's Amaterasu Experience (sofern du es besitzt) auch Wale hinzu.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Basta guardare questa luccicante balena blu per pensare "Ohhhh, brilla!" Comprando questo articolo sbloccherai le balene per LOOT’s Amaterasu Experience (ammesso che tu ce l'abbia). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sabemos que cuando miras esta flamante ballena azul, te quedas sin palabras, pero cuando compres esta pieza, desbloquearás una ballena marina para LOOT's Amaterasu Experience (si lo tienes, claro). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この輝く青いクジラを見たときに、「うわぁ、キラキラだ！」っていいたくなるでしょう！　でもこれを買うことができるのはLOOTアマテラス・エクスペリエンスのためのホェール・シーライフを開放してからです。（持っていることが条件です。） [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">We know when you stare at this glittering blue whale you can’t help but say, ‘Oooh, shiny!” But when you purchase this piece you’ll unlock whale sea-life for LOOT’s Amaterasu Experience (if you own it, that is.) [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>