<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Loco Slippers (Kulche/women's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pantoufles Loco (Kulche/femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Loco-Pantoffeln (Kulche/Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pantofole Loco (Kulche) da donna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Loco pantuflas (Kulche/mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ロコスリッパ(クルチェ・女性用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">로코 슬리퍼(크루체/여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Loco Slippers (Kulche/women's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">樂克拖鞋（克魯傑/女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">樂克拖鞋（克魯傑/女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Loco Slippers (Kulche: for women)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">These slippers are perfect for lounging at home.\n
The smiling LocoRoco and plush feel will have you feeling relaxed the moment you slip them on.
Wear them out to show off their utter cuteness!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ces pantoufles sont idéales pour paresser à la maison.
Le LocoRoco souriant et la sensation pelucheuse auront un effet relaxant immédiat dès que tu te glisseras dedans.
Use-les jusqu'à la corde et épate ton entourage par leur aspect véritablement craquant !\n\nAcheter cet objet ajoute 1 LocoRoco à ton espace personnel de l'île Loco.
Tu peux ajouter jusqu'à 20 LocoRoco à l'île Loco. Une fois le maximum atteint, tu ne peux plus ajouter d'unités.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese Pantoffeln sind perfekt, um zu Hause zu faulenzen.
Der lächelnde LocoRoco und das Plüschmaterial lassen dich sofort entspannen, wenn du sie anziehst.
Trage sie auch draußen, um ihre Niedlichkeit zu zeigen!\n\nDieser Gegenstand fügt deinem Loco-Insel-Apartment 1 LocoRoco hinzu.
Du kannst bis zu 20 LocoRoco hinzufügen. Ist das Maximum erreicht, können keine weiteren Einheiten hinzugefügt werden.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Queste pantofole sono perfette per rimanere in casa.
I sorridenti LocoRoco e la sensazione di morbidezza ti daranno un immediato senso di relax appena le indossi.
Calzale per mostrare tutta la loro tenerezza!\n\nAcquistando questo oggetto, aggiungerai un LocoRoco al tuo spazio personale su Loco Island.
Puoi aggiungere fino a 20 LocoRoco su Loco Island. Una volta raggiunto il numero massimo, non potrai aggiungerne altri.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estas pantuflas son perfectas para estar en casa sin hacer nada.
El LocoRoco sonriente y la sensación del peluche te harán sentirte relajado cuando te las pongas.
¡Llévalas cuando salgas para que vean lo lindas que son!\n\nComprar este objeto añade 1 LocoRoco a tu espacio personal en la Loco Isla.
Puedes añadir un máximo de 20 LocoRoco a la Loco Isla. Cuando hayas alcanzado este número, no podrás añadir más unidades.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">のんびり家でくつろぎたい気分の時にうってつけなスリッパです。
笑顔のロコロコとフカフカした履き心地が、あなたをすぐにリラックスモードにしてくれます。
外で履いても注目度抜群の可愛さです！\n\nこのアイテムを購入するとパーソナルスペース”ロコアイランド”に\n”ロコロコ”が１匹追加されます。”ロコアイランド”には最大20匹まで”ロコロコ”を追加できます。最大数に達した場合は、それ以上の追加はされません。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">한가로이 집에서 쉬고 싶을 때 안성맞춤인 슬리퍼에요.\n
웃고 있는 로코로코와 폭신한 착용감이 당신을 금방 릴렉스 모드로 만들어 줄 거에요.
밖에서 신고 다니면, 주목도가 확 올라갈 귀여운 디자인이죠!\n\n이 아이템을 구입하면 퍼스널 스페이스 '로코 아일랜드'에 '로코로코'가 1마리 추가됩니다.
'로코 아일랜드'에는 최대 20마리까지 '로코로코'를 추가할 수 있습니다. 
최대치에 다다르면 더 이상은 추가할 수 없습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">These slippers are perfect for lounging at home.\n
The smiling LocoRoco and plush feel will have you feeling relaxed the moment you slip them on.
Wear them out to show off their utter cuteness!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">想在家裡悠閒度過時適合穿的拖鞋。
面帶笑容的樂克樂克和穿起來柔軟舒適的觸感，能讓您馬上進入放鬆狀態。
在外頭穿也相當可愛，超引人注目！\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。
「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，
便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">想在家裡悠閒度過時適合穿的拖鞋。
面帶笑容的樂克樂克和穿起來柔軟舒適的觸感，能讓您馬上進入放鬆狀態。
在外頭穿也相當可愛，超引人注目！\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。
「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，
便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">These slippers are perfect for lounging at home.
The smiling LocoRoco and the flufy comfort help you relax and get away.
You can also wear them outside and catch everyone's attention!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your LocoIsland personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to LocoIsland. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>