<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Glittering Sands Secluded Retreat</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Sables Scintillants du Havre de Paix</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Abgeschiedener Rückzugsort am Funkelstrand</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Ritiro Isolato delle Sabbie Scintillanti</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Refugio solitario de arenas brillantes</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ふたりだけの熱い砂浜</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">숨겨진 반짝이는 모래 휴양지</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Glittering Sands Secluded Retreat</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">閃閃發亮的閒靜沙灘</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">閃閃發亮的閒靜沙灘</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Glittering Sands Secluded Retreat</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Spend your holiday on a luxurious private beach. 
The clear blue sea, the white sandy beach, and the cottage on the ocean are all yours. 
With a friend, or with that special someone. Your holiday has just begun. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Passez vos vacances sur une plage privée somptueuse. 
La mer bleue et limpide, la plage de sable blanc et le chalet sur l’océan sont à vous.
Avec un(e) ami(e), ou la personne que vous aimez. Vos vacances ne font que commencer. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Verbringe deine Ferien an einem luxuriösen Privatstrand 
Das kristallklare Wasser, der weiße Sandstrand und das Ferienhaus am Meer, all dies gehört dir.  
Mit einem Freund oder dieser einen besonderen Person. Deine Ferien haben gerade erst begonnen. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Passa le tue vacanze in una lussuosa spiaggia privata. 
Il mare cristallino, la spiaggia di sabbia bianchissima e la casetta sull'oceano sono tutti tuoi. 
Con un amico, o con una persona speciale. La tua vacanza è appena iniziata. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Pasa tus vacaciones en una lujosa playa privada. 
El mar cristalino, la playa de arena blanca y la casa en el océano te pertencen... 
Con un amigo, o con ese alguien especial. Tus vacaciones acaban de comenzar. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">バカンスは、贅沢なプライベートビーチで。\n透き通った青い海も、広い砂浜も、海上のコテージも、全てあなたのもの。\n仲間と、恋人と。あなたのバカンスは始まったばかりです。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">럭셔리한 개인 모래사장에서 휴가를 보내세요. 맑고 푸른 바다, 하얀 모래사장, 그리고 바다 위의 오두막까지 모두 여러분의 소유입니다. 친구와, 혹은 당신에게 특별한 그분과 함께. 여러분의 휴가는 이제 시작일 뿐입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Spend your holiday on a luxurious private beach. 
The clear blue sea, the white sandy beach, and the cottage on the ocean are all yours. 
With a friend, or with that special someone. Your holiday has just begun. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">在豪華的私人海灘度假。不論是清澈見底的碧藍色的海、廣闊無比的沙灘、或海上的別墅都全屬於您。和朋友或情人一同到訪，您的假期才正要開始。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">在豪華的私人海灘度假。不論是清澈見底的碧藍色的海、廣闊無比的沙灘、或海上的別墅都全屬於您。和朋友或情人一同到訪，您的假期才正要開始。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Spend your holiday on a luxurious private beach. 
The clear blue sea, the white sandy beach, and the cottage on the ocean are all yours. 
With a friend, or with that special someone. Your holiday has just begun. [#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
