<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">T-shirt PlayStation®Move (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">PlayStation®Move-T-Shirt (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">T-shirt PlayStation®Move (femminile)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta de PlayStation®Move (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">PlayStation®Move 티셔츠 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">PlayStation®Move T-shirt (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">PlayStation®Move T恤(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">PlayStation®Move T恤(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">PlayStation®Move T-shirt (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Affichez votre soutien pour PlayStation®Move avec ce T-shirt en édition limitée. Le design est basé sur le vrai T-shirt distribué lors des événements PlayStation®Move à Seattle et au cours de l'E3 2010. Pour les avatars féminins seulement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeigen Sie mit diesem limitiert erhältlichen T-Shirt allen, dass Sie PlayStation®Move mögen. Das Design basiert auf dem realen T-Shirt, das auf den PlayStation®Move-Events in Seattle und bei der E3 2010 verteilt wird. Nur für weibliche Avatare.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sostieni PlayStation®Move con orgoglio sfoggiando questa t-shirt a edizione limitata. Il modello è basato su quello della vera t-shirt distribuita agli eventi PlayStation®Move di Seattle e dell'E3 2010. Solo per avatar femminili.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Demuestra tu apoyo a PlayStation®Move con esta camiseta de edición limitada. El diseño está basado en la camiseta real repartida en los eventos de PlayStation®Move realizados en Seattle y en el E3 2010. Solo para avatares femeninos.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">PlayStation®Move 를 응원하는 마음을 담은 한정판 티셔츠입니다. 디자인은 E3 2010에서 실제로 주어지는 티셔츠에서 따 왔습니다. 여성용입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Show your support for PlayStation®Move with this limited edition T-shirt. The design is based on the real T-shirt given out at PlayStation®Move events at E3 2010. For female avatars only.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">穿上這件T恤展現您對PlayStation®Move的喜愛吧。T恤的設計跟在E3 2010會場所舉辦的PlayStation®Move活動所贈送的T恤相同。僅限女性分身角色使用。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">穿上這件T恤展現您對PlayStation®Move的喜愛吧。T恤的設計跟在E3 2010會場所舉辦的PlayStation®Move活動所贈送的T恤相同。僅限女性分身角色使用。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Show your support for PlayStation®Move with this limited edition T-shirt. The design is based on the real T-shirt given out at PlayStation®Move events at Seattle and E3 2010. For female avatars only.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>