<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Buy a Mech</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Acheter un mecha</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kaufe einen Mech</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Acquista un Mecha</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Comprar un Mech</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">メカを買う</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">멕 구입</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Buy a Mech</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">購買機械服</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">購買機械服</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Buy a Mech</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Buy a Mech [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Acheter un mecha [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kaufe einen Mech [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Acquista un Mecha [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Comprar un Mech [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">メカを買う [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">멕 구입 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Buy a Mech [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">購買機械服 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">購買機械服 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Buy a Mech [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kBuyMech</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Buy a Mech</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Acheter un mecha</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kaufe einen Mech</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Acquista un Mecha</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Comprar un Mech</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">メカを買う</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">멕 구입</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Buy a Mech</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">購買機械服</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">購買機械服</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Buy a Mech</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kBuyMechLegend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Buy a Mech</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Acheter un mecha</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Kaufe einen Mech</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Acquista un Mecha</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Comprar un Mech</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[ACCEPT] メカを買う</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[ACCEPT] 멕 구입</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[ACCEPT] Buy a Mech</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[ACCEPT] 購買機械服</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[ACCEPT] 購買機械服</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Buy a Mech</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kMechShopWelcome</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to the Novus Prime Mech Shop</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue au Magasin de Mecha Novus Prime</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen im Novus Prime Mech Shop</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuto al Negozio di mecha Novus Prime</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido a la tienda Mech Novus Prime</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライム　メカショップへようこそ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임 멕 숍에 오신 것을 환영합니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Welcome to the Novus Prime Mech Shop</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">歡迎光臨Novus Prime機械服商店</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">歡迎光臨Novus Prime機械服商店</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome to the Novus Prime Mech Shop</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kMechShopDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Purchase a Novus Prime Power Mech Suit today!  This fully-automated mech features state-of-the-art movement and stabilization technology, allowing for custom maneuvers, walking, and even flying!  A Nebulon Magnet is included, which  draws Nebulon towards your fighter ships during Novus Prime missions.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Achetez une tenue de mecha Novus Prime aujourd'hui ! Ce mecha totalement automatisé inclut les toutes dernières technologies de mouvement et de stabilisation, permettant des manœuvres customisées, la marche et même le vol ! Un aimant à nébulon est intégré et attire le nébulon alentour vers vos vaisseaux de combat durant les missions Novus Prime.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kaufe noch heute deinen Novus Prime Power-Mech-Anzug!  Dieser vollautomatisierte Mech zeichnet sich durch modernste Bewegungs- und Stabilisationstechnologie aus, welche individuelle Manöver, ausbalanciertes Laufen und sogar Fliegen ermöglicht!  Der beigefügte Nebulon-Magnet deines Kampfschiffes zieht während Novus Prime Missionen Nebulon an.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Acquista un esoscheletro mecha Novus Prime! Questo mecha automatico vanta della tecnologia di stabilizazzione e di movimento di ultima generazione, che permette manovre personalizzate, camminata autobilanciata e addirittura il volo! Vi è incluso un magnete nebulon, che attira i nebulon alle tue navi da combattimento durante le missioni della Novus Prime.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Compra hoy un Traje Power Mech Novus Prime! Este mech totalmente automatizado ofrece movimiento de punta, permitiendo maniobras personalizadas, caminado auto-balanceado, ¡e incluso vuelo! Un imán de nebulón está incluido, el cual atrae nebulón hacia tus naves de combate durante las misiones Novus Prime.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">最新のノーバス・プライムのメカスーツを購入しよう！ このフルオートメーションメカは、最先端の動作と安定化技術が特徴で、カスタム操縦、自己平衡歩行、さらに飛行も可能！ ノーバス・プライムでのミッションの間、あなたの戦闘機に ネブロンを引き寄せるネブロンマグネットが搭載されています。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임 파워멕 슈츠를 지금 바로 구입하세요! 완전 자동화 기능을 탑재한 본 멕은 최첨단 동작과 안정화 기술을 사용하여, 자체 조작과 걷기는 물론, 비행도 가능합니다. 노부스 프라임 미션을 수행하는 동안 네뷸론을 함선으로 끌어올 수 있는 네뷸론 마그넷도 포함되어 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Purchase a Novus Prime Power Mech Suit today!  This fully-automated mech features state-of-the-art movement and stabilization technology, allowing for custom maneuvers, walking, and even flying!  A Nebulon Magnet is included, which  draws Nebulon towards your fighter ships during Novus Prime missions.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">今天就購買Novus Prime的威力機械服吧！這種完全自動化的機械服裝搭載了最先進的動作和穩定技術，允許自訂操作，自我平衡步行，甚至飛行！裝備包括了Nebulon磁石，讓你的戰鬥機在Novus Prime任務當中吸引Nebulon。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">今天就購買Novus Prime的威力機械服吧！這種完全自動化的機械服裝搭載了最先進的動作和穩定技術，允許自訂操作，自我平衡步行，甚至飛行！裝備包括了Nebulon磁石，讓你的戰鬥機在Novus Prime任務當中吸引Nebulon。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Purchase a Novus Prime Power Mech Suit today!  This fully-automated mech features state-of-the-art movement and stabilization technology, allowing for custom maneuvers, walking, and even flying!  A Nebulon Magnet is included, which  draws Nebulon towards your fighter ships during Novus Prime missions.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kMechShopRogue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Purchase a Novus Prime Rogue Mech Suit today!  This fully-automated mech features state-of-the-art movement and stabilization technology, allowing for custom maneuvers, walking, and even flying!  This space pirate mech also "gathers" Nebulon every night, which increases your Novus Prime daily salary!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Achetez une tenue de mecha intrépide Novus Prime aujourd'hui ! Ce mecha totalement automatisé inclut les toutes dernières technologies de mouvement et de stabilisation, permettant des manœuvres customisées, la marche et même le vol ! Ce mecha venant des pirates de l'espace "récolte" aussi du nébulon chaque nuit, ce qui augmente votre salaire Novus Prime quotidien !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kaufe noch heute deinen Novus Prime Schurken-Mech-Anzug! Dieser vollautomatisierte Mech zeichnet sich durch modernste Bewegungs- und Stabilisationstechnologie aus, welche individuelle Manöver, ausbalanciertes Laufen und sogar Fliegen ermöglicht! Dieser Weltraumpiraten-Mech "sammelt" außerdem jede Nacht Nebulon ein, wodurch sich täglich dein Novus Prime Sold erhöht!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Acquista un esoscheletro mecha Novus Prime! Questo mecha automatico vanta della tecnologia di stabilizazzione e di movimento di ultima generazione, che permette manovre personalizzate, camminata autobilanciata e addirittura il volo! Questo mecha, una volta posseduto dai pirati spaziali, "raccoglie" nebulon ogni notte, incrementando il salario della tua Novus Prime!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Compra hoy un Traje Mech Furtivo Novus Prime! Este mech totalmente automatizado ofrece movimiento de punta, permitiendo maniobras personalizadas, caminado auto-balanceado, ¡e incluso vuelo!  Este mech pirata espacial también "reúne" nebulón cada noche, ¡lo cual incrementa tu salario diario Novus Prime!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">最新のノーバス・プライムのメカスーツを購入しよう。 このフルオートメーションメカは、最先端の運動と安定化技術を特徴とし、カスタム操縦、自己平衡歩行、並びに飛行が可能！ この宇宙海賊メカはまた、毎晩ネブロンを収集しあなたのノーバス・プライムでのデイリーサラリーを増加させてくれます！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임 로그멕 슈츠를 지금 바로 구입하세요! 완전 자동화 기능을 탑재한 본 멕은 최첨단 동작과 안정화 기술을 사용하여, 자체 조작과 걷기는 물론, 비행도 가능합니다. 또한 이 우주 해적 멕은 매일 밤 노부스 프라임의 보수를 늘려주는 네뷸론을 "모으기"도 합니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Purchase a Novus Prime Rogue Mech Suit today!  This fully-automated mech features state-of-the-art movement and stabilization technology, allowing for custom maneuvers, walking, and even flying!  This space pirate mech also "gathers" Nebulon every night, which increases your Novus Prime daily salary!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">今天就購買Novus Prime的海盜機械服吧！這種完全自動化的機械服裝搭載了最先進的動作和穩定技術，允許自訂操作，自我平衡步行，甚至飛行！這套海盜機械服也會每天晚上“收集”Nebulon，從而增加您每天在Novus Prime中所獲得的工資！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">今天就購買Novus Prime的海盜機械服吧！這種完全自動化的機械服裝搭載了最先進的動作和穩定技術，允許自訂操作，自我平衡步行，甚至飛行！這套海盜機械服也會每天晚上“收集”Nebulon，從而增加您每天在Novus Prime中所獲得的工資！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Purchase a Novus Prime Rogue Mech Suit today!  This fully-automated mech features state-of-the-art movement and stabilization technology, allowing for custom maneuvers, walking, and even flying!  This space pirate mech also "gathers" Nebulon every night, which increases your Novus Prime daily salary!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kLegal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">TERMS OF SERVICE Download is subject to the PlayStation®Network Terms of Service/User Agreement and any specific additional conditions applying to this item. If you do not wish to accept these terms, do not download this item. Download is for use solely within PlayStation®Home by the purchasing PSN account. Content may not be used by any other account.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">CONDITIONS D’UTILISATION Le téléchargement est soumis aux Conditions d'utilisation / Accord utilisateur de PlayStation®Network ainsi qu'à toutes conditions supplémentaires concernant spécifiquement cet article. Si vous ne souhaitez pas accepter ces conditions, ne téléchargez pas l'article. Téléchargement uniquement pour une utilisation dans PlayStation®Home par le compte d'achat PSN. Le contenu ne peut être utilisé par un autre compte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">NUTZUNGSBEDINGUNGEN Der Download unterliegt den Nutzungsbedingungen und Endbenutzervereinbarung von PlayStation®Network und jedweden für diesen Artikel geltenden Zusatzbedingungen. Wenn du diese Bedingungen nicht akzeptierst, lade diesen Artikel nicht herunter. Der Download ist ausschließlich zur Nutzung in PlayStation®Home und durch das PlayStation®Network-Konto. Inhalt kann nicht über ein anderes Konto genutzt werden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">TERMINI DI SERVIZIO I contenuti scaricabili sono soggetti ai Termini di Servizio e Condizioni d'Uso di PlayStation®Network e a qualsiasi altra condizione supplementare specifica applicabile a questo scopo. Se non si desidera accettare questi Termini, non scaricare questo articolo. Contenuti scaricabili dall'account acquirente PSN per utilizzo esclusivo in PlayStation®Home. I contenuti non devono esser utilizzati da nessun altro account.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">TÉRMINOS DE SERVICIO La descarga está sujeta a los Términos de servicio y Acuerdo de usuario de PlayStation®Network y cualquier condición adicional específica que cubra este artículo. Si no deseas aceptar estos términos, no descargues este artículo. Esta descarga es para su uso exclusivo en PlayStation®Home a través de la cuenta de compra PlayStation®Network. Ninguna otra cuenta podrá usar el contenido.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このコンテンツは、PlayStation®Network利用規約および個別条件に従って提供されております。 ご購入されたPSNアカウントにより、PlayStation®Homeの中でのみ、ご利用いただけます。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">TERMS OF SERVICE Download is subject to the PlayStation®Network Terms of Service/User Agreement and any specific additional conditions applying to this item. If you do not wish to accept these terms, do not download this item. Download is licensed or sublicensed to you for use solely within PlayStation®Home by the purchasing PSN account. Content may not be used by any other account.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kAccept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] Accept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] Confirmer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] Annehmen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] Accetta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] Aceptar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[ACCEPT]許可</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[ACCEPT] 결정</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[ACCEPT] Accept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[ACCEPT] 接受</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[ACCEPT] 接受</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[CROSS] Accept</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kBack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CIRCLE] Back</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CIRCLE] Retour</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CIRCLE] Zurück</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CIRCLE] Indietro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CIRCLE] Back</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[DECLINE]戻る</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[DECLINE] 뒤로</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[DECLINE] Back</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[DECLINE] 返回</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[DECLINE] 返回</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[CIRCLE] Back</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>