<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Game Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Goalie Skill</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Goalie Skill</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Compétence du Goalie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Torwartfähigkeit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Abilità del Goalie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nivel de Goalie</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Your Score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Your Score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Votre score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ihre Punktzahl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il tuo punteggio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tu puntuación</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Your Best</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Your Best</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Votre meilleur score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ihre höchste Punktzahl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il tuo punteggio più alto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tu mejor puntuación</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">World Best</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">World Best</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Champion du monde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weltbestes Ergebnis</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Migliore al mondo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mejor del mundo</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">World Best By</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">By</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Par</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Von</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Autore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">De</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Fetching</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fetching The</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Atteindre les</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die höchsten Punktzahlen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Accaparrarsi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Alcanzar las</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Top Scores</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Top Scores</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">meilleurs scores</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">werden abgerufen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">i punteggi più alti</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">máximas puntuaciones</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Scroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Scroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Faire défiler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Scrollen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scorri</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Desplazarte</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Select</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Select</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sélectionner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Auswählen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Seleziona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Seleccionar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Play Now</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Play Now</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jouer maintenant</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jetzt spielen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gioca adesso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Jugar ahora</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Buy Balls</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Buy Balls</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Acheter des ballons</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bälle kaufen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Acquista palle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Comprar balones</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Skip Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">To Skip Instructions Press</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour passer les instructions, appuyez sur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spielanleitung überspringen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per saltare le istruzioni premi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Para saltar las instrucciones, presiona</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Header</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!! Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Instructions Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spielanleitung für Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Istruzioni per Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Instrucciones de "Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!"</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Play Now Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Play Now</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jouer maintenant</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jetzt spielen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gioca adesso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Jugar ahora</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Play Now Subtitle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome To SFRGT!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue dans SFRGT !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen bei SFRGT!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuto a SFRGT!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Bienvenido a SFRGT!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Welcome</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Can you take on the MASTER of 12 Yards, the DEMON of the spot kick, the one-eyed HERO that is ROBO-GOALIE?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pouvez-vous battre le MAÎTRE de 11 mètres, le DÉMON du penalty, le HÉROS cyclope qu’est le ROBOT-GOALIE ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schaffen Sie es, den SUPERTORWART, den STRAFSTOSSTEUFEL, den einäugigen Helden ROBO-GOALIE beim Elfmeterschießen zu besiegen?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sei pronto a sfidare il MAESTRO degli undici metri, il MAGO del calcio di rigore, quell'EROE con un occhio solo chiamato ROBO-GOALIE?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Podras batir al MAESTRO de los 11 metros, CANCERBERO de los tres palos, y HÉROE de un solo ojo, es decir, a ROBO-GOALIE?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Object</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Score as many goals past ROBO-GOALIE as you can. There are rewards and prizes for those who look into his multi-coloured eye and bamboozle him with the POWER and PRECISION of their spot kicks.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tirez autant de penalties que vous pouvez sans que le ROBOT-GOALIE ne les arrête. Ceux qui fixent son œil multicolore et parviennent à l’embobiner avec la PUISSANCE et la PRÉCISION de leur tirs obtiendront des prix et des récompenses.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schießen Sie so viele Tore wie Sie können. Wer erfolgreich gegen ROBO-GOALIE antritt, ihm ins vielfarbige Auge blickt und seine Elfmeter mit KRAFT und PRÄZISION setzt, kann tolle Preise gewinnen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Segna quanto più puoi senza farti parare i tiri da ROBO-GOALIE. Ci sono in palio ricompense e premi per quanti guardano dritto nel suo occhio multicolore e lo confondono con la POTENZA e la PRECISIONE dei loro calci di rigore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Métele a ROBO-GOALIE todos los goles que puedas. Hay premios y recompensas para aquellos que miren a su ojo multicolor y sean capaces de confundirlo con la POTENCIA y PRECISIÓN de sus tiros.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Turns</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">One football allows you to take penalties against ROBO-GOALIE. You will continue to play as long as you score, but fail to score and it is GAME OVER. Any remaining footballs you own will allow you to return to face ROBO-GOALIE. If you have no footballs you'll need to purchase more from the PlayStation®Store. Balls are available in packs of 20 or 50. Each ball begins a new game starting from a score of zero.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un ballon de foot vous permet de marquer des points contre le ROBOT-GOALIE. Vous continuez à jouer tant que vous marquez. Si vous ratez un tir, LE JEU EST TERMINÉ. Tous les ballons de foot qui vous restent vous permettront de revenir affronter le ROBOT-GOALIE. Si vous n’avez plus de ballons, vous devez en acheter dans le PlayStation®Store. Les ballons sont disponibles par lots de 20 ou 50. Chaque ballon permet de commencer une partie en partant d’un score de zéro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie brauchen nur einen Fußball, um ROBO-GOALIE zum Elfmeterschießen herauszufordern. Das Spiel geht ununterbrochen weiter, solange Sie Tore schießen. Wenn Sie jedoch danebenschießen oder ROBO-GOALIE einen Ball hält, ist das Spiel vorbei. Wenn Sie noch Fußbälle übrig haben, können Sie erneut gegen ROBO-GOALIE antreten. Wenn Sie keine Bälle mehr haben, können Sie weitere Bälle vom PlayStation®Store erwerben. Sie können Pakete von 20 oder 50 Bällen kaufen. Mit jedem neuen Ball beginnt ein neues Spiel, das wieder bei Null anfängt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Basterà una palla per sfidare ROBO-GOALIE ai calci di rigore. La partita proseguirà finché continui a fare goal, ma al primo rigore sbagliato sarà GAME OVER. Se possiedi altre palle potrai tornare a sfidare ROBO-GOALIE. Se, invece, hai terminato le palle dovrai acquistarne altre al PlayStation®Store. Le palle vengono vendute in lotti di 20 o 50. Con ogni palla comincia una nuova partita ed il punteggio riparte da zero.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Necesitarás al menos un balón de fútbol para poder tirar penaltis contra ROBO-GOALIE. Podrás seguir jugando mientras sigas marcando, pero si fallas, SE ACABA LA PARTIDA. Podrás volver a enfrentarte a ROBO-GOALIE siempre que te queden más balones. Si no te quedan balones, tendrás que comprar más en la tienda de PlayStation®Store. Los balones están disponibles en paquetes de 20 ó 50 unidades. Con cada balón, se inicia una nueva partida con el marcador a cero.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Skill</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">ROBO-GOALIE has five skill levels. He doesn't like losing and will increase his skill level after each block of 5 goals. His skill colour range is from Blue to Red: Blue is One Star Skill and Red is Five Star Skill. As ROBO-GOALIE progresses through these levels, your chances of seeing him block your shot increase, so you'll need to master your penalty PLACEMENT and POWER!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le ROBOT-GOALIE dispose de cinq niveaux de compétence. Il n’aime pas perdre et augmente son niveau de compétence tous les 5 tirs. Sa couleur change selon le niveau de compétence, de bleu à rouge : le bleu correspond au niveau à une étoile, et le rouge au niveau à cinq étoiles. Alors que le ROBOT-GOALIE gagne en compétence, les risques de le voir bloquer vos tirs augmentent. Vous devez donc améliorer votre PLACEMENT et votre PUISSANCE de tir !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der ROBO-GOALIE verfügt über fünf Fähigkeitsstufen. Er verliert nicht gern und steigert daher alle 5 Tore seine Fähigkeitsstufe. Die Fähigkeitsstufen sind farblich von blau bis rot gekennzeichnet: Blau bedeutet Fähigkeitsstufe eins. Rot bedeutet Fähigkeitsstufe fünf. Wenn ROBO-GOALIE die einzelnen Stufen durchläuft, wird er von Mal zu Mal besser beim Halten, was bedeutet, dass auch Sie die BALLRICHTUNG und SCHUSSKRAFT immer besser bestimmen müssen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le abilità di ROBO-GOALIE si articolano in cinque livelli. Lui è uno a cui non piace perdere, per cui aumenta il livello di abilità ogni 5 goal subiti. Ciascun livello è indicato da una gamma di colori dal blu al rosso: il blu indica il livello di abilità ad una stella, mentre il rosso quello a cinque stelle. Man mano che ROBO-GOALIE passa da un livello all'altro, le possibilità che pari il tuo tiro aumentano, quindi dovrai avere piena padronanza della DIREZIONE e della POTENZA del tuo rigore!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">ROBO-GOALIE tiene cinco niveles de dificultad. No le gusta perder, así que aumentará de nivel con nada 5 goles marcados. Los colores de cada dificultad van desde el azul al rojo: el azul corresponde a la dificultad de una estrella y rojo a la de cinco estrellas. A medida que ROBO-GOALIE sube de nivel, aumentan las posibilidades de que pare tu tiro, ¡así que para vencerle, tendrás que perfeccionar la DIRECCIÓN y la POTENCIA de tu penalti!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Placement</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use [LEFTSTICK] to adjust the Targeter to aim in the direction you wish to place your penalty. Once you are happy with your PLACEMENT it is time to use the POWER. Be aware that you cannot move the PLACEMENT once the POWER selection is in progess.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez [LEFTSTICK] pour ajuster votre tir et viser dans le direction que vous souhaitez. Dès que le PLACEMENT vous convient, il est temps de déterminer la PUISSANCE. Vous ne pouvez plus modifier le PLACEMENT quand la sélection de la PUISSANCE est en cours.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit dem [LEFTSTICK] können Sie die Richtung bestimmen, in die der Ball gehen soll. Wenn Sie mit der BALLRICHTUNG zufrieden sind, kann die SCHUSSKRAFT eingestellt werden. Bitte beachten Sie, dass die BALLRICHTUNG nicht mehr verändert werden kann, wenn die SCHUSSKRAFT eingestellt wird.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usa [LEFTSTICK] per indirizzare il rigore nella direzione desiderata. Dopo aver impostato la DIREZIONE desiderata, viene il momento di applicare la POTENZA. Tieni presente che la DIREZIONE non può essere modificata una volta avviata la selezione della POTENZA.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Utiliza [LEFTSTICK] para ajustar el objetivo y apuntar en la dirección que desees lanzar tu penalti. Cuando estés satisfecho con la DIRECCIÓN, tendrás que ajustar la POTENCIA. Recuerda que no puedes cambiar la DIRECCIÓN cuando estés seleccionando la POTENCIA.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Power</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use [RIGHTSTICK] to adjust the POWER of the kick. To shoot, tilt [RIGHTSTICK] towards you. The further you tilt, the faster the power will increase. When you are happy with your POWER flick [RIGHTSTICK] forward. If you move it far enough the penalty will be taken. Be aware that any movement left or right on the stick will result in the penalty not going exactly where you placed it. Will your combination of POWER and PLACEMENT be good enough to beat ROBO-GOALIE?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez [RIGHTSTICK] pour ajuster la PUISSANCE de votre tir. Pour tirer, inclinez [RIGHTSTICK] vers vous. Plus vous l’inclinez, plus la puissance augmente rapidement. Quand la PUISSANCE vous convient, tirez rapidement [RIGHTSTICK] vers l’avant. Si vous le déplacez suffisamment, le tir partira. Faites attention à ne pas déplacer les joysticks vers la gauche ou la droite où le tir n’ira pas exactement là où vous le désirez. L’association de votre PUISSANCE et de votre PLACEMENT est-elle suffisamment bonne pour battre le ROBOT-GOALIE ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit dem [RIGHTSTICK] können Sie wählen, wie kräftig der Schuss ausfallen soll. Um zu schießen, bewegen Sie den [RIGHTSTICK] nach hinten. Je weiter Sie ihn bewegen, umso mehr steigert sich die SCHUSSKRAFT. Wenn Sie mit der SCHUSSKRAFT zufrieden sind, bewegen Sie den [RIGHTSTICK] schnell nach vorne. Bewegen Sie ihn weit genug, wird der Ball geschossen. Beachten Sie jedoch, dass der Ball durch leichte Rechts- oder Linksbewegungen von der gewählten Ballrichtung abweichen kann. Haben Sie die richtige Kombination von SCHUSSKRAFT und BALLRICHTUNG um ROBO-GOALIE zu schlagen?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Utilizza [RIGHTSTICK] per regolare la POTENZA del calcio. Per tirare, inclina [RIGHTSTICK] verso di te. Maggiore è l'inclinazione, più velocemente aumenterà la potenza. Una volta raggiunta la POTENZA desiderata, spostare [RIGHTSTICK] in avanti. Se il movimento è sufficiente il rigore sarà tirato. Tieni presente che ogni movimento dello stick verso sinistra o destra farà sì che il rigore non conservi esattamente la posizione prescelta. La tua combinazione di POTENZA e DIREZIONE sarà sufficiente a battere ROBO-GOALIE?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Utiliza [RIGHTSTICK] para ajustar la POTENCIA de tu lanzamiento. Para lanzar, tira del [RIGHTSTICK] hacia ti. Cuanto más lo inclines, más rápido aumentará la potencia. Cuando estés satisfecho con la POTENCIA, empuja [RIGHTSTICK] hacia adelante. Si lo haces correctamente, lanzarás el penalti. Recuerda que si lo mueves a la derecha o a la izquierda, el lanzamiento no irá adonde habías apuntado inicialmente. ¿Podrá tu combinación de POTENCIA y DIRECCIÓN derrotar a ROBO-GOALIE?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Time</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Each penalty must be taken within a strict time limit. The more goals you score the less time you will have to adjust your PLACEMENT and POWER. If the timer reaches zero the kick will be taken with RANDOM values. Can you handle the pressure as ROBO-GOALIE stares in MONO-VISION right into your face?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaque penalty doit être tiré dans un délai très strict. Plus vous marquez de buts, moins vous aurez de temps pour ajuster votre PLACEMENT et votre PUISSANCE. Si le minuteur atteint zéro, le tir est réglé sur des valeurs au HASARD. Pouvez-vous gérer la pression pendant que le ROBOT-GOALIE vous fixe droit dans les yeux en MONO-VISION ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben für jeden Elfmeter nur eine bestimmte Zeitspanne zur Verfügung. Je mehr Tore Sie schießen, umso weniger Zeit haben Sie, um BALLRICHTUNG und SCHUSSKRAFT richtig einzustellen. Wenn die Zeit abgelaufen ist, wird der Schuss ZUFÄLLIG abgeschossen. Wie spielen Sie unter Zeitdruck, während ROBO-GOALIE Ihnen einäugig ins Gesicht starrt?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ogni rigore va tirato entro il tempo limite prefissato. Più goal segni, meno tempo avrai per regolare DIREZIONE e POTENZA. Se il timer raggiunge lo zero, il calcio verrà tirato con valori CASUALI. Sei in grado di reggere alla pressione di ROBO-GOALIE che punta il SOLO OCCHIO che ha dritto sul tuo viso?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hay que lanzar el penalti dentro de un límite de tiempo. Cuantos más goles marques, menos tiempo tendrás para ajustar la DIRECCIÓN y la POTENCIA. Si el cronómetro marca cero, se realizará el lanzamiento con ajustes ALEATORIOS. ¿Podrás soportar la presión cuando ROBO-GOALIE te mire fijamente a la cara con su único y penetrante ojo?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Welcome Welcome</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C’est l’heure de Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das ist Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo è Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡¡Esto es Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Welcome Purchase</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Buy tokens to play the game.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Achetez des ballons pour jouer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kaufen Sie Bälle, um mitzuspielen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Acquista le palle per giocare.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Primero, necesitarás comprar balones para poder jugar.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Welcome Purpose</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take aim and shoot to beat the goalie and win ‘Supa’ prizes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Visez et tirez sans que le goalie n'arrête le tir pour gagnez des «Supa» prix.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zielen und schießen Sie, um den Torwart zu schlagen und vielleicht auch einen tollen "Supa"-Preis zu gewinnen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mira e segna per battere il Goalie e vincere premi 'Supa'.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apunta y lanza para batir al portero y ganar premios "Supa".</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Welcome Header</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome To SFRGT!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue dans SFRGT !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen bei SFRGT!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuto a SFRGT!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Bienvenido a SFRGT!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Welcome Owned</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Number Of Balls Owned Is</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nombre de ballons en votre possession</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bälle im Inventar:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il numero di palle in tuo possesso è</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Número de balones que tienes</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spielanleitung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Istruzioni</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Instrucciones</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Abbrechen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Review</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [TRIANGLE] to view the instructions again during the game.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyez sur [TRIANGLE] pour revoir les instructions pendant la partie.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücken Sie [TRIANGLE] um die Spielanleitung während des Spiels anzuzeigen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi  [TRIANGLE]  per visualizzare nuovamente le istruzioni durante il gioco.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Presiona [TRIANGLE] para ver las instrucciones de nuevo durante la partida</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Welcome Reward</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Top scorers will have the chance to win a special prize!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les meilleurs joueurs auront la chance de gagner un prix spécial !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die besten Spieler können tolle Preise gewinnen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I punteggi più alti vinceranno un premio speciale!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Los que obtengan mayor puntuación podrán llevarse un premio especial!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Old Score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Previous Best</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ancien meilleur score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vorige höchste Punktzahl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Miglior punteggio precedente</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Anterior mejor puntuación</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Punkte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Punteggio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Puntuación</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nom</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nome</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nombre</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Time</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Time</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Temps</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tempo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tiempo</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>