<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Caserne Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Valor-Kaserne</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caserma Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Barracones de Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">兵舎 ベイラー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Valor 병영</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Valor軍營</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Valor軍營</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Valor Barracks</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Caserne Valor - Pour les employés Valor, les casernes sont un peu comme un chez soi loin de chez soi. Cet appartement ravira le plus exigeant des soldats. De l'air pur, des sapins immenses et un hélico lourdement armé à deux pas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Valor-Kaserne: Für Valor-Soldaten ist die Kaserne eine Heimat fern der Heimat. Dieses Apartment hat alle Annehmlichkeiten, die ein Soldat braucht. Es gibt frische Bergluft, hohe, immergrüne Bäume, und direkt um die Ecke steht ein schwerbewaffneter Helikopter. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caserma Valor -  Per gli impiegati della Valor la caserma è praticamente la propria casa mentre sono in guerra. Questa abitazione è dotata di tutte le comodità che un soldato potrebbe desiderare. Aria di montagna, alberi sempreverdi e un elicottero armato dietro l'angolo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Barracones de Valor - Para los empleados de Valor, los barracones son su segundo hogar. Este edificio posee todas las comodidades que cualquier soldado podría llegar a necesitar: aire puro de montaña, árboles altos de hoja perenne y un helicóptero repleto de armas a la vuelta de la esquina. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ベイラーの兵舎　―　ベイラー社員専用の兵舎。兵士が必要とするすべてが備わっている。そして壮大な山に、高く聳え立つ青々とした木、輸送ヘリコプターがすぐ外にある。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Valor 병영 - Valor의 병사들을 위한 장소입니다. 집에서 멀리 떨어진 곳에서도, 자신을 위한 집이 되어 줍니다. 이 아파트는 병사가 필요한 모든 것을 갖추고 있기도 합니다. 예를 들어 상쾌한 산악의 공기나 울창한 침엽수, 그리고 바깥에서 자신을 기다리는 무장 헬리콥터 등. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Valor軍營，對Valor僱員而言，軍營就是離開家園之後的另一個家。這裡有軍人所需的全部設施。此外，這裡也有新鮮的山區空氣、高大的常綠樹，和一部重型武裝直升機在附近。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Valor軍營，對Valor僱員而言，軍營就是離開家園之後的另一個家。這裡有軍人所需的全部設施。此外，這裡也有新鮮的山區空氣、高大的常綠樹，和一部重型武裝直升機在附近。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Valor Barracks -  For Valor employees, the barracks are your home away from home.  This apartment has all the amenities a soldier should ever need.  There's fresh mountain air, tall evergreen trees and a heavily armed chopper just around the corner. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>