<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Beautiful Eyes: Normal, Set of 5 (Male)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Beaux yeux : Normaux, set de 5 (homme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Schöne Augen: Normal, 5er Set (für Männer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Occhi belli: Normali, set da 5 paia (da uomo)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Ojos bellos: Normales, juego de 5 (hombre)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ビューティフルアイ・ノーマル５点セット（男性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">뷰티풀아이 - 노멀 5개 세트(남성)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Beautiful Eyes Set of 5, Normal (Men)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">漂亮眼睛5對組合包：一般（男用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">漂亮眼睛5對組合包：一般（男用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Beautiful Eyes: Normal, Set of 5 (Male)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A set containing 5 pairs of coloured contact lenses that change the look of your eyes.\nThe following items are included in this set.\n\n- Beautiful Eyes: Normal (Red, Male) (Face Accessory)\n- Beautiful Eyes: Normal (Sapphire Blue, Male) (Face Accessory)\n- Beautiful Eyes: Normal (Brown, Male) (Face Accessory)\n- Beautiful Eyes: Normal (Gray, Male) (Face Accessory)\n- Beautiful Eyes: Normal (Emerald Green, Male) (Face Accessory)\n\n*By purchasing this set, each item will be added its respective category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set contenant 5 paires de lentilles de couleur qui modifient l'apparence de vos yeux.\nLes objets suivants sont inclus dans ce set.\n\n- Beaux yeux : Normaux (rouges, homme) (accessoire de visage)\n- Beaux yeux : Normaux (bleus saphir, homme) (accessoire de visage)\n- Beaux yeux : Normaux (marrons, homme) (accessoire de visage)\n- Beaux yeux : Normaux (gris, homme) (accessoire de visage)\n- Beaux yeux : Normaux (verts émeraude, homme) (accessoire de visage) \n\n* Après l’achat chaque article sera ajouté à leur catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Satz aus 5 Paaren farbiger Kontaktlinsen, die den Ausdruck in deinen Augen ändern.\nDie folgenden Gegenstände sind in diesem Satz enthalten.\n\n- Schöne Augen: Normal (rot, für Männer) (Zubehör für das Gesicht)\n- Schöne Augen: Normal (saphirblau, für Männer) (Zubehör für das Gesicht)\n- Schöne Augen: Normal (braun, für Männer) (Zubehör für das Gesicht)\n- Schöne Augen: Normal (grau, für Männer) (Zubehör für das Gesicht)\n- Schöne Augen: Normal (smaragdgrün, für Männer) (Zubehör für das Gesicht) \n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand in entsprechender Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set contenente 5 paia di lenti a contatto colorate che cambiano l'aspetto degli occhi.\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Occhi belli: Normali (rossi, da uomo)(accessorio per il viso)\n- Occhi belli: Normali (blu zaffiro, da uomo)(accessorio per il viso)\n- Occhi belli: Normali (castani, da uomo)(accessorio per il viso)\nOcchi belli: Normali (grigi, da uomo)(accessorio per il viso)\nOcchi belli: Normali (verde smaraldo, da uomo)(accessorio per il viso)\n\n*Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Un juego que contiene 5 pares de lentes de contacto de colores que cambian el look de tus ojos.\nEste juego contiene los siguientes objetos.\n\n- Ojos bellos: Normales (rojos, hombre) (accesorio de cara)\n- Ojos bellos: Normales (azul zafiro, hombre) (accesorio de cara)\n- Ojos bellos: Normales (marrones, hombre) (accesorio de cara)\n- Ojos bellos: Normales (grises, hombre) (accesorio de cara)\n- Ojos bellos: Normales (verdes esmeralda, hombre) (accesorio de cara)\n\n*Después de la compra, cada objeto será agregado a la categoría a la que aplica.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">瞳の印象が変わる、カラーコンタクトの５点セット。\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・ビューティフルアイ・ノーマル（レッド・男性）（フェイスアクセサリ）\n・ビューティフルアイ・ノーマル（サファイアブルー・男性）（フェイスアクセサリ）\n・ビューティフルアイ・ノーマル（ブラウン・男性）（フェイスアクセサリ）\n・ビューティフルアイ・ノーマル（グレー・男性）（フェイスアクセサリ）\n・ビューティフルアイ・ノーマル（エメラルドグリーン・男性）（フェイスアクセサリ）\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">눈동자의 느낌이 변하는 컬러 콘택트 5개 세트. \n
본 세트에는 하기 아이템이 포함되어 있습니다. \n\n
●뷰티풀아이 - 노멀(레드, 남성)(얼굴 액세서리)\n
●뷰티풀아이 - 노멀(사파이어블루, 남성)(얼굴 액세서리)\n
●뷰티풀아이 - 노멀(브라운, 남성)(얼굴 액세서리)\n
●뷰티풀아이 - 노멀(그레이, 남성)(얼굴 액세서리)\n
●뷰티풀아이 - 노멀(에메랄드그린, 남성)(얼굴 액세서리)\n\n
※구입하면 해당 카테고리에 각 아이템이 추가됩니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Five pairs of color contact lens in a set to give your pupils a different impression. \n
This set includes the following items. \n\n
・Beautiful Eyes, Normal (Red, Men)(Face Accessory) \n
・Beautiful Eyes, Normal (Sapphire Blue, Men)(Face Accessory) \n
・Beautiful Eyes, Normal (Brown, Men)(Face Accessory) \n
・Beautiful Eyes, Normal (Grey, Men)(Face Accessory) \n
・Beautiful Eyes, Normal (Emerald Green, Men)(Face Accessory) \n\n
※Upon purchase, the items will be placed into their respective categories. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">一組5對的有色隱形眼鏡，可改變瞳孔給人的印象。\n
本組合包包括以下道具。\n\n
●漂亮眼睛：一般（紅色/男用）（臉部配件）\n
●漂亮眼睛：一般（藍寶石藍/男用）（臉部配件）\n
●漂亮眼睛：一般（褐色/男用）（臉部配件）\n
●漂亮眼睛：一般（灰色/男用）（臉部配件）\n
●漂亮眼睛：一般（祖母綠/男用）（臉部配件）\n\n
※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別內。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">一組5對的有色隱形眼鏡，可改變瞳孔給人的印象。\n
本組合包包括以下道具。\n\n
●漂亮眼睛：一般（紅色/男用）（臉部配件）\n
●漂亮眼睛：一般（藍寶石藍/男用）（臉部配件）\n
●漂亮眼睛：一般（褐色/男用）（臉部配件）\n
●漂亮眼睛：一般（灰色/男用）（臉部配件）\n
●漂亮眼睛：一般（祖母綠/男用）（臉部配件）\n\n
※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別內。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A set containing 5 pairs of colored contact lenses that change the look of your eyes.\nThe following items are included in this set.\n\n- Beautiful Eyes: Normal (Red, Male) (Face Accessory)\n- Beautiful Eyes: Normal (Sapphire Blue, Male) (Face Accessory)\n- Beautiful Eyes: Normal (Brown, Male) (Face Accessory)\n- Beautiful Eyes: Normal (Gray, Male) (Face Accessory)\n- Beautiful Eyes: Normal (Emerald Green, Male) (Face Accessory)\n\n*By purchasing this set, each item will be added its respective category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
