<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Powered Ark Hunter - Female</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pillarche augmenté - Femme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Turbo-Archenjäger - Für Sie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Powered Ark Hunter - Donna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Powered Ark Hunter - Mujer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Powered Ark Hunter - Female</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You've braved the arkfalls in the new frontier of Defiance, and lived to tell the tale.  But even an expert ark hunter needs extra protection on this new Earth. You’ve got that covered with this heavy armored combat suit which will protect you head to toe against any foe! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez bravé les dangers des retombées d'arches de Defiance, la Nouvelle Frontière, avez survécu et êtes aujourd'hui en mesure de raconter vos exploits. Mais même un Pillarche expert a besoin de protection supplémentaire sur cette nouvelle Terre. Voilà qui est fait avec cette tenue de combat lourdement blindée qui vous protègera de la tête aux pieds ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast es nicht nur todesmutig mit den Archenfällen im Neuen Grenzland aufgenommen, sondern diese auch überlebt und kannst nun von deinen Heldentaten berichten. Aber auch ein Archenjäger-Experte benötigt zusätzlichen Schutz in dieser neuen Welt. Dafür sorgt dieser schwere, gepanzerte Kampfanzug, der dich von Kopf bis Fuß gegen jeden Feind schützt! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai affrontato le arkfall nella nuova frontiera di Defiance e sei sopravvissuto per poterne parlare.  Ma persino un ark hunter esperto ha bisogno di un po' di protezione extra su questa nuova Terra. Con questa armatura pesante sarai protetto dalla testa ai piedi contro qualsiasi avversario! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Has superado a los arkfalls en la nueva frontera de Defiance y has vivido para contarlo. Pero hasta los más expertos ark hunter necesitan protección adicional en esta nueva Tierra. ¡Este traje de combate blindado te protegerá de los pies a la cabeza ante cualquier enemigo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You've braved the arkfalls in the new frontier of Defiance, and lived to tell the tale.  But even an expert ark hunter needs extra protection on this new Earth. You’ve got that covered with this heavy armored combat suit which will protect you head to toe against any foe! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
