<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">1940's Gal Bundle (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack années 40 (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">40er-Jahre: Paket (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto ragazza anni '40 (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto mujer años 40 (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">1940년대 여성 세트 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">1940's Gal Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">1940年代女郎服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">1940年代女郎服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">1940's Gal Bundle (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take a trip back to 1940's Americana where this attire saw some of the first widespread use of man-made fibres. Bundle includes hair, blouse, skirt, gloves, and heels. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plongez dans l'Amérique des années 1940 qui vit l'apparition des premières fibres synthétiques. Ce pack comprend une coiffure, un chemisier, une jupe, des gants et des chaussures à talon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Reisen Sie in das Amerika der 40er-Jahre, als Kleidung aus synthetischen Stoffen gerade erst populär wurde. Im Paket enthalten sind Haare, Bluse, Rock, Handschuhe und Schuhe mit Absatz. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fai un salto indietro nell'America degli anni '40 dove questo stile favorì l'inizio della diffusione delle fibre sintetiche. Il pacchetto include capelli, blusa, gonna, guanti e scarpe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Retrocede hasta los años 40 estadounidenses, la época en que empezaron a popularizarse las fibras artificiales. El conjunto comprende peinado, blusa, falda, guantes y zapatos de tacón. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">1940년대의 미국으로 돌아가, 처음으로 대량생산된 인조섬유로 제작한 의상을 만나 보세요. 이 세트는 헤어스타일, 상의, 하의, 장갑, 그리고 구두를 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Take a trip back to 1940's Americana where this attire saw some of the first widespread use of man-made fibers. Bundle includes hair, blouse, skirt, gloves, and heels. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">時光倒流，回到1940年代的美洲。這套服裝標誌著人造物料首次被廣泛使用。本服裝組包括髮型、襯衫、裙、手套和高跟鞋。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">時光倒流，回到1940年代的美洲。這套服裝標誌著人造物料首次被廣泛使用。本服裝組包括髮型、襯衫、裙、手套和高跟鞋。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Take a trip back to 1940's Americana where this attire saw some of the first widespread use of man-made fibers. Bundle includes hair, blouse, skirt, gloves, and heels. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>