<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Winter Holiday White Tiger Companion 2011</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Compagnon tigre blanc 2011</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weißer Tiger als Gefährte für die Winterferien 2011</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Compagno tigre bianca vacanze invernali 2011</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mascota tigre blanco, vacaciones de invierno</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">크리스마스 연휴 백호 친구</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Winter Holiday White Tiger Companion 2011</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">冬季假期白老虎隨身夥伴2011</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">冬季假期白老虎隨身夥伴2011</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Winter Holiday White Tiger Companion 2011</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Winter White Tiger is cooler than a polar bear's toe nails. Man's best friend just got some serious competition from this fluffy companion critter. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le tigre blanc d'hiver est plus cool que les griffes d'un ours polaire. Le meilleur ami de l'homme va avoir de la concurrence avec cette petite boule de poils. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser weiße Schneetiger ist cooler als die Krallen eines Eisbären. Der tierisch flauschige Begleiter macht dem besten Freund des Menschen ernsthaft Konkurrenz. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa tigre bianca invernale è più fredda delle unghie dei piedi di un orso polare. Il migliore amico dell'uomo dovrà darsi da fare contro questa morbida creatura da compagnia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este tigre blanco mola más que una buena nevada en Navidad. Al mejor amigo del hombre le ha salido un serio competidor en este amiguito peludo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이번 겨울에는 백호가 북극곰의 발톱보다 더 유행입니다. 다른 친구들은 지금 이 보들보들한 친구 때문에 큰 위협을 느끼겠네요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This Winter White Tiger is cooler than polar bear's toe nails. Man's best friend just got some serious competition from this fluffy companion critter. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這頭冬季白老虎比北極熊的指甲還要冷。有了這頭毛絨的隨身夥伴，人類的好朋友看來得面對一些認真的競爭了。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這頭冬季白老虎比北極熊的指甲還要冷。有了這頭毛絨的隨身夥伴，人類的好朋友看來得面對一些認真的競爭了。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This Winter White Tiger is cooler than polar bear's toe nails. Man's best friend just got some serious competition from this fluffy companion critter. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>