<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A Dark Wizard’s Mansion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le manoir de mage noir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Villa des Schwarzen Magiers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Casa del mago Oscuro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una mansión para un mago tenebroso</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Who knows what Dark magic has been performed within these walls? This centuries-old stately home is the perfect residence for the aspiring Dark witch or wizard. Please be aware that only Pottermore furniture can be placed in Pottermore personal apartments and that all chat functions have been disabled. Pottermore furniture can be purchased from the Pottermore shop. [#PMExtraCommerce] [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Qui sait quels rites de magie noire ont été accomplis derrière ces murs ? Ce bâtiment majestueux vieux de plusieurs siècles est une demeure idéale pour les mages et sorcières experts en magie noire.  Attention : seuls les meubles Pottermore peuvent être placés dans les espaces personnels Pottermore, et tous les salons de chat sont désactivés. Vous pouvez acheter des meubles Pottermore dans la boutique Pottermore.[#PMExtraCommerce] [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer weiß, welch finstere Magie in diesen Mauern vollführt wurde? Dieses jahrhundertealte, imposante Anwesen ist das perfekte Heim für aufstrebende schwarze Magier und Hexen. Bitte beachten, dass  nur Pottermore-Möbel in persönlichen Apartments von Pottermore verwendet werden können und dass alle Chat-Funktionen deaktiviert sind. Pottermore-Möbel können im Pottermore-Shop erworben werden. [#PMExtraCommerce] [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chissà quali magie Oscure hanno visto queste mura? Questa maestosa dimora secolare è la residenza ideale per un'aspirante strega Oscura o un aspirante mago Oscuro. Gli appartamenti personali Pottermore possono essere arredati solo con mobili Pottermore. Tutte le funzionalità di chat sono state disabilitate. I mobili Pottermore possono essere acquistati nel negozio Pottermore. [#PMExtraCommerce] [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Quién sabe qué magia tenebrosa se habrá practicado entre estas paredes? Esta mansión de siglos de antigüedad es la residencia perfecta para una bruja o un mago que aspiren a ejercer la magia tenebrosa. Ten en cuenta que solo el mobiliario de Pottermore se puede colocar en los apartamentos personales Pottermore y que todas las funciones de chat se han desactivado. El mobiliario de Pottermore se puede comprar en Pottermore Shop. [#PMExtraCommerce] [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>