<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Avatar Projection System (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Système de projection d'avatar (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Avatar-Projektionssystem (männliche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sistema di proiezione Avatar (per uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sistema de proyección de avatar (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アバター投射システム（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Avatar Projection System (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Avatar Projection System (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This tiny mobile holographic generator projects a human-sized wireframe avatar that can move to mirror whoever carries it.  The user's body becomes completely invisible, with the wireframe body being the only thing seen by the naked eye. This item passively feeds skills and knowledge to its owner, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base experience point gains by about 5%.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce petit générateur holographique mobile projette une silhouette d'avatar humanoïde qui peut bouger en imitant les mouvements de la personne le portant. Le corps de l'utilisateur devient complètement invisible et la silhouette devient la seule chose visible à l'œil nu. Cet objet nourrit passivement son porteur de techniques et de connaissances, augmentant efficacement ses gains de points d'expérience de base Novus Prime d'environ 5%.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser winzige holografische Generator projeziert ein Drahtgittermodell eines menschengroßen Avatars, das dazu verwendet werden kann, jeden wiederzuspiegeln der ihn mit sich herumträgt. Der Körper des Nutzers wird vollständig unsichtbar, während der projezierte Körper das einzige ist, das mit bloßem Auge gesehen werden kann. Dieser Ausrüstungsgegenstand versorgt seinen Träger zusätzlich mit Fähigkeiten und Wissen und erhöht die Zufuhr von Erfahrungspunkten deiner Novus Prime Basis effektiv um ca. 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo piccolo generatore di ologrammi portatili proietta avatar reticolati a grandezza d'uomo che possono riprodurre perfettamente i movimenti di chi porta il generatore. Il corpo di chi lo usa diventa completamente invisibile, rendendo il corpo reticolato l'unica cosa percepibile ad occhio nudo. Questo oggetto fornisce a chi ne usufruisce abilità e conoscenza in modo passivo, incrementando l'acquisizione di punti esperienza della base Novus Prime di circa il 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este pequeño generador holográfico móvil proyecta un avatar de alambre de tamaño humano que puede moverse para reflejar quien lo porte.  El cuerpo del usuario se hace completamente invisible, con el cuerpo de alambre siendo la única cosa que puede ser vista a simple vista. Este objeto alimenta pasivamente las habilidades y los conocimientos de su dueño, incrementando efectivamente tus puntos de experiencia base Novus Prime en un 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この小さな携帯型ホログラフィー発生装置は反射する為に動くことが出来る人間サイズのワイヤーフレーム・アバターを投射する。使用者の身体は完全に視認が不可能になり、ワイヤーフレームの身体のみが裸眼で確認できるようになる。\n\n※購入すると、ミニゲーム「ノーバス・プライム」内での経験値の増加量が5%上がります。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This tiny mobile holographic generator projects a human-sized wireframe avatar that can move to mirror whoever carries it.  The user's body becomes completely invisible, with the wireframe body being the only thing seen by the naked eye. This item passively feeds skills and knowledge to its owner, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base experience point gains by about 5%.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This tiny mobile holographic generator projects a human-sized wireframe avatar that can move to mirror whoever carries it.  The user's body becomes completely invisible, with the wireframe body being the only thing seen by the naked eye. This item passively feeds skills and knowledge to its owner, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base experience point gains by about 5%.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>