<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LocoTable (Kulche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Table Loco (Kulche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Loco-Tisch (Kulche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">LocoTavolo (Kulche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LocoMesa (Kulche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ロコテーブル（クルチェ）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">로코 테이블(크루체)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">LocoTable (Kulche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">樂克桌子（克魯傑）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">樂克桌子（克魯傑）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LocoTable (Kulche)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A LocoRoco design adorns the top of this lovely, kitschy table. Co-ordinate with the Loco Sofa too for a positively LocoRoco atmosphere!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space. Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un motif LocoRoco orne le haut de cette adorable table kitsch.\n
Va avec le Fauteuil Loco pour créer une ambiance positivement LocoRoco !\n\nAcheter cet objet ajoute 1 LocoRoco à ton espace personnel de l'île Loco. Tu peux ajouter jusqu'à 20 LocoRoco à l'île Loco. Une fois le maximum atteint, tu ne peux plus ajouter d'unités.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein LocoRoco™-Design ziert diesen herrlichen, kitschigen Tisch. Zusammen mit dem Loco-Sofa entsteht eine echte LocoRoco-Atmosphäre!\n\nDieser Gegenstand fügt deinem Loco-Insel-Apartment 1 LocoRoco hinzu. Du kannst bis zu 20 LocoRoco hinzufügen. Ist das Maximum erreicht, können keine weiteren Einheiten hinzugefügt werden.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un motivo ispirato ai LocoRoco decora la parte superiore di questo grazioso ed eccentrico tavolo. Si abbina perfettamente al sofà dei Loco per creare la giusta atmosfera LocoRoco!\n\nAcquistando questo oggetto, aggiungerai un LocoRoco al tuo spazio personale su Loco Island. Puoi aggiungere fino a 20 LocoRoco su Loco Island. Una volta raggiunto il numero massimo, non potrai aggiungerne altri.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un diseño de LocoRoco adorna la parte superior de esta encantadora y extravagante mesa. ¡Combínala con el LocoSofá para crear una auténtica atmósfera LocoRoco!\n\nComprar este objeto añade 1 LocoRoco a tu espacio personal en la Loco Isla. Puedes añadir un máximo de 20 LocoRoco a la Loco Isla. Cuando hayas alcanzado este número, no podrás añadir más unidades.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">天板にロコロコをそのままデザインしたポップでキュートなテーブルです。\nロコソファと合わせてロコロコに囲まれた生活を送ってみては！？\n\nこのアイテムを購入するとパーソナルスペース”ロコアイランド”に\n”ロコロコ”が１匹追加されます。”ロコアイランド”には最大20匹まで”ロコロコ”を追加できます。最大数に達した場合は、それ以上の追加はされません。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">로코로코 모습 그대로 디자인한 POP하고 CUTE한 테이블이에요. 로코로코 소파도 구해서 로코로코가 가득한 생활을 보내보는 것은 어떠세요?\n\n이 아이템을 구입하면 퍼스널 스페이스 '로코 아일랜드'에 '로코로코'가 1마리 추가됩니다. '로코 아일랜드'에는 최대 20마리까지 '로코로코'를 추가할 수 있습니다.  최대치에 다다르면 더 이상은 추가할 수 없습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A LocoRoco design adorns the top of this lovely, kitschy table. Co-ordinate with the Loco Sofa too for a positively LocoRoco atmosphere!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space. Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">直接在桌面設計成樂克樂克的樣子，是張又可愛又花俏的桌子。不妨和樂克沙發一起搭配購買，過著被樂克樂克包圍的生活吧！\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">直接在桌面設計成樂克樂克的樣子，是張又可愛又花俏的桌子。不妨和樂克沙發一起搭配購買，過著被樂克樂克包圍的生活吧！\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Pop and cute, the table top is literally LocoRoco. Combined use with the Loco Sofa will take you deep into the world of LocoRoco!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your LocoIsland personal space. Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to LocoIsland. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>