<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Jacket and Scarf with Pencil Skirt and Stockings (White, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Veste et écharpe avec jupe fourreau et collants (blanche, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Jacke und Schal mit Bleistiftrock und Strümpfe (weiß, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Giacca e sciarpa con gonna attillata e calze (bianche, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Chaqueta y fular con minifalda de tubo y medias (blanca, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ジャケット＆ストールとタイトスカート・ストッキングつき（ホワイト・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Jacket and Scarf with Pencil Skirt and Stockings (White, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Outfit featuring a tailored jacket and wrapped snood scarf for the top and a pencil skirt with stockings for the bottom.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nCoolness: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Une tenue avec une veste taillée et une écharpe tube en haut et une jupe serrée avec des collants en bas.\nDéfense : ★\nNiveau de cool : ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Outfit, das für den Oberkörper eine maßgeschneiderte Jacke und einen Wickelschal, und für die Beine einen engsitzenden Rock und Strümpfe enthält.\nVerteidigung: ★\nCoolness: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un completo comprendente una giacca fatta su misura e una sciarpa di lana avvolta al collo per la parte superiore, e una gonna attillata con calze per la parte inferiore.\nDifesa: ★\nRicercatezza: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Traje que consiste en una chaqueta entallada y un fular enrollado en la parte superior, y una minifalda de tubo y medias en la inferior.\nDefensa: ★\nPorte: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">上はテーラードジャケットとスヌード風に巻いたストール、下はタイトスカートとストッキングの組み合わせ。\n防御力：　★\nかっこよさ：　★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Outfit featuring a tailored jacket and wrapped snood scarf for the top and a pencil skirt with stockings for the bottom.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nCoolness: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
