<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dead to Rights®: Retribution GAC Scout Shoes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaussures d'éclaireur du GAC Dead to Rights®: Retribution</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dead to Rights®: Retribution - scarpe esploratore GAC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Calzado de observador del GAC de Dead to Rights®: Retribution</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">『DEAD TO RIGHTS®：RETRIBUTION』GACスカウトシューズ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">「Dead to Rights®: Retribution」 전투 부츠(여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Dead to Rights®: Retribution GAC Scout Shoes (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「Dead to Rights®: Retribution」 GAC軍靴(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「Dead to Rights®: Retribution」 GAC軍靴(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dead to Rights®: Retribution GAC Scout Shoes</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">GAC model 12 footwear combines a firm durable top with reinforced carbon fibre/para-aramid toe caps and high traction sole for superior slip resistance in virtually all slick conditions.  A built-in Shock Diffusion System combines optimal boot support and performance with the comfort and lightweight properties of an athletic shoe.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les chaussures modèle 12 du GAC combinent une surface solide, une extrémité renforcée en fibre de carbone/aramide et une semelle haute technologie pour une résistance accrue aux glissements dans quasiment toutes les conditions météorologiques.  Un système de diffusion des chocs intégré associe un soutien à toute épreuve et des performances optimales au confort et à la légèreté d'une chaussure de sport.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le calzature modello 12 GAC combinano uno strato resistente con punte rinforzate in fibra di carbonio e kevlar, e una suola a trazione elevata che garantisce il miglior equilibrio possibile nelle condizioni più scivolose.  Il sistema di diffusione d'urto integrato combina il supporto e le prestazioni ottimali di uno stivale con la comodità e la leggerezza di una scarpa da atletica.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El calzado modelo 12 del GAC combina una parte superior firme y resistente con unas punteras reforzadas de fibra de carbono y para-aramida. Las suelas de alta tracción previenen los patinazos en casi cualquier superficie, por resbaladiza que sea.  El sistema incorporado de difusión de impacto combina la resistencia y rendimiento de una bota con la comodidad y ligereza del calzado deportivo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">GACモデル12シューズは、強固で耐久性の高い上部と、強化カーボン/パラアラミド繊維の爪先部を組み合わせて製造されている。靴底は摩擦力が極めて高く、いかなる地形であってもまず滑ることはない。組み込まれた衝撃緩和システムと、運動靴さながらの軽さと心地良さが融合し、非常に高い性能を実現している。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">GAC 표준 모델 12 전투화는 카본 섬유와 파라-아라미드로 튼튼한 외부를 자랑합니다. 높은 마찰력을 지닌 밑창은 어떤 지형에서든 강한 접지력을 보여 줍니다. 충격 흡수 시스템이 탑재되어 전투화의 보호력과 기능화의 운동성을 고루 겸비하였습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">GAC model 12 footwear combines a firm durable top with reinforced carbon fibre/para-aramid toe caps and high traction sole for superior slip resistance in virtually all slick conditions.  A built-in Shock Diffusion System combines optimal boot support and performance with the comfort and lightweight properties of an athletic shoe.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">GAC的12號軍靴上半部份堅固耐用，腳指部份則以經強化的碳纖維／對位芳香聚醯胺纖維製成。鞋底的磨擦力極高，在任何地形都不易滑倒。軍靴揉合了可緩和衝擊的設計構造和運動鞋特有的輕型舒適，性能無出其右。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">GAC的12號軍靴上半部份堅固耐用，腳指部份則以經強化的碳纖維／對位芳香聚醯胺纖維製成。鞋底的磨擦力極高，在任何地形都不易滑倒。軍靴揉合了可緩和衝擊的設計構造和運動鞋特有的輕型舒適，性能無出其右。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">GAC model 12 footwear combines a firm durable top with reinforced carbon fiber/para-aramid toe caps and high traction sole for superior slip resistance in virtually all slick conditions.  A built-in Shock Diffusion System combines optimal boot support and performance with the comfort and lightweight properties of an athletic shoe.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>