<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Pretend horse-riding</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">A dada!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vorgetäuscht Pferdereiten</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Finto cavallo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Caballo falso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Pretend horse-riding</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Pretend horse-riding</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You love horse-riding, but can't afford the real thing? No worries, here's a cheaper option: just pretend to ride an imaginary steed... It won't look as good, but will be a lot funnier! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous adorez le cheval, mais n'avez pas les moyens de vous en acheter un vrai? Pas de problème: faites juste semblant de chevaucher un destrier imaginaire... Ça aura moins d'allure, mais ça aura l'avantage d'être drôle![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie lieben Reiten, aber nicht leisten können die reale Sache? Keine Sorge, hier ist eine billigere Alternative: einfach so tun, als einen imaginären Pferd reiten ... Es wird nicht so gut aussehen, aber wird viel lustiger![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tu ami i cavalli, ma non hanno i mezzi per acquistare la vera? Nessun problema: basta fare finta di cavalcare un cavallo fantasia ... Sarà meno grande, ma ha il vantaggio di essere divertente![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Usted ama a los caballos, pero no tienen los medios para que compre uno de verdad? No hay problema: basta con pretender montar un caballo imaginación ... Será menos grande, pero tiene la ventaja de ser divertido![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">You love horse-riding, but can't afford the real thing? No worries, here's a cheaper option: just pretend to ride an imaginary steed... It won't look as good, but will be a lot funnier! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You love horse-riding, but can't afford the real thing? No worries, here's a cheaper option: just pretend to ride an imaginary steed... It won't look as good, but will be a lot funnier! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>