<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Epic Ark Hunter - Female</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pillarche épique - Femme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Epischer Archenjäger - Für Sie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Epic Ark Hunter - Donna </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Epic Ark Hunter - Mujer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Epic Ark Hunter - Female</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Most Humans and Votans run from arkfalls. This outfit makes it clear that you’re not like most; you have braved the new frontier of Defiance and now have the look to prove it! These rugged boots, trousers, and leather jacket are modeled on the outfit worn by the famous ark hunter Irisa in Defiance. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La maggior parte degli Human e dei Votan si tengono ben distanti dalle arkfall. Questa divisa mette in chiaro che tu non sei come gli altri, hai affrontato la nuova frontiera di Defiance e hai il look che lo dimostra! Questo set di stivali, pantaloni e giubbotto in pelle dall'aria vissuta seguono lo stile sfoggiato dal famoso ark hunter Irisa di Defiance. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die meisten Menschen und Votaner nehmen vor Archenfällen Reißaus. Mit diesem Outfit kannst du eines klarstellen: Du bist nicht wie alle anderen. Du hast dich dem Neuen Grenzland von Defiance wagemutig entgegengestellt und dieser Look ist der Beweis dafür. Für die derben Stiefel, robuste Hose und die Lederjacke stand das Outfit des berühmten Archenjägers Irisa in Defiance Pate. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La maggior parte degli Human e dei Votan si tengono ben distanti dalle arkfall. Questa divisa mette in chiaro che tu non sei come gli altri, hai affrontato la nuova frontiera di Defiance e hai il look che lo dimostra! Questo set di stivali, pantaloni e giubbotto in pelle dall'aria vissuta seguono lo stile sfoggiato dal famoso ark hunter Irisa di Defiance. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La mayoría de Humans y Votans huyen de los arkfalls. Este atuendo deja claro que no eres como la mayoría; has superado la nueva frontera de Defiance y lo demuestras con tu aspecto. Chaqueta de cuero, pantalones y botas reforzadas al estilo del famoso ark hunter Irisa de Defiance. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Most Humans and Votans run from arkfalls. This outfit makes it clear that you’re not like most; you have braved the new frontier of Defiance and now have the look to prove it! These rugged boots, trousers, and leather jacket are modeled on the outfit worn by the famous ark hunter Irisa in Defiance. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
