<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Black Shirt with Graphic Print, Rolled-up Sleeves and Black Tie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chemise noire à imprimé graphique, manches retroussées et cravate noire</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schwarzes Langarmhemd mit Grafikaufdruck, aufgerollten Ärmeln und schwarzer Krawatte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Camicia nera con disegno grafico, maniche arrotolate e cravatta nera</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camisa negra con estampado gráfico, mangas remangadas y corbata negra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">グラフィックプリント入り捲り上げられた袖の黒のシャツ、黒のネクタイ付き</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">검은색 셔츠와 그래픽 문양, 걷은 소매와 검은색 넥타이</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Black Shirt with Graphic Print, Rolled-up Sleeves and Black Tie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">绘画图案、卷袖和黑领带的黑色衬衫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">繪畫圖案、捲袖和黑領帶的黑色襯衫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Black Shirt with Graphic Print, Rolled-up Sleeves and Black Tie</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Untucked shirt with rolled up sleeves and tie - they look great paired with anything from smart trousers casual pants. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chemise non rentrée,  manches retroussées et cravate – elles sont parfaites avec un pantalon chic ou décontracté. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein lässig getragenes Langarmhemd mit aufgerollten Ärmeln und Krawatte - ein Superlook, der zu Allem passt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Camicie fuori dai pantaloni con maniche arrotolate e cravatta, perfette per qualsiasi abbinamento, dai pantaloni eleganti a quelli casual. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camisa por fuera del pantalón con mangas remangadas y corbata – quedan perfectas con pantalones de vestir o casuales. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">袖が捲り上げられたはみ出しシャツ、ネクタイ付き - どんなズボンと組み合わせることができます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">겉으로 내논 셔츠와 걷은 소매와 넥타이 - 스마트 바지 캐쥬얼 바지등과 멋지게 잘 어울립니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Untucked shirt with rolled up sleeves and tie - they look great paired with anything from smart trousers casual pants. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">卷袖、配领带的无褶衬衫 - 与任何时尚长裤或休闲长裤都能完美搭配。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">捲袖、配領帶的無褶襯衫- 與任何時尚長褲或休閒長褲都能完美搭配。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Untucked shirt with rolled up sleeves and tie - they look great paired with anything from smart trousers casual pants. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>