<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rapture Metro Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appartement à Rapture</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wohnung in Rapture</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Appartamento di Rapture</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apartamento en Rapture</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rapture Metro Apartment</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">From Sinclair Solutions, please enjoy your new apartment in Rapture.  As a valued Sinclair Solutions tester, we know you need a place to relax after trying out our new products.  Remember to explore the space and see all that Rapture has to offer.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tout droit sorti de Sinclair Solutions, voici votre nouvel appartement dans Rapture. En tant que membre estimé de l'équipe de Sinclair Solutions, nous savons qu'il vous faut un endroit où vous détendre après avoir essayé nos nouveaux produits. N'oubliez pas d'explorer l'endroit pour découvrir tout ce que Rapture a à offrir.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wsinclair Solutions wünscht Ihnen viel Freude an Ihrer neuen Wohnung in Rapture. Wir wissen, als geschätzter Sinclair Solutions Tester, brauchen Sie nach getaner Arbeit einen Ort der Entspannung. Denken Sie daran, alles zu erkunden. Erleben Sie, was Rapture zu bieten hat. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Goditi il tuo nuovo appartamento a Rapture offerto della Sinclair Solutions. Quale migliore impiegato della Sinclair Solutions, sappiamo che hai bisogno di un luogo dove rilassarti dopo aver provato i nostri prodotti. Esplora e osserva tutto quello che ha da offrire Rapture.   [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Disfruta de tu nuevo apartamento en Rapture gracias a Sinclair Solutions. Como miembro del equipo de pruebas de Sinclair Solutions, sabemos que necesitas un lugar donde relajarte tras probar nuestros nuevos productos. No olvides explorar la zona para ver todo lo que te ofrece Rapture. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">From Sinclair Solutions, please enjoy your new apartment in Rapture.  As a valued Sinclair Solutions tester, we know you need a place to relax after trying out our new products.  Remember to explore the space and see all that Rapture has to offer.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>