<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Heavy Pets Halloween Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Groupe Halloween Heavy Pets</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Heavy Pets Halloween Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Halloween Heavy Pets</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de Halloween Heavy Pets</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Heavy Pets Halloween Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Heavy Pets Halloween Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Heavy Pets Halloween Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Heavy Pets Halloween Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Heavy Pets Halloween Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Heavy Pets Halloween Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Get all three spooky Heavy Pets with this Halloween Bundle! Includes the Ghostling, Flaming Skull, and Vampire Batling pet items. Place one of these in your apartment and set the mood for the season with these roaming pets![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Obtenez tous les trois lourds et effrayants Animaux avec cet ensemble Halloween! incluant bebe phantome, crane flamboyant, et articles pour animal de compagnie bebe vampire chauve-souris. Placez un de ces objects dans votre appartement et mettez de l'ambiance pour la saison avec ces animaux de compagnie d'itinérance![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nimm doch gleich alle drei schauerlichen Heavy Pets Haustiere mit diesem Halloween Paket! Enthält die Gespenster, Flammenschädel, und Vampirfledermaus Haustiere. Platziere eines davon in deiner Wohnung, das bringt reichlich Stimmung in dieser Jahreszeit![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ottieni questi tre spaventosi Animali con il Pacco Halloween!! Include il Fantasma, il Teschio in Fiamme ed il Vampiro di Battaglia. Metti uno di questi animali nel tuo appartamento per avere l’atmosfera giusta in questa stagione!![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Obtèn estos tres Animales Espeluznantes con el Paquete Halloween!! Incuye el Fantasma, la Calaca en Llamas y el Vampiro de Batalla. Pon uno de èstos animales en tu casa, y asì pondràs el clima adecuado para èsta època!![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* pets [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* pets [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* pets [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* pets [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* pets [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Get all three spooky Heavy Pets with this Halloween Bundle! Includes the Ghostling, Flaming Skull, and Vampire Batling pet items. Place one of these in your apartment and set the mood for the season with these roaming pets![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>