<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Emo's Garage Loft</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Grenier garage de Emo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Werkstatt Dachboden von Emo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Soppalco garage di Emo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Garaje desván de Emo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* Emo's Garage Loft</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">EMO의 차고 다락방</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Emo's Garage Loft</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">車庫閣樓的EMO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">車庫閣樓的EMO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Emo's Garage Loft</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Your very own Emo Ray Garage Loft. A great place to relax after saving the world from intergalactic teddy bears! This apartment connects directly into the Public and Game spaces for Emo Ray Vs. Intergalactic Teddy Bears! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Votre propre "Emo Ray" Grenier garage. Un endroit idéal pour se détendre après avoir sauvé le monde de intergalactique ours en peluche! Cet appartement se connecte directement dans les espaces publics et de jeux pour Emo Ray Vs. Intergalactic Teddy Bears! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ihre ganz eigene "Emo Ray" Werkstatt Dachboden. Ein großartiger Ort, um nach der Rettung der Welt vor den intergalaktischen Teddybären entspannen! Diese Wohnung wird direkt durch den öffentlichen und Räume für Spiel Emo Ray Vs. Intergalactic Teddy Bears! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il tuo "Emo Ray" soppalco garage. Un luogo ideale per rilassarsi dopo aver salvato il mondo dalla intergalattico orsacchiotti! Questo appartamento si collega direttamente negli spazi pubblici e gioco per Emo Ray Vs. Intergalactic Teddy Bears! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Su propio "Emo Ray" Garaje desván. Un gran lugar para relajarse después de salvar al mundo de los osos de peluche intergaláctico! Este apartamento se conecta directamente en los espacios públicos y el Juego de Emo Ray vs. Intergalactic Teddy Bears! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">너만의 "EMO 레이, '차고 다락방.좋은 장소는 은하간 테디 베어의 세계를 저장한 후 휴식을 취할 수 있습니다! 이 아파트는 Emo Ray Vs. Intergalactic Teddy Bears에 대한 공공 및 게임 공간에 직접 연결! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Your very own Emo Ray Garage Loft. A great place to relax after saving the world from intergalactic teddy bears! This apartment connects directly into the Public and Game spaces for Emo Ray Vs. Intergalactic Teddy Bears! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">你自己的“EMO雷”車庫的閣樓。一個偉大的地方放鬆，保存後星系間泰迪熊的世界！這間公寓直接連接到Emo Ray Vs. Intergalactic Teddy Bears展的公共及遊戲空間！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">你自己的“EMO雷”車庫的閣樓。一個偉大的地方放鬆，保存後星系間泰迪熊的世界！這間公寓直接連接到Emo Ray Vs. Intergalactic Teddy Bears展的公共及遊戲空間！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Your very own Emo Ray Garage Loft. A great place to relax after saving the world from intergalactic teddy bears! This apartment connects directly into the Public and Game spaces for Emo Ray Vs. Intergalactic Teddy Bears! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>