<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Scribble Shooter Evil Pilot Bundle (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble de pilote diabolique Scribble Shooter (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Böses "Scribble Shooter"-Pilotenpaket (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scribble Shooter - Completo Pilota malefico (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack de piloto malvado de Scribble Shooter (Hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Scribble Shooter イビルパイロットセット（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">스크리블 슈터 악의 파일럿 세트 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Scribble Shooter Evil Pilot Bundle (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Scribble Shooter邪惡飛行員服裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Scribble Shooter邪惡飛行員服裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Scribble Shooter Evil Pilot Bundle (male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Why save the PlayStation®Home Universe when you can destroy it!?!  Purchase an exact replica of the Scribble Shooter Evil Pilot costume and watch the PlayStation®Home population cower at the mere sight of you. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pourquoi sauver l'univers PlayStation®Home quand on peut le détruire !?! Achetez la réplique exacte du costume de pilote diabolique Scribble Shooter et faites trembler la population de PlayStation®Home par votre seule présence. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Warum das PlayStation®Home-Universum retten, wenn man es auch vernichten kann?! Allein der Anblick dieser exakten Nachbildung des "Scribble Shooter"-Kostüms des bösen Piloten bringt die gesamte Bevölkerung von PlayStation®Home zum Erzittern. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Perché salvare l'Universo PlayStation®Home se puoi distruggerlo!?! Acquista una fedele riproduzione del costume del Pilota malefico di Scribble Shooter e raggela gli abitanti di PlayStation®Home con un semplice sguardo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡¿Para qué salvar el universo PlayStation®Home si puedes destruirlo?! Compra una réplica exacta del traje de piloto malvado de Scribble Shooter y contempla cómo la población de PlayStation®Home se encoge de miedo al verte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ヒーローなんてつまらなすぎる！ここは敢えてScribble Shooterイビルパイロットに変身して、闊歩しちゃえ！\n\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n・Scribble Shooter イビルパイロットマスク（男性用）（頭）\n・Scribble Shooter イビルパイロットグローブ（男性用）（手）\n・Scribble Shooter イビルパイロットボディー（男性用）（トップス）\n・Scribble Shooter イビルパイロットボトムズ（男性用）（ボトムズ）\n・Scribble Shooter イビルパイロットシューズ（男性用）（靴）\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリーに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">홈의 세계를 파괴할 수 있다면, 당신은 그렇게 하시겠습니까? 스크리블 슈터 악의 파일럿과 동일한 복장을 입고, 당신의 모습 덕분에 겁에 질릴 주위 사람들을 관찰해 보십시오.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Why save the PlayStation®Home Universe when you can destroy it!?! Purchase an exact replica of the Scribble Shooter Evil Pilot costume and watch PlayStation®Home's population cower at the mere sight of you.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">既然你可毀滅PlayStation®Home宇宙，為什麼還要拯救它？購買Scribble Shooter邪惡飛行員服裝組的完全複製品，看著PlayStation®Home的人看到你便戰戰兢兢。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">既然你可毀滅PlayStation®Home宇宙，為什麼還要拯救它？購買Scribble Shooter邪惡飛行員服裝組的完全複製品，看著PlayStation®Home的人看到你便戰戰兢兢。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Why save the PlayStation®Home Universe when you can destroy it!?!  Purchase an exact replica of the Scribble Shooter Evil Pilot costume and watch PlayStation®Home's population cower at the mere sight of you. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>