<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Hello Bondi Top - Cool Wip (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong – Haut Hello Bondi – Crème fouettée (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Hello Bondi Top - Cool Wip/Weiß (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Maglia Hello Bondi - Panna (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Camisola Hello Bondi - Color crema batida (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Inspired by bondi beach in Australia, this tank has fully exposed side that tie at the hips. This is a must have tank to be rocked as a beach cover up or worn over a cami. A unique Peace Out tie-dye pattern. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Inspiré de la plage de Bondi, en Australie, ce débardeur a un côté totalement exposé resserré aux hanches. Ce débardeur est un must comme tenue de plage ou à porter par dessus une cami. Un motif Peace Out bariolé unique. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der australische Bondi Beach inspirierte zu diesem Tanktop mit offenen Seiten, die sich mit Bändchen an den Hüften zusammenknoten lassen. Das Tanktop  ist ein Must-have-Kleidungsstück, egal ob zum Überziehen am Strand oder über einem Unterhemdchen. Einzigartiges Batikmuster mit Peace Out-Grafik [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ispirata a Bondi Beach in Australia, questa canottiera è completamente aperta sui lati e legata sui fianchi. Un indumento "must" da indossare come copricostume o sopra un top. Disegno tie-dye unico Peace Out. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Inspirado en la australiana Bondi Beach, esta camisola sin mangas tiene un lateral totalmente descubierto que se ata en la cadera. Es una prenda imprescindible de la que presumir, ya sea como pareo en la playa o por encima de un top. Y con un estampado Peace Out desteñido anudado. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>