<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Island Records</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Island Records</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Island Records</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Island Records</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Island Records</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Island Records</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Island Records</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Island Records</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Island Records</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Island Records</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Island Records</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Chris Blackwell founded the Island label in Kingston, Jamaica in 1959 with just £1000.  Relocating to London in the early 60s Blackwell built the most diverse and enviable catalogue of any independent record label in history. From Island’s early Jamaican roots in ska and rock-steady,  through  the label’s expansion to the cutting edge of progressive rock and the signing of superstars like Bob Marley and U2, Blackwell brought to Island a unique vision and passion which still informs this iconic label’s approach to this day. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En 1959, Chris Blackwell fonda le label Island à Kingston, en Jamaïque, avec seulement 1000 £. De retour à Londres au début des années 60, Blackwell constitua le catalogue de labels indépendants le plus éclectique et le plus intéressant de l'histoire. Grâce aux origines jamaïcaines ska et rocksteady d'Island, à son évolution avant-gardiste vers le rock progressif et aux contrats signés avec des superstars comme Bob Marley et U2, Blackwell a apporté au label sa passion et sa vision unique qui le caractérisent encore aujourd'hui. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Chris Blackwell gründete 1959 in Kingston, Jamaica mit gerade mal 1000 € das Label Island. Nach seinem Umzug nach London in den frühen 60er-Jahren stellte Blackwell den abwechslungsreichsten und beneidenswertesten Katalog eines unabhängigen Plattenlabels der Geschichte zusammen. Von den frühen jamaikanischen Wurzeln von Island im Ska und im Rocksteady bis hin zur Erweiterung des Labels durch innovativen Progressive Rock und den Gesang von Superstars wie Bob Marley und U2 hat Blackwell Island eine einzigartige Vision und Leidenschaft entgegengebracht, die die Arbeitsweise dieses symbolträchtigen Labels heute noch prägt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nel 1959 Chris Blackwell fondò l'etichetta Island a Kingston, Giamaica, con un capitale di soli 1.000 dollari. Trasferitosi a Londra all'inizio degli anni '60, Blackwell riuscì a realizzare uno dei cataloghi più ampi e invidiabili di sempre nel mondo delle etichette discografiche indipendenti. Dalle radici giamaicane di ska e rock-steady, all'apertura verso l'avanguardia del progressive rock e la firma di colossi come Bob Marley e gli U2, Blackwell portò all'Island una visione e una passione uniche, e che ancora oggi caratterizzano l'approccio di questa etichetta, diventata una vera e propria icona. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chris Blackwell fundó en 1959 el sello Island en Kingston, Jamaica, con solo 1.000 libras. Se trasladó a Londres a principios de los 60 donde elaboró el catálogo más diverso y envidiable para cualquier sello discográfico independiente de la historia. Desde los inicios jamaicanos de Island, con raíces ska y rock-steady, hasta la expansión del sello hacia el rock progresivo más vanguardista y la colaboración con estrellas de la canción como Bob Marley y U2, Blackwell dotó a Island de una visión única y una pasión que aún hoy forma parte de la perspectiva icónica del sello. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Chris Blackwell founded the Island label in Kingston, Jamaica in 1959 with just £1000.  Relocating to London in the early 60s Blackwell built the most diverse and enviable catalogue of any independent record label in history. From Island’s early Jamaican roots in ska and rock-steady,  through  the label’s expansion to the cutting edge of progressive rock and the signing of superstars like Bob Marley and U2, Blackwell brought to Island a unique vision and passion which still informs this iconic label’s approach to this day. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Chris Blackwell founded the Island label in Kingston, Jamaica in 1959 with just £1000.  Relocating to London in the early 60s Blackwell built the most diverse and enviable catalogue of any independent record label in history. From Island’s early Jamaican roots in ska and rock-steady,  through  the label’s expansion to the cutting edge of progressive rock and the signing of superstars like Bob Marley and U2, Blackwell brought to Island a unique vision and passion which still informs this iconic label’s approach to this day. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Chris Blackwell founded the Island label in Kingston, Jamaica in 1959 with just £1000.  Relocating to London in the early 60s Blackwell built the most diverse and enviable catalogue of any independent record label in history. From Island’s early Jamaican roots in ska and rock-steady,  through  the label’s expansion to the cutting edge of progressive rock and the signing of superstars like Bob Marley and U2, Blackwell brought to Island a unique vision and passion which still informs this iconic label’s approach to this day. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Chris Blackwell founded the Island label in Kingston, Jamaica in 1959 with just £1000.  Relocating to London in the early 60s Blackwell built the most diverse and enviable catalogue of any independent record label in history. From Island’s early Jamaican roots in ska and rock-steady,  through  the label’s expansion to the cutting edge of progressive rock and the signing of superstars like Bob Marley and U2, Blackwell brought to Island a unique vision and passion which still informs this iconic label’s approach to this day. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Chris Blackwell founded the Island label in Kingston, Jamaica in 1959 with just £1000.  Relocating to London in the early 60s Blackwell built the most diverse and enviable catalogue of any independent record label in history. From Island’s early Jamaican roots in ska and rock-steady,  through  the label’s expansion to the cutting edge of progressive rock and the signing of superstars like Bob Marley and U2, Blackwell brought to Island a unique vision and passion which still informs this iconic label’s approach to this day. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Island" T-Shirt female. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>