<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ajagara Phoenix Guardian Cuirass and Pauldrons - Golden (for Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cuirasse et épaulières de la gardienne phénix d'Ajagara - Or (pour femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ajagara-Phönixwächterkürass und -schulterpanzer - Gold (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Corazza e spallacci da guardiana della fenice di Ajagara - Dorato (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Coraza y hombreras de Guardián del Fénix de Ajagara; Dorado (para mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Ajagara Phoenix Guardian Cuirass and Pauldrons - Golden (for Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Ajagara Phoenix Guardian Cuirass and Pauldrons - Golden (for Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ajagara Phoenix Guardian Cuirass and Pauldrons - Golden (for Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Ajagara Phoenix Guardian Cuirass and Pauldrons - Golden (for Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Ajagara Phoenix Guardian Cuirass and Pauldrons - Golden (for Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ajagara Phoenix Guardian Cuirass and Pauldrons - Golden (for Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have proven yourself a fierce warrior and have been chosen to become a Phoenix Guardian, protecting the creatures and kingdom of Ajagara. This fine armour will serve you well whether you battle on the plains, mountain side, or in the skies. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez prouvé votre valeur de guerrier féroce, et vous avez été choisi par les dieux pour devenir un gardien phénix, voué à protéger le royaume d'Ajagara et ses créatures. Cette armure de qualité vous sera fidèle dans toutes les batailles, que ce soit en montagne, dans les cieux ou dans les plaines. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast dich als tapferer Krieger ausgezeichnet und wurdest zum Phönixwächter ernannt. Dir obliegt es nun, das Königreich Ajagara und alle Kreaturen in ihm zu beschützen. Diese prächtige Rüstung wird dir in Schlachten auf weiten Feldern, in den Bergen oder am Himmel gute Dienste leisten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai dato prova di essere un guerriero spietato e hai scelto di diventare un guardiano della fenice che protegge le creature e il regno di Ajagara. Questa eccellente armatura ti sarà utile sia mentre combatti sulle pianure, sia sulle montagne, sia mentre solchi i cieli. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Has demostrado ser un feroz guerrero, por lo que has sido elegido para convertirte en un Guardián del Fénix, tu cometido será proteger a las criaturas y el reino de Ajagara. Esta excelente armadura te ofrecerá gran protección tanto si luchas en las llanuras, como junto a las montañas o en el cielo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">You have proven yourself a fierce warrior and have been chosen to become a Phoenix Guardian, protecting the creatures and kingdom of Ajagara. This fine armour will serve you well whether you battle on the plains, mountain side, or in the skies. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">You have proven yourself a fierce warrior and have been chosen to become a Phoenix Guardian, protecting the creatures and kingdom of Ajagara. This fine armour will serve you well whether you battle on the plains, mountain side, or in the skies. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">You have proven yourself a fierce warrior and have been chosen to become a Phoenix Guardian, protecting the creatures and kingdom of Ajagara. This fine armour will serve you well whether you battle on the plains, mountain side, or in the skies. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">You have proven yourself a fierce warrior and have been chosen to become a Phoenix Guardian, protecting the creatures and kingdom of Ajagara. This fine armour will serve you well whether you battle on the plains, mountain side, or in the skies. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">You have proven yourself a fierce warrior and have been chosen to become a Phoenix Guardian, protecting the creatures and kingdom of Ajagara. This fine armour will serve you well whether you battle on the plains, mountain side, or in the skies. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You have proven yourself a fierce warrior and have been chosen to become a Phoenix Guardian, protecting the creatures and kingdom of Ajagara. This fine armor will serve you well whether you battle on the plains, mountain side, or in the skies. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>