<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wardrobe Wars</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Wardrobe Wars</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">War of the fashionable Avatars [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La guerre du style entre avatars [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ID</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">en-GB</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">fr-FR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">de-DE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">it-IT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">es-ES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ja-JP</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">ko-KR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">en-SG</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">zh-HK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">zh-TW</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">en-US</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PARTICIPANT_PRIZE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Participant</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Participant</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">DAILY_WINNER_PRIZE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Daily Winner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vainqueur du jour</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">WEEKLY_WINNER_PRIZE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Weekly Winner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vainqueur de la semaine</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MONTHLY_WINNER_PRIZE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Monthly Winner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vainqueur du mois</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PRIZE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">REWARD</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÉCOMPENSE</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">DAILY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Daily</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quotidien</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">WEEKLY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Weekly</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Hebdomadaire</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MONTHLY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Monthly</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mensuel</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">WINNER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Winner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vainqueur</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">THEME</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Today's Theme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Thème du jour</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">NAVIGATE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFT][RIGHT] Navigate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFT][RIGHT] Naviguer</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SELECT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Select</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Sélectionner</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">EXIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Quitter</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BACK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Back</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Retour</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TAKE_PICTURE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Take picture</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Prendre photo</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ROTATE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[L2][R2] Rotate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[L2][R2] Pivoter</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TARGET</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFT][RIGHT] Target</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFT][RIGHT] Cibler</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SCROLL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[UP][DOWN] Scroll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[UP][DOWN] Faire défiler</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ZOOM</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[UP][DOWN] Zoom In/Out</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[UP][DOWN] Zoomer / dézoomer</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ENTER_THANK_YOU</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Thank you for entering.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Merci d'avoir participé.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ENTER_REWARD</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Check out the big screens for rewards and come back tomorrow to see if you won!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jetez un œil aux grands écrans pour découvrir les récompenses et revenez demain pour savoir si vous avez gagné !</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">VOTE_SUCCESS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Thank you for voting.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Merci d'avoir voté.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">VOTE_FAIL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have already voted for this entry.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez déjà voté pour cette photo.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">VOTE_RATE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[UP][DOWN] Rating</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[UP][DOWN] Note</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">VOTE_SUBMIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Vote</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Voter</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">VOTE_NEXT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[SQUARE] Next Entry</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[SQUARE] Photo suivante</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TARGET_GAME</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Play Wardrobe Wars</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jouer à Wardrobe Wars</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">OPTION_PHOTO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Enter the competition.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Participer.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">OPTION_ENTRIES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Vote on all entries for today.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Voter pour toutes les photos du jour.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">OPTION_MYENTRIES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">View your entries for today.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Voir toutes les photos du jour.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">VOTE_PROCESS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Processing...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chargement...</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">THEME_PHOTO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Today's theme: %s</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le thème du jour est : %s</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TARGET_VOTE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Vote</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Voter</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">INSTRUCTIONS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[SQUARE] Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[SQUARE] Instructions</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">INSTRUCTION_TEXT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Enter the competition\nTake a photo of yourself while dressing accordingly to the theme. Once you have submitted a photo you will get a participation prize.\n\nRate all entries for today\nRate avatars by approaching a poster or through the kiosk. To rate an avatar, pick a number between 1 and 10 (1 = bad, 10 = good). The avatar’s rating will update based on your rating.\nNote: You can only rate on each entry once.\n\nView your entries for the day\nYou can enter the competition more than once each day. You can only rate each of your entries once.\n\nAt the end of each day a winner will be chosen with the highest rating. Visit the scene the next day to see if you are the winner and receive your reward, which will be posted on the big screen.\n\nWinners from the daily competition will automatically enter into a weekly competition and winners of the weekly competition will enter into a monthly competition. At each competition level, exclusive rewards will be given out. \n\nCheck out the big screens for what rewards are being offered, the weekly theme, and images of previous winner.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Participer au concours\nPrenez une photo de votre avatar habillé sur le thème du jour. Une fois votre photo envoyée, vous remporterez un prix en remerciement de votre participation.\n\nVoter pour toutes les photos du jour\nNotez les avatars en vous approchant d'un poster ou via le kiosque. Pour noter un avatar, choisissez un nombre entre 1 et 10 (1 = mauvais, 10 = excellent). La note de l'avatar sera mise à jour une fois votre note donnée.\nRemarque : vous ne pouvez noter chaque photo qu'une fois.\n\nVoir toutes les photos du jour\nVous pouvez participer au concours plus d'une fois par jour. Vous ne pouvez noter chaque photo qu'une fois.\n\nÀ la fin de chaque journée, est déclaré vainqueur celui ou celle qui a obtenu la meilleure note. Revenez nous voir le lendemain pour savoir si vous avez gagné et recevoir votre récompense, qui sera affichée sur le grand écran.\n\nLes vainqueurs du concours quotidien sont automatiquement sélectionnés pour participer au concours hebdomadaire, et les vainqueurs du concours hebdomadaire participent automatiquement au concours mensuel. À chaque niveau de la compétition, des récompenses exclusives seront distribuées.\n\nJetez un œil aux grands écrans pour savoir quelles récompenses sont à gagner, quel est le thème et voir les photos des vainqueurs précédents.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[TRIANGLE] Rules</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[TRIANGLE] Règlement</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES_TEXT_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OFFICIAL RULES\nPlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest\n\n
NO PURCHASE NECESSARY. Void outside the 50 United States and D.C. and where prohibited.  The following promotion is intended for viewing in the 50 United States and D.C. only and shall only be construed and evaluated according to United States law.  Do not proceed in this contest if you are not a legal resident of, and located in, the 50 United States or D.C. and are at least 13 years of age at the time of entry.  To enter, you must have a PlayStation®3 computer entertainment system, a valid PlayStation®Network account, internet access, a valid e-mail address, and PlayStation®Home installed on your system.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÈGLEMENT\nConcours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home\n\n
SANS OBLIGATION D’ACHAT. Valable uniquement dans les 50 états des États-Unis et D.C, invalide si interdit. La promotion suivante est destinée aux 50 états des États-Unis et à D.C. uniquement et ne sera interprétée et évaluée que vis-à-vis des lois américaines. Vous ne pouvez pas participer à ce concours si vous ne résidez pas légalement et n’êtes pas domicilié(e) dans l’un des 50 états des États-Unis ou à D.C. et si vous n’avez pas au moins 13 ans lors de votre participation. Pour participer, vous devez posséder un système de loisir interactif PlayStation®3, un compte PlayStation®Network valide, un accès à Internet, une adresse e-mail valide et vous devez avoir installé PlayStation®Home sur votre système.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES_TEXT_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OFFICIAL RULES\nPlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest\n\n
1. SPONSOR:  Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC, 919 E. Hillsdale Blvd., Foster City, CA 94404 (“Sponsor”).\n2. ELIGIBILITY: Open to legal U.S. residents only aged 13 or older.  Prize winners or prize winners’ parent or guardian (if the winner is under the age of 18) may be required to sign a notarized Affidavit of Eligibility and Release of Liability within fourteen (14) days of prize notification.  By acceptance of prize, winners agree to the use of their name and/or likenesses by the sponsor for purposes of advertising, trade, or promotion without further compensation, unless prohibited by law.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÈGLEMENT\nConcours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home\n\n
1. ORGANISATEUR : Sony Computer Entertainment America LLC, 919 E. Hillsdale Blvd., Foster City, CA 94404, USA ("organisateur").\n2. ÉLIGIBILITÉ : ouvert aux résidants légaux des États-Unis âgés de 13 ans ou plus. Les vainqueurs des prix ou leur parent ou représentant légal (si les vainqueurs sont âgés de moins de 18 ans) peuvent être amenés à signer un certificat d’éligibilité et une décharge de responsabilité dans les quatorze (14) jours qui suivront l’annonce du prix. En acceptant le prix, les vainqueurs autorisent l’utilisation de leur nom et/ou photo par l’organisateur à des fins publicitaires, commerciales ou promotionnelles, sans aucune autre forme de compensation, sauf mention légale contraire.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES_TEXT_3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OFFICIAL RULES\nPlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest\n\n
3. TIMING: PlayStation Home’s Wardrobe Wars Contest (“Promotion”) begins February 22 2012 at 12:00 a.m. (Midnight) Pacific Daylight Time “PDT” and ends February 17, 2013 at 11:59 p.m. PDT (“Promotion Period”).  There will be 362 daily contests which begin daily at 12:00 a.m. PDT and end at 11:59 p.m. PDT.  There will be 52 weekly contests which begin on the Monday of each week and end on the Sunday of that week. There will be 13 monthly contests which begin on the first day of each month and end on the last day of each month during the promotion period.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÈGLEMENT\nConcours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home\n\n
3. DURÉE : le concours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home ("promotion") commence le 22 février 2012 à 00h00 (minuit), heure de Los Angeles, et se termine le 17 février 2013 à 23h59, heure de Los Angeles ("période de promotion"). Il y aura 362 concours quotidiens qui auront lieu chaque jour entre 00h00 et 23h59, heure de Los Angeles. Il y aura également 52 concours hebdomadaires qui commenceront le lundi de chaque semaine et se termineront le dimanche de la même semaine. Il y aura de plus 13 concours mensuels qui commenceront le premier jour de chaque mois et se termineront le dernier jour du mois, au cours de la période de promotion.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES_TEXT_4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OFFICIAL RULES\nPlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest\n\n
4. HOW TO ENTER: Log into your PlayStation Network account and launch the PlayStation Home application.  Take your avatar to the Wardrobe Wars kiosk on the first floor or second floor of the Mall. Dress your avatar according to the weekly theme indicated on the screen.  To enter, take a picture of your theme dressed avatar in the Wardrobe Wars kiosk and submit your photo according to the instructions and return to the Wardrobe Wars kiosk the following day (“Entry”). You may enter as many times as you like each day throughout the promotion period.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÈGLEMENT\nConcours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home\n\n
4. PARTICIPATION : connectez-vous à votre compte PlayStation®Network et lancez l’application PlayStation®Home. Conduisez votre avatar au kiosque Wardrobe Wars au premier ou deuxième étage du Centre commercial. Habillez votre avatar selon le thème de la semaine, indiqué sur l’écran. Pour participer, prenez une photo de votre avatar habillé selon le thème dans le kiosque Wardrobe Wars et envoyez-la en suivant les instructions, puis revenez au kiosque Wardrobe Wars le jour suivant ("participation"). Vous pouvez participer autant de fois que vous le souhaitez chaque jour, tout au long de la période de promotion.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES_TEXT_5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OFFICIAL RULES\nPlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest\n\n
5. ENTRY CONDITIONS: There will be 365 daily prizes (1 given out each day of the promotion).  A day is defined as starting at 12:00 a.m. PDT and ending at 11:59 p.m. PDT.  The entrant with that day’s highest score as determined by the votes of other PlayStation Home users and returns to the mall the next day will win the prize. To see if you have won the prize you must re-visit the Wardrobe Wars kiosk in the mall and look at the winner’s screen on the kiosk. Each winner of the daily prize is also eligible for that week’s weekly prize, and the winner of the weekly prize is eligible for that month’s monthly prize.  A week is defined as starting on Monday and ending on Sunday. The daily winner with the highest score each week who returns to the mall on the Monday after the weekly competition will receive the weekly prize.  The weekly winner with the highest score each month who returns to the mall on the Monday after the monthly competition will win that month’s monthly prize. In case of a tie, a qualified judge designated by the Sponsor will follow the Judging Criteria as described below to determine the winner.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÈGLEMENT\nConcours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home\n\n
5. CONDITIONS DE PARTICIPATION : il y aura 365 prix quotidiens (un par jour de promotion). Un jour commence à 00h00, heure de Los Angeles, et se termine à 23h59, heure de Los Angeles. Pour remporter le prix, un participant doit obtenir le meilleur score de la journée selon les votes des autres utilisateurs de PlayStation®Home et revenir le lendemain au Centre commercial. Pour savoir si vous avez remporté un prix, vous devez vous rendre à nouveau dans le kiosque Wardrobe Wars dans le Centre commercial et consulter l’écran des vainqueurs dans le kiosque. Chaque vainqueur d’un prix quotidien peut tenter de gagner le prix de la semaine en cours et le vainqueur d’un prix hebdomadaire peut tenter de gagner le prix du mois en cours. Une semaine commence le lundi et se termine le dimanche. C’est le vainqueur d’un prix quotidien qui obtient le meilleur score de la semaine et qui revient dans le Centre commercial le lundi suivant cette semaine qui reçoit le prix hebdomadaire. Le vainqueur d’un prix hebdomadaire qui obtient le meilleur score du mois et qui revient dans le Centre commercial le lundi suivant ce mois reçoit le prix mensuel. En cas d’égalité, un juge qualifié désigné par l’organisateur détermine le vainqueur en utilisant les critères d’évaluation ci-dessous.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES_TEXT_6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OFFICIAL RULES\nPlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest\n\n 6. PRIZES: The following chart shows the virtual clothing items that are available by entering the Contest as set forth in Section 5.\n\nPrizes - Approximate ARV of Each Prize - Quantity of Each Prize for the Entire Contest Period\n
Daily Prize – Virtual Clothing Item - $0.49 - 362\n
Weekly Prize – Virtual Clothing Item - $1.49 - 52\n
Monthly Prize – Virtual Clothing Item - $1.49 - 13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÈGLEMENT\nConcours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home\n\n 6. PRIX : le tableau ci-dessous indique les objets virtuels d’habillement qui peuvent être remportés en participant au concours, comme défini dans la section 5.\n\nPrix - Prix de vente conseillé approximatif de chaque objet - Nombre de prix disponibles pour toute la période de promotion\n
Prix quotidien – Objet virtuel d’habillement - 0,49 $ - 362\n
Prix hebdomadaire – Objet virtuel d’habillement - 1,49 $ - 52\n
Prix mensuel – Objet virtuel d’habillement - 2,49 $ - 13</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES_TEXT_7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OFFICIAL RULES\nPlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest\n\n
7. Each winner’s Entry and PSN ID will also be featured on the Wardrobe Wars kiosk.  Sponsor reserves the right to substitute prize of equal or greater value if prize is unavailable.  Prizes are non-transferable and no substitutions allowed.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÈGLEMENT\nConcours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home\n\n
7. Les photos des vainqueurs et leur ID en ligne seront affichés dans le kiosque Wardrobe Wars. L’organisateur se réserve le droit de remplacer le prix par un autre d’une valeur équivalente ou supérieure si le prix n’est pas disponible. Les prix ne sont ni cessibles, ni échangeables.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES_TEXT_8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OFFICIAL RULES\nPlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest\n\n
8. JUDGING CRITERIA: Voting is open to all PlayStation Home users during the Promotion Period.  Using the rating system, users may vote on Entries by approaching the Wardrobe Wars kiosk, highlighting an Entry and then rating the Entry.  PlayStation Home users should rate each Entry on a scale of 1 to 10 (1 being low and 10 being high) based on the following criteria and criteria weights: (a) Demonstration of commitment to theme – 50%; (b) Creativity – 30%; (c) Originality – 20% (“Judging Criteria”).  Voters can vote on more than one Entry, but can only vote for each Entry ONCE.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÈGLEMENT\nConcours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home\n\n
8. CRITÈRES D’ÉVALUATION : les votes sont ouverts à tous les utilisateurs de PlayStation®Home au cours de la période de promotion. À l’aide du système de notation, les utilisateurs peuvent voter pour les meilleurs participants en s’approchant du kiosque Wardrobe Wars, en mettant leur photo en surbrillance et en la notant. Les utilisateurs de PlayStation®Home doivent noter chaque photo sur une échelle de 1 à 10 (1 étant la note la plus basse et 10 la plus haute) selon les critères et les coefficients suivants : (a) respect du thème – 50 % ; (b) créativité – 30 % ; (c) originalité – 20 % ("critères d’évaluation"). Les utilisateurs peuvent voter pour plus d’une photo mais ne peuvent voter qu’une fois par photo.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES_TEXT_9</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OFFICIAL RULES\nPlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest\n\n
9. WINNERS: As described above, the Entry that receives the highest score each day and returns to the Wardrobe Wars kiosk the day after entering wins the daily prize, the entry that receives the highest score each week and returns to the Wardrobe Wars kiosk the day after the end of the week wins the weekly prize and the entry that receives the highest score each month and returns to the Wardrobe Wars kiosk the day after the end of the week wins the monthly prize. To claim your prize you must re-visit the mall. Once you enter the mall your prize will be automatically downloaded to your wardrobe.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÈGLEMENT\nConcours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home\n\n
9. VAINQUEURS : comme décrit ci-dessus, le participant qui obtient le meilleur score du jour et qui revient dans le kiosque Wardrobe Wars le lendemain de sa participation remporte le prix quotidien. Le participant qui obtient le meilleur score de la semaine et qui revient dans le kiosque Wardrobe Wars le jour suivant la fin de la semaine remporte le prix hebdomadaire. Le participant qui obtient le meilleur score du mois et qui revient dans le kiosque Wardrobe Wars le jour suivant la fin du mois remporte le prix mensuel. Pour obtenir votre prix, vous devez retourner dans le Centre commercial. Une fois dans le Centre commercial, votre prix sera automatiquement téléchargé dans votre garde-robe.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES_TEXT_10</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OFFICIAL RULES\nPlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest\n\n
10. GENERAL CONDITIONS: All Entries are subject to Sponsor’s verification.  Sponsor’s decisions are final and binding in all matters related to the Promotion.  Sponsor reserves the right to remove a winning entry’s photo for any reason.  Potential winners must comply with the Official Rules, and receipt of prizes is contingent upon fulfilling all requirements.  Sponsor is not responsible for technical, hardware or software failures, malfunctions, lost or unavailable network connections or failed, incomplete, garbled or delayed computer transmissions or unforeseen schedule changes that may limit the ability to participate in the Promotion, even if caused by Sponsor’s negligence.  Sponsor has the sole discretion to modify, cancel or suspend this Promotion should virus, bugs, unauthorized human intervention or other causes beyond Sponsor’s control affect the administration, security or proper play of the Promotion or Sponsor otherwise becomes incapable of running the Promotion as planned.  Sponsor is not responsible for changes to contact information.  Sponsor has the sole discretion to disqualify any participant who violates these Official Rules, tampers with the operation of the Promotion or engages in any conduct that is detrimental or unfair to Sponsor, the Promotion or any other participant.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÈGLEMENT\nConcours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home\n\n
10. CONDITIONS GÉNÉRALES : toutes les photos des participants sont soumises à l’approbation de l’organisateur. Les décisions de l’organisateur sont finales et vous engagent dans tous les sujets liés à la promotion. L’organisateur se réserve le droit de supprimer la photo d’un vainqueur quelle que soit la raison. Les vainqueurs potentiels doivent respecter le règlement et l’obtention des prix est liée au respect de toutes les obligations. L’organisateur n’est pas responsable des problèmes techniques, matériels ou logiciels, des disfonctionnements, de la perte ou de l’indisponibilité des connexions réseau, de l’échec, de l’incomplétude, du mélange ou du retard des transmissions informatiques ou des changements imprévus de calendrier qui pourraient limiter la capacité à participer à la promotion, même s’ils sont la conséquence d’une négligence de l’organisateur. L’organisateur seul est habilité à modifier, annuler ou suspendre la promotion en cas de virus, bug, intervention humaine non autorisée ou toute autre raison hors du contrôle de l’organisateur qui affecterait l’administration, la sécurité ou le bon déroulement de la promotion, ou si l’organisateur devient incapable de mener la promotion à son terme. L’organisateur n’est pas responsable des modifications de coordonnées. L’organisateur seul est habilité à disqualifier tout participant qui contreviendrait aux règles officielles, tenterait de modifier le déroulement de l’opération de promotion ou aurait un comportement préjudiciable ou injuste vis-à-vis de l’organisateur, de la promotion ou d’un ou des autres participants.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES_TEXT_11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OFFICIAL RULES\nPlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest\n\n
11. RELEASE: As a condition of participating in the Promotion, all participants agree to release Sponsor and its parent, subsidiaries, agencies, divisions and affiliates from liability, for loss, harm, damage, injury, cost or expense whatsoever including property damage, personal injury and death that may occur in connection with, preparation for, travel to, or participation in the Promotion, or possession, acceptance or use or misuse of prize or participation in any Promotion-related activity and claims based on publicity rights, copyright or trademark infringement, defamation or invasion of privacy and merchandise delivery.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÈGLEMENT\nConcours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home\n\n
11. DÉCHARGE : pour participer à la promotion, tous les participants acceptent de décharger l’organisateur et son organisation mère, ses filiales, agences, divisions et affiliés de toute responsabilité en cas de perte, blessure, dégâts, coûts ou dépenses, y compris les dégâts sur les propriétés, les blessures corporelles ou les décès qui pourraient survenir dans le cadre de la préparation, le transport ou la participation à la promotion, ou de la possession, l’acceptation, l’utilisation ou la mauvaise utilisation du prix, ou de la participation à toute activité liée à la promotion et en cas de réclamations liées à la violation des droits de diffusion, du copyright ou de l’utilisation des marques commerciales, à la diffamation ou à la violation de la vie privée et à la livraison des marchandises.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES_TEXT_12</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OFFICIAL RULES\nPlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest\n\n
12. WINNER LIST: To obtain names of the winners, send a stamped, self-addressed envelope to PlayStation Home Wardrobe Wars Contest, 919 E. Hillsdale Blvd. Foster City, CA 94404.  Prize winners’ name request will be fulfilled within four weeks.  Requests for winner list must be received by January 13, 2013.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÈGLEMENT\nConcours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home\n\n
12. LISTE DES VAINQUEURS : pour obtenir les noms des vainqueurs, envoyez une enveloppe affranchie et à votre nom et adresse à PlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest, 919 E. Hillsdale Blvd. Foster City, CA 94404, USA. Les demandes des listes des vainqueurs des prix seront traitées sous quatre semaines. Ces demandes doivent être reçues avant le 13 janvier 2013.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RULES_TEXT_13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OFFICIAL RULES\nPlayStation®Home Wardrobe Wars Contest\n\n
13. RESTRICTIONS: Void where prohibited or restricted by law.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RÈGLEMENT\nConcours "Wardrobe Wars" PlayStation®Home\n\n
13. RESTRICTIONS : invalide là où le concours est interdit ou illégal.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TARGET_SCREEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Full Screen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plein écran</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vollbild</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Schermo intero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pantalla completa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">전체화면</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Full Screen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">全螢幕</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">全螢幕</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">NO_ENTRIES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">no photos to vote on.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">aucune photo à noter.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">NO_USER_ENTRIES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have no photos to vote on.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il n'y a aucune photo à noter.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">VOTED</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">voted</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">notée</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>