<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ObjectName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Libble Rabble T-Shirt (Womens)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">T-shirt Libble Rabble (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Libble Rabble-T-Shirt (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">T-shirt Libble Rabble (Per donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta Libble Rabble (Femenina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">女性用リブルラブルTシャツ１</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">리블래블 티셔츠 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Libble Rabble T-shirt (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Libble Rabble T恤（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Libble Rabble T恤（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Libble Rabble T-Shirt</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ObjectDescription</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A shop exclusive Libble Rabble T-shirt. Fairies, or Topkap, from the game adorn the back of this stylish item![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un T-shirt Libble Rabble exclusif dans la boutique. Des fées, ou Topkap, issues du jeu sont représentées au dos de cet article très stylé ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein exklusiv nur im Shop erhältliches Libble Rabble-T-Shirt. Dieser topmodische Artikel ist an der Rückseite mit Elfen (Topkap) aus dem Spiel verziert![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esclusive T-shirt Libble Rabble. Le fate del gioco, o Topkap, adornano il retro di questo articolo di grande stile![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Exclusiva camiseta Libble Rabble en la tienda. ¡La parte trasera de este artículo tan de moda está adornada con hadas (Topkap) del juego![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ショップ限定リブルラブルＴシャツです。ゲーム中に出てくる妖精「トプカプ」を背中にあしらったナイスな一品！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">샵 한정 리블래블 티셔츠입니다.  게임에 나오는 요정 토프카프로 등을 멋지게 장식했습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A shop exclusive Libble Rabble T-shirt. Fairies, or Topkap, from the game adorn the back of this stylish item![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">本店限定的Libble Rabble T恤！背部的圖案是遊戲中出現的妖精。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">本店限定的Libble Rabble T恤！背部的圖案是遊戲中出現的妖精。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Live it up in old school flair with this designer T-shirt, packed with unforgettable characters from the classic loop-'em-up game Libble Rabble! From the dancing Topcups on the back to the curious Mushlin on the sleeve, this is one piece classic gamers shouldn't go without! Who knows, pretty soon you may find yourself lassoing in some attention...[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>