<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Peasant Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Paysanne paquet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Peasant Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Peasant pacchetto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Campesina paquete</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">農民のパッケージ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">농민 패키지</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Peasant Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">农民包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">农民包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Peasant Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Basic wares for your house. Includes Plank Bench, Wooden Seat, Plank Stool, Sanded Table, Plank Table, Ornate Chest, Sealed Barrel, Open Barrel, Barrel Lid and Storage Crate.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Liaison avec les marchandises de base pour votre maison. Comprend Banc planche, Siège en bois, Selles planche, Table de poncé, Table de planches, Coffre ornée, Le baril étanche, Le baril ouvert, Couvercle baril et Caisse de stockage.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wares für Ihre Heimatbasis. Beinhaltet Planke Bank, Holzsitz, Planke Stuhl, Geschliffen Tisch, Brettertisch, Verzierten Kasten, Verschlossenen Faß, Offene Faß, Faßdeckel, und Aufbewahrungsbox.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Wares per la tua casa base. Include Plancia panchina, Seduta in legno, Selle di bordo, Tabella sabbiato, Tabella schede, Petto ornato, Stretta barile, Il tamburo aperto, Barile coperchio, e Contenitore.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mercancías para su base de operaciones. Incluye Banco de la Junta, Asiento de madera, Sillas de montar placa, Tabla arena, Encimeras, El pecho adornado, Barril apretado, El tambor abierto, Barril tapa, y Caja de almacenamiento.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">あなたの家の基本的な用品。プランクベンチ、木製の座席、プランクスツール、サンディングテーブル、プランク表、飾り箱、密封されたバレル、オープンバレル、バレル蓋とストレージクレートが含まれています。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">당신의 집에 대한 기본 실력. 판자 교체 멤버, 나무 의자, 널빤지 의자, 모래를 뿌려 장식 테이블, 널빤지 테이블, 화려한 가슴, 봉인된 배럴, 오픈 바렐, 바렐, 리드 및 보관 상자가 포함됩니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Basic wares for your house. Includes Plank Bench, Wooden Seat, Plank Stool, Sanded Table, Plank Table, Ornate Chest, Sealed Barrel, Open Barrel, Barrel Lid and Storage Crate.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">为你的房子的基本商品。包括板椅，木椅子，木板凳子，沙化表，板表，华丽的胸部，密封桶，开桶，筒盖和存储木箱。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">为你的房子的基本商品。包括板椅，木椅子，木板凳子，沙化表，板表，华丽的胸部，密封桶，开桶，筒盖和存储木箱。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Basic wares for your house. Includes Plank Bench, Wooden Seat, Plank Stool, Sanded Table, Plank Table, Ornate Chest, Sealed Barrel, Open Barrel, Barrel Lid and Storage Crate.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>