<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Fifty Cord Denim Jeans - Camel (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Jean denim Fifty Cord - Chameau (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Fifty Cord Denim Jeans - Kamelhaarfarbe (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Fifty Cord Jeans - Cammello (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Fifty Cord Vaquero - Color camello (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Looking good comes easy to our straight leg Fifty pants, as its distinct colourways and modern design take surf inspired corduroy to the next level of cool. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Soigner son apparence n'a jamais été aussi facile avec notre pantalon droit Fifty, ses coloris distingués et sa conception moderne confèrent à ce velours d'inspiration surf un look cool jamais égalé. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">So wird gut aussehen leicht gemacht - mit dieser modischen, gerade geschnittenen Fifty Cordhose in attraktiv ausgebleichten Grautönen. Mit der Fifty erreicht die vom Surfen inspirierte Cordhose einen ganz neuen Level von Cool. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Con i pantaloni Fifty a gamba dritta è facile sentirsi al meglio, grazie ai colori definiti e al design moderno che portano questi pantaloni di velluto di ispirazione surfista a nuovi livelli di tendenza. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acertar en tu vestimenta es fácil con el pantalón de corte recto Fifty, por su marcado color y moderno diseño, que llevan la pana surfera a un nuevo nivel de lo "cool". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Looking good comes easy to our straight leg Fifty pants, as its distinct colorways and modern design take surf inspired corduroy to the next level of cool. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>