<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Xero Boardshorts - Lime Aqua (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Short de planchiste Xero - Vert turquoise (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Xero Boardshorts - Limone (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Xero Shorts da mare - Lime Acqua (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Xero Bermudas - Agua lima (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Zero means none and so does the Xero 21" boardshort because it has no back seam. This top of the line boardshort is like no other. Heat transfer detailing appears at the waistband, side seam and side pocket. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Zéro signifie néant, et il en est de même pour le short de planchiste Xero 21" car il n'a aucune couture dorsale. Le short de planchiste haut de gamme n'a pas son pareil. Des motifs apposés par transfert thermique apparaissent au niveau de la ceinture, de la couture latérale et de la poche latérale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zero bedeutet Null - und zwar auch bei den Xero 21" Boardshorts, denn diese haben hinten keine Naht. Diese hochwertigen Boardshorts sind daher etwas ganz Besonderes. Mit Wärmeübertragungsband am Bund, an den Seitennähten und an der Tasche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Zero significa niente e lo stesso vale per gli shorts da mare Xero 21" perché non hanno cuciture posteriori. Questi shorts da mare sono unici nel loro genere. Presentano rifiniture traspiranti sulla fascia in vita, sulla cucitura laterale e sulla tasca laterale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cero significa ninguno, igual que las bermudas Xero 21" con ninguna costura trasera. Estas bermudas de máxima calidad no tienen rival. En la cintura se aprecian detalles de impresión por transferencia de calor, así como en la costura y el bolsillo laterales. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>