<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cherry Blossom Fairy Set (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble de fée Cerise (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kirschblütenfee-Set (Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set fata dei fiori di ciliegio (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto del hada del cerezo en flor (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">桜の妖精セット（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">벚꽃의 요정 세트(여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sakura Fairy Set (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">櫻花妖精服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">櫻花妖精服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cherry Blossom Fairy Set (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The perfect costume set for a cherry blossom fairy. \n\nThis set includes the following items for avatar customisation. \n・Blossom Fairy Dress (Female)/Combination
\n・Blossom Fairy Boots (Female)/Feet
\n・Blossom Fairy Wand (Female)/Hands
\n・Blossom Fairy Hair Accessory (Female)/Head Accessory\n\n※Once purchased, each item is added to the relevant category under "Avatar Customisation." \n※Cherry Blossom Fairy Dress (Female) includes both the torso and legs counted as one item. Items in the same category cannot be used separately.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La tenue parfaite pour une fée Cerise. \n\nPersonnalisez votre avatar avec cet ensemble comprenant les éléments suivants : \n・Vêtements de fée Cerise pour femme/Combinaison 
\n・Bottes de fée Cerise (femme)/Pieds
\n・Baguette de fée Cerise (femme)/Mains \n・Accessoire de fée Cerise (femme)/Accessoire tête \n\n※Une fois acheté, chaque accessoire est ajouté dans la catégorie appropriée. \n※La tenue de fée Cerise (femme) comprend un haut et un bas indissociables. Les éléments d'une même catégorie ne peuvent pas être utilisés séparément. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das perfekte Kostümset für eine Kirschblütenfee. \n\nDieses Set enthält die folgenden Gegenstände zur Anpassung des Avatars. \n・Blütenfee-Kleid (Frauen)/Kombination 
\n・Blütenfee-Stiefel (Frauen)/Füße
\n・Blütenfee-Zauberstab (Frauen)/Hände \n・Blütenfee-Haarschmuck (Frauen)/Kopf \n\n※Nach dem Kauf wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt. \n※Das "Kirschblütenfee-Kleid (Frauen)" enthält sowohl die Kleidung für den Rumpf als auch für die Beine, die zusammen als ein Gegenstand zählt. Gegenstände in derselben Kategorie können nicht einzeln verwendet werden. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il set costume perfetto per una fata dei fiori di ciliegio. \n\nQuesto set contiene una serie di articoli per personalizzare l'avatar. \n・Abito fata dei fiori di ciliegio (donna)/Abbinamento 
\n・Stivali fata dei fiori di ciliegio (donna)/Piedi
\n・Bacchetta fata dei fiori di ciliegio (donna)/Mani \n・Accessorio per capelli fata dei fiori di ciliegio (donna)/Accessorio \n\n※Dopo l'acquisto, ciascun elemento viene inserito nella categoria corrispondente. \n※L'abito fata dei fiori di ciliegio (donna) consiste in un unico articolo composto da due capi già abbinati, uno per il torso e uno per le gambe, non indossabili separatamente. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El conjunto perfecto para un hada del cerezo en flor. \n\nEste conjunto incluye los siguientes artículos para la personalización del avatar: \n・Vestido del hada del cerezo en flor (mujer)/Combinación 
\n・Botas del hada del cerezo en flor (mujer)/Pies
\n・Varita del hada del cerezo en flor (mujer)/Manos \n・Complemento para el pelo del hada del cerezo en flor (mujer)/Complementos \n\n※Una vez comprados, cada artículo se agrega a la categoría relevante. \n※El vestido del hada del cerezo en flor (mujer) incluye tanto el torso como las piernas en un mismo artículo. Los artículos de la misma categoría no se pueden usar por separado.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">桜の妖精をイメージした衣裳セットです。\n\n本セットには、アバターカスタマイズ用の下記アイテムが含まれています。\n
・桜のドレス（女性用）/組み合わせ\n
・桜のブーツ（女性用）/靴\n
・桜のステッキ（女性用）/手\n
・桜のヘアアクセ（女性用）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n\n
※購入すると、「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。\n
※桜のドレス（女性用）は、トップス・ボトムズをまとめて１つのアイテムとしております。カテゴリ毎のアイテムを単体で使用することはできませんのでご注意ください。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">벚꽃의 요정을 이미지화한 의상 세트입니다.\n\n본 세트에는 아바타 꾸미기용의 하기 아이템이 포함되어 있습니다.\n
●벚꽃 드레스(여성)\n
●벚꽃 부츠(여성)\n
●벚꽃 지팡이(여성)\n
●벚꽃 헤어 액세서리(여성)\n\n
※구입하면「아바타 꾸미기」내의 해당 카테고리에 각 아이템이 추가됩니다.\n
※벚꽃 드레스(여성)은 상의・하의를 합친 하나의 아이템으로 되어 있습니다. 각 카테고리의 아이템을 단품으로 사용하는 것은 불가능하므로 주의해 주시기 바랍니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This is a costume set based on a sakura fairy.\n\nThis set includes the following items for avatar customization.\n
・Sakura Costume (Women)\n
・Sakura Boots (Women)\n
・Sakura Stick (Women)\n
・Sakura Hair Accessory (Women)\n\n
※Upon purchase, the items will be added into the respective categories in "Go to Wardrobe". \n
※The Sakura Costume (Women)  is counted as one item including top and bottom. Please note that items under one category cannot be used independent of other items.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這是以櫻花妖精為設計概念的服裝組。\n\n本組合包括以下可用來自訂角色的物品。\n
●櫻花服裝（女用）\n
●櫻花短靴（女用）\n
●櫻花仙棒（女用）\n
●櫻花頭飾（女用）\n\n
※購買後，各項物品會被加到「前往衣帽間」的所屬類別內。\n
※櫻花服裝（女用）以整套出售，包括上身和下身。請注意各個類別內的物件不能單獨使用。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這是以櫻花妖精為設計概念的服裝組。\n\n本組合包括以下可用來自訂角色的物品。\n
●櫻花服裝（女用）\n
●櫻花短靴（女用）\n
●櫻花仙棒（女用）\n
●櫻花頭飾（女用）\n\n
※購買後，各項物品會被加到「前往更衣室」的所屬類別內。\n
※櫻花服裝（女用）以整套出售，包括上半身和下半身。請注意各個類別內的物件不能單獨使用。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The perfect costume set for a cherry blossom fairy. \n\nThis set includes the following items for avatar customisation. \n・Blossom Fairy Dress (Female)/Combination
\n・Blossom Fairy Boots (Female)/Feet
\n・Blossom Fairy Wand (Female)/Hands
\n・Blossom Fairy Hair Accessory (Female)/Head Accessory\n\n※Once purchased, each item is added to the relevant category under "Avatar Customisation." \n※Cherry Blossom Fairy Dress (Female) includes both the torso and legs counted as one item. Items in the same category cannot be used separately.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>