<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">NAME</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Eviscerator Figure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Figurine de l'Éviscérator</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ausschlachter-Figur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Modellino Eviscerator</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Muñeco de Eviscerator</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">エビサレイターのフィギュア</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이비서레이터 피규어</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Eviscerator Figure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Eviscerator角色模型</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Eviscerator角色模型</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Eviscerator Figure</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">He was one of the many illegal robot-alien hybrids. Kidnapped by Gleeman Vox, the Eviscerator sliced it's way through DreadZone, becoming one of Ace Hardlight's trusted Exterminators.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'un des nombreux hybrides illégaux de robot et d'extraterrestre. Enlevé par Gleeman Vox, l'Éviscérator s'est taillé un chemin à travers DreadZone pour devenir l'un des fameux Exterminateurs d'Ace Hardlight.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Einer der vielen illegalen Roboter-Alien-Hybride. Nach seiner Entführung durch Gleeman Vox schlitzte sich der Ausschlachter seinen Weg durch die DreadZone und wurde zu einem von Ace Hardlights zuverlässigen Exterminatoren. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">È stato uno dei tanti ibridi illegali robot-alieni. Rapito da Gleeman Vox, Eviscerator si è distinto in DreadZone, diventando uno dei fedeli Sterminatori di Ace Hardlight. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Era uno de los muchos híbridos robot-alienígena ilegales. Secuestrado por Gleeman Vox, Eviscerator se abrió camino a cuchilladas en La hora del terror, convirtiéndose en uno de los Exterminadores de confianza de Ace Hardlight.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">違法なロボットとエイリアンの合成生物だったが、グリーマン・ヴォックスにさらわれて、『ドレッドゾーン』で戦うことになった。エース・ハイドライトが信頼するグラディエーターのひとり。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">수많은 불법 로봇-외계인 가운데 하나. 글리맨 복스에 의하여 납치된 다음, 이비서레이터는 드레드존을 휩쓸며 이름을 날렸습니다. 에이스 하드라이트의 믿음직한 부하. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">He was one of the many illegal robot-alien hybrids. Kidnapped by Gleeman Vox, the Eviscerator sliced it's way through DreadZone, becoming one of Ace Hardlight's trusted Exterminators.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">他是許多違法機器外星人混血兒中的一份子。先是被格里曼‧維克斯給綁架，Eviscerator在恐懼地帶把它切成碎片後，轉而變成信仰毀滅者的強光艾司成員。  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">他是許多違法機器外星人混血兒中的一份子。先是被格里曼‧維克斯給綁架，Eviscerator在恐懼地帶把它切成碎片後，轉而變成信仰毀滅者的強光艾司成員。  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">He was one of the many illegal robot-alien hybrids. Kidnapped by Gleeman Vox, the Eviscerator sliced it's way through DreadZone, becoming one of Ace Hardlight's trusted Exterminators.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>