<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">U Love Green dress (green)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Robe U Love Green (vert)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kleid von U Love Green (grün)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vestito U Love Green (verde)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Vestido U Love Green (verde)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">U Love Greenドレス（緑）(女性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">당신은 자연을 사랑해 드레스 (녹색, 여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">U Love Green Dress (Green, Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">你愛綠色連身裙（綠色/女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">你愛綠色連身裙（綠色/女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">U Love Green dress (green)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Be chic with this elegant dress with a timeless style. Its subtle and feminine look has lots of character. Made from organic cotton, it gives you softness and comfort. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Soyez bon chic bon genre grâce à cette élégante robe intemporelle. Son allure sobre et féminine a beaucoup de caractère. Fabriquée à base de coton biologique, elle vous procure douceur et confort. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beweise Stil und Klasse in diesem eleganten, zeitlosen Kleid. Der feine, feminine Look strahlt viel Charakter aus. Und das aus Biobaumwolle bestehende Material fühlt sich überaus weich und bequem an. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo abito dall'eleganza senza tempo metterà in risalto la tua femminilità con discrezione e personalità. Il tessuto in cotone organico ti offre morbidezza e comfort. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Llénate de elegancia con este vestido que no pasa de moda. Su look delicado y femenino demuestra mucho carácter. Hecho de algodón ecológico, te proporcionará suavidad y comodidad. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">流行に左右されないスタイルの優雅なドレスでシックなあなたを演出しましょう。繊細で女性らしいデザインは非常に個性豊かです。オーガニックコットン製なので、柔らかさと快適さを与えてくれます。by U Love Green[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">시대에 구애받지 않는 이 우아한 드레스로 세련미를 뽐내세요. 조용하면서도 여성스러운 모양은 많은 것을 보여줍니다. 유기농 솜으로 만들어, 여러분께 부드러움과 편안함을 선사합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Be chic with this elegant dress with a timeless style. Its subtle and feminine look has lots of character. Made from organic cotton, it gives you softness and comfort. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">穿上這條永不過時的優雅連身裙，型格登場。連身裙設計含畜、女性化並充滿個性。採用有機棉的質料，穿著舒適。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">穿上這條永不過時的優雅連身裙，型格登場。連身裙設計含畜、女性化並充滿個性。採用有機棉的質料，穿著舒適。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Be chic with this elegant dress with a timeless style. Its subtle and feminine look has lots of character. Made from organic cotton, it gives you softness and comfort. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>