<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blimps - Flamer Blimp Bundle (2nd Class)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Blimps - Lot Ballon à flammes (2ème classe)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blimps – Flammen-Blimp-Paket (2. Klasse)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dirigibili - Pacchetto Dirigibile Fiamma (II classe)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dirigibles: Paquete “Dirigible afeminado” (2.ª clase)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">フレーマーブリンプ（クラス2）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블림프 - 플레이머 블림프 번들 (2등급)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Blimps - Flamer Blimp Bundle (2nd Class)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">軟式飛艇 - 火焰噴射器軟式飛艇組合包（第2級）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">軟式飛艇 - 火焰噴射器軟式飛艇組合包（第2級）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blimps - Flamer Blimp Bundle (2nd Class)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blimps ahoy! This fantastic value for money bundle contains the following items: \n\n

* Flamer Blimp Companion \n
* 5000 Aurora XP \n
* Flamer Blimp unlocked in the Blimps game within Aurora \n\n

※ On purchasing this bundle the companion item will be placed in the relevant category. The Aurora XP will be awarded after entering Aurora. The Blimp can be accessed via the Blimps mini game, also found in Aurora. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ohé du ballon ! Ce lot au rapport qualité-prix exceptionnel comporte les objets suivants : \n\n

* Compagnon Ballon à flammes \n
* 5000 points de XP Aurora \n
* Ballon à flammes déverrouillé dans le jeu Blimps d’Aurora \n\n

※ À l’achat de ce lot, l’objet compagnon sera placé dans la catégorie appropriée. Les points de XP Aurora seront décernés après être entré dans Aurora. Le ballon est accessible par le biais du mini-jeu Blimps, également disponible dans Aurora. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blimps ahoi! Dieses fantastische Paket mit tollem Preis-Leistungs-Verhältnis enthält die folgenden Gegenstände: \n\n

* Flammen-Blimp-Begleiter \n
* 5000 Aurora-EP \n
* Im Spiel Blimps in Aurora freigeschalteter Flammen-Blimp \n\n

※ Beim Kauf dieses Pakets wird der Begleiter-Gegenstand in der entsprechenden Kategorie platziert. Die Aurora-EP werden nach dem Betreten von Aurora zugeteilt. Auf den Blimp kann über das Minispiel Blimps zugegriffen werden, das ebenfalls in Aurora zu finden ist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ciao dirigibile! Questo pacchetto vale tutti i soldi che costa e contiene i seguenti oggetti:\n\n

* Compagno dirigibile Fiamma \n
* 3000 XP Aurora \n
* Il dirigibile Fiamma sbloccato nel gioco all'interno di Aurora \n\n

※ Comprando questo pacchetto, l'oggetto compagno sarà piazzato nella categoria di appartenenza. Gli XP Aurora saranno assegnati dopo che sarai entrato in Aurora. Puoi accedere al dirigibile attraverso il mini gioco Dirigibili, reperibile anche in Aurora. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Dirigible a la vista! Este fantástico paquete con una buena relación calidad-precio contiene: \n\n

* Dirigible afeminado (compañero).\n
* 5000 de EXP Aurora.\n
* Dirigible afeminado, desbloqueado en el minijuego “Dirigibles” de Aurora.\n\n

※ Una vez que compres este paquete, el artículo compañero se colocará en la categoría correspondiente. La EXP de Aurora se otorgará en cuanto se entre en Aurora. Podrás acceder al dirigible en el minijuego “Dirigibles” que encontrarás en Aurora. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブリンプ! このお値打ちアイテムを購入するとオーロララウンジ入場時にオーロラ島防衛やOrbRunnerのゲームに参加したときに得られる経験値5000とブリンプミニゲーム内のフレーマーブリンプがアンロックされます。\n※このアイテムはポータブルアイテムです。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이봐요, 블림프! 가격 대 성능비가 높은 이 환상적인 번들은 다음 아이템을 포함합니다: \n\n

●플레이머 블림프 컴패니언 \n
●5000 Aurora XP \n
●Aurora 내의 블림프 게임에서 플레이머 블림프가 해제 \n\n

※ 구입과 동시에 이 번들의 컴패니언 아이템은 적절한 카테고리에 배치될 것입니다. Aurora XP는 Aurora에 입장한 후에 지급될 것입니다. 블림프는 Aurora에서도 찾을 수 있는 블림프 미니 게임을 통해서 이용할 수 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Blimps ahoy! This fantastic value for money bundle contains the following items: \n\n

* Flamer Blimp Companion \n
* 5000 Aurora XP \n
* Flamer Blimp unlocked in the Blimps game within Aurora \n\n

※ On purchasing this bundle the companion item will be placed in the relevant category. The Aurora XP will be awarded after entering Aurora. The Blimp can be accessed via the Blimps mini game, also found in Aurora. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">軟式飛艇！物超所值的組合包包括以下物品：\n\n

●火焰噴射器軟式飛艇隨身夥伴\n
●5000點極光群島經驗值\n
●火焰噴射器軟式飛艇(極光群島軟式飛艇遊戲專用物品)\n\n

※ 購買此組合包後，隨身夥伴物品將會放在相關類別中。進入極光群島後將會獲得本組合包附帶的極光群島XP。軟式飛艇遊戲專用飛艇亦可在極光群島中找到。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">軟式飛艇！物超所值的組合包包括以下物品：\n\n

●火焰噴射器軟式飛艇隨身夥伴\n
●5000點極光群島經驗值\n
●火焰噴射器軟式飛艇(極光群島軟式飛艇遊戲專用物品)\n\n

※ 購買此組合包後，隨身夥伴物品將會放在相關類別中。進入極光群島後將會獲得本組合包附帶的極光群島XP。軟式飛艇遊戲專用飛艇亦可在極光群島中找到。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blimps ahoy! This fantastic value for money bundle contains the following items: \n\n

* Flamer Blimp Companion \n
* 5000 Aurora XP \n
* Flamer Blimp unlocked in the Blimps game within Aurora \n\n

※ On purchasing this bundle the companion item will be placed in the relevant category. The Aurora XP will be awarded after entering Aurora. The Blimp can be accessed via the Blimps mini game, also found in Aurora. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="Description">ensure that Aurora and XP are consistant with the translations in th other aurora strings [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kCompanionName1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blimps - Flamer Blimp (2nd Class)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Blimps - Lot Ballon à flammes (2ème classe)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blimps – Flammen-Blimp-Paket (2. Klasse)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dirigibili - Pacchetto Dirigibile Fiamma (II classe)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dirigibles: Paquete “Dirigible afeminado” (2.ª clase)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">フレーマーブリンプ（クラス2）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블림프 - 플레이머 블림프 번들 (2등급)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Blimps - Flamer Blimp (2nd Class)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">軟式飛艇 - 火焰噴射器軟式飛艇組合包（第2級）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">軟式飛艇 - 火焰噴射器軟式飛艇組合包（第2級）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blimps - Flamer Blimp (2nd Class)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>