<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Once you are level 55, the Auroralite Hoody, crafted with energy weave from the Vortex empowers you letting you double the XP you earn playing the Aurora Island Defence and OrbRunner games.  May your journey to enlightenment be swift. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une fois que vous avez atteint le niveau 55, le sweat à capuche Auroralite, fabriqué avec des tissus énergétiques issus du Vortex, augmente vos capacités et vous permet de doubler votre XP gagné lors des jeux Défense de l'Île d'Aurora et OrbRunner. Que votre voyage vers l'illumination soit rapide. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ab Level 55 verleiht dir der Auroralite-Kapuzenpullover mit der aus dem Wirbel gewebten Energie doppelten EP-Gewinn sowohl bei der Verteidigung Auroras oder in Orbrunner. Möge deine Reise zur Erleuchtung geschwind verlaufen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una volta raggiunto il livello 55, la felpa con cappuccio Auroralite, creata con tessuti di energia del Vortice, ti conferisce il potere di raddoppiare gli XP che ottieni giocando ai giochi Difesa dell'isola di Aurora e Acchiappa le sfere. Che il tuo viaggio verso la cultura possa essere veloce. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuando llegues al nivel 55, la sudadera con capucha Auroralite, creada con un tejido de energía del Vórtice que te confiere poderes para conseguir duplicar la XP que consigas al jugar a Defensa de la Isla de Aurora y a OrbRunner. Que el viaje hacia la luz sea veloz. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">レベル55になると、ボルテックスのエネルギー織で丁寧に作られたAuroraliteパーカーの力により、オーロラ島防衛やOrbRunnerのゲームに参加したときに得られる経験値が2倍になります。あなたの悟りへの旅路が速やかでありますように。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">레벨 55가 되면, Vortex로부터의 에너지로 만들어낸 Aurora 후디는 당신이 Aurora 섬 방어 및 OrbRunner 게임을 플레이하며 얻은 XP를 두 배로 만들어줍니다. 여정을 통해 빠른 깨달음을 얻으십시오. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Once you are level 55, the Auroralite Hoody, crafted with energy weave from the Vortex empowers you letting you double the XP you earn playing the Aurora Island Defence and OrbRunner games.  May your journey to enlightenment be swift. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">一旦你達到55級，由來自「Vortex」的能量編織而成的極光連帽外套將讓你在玩極光島嶼守衛戰和OrbRunner遊戲時所獲得的XP倍增。祝你很快就能達到這境界。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">一旦你達到55級，由來自「Vortex」的能量編織而成的極光連帽外套將讓你在玩極光島嶼守衛戰和OrbRunner遊戲時所獲得的XP倍增。祝你很快就能達到這境界。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Once you are level 55, the Auroralite Hoody, crafted with energy weave from the Vortex empowers you letting you double the XP you earn playing the Aurora Island Defence and OrbRunner games.  May your journey to enlightenment be swift. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Auroralite Hoody (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sweat à capuche Auroralite (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Auroralite-Kapuzenpullover (Mann)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Felpa con cappuccio Auroralite (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sudadera con capucha de Auroralite (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Auroraliteパーカー（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Aurora 후디 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Auroralite Hoody (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">極光連帽外套（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">極光連帽外套（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Auroralite Hoody (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>