<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Indoor Catherine Wheel - Sunset Sparks</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Soleil d’Intérieur - Éclairs du Crépuscule</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Feuerrad (für Inneneinsatz) - Sonnenfunken</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Girandola da interni - Luccichii al tramonto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Rueda Catherine para interior - Destellos crepusculares</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">インドアねずみ花火　サンセットスパーク</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">실내용 캐서린 휠 - 선셋 스파크</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Indoor Catherine Wheel - Sunset Sparks</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">室內蝴蝶炮：夕照</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">室內蝴蝶炮：夕照</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Indoor Catherine Wheel - Sunset Sparks</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use these indoor animated fireworks to produce a beautiful and breathtaking spectacle. Impress your guests or just to satisfy your creative pyrotechnic desires. Suitable for indoor use. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez ces feux d'artifice d'intérieur animés pour un spectacle à couper le souffle. Impressionnez vos invités ou comblez vos propres désirs de création pyrotechnique. Adapté à l'utilisation en intérieur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zünde dieses animierte Innenfeuerwerk für ein wunderschönes und atemberaubendes Spektakel. Beeindrucke damit deine Gäste oder erfülle dir einfach deine pyrotechnischen Träume. Für den Inneneinsatz geeignet. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usa questo fuoco d'artificio animato da interni per creare un meraviglioso spettacolo emozionante. Lascia i tuoi ospiti a bocca aperta o soddisfa i tuoi desideri creativi pirotecnici. Adatto per gli interni. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Crea un espectáculo maravilloso y extraordinario con estos fuegos artificiales animados. Impresiona a tus invitados o simplemente satisface tus deseos pirotécnicos creativos. Apta para uso interior. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">こちらの屋内用花火を使って屋内でもスペクタルをお楽しみください。注：屋内用 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">실내용 에니메이션 불꽃놀이로 아름다우면서도 숨막히는 장관을 연출하세요. 여러분의 손님들에게 감동을 주거나 아니면 본인의 창조적인 불꽃놀이 욕구를 만족시켜 보세요. 실내 사용에 적합. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Use these indoor animated fireworks to produce a beautiful and breathtaking spectacle. Impress your guests or just to satisfy your creative pyrotechnic desires. Suitable for indoor use. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這些室內動態煙火，讓你創造美麗的驚喜畫面，保證讓賓客讚不絕口，或是滿足你的煙火創作慾望。適合室內使用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這些室內動態煙火，讓你創造美麗的驚喜畫面，保證讓賓客讚不絕口，或是滿足你的煙火創作慾望。適合室內使用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Use these indoor animated fireworks to produce a beautiful and breathtaking spectacle. Impress your guests or just to satisfy your creative pyrotechnic desires. Suitable for indoor use. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>