<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A Green Day Bundle (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble de Jour Vert (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Grün Tag Set (mann)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set di Giorno Verde (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lote del Día Verde (hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Paint your day green with the joy of this St. Patrick´s day collection! Forget about being one of the bunch, become the life of the party through this collection and its original accessories. With this line, luck will always be on your side. Fill your pot with laughter and fun and you will shine brighter than the gold on your boots! 

This bundle contains:

- Green Day Suit
- Green Day Boots (male)
- Green Day Hat (male)
- Green Day Pot of Gold (male)


[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Peignez votre jour en vert joyeusement avec cette collection de la journée de St Patrick ! Oubliez être un parmi tant d’autres, devenez le roi de la fête avec cette collection et ses accessoires d'origine. Avec cette ligne, la chance sera toujours de votre côté. Remplissez-vous de rire et de plaisir et faites briller de l'or de vos bottes ! 

Cet ensemble contient:

- Costume de Jour Vert
- Bottes de Jour Vert (homme)
- Chapeau de Jour Vert (homme)
- Pot d'or de Jour Vert (homme)

[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Färben Sie Ihren Tag grün mit der Freude, die diese St. Patricks Tag Sammlung bereitet! Heben Sie sich von der Masse ab und werden Sie mit dieser Sammlung und ihre Original-Accessoires zum Mittelpunkt der Party. Mit dieser Linie haben Sie das Glück immer auf Ihrer Seite. Füllen Sie Ihren Topf mit Gelächter und Spaß und Sie werden heller strahlen, als das Gold an Ihren Stiefeln!

Dieses Set enthält:

- Grün Tag Kostüm
- Grün Tag Schuhe (mann)
- Grün Tag Hut (mann)
- Grün Tag Hut Goldschatz (mann)

 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dipingi la tua giornata di verde con la gioia di questa raccolta del giorno di San Patrizio! Dimenticati di essere uno tra tanti, diventa l'anima della festa attraverso questa raccolta e i suoi accessori originali. Con questa linea, la fortuna sarà sempre dalla tua parte. Riempi la tua pentola con le risate e il divertimento e splenderai più dell'oro sui tuoi stivali! 

Questo set contiene:

- Costume di Giorno Verde
- Stivali di Giorno Verde (uomo)
- Capello di Giorno Verde (uomo)
- Pentola d'oro di Giorno Verde (uomo)


[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Tiñe tu día de verde y alegría con la colección de St. Patricks!  Olvídate de ser uno más del montón y conviértete en el alma de la fiesta gracias a esta colección y sus originales complementos. ¡Con esta línea la suerte siempre estará de tu parte! Llena tu marmita de risas y de diversión, brillarás más que el oro de tus botas! 

Este lote contiene:

- Traje del Día Verde
- Botas del Día Verde (hombre)
- Sombrero del Día Verde (hombre)
- Marmita de Oro del Día Verde (hombre)


 [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>