<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Radiant Storm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tempête rayonnante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Strahlensturm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tempesta radiante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tormenta radiante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ラディアントストーム</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">복사 폭풍</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Radiant Storm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">輻射風暴彈</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">輻射風暴彈</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Radiant Storm</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Engulf your enemies in lightning with the Radiant Storm Bomb!  You control when this bomb detonates, causing it to explode into a devastating field of crackling energy. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Enveloppez vos ennemis de foudre grâce à la Tempête rayonnante ! Vous contrôlez la détonation de la bombe dont l'explosion produira un champ d'énergie crépitante infligeant des dégâts dévastateurs. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hülle Deine Feinde mit der Strahlensturm-Bombe in Blitze ein! Du kontrollierst selber, wann die Bombe ausgelöst wird, wodurch sie zu einem verheerenden Feld aus knisternder Energie detoniert. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ingloba i tuoi nemici in un fulmine con la tempesta radiante! Sarai tu a comandare l'esplosione della bomba, che emetterà un devastante campo di crepitante energia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Atrapa a tus enemigos en un rayo con la bomba Tormenta radiante. Controlarás el momento de detonación de la bomba, haciéndola explotar en un campo devastador de energía chispeante. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ラディアントストームボムを使って雷で敵を包み込め！このボムは強力なエネルギーに満ちた壊滅的なフィールドを作り出す。爆発するタイミングをコントロールすることができる。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">복사 폭풍 폭탄으로 적을 전기로 뒤덮으십시오! 폭탄이 터질 때를 직접 조절할 수 있으며, 폭발 시 벼락이 몰아치는 파괴적인 에너지장이 펼쳐집니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Engulf your enemies in lightning with the Radiant Storm Bomb!  You control when this bomb detonates, causing it to explode into a devastating field of crackling energy. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用輻射風暴炸彈的閃電將敵人重重包圍！你可引爆炸彈，讓極具破壞力的能量一發不可收拾。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用輻射風暴炸彈的閃電將敵人重重包圍！你可引爆炸彈，讓極具破壞力的能量一發不可收拾。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Engulf your enemies in lightning with the Radiant Storm Bomb!  You control when this bomb detonates, causing it to explode into a devastating field of crackling energy. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>