<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Centipede bench</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">un banc de mille-pattes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tausendfüssler-Bank</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Panca-centopiedi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">banco de ciempiés</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A creepy crawly bench/ stool for the more adventurous, sure to get a great reaction from your friends. This unique bench with it's shiny aluminium legs and leather seat is set at a comfortable height and can be used in a variety of positions. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un banc creepy crawly / tabouret pour les plus aventureux, sûr d'obtenir une grande réaction de vos amis. Ce banc unique avec des pieds en aluminium brillant et siège en cuir est fixé à une hauteur confortable et peut être utilisé dans des positions diver. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein gruselig krabbliger Stuhl/Bank für die Abenteuerfreudigen, der garantiert positive Reaktionen von Ihren Freunden bekommt. Diese einzigartige Bank mit ihren glänzenden Aluminiumbeinen und dem Ledersitz hat eine angenehme Höhe und kann in einer Vielzahl. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una panca (o un poggiapiedi) munita di zampe pensata per i più audaci che sicuramente vorranno sorprendere i propri amici. Le zampe sono in alluminio lucido, mentre la seduta è in pelle; la sua comoda altezza dal pavimento consente svariati modi d'utilizz. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un banco espeluznantes espeluznante / heces para los más aventureros, asegúrese de obtener una gran reacción de tus amigos. Este banco único, con sus piernas brillantes de aluminio y asiento de cuero se fija a una altura cómoda y se puede utilizar en una. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>