<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dead to Rights®: Retribution GAC Scout Glasses</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lunettes d'éclaireur du GAC Dead to Rights®: Retribution</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dead to Rights®: Retribution - visore esploratore GAC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Gafas de observador del GAC de Dead to Rights®: Retribution</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">『DEAD TO RIGHTS®：RETRIBUTION』GACスカウトゴーグル</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">「Dead to Rights®: Retribution」 GAC 군용 고글(남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Dead to Rights®: Retribution GAC Scout Glasses (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「Dead to Rights®: Retribution」 GAC軍用風鏡(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「Dead to Rights®: Retribution」 GAC軍用風鏡(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dead to Rights®: Retribution GAC Scout Glasses</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The GAC Tactical Air Seal Scout Goggle is an advanced-design dual-lens goggle for Military and Law Enforcement, providing high-impact fragment protection, excellent optical performance and 100% UV protection packaged in a stylish, comfortable, lightweight design.  The frame is built from lightweight, durable alloy, moulded to fit the contours of the face, and sealed against water and dust for use in the most harsh climatic conditions.  2mm thick hard lenses are made of high impact, optical grade polycarbonate to ensure visual clarity, and coated with a matte finish for low visual profile.  The GAC Tactical Air Seal Scout Goggle comes with manual zoom option for ranged focus and extra-wide field of view, and 4 built-in low-light illuminators for use in complete darkness.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les lunettes d'éclaireur du GAC constituent un outil de pointe à double lentille destiné aux forces de l'ordre et aux militaires, offrant une protection contre tous types d'impacts, d'excellentes performances optiques et une protection UV totale, ainsi qu'une monture stylée, confortable et légère.  Le cadre est fabriqué dans un alliage léger et solide, conçu pour épouser parfaitement les contours du visage, et offrant une protection totale contre l'eau et la poussière, pour une utilisation dans les conditions météorologiques les plus difficiles.  Les verres de 2mm d'épaisseur sont en polycarbonate extrêmement résistant qui assure la netteté du champ de vision, et sont recouverts d'un fini mat pour plus de discrétion.  Les lunettes d'éclaireur du GAC sont également dotées d'une option de zoom manuel pour une mise au point à distance et un champ de vision extra-large, ainsi que 4 lampes torches intégrées pour une utilisation même en pleine nuit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il visore tattico isolante da esploratore GAC è uno strumento di stampo avanzato, per operazioni militari e civili, composto da due lenti e dotato di un'elevata protezione anti-frammentazione, con ottime prestazioni visive e una schermatura UV completa. Il tutto in un modello elegante e leggero.  La montatura è in lega leggera e durevole, plasmata per seguire i contorni del viso, e anti-acqua e anti-polvere, per resistere alle condizioni ambientali più impervie.  Le lenti anti-graffio di 2 mm sono in policarbonato ultra resistente e di qualità, per garantire un'immagine migliore, e sono ricoperte da uno strato opaco per passare inosservate.  Il visore tattico isolante da esploratore GAC è provvisto di ingrandimento manuale per regolare la focale, di un campo di visuale ampio e di quattro luci integrate e tenui da utilizzare in caso di completa oscurità.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las gafas tácticas aislantes de observador del GAC poseen lentes duales y un diseño avanzado. Empleadas por cuerpos militares y policiales, proporcionan protección contra impactos, un rendimiento óptico excelente y un bloqueo completo de los rayos UVA con un diseño cómodo, ligero y estiloso.  La montura está hecha de una aleación ligera y duradera moldeada para ajustarse a los contornos de la cara y es resistente al agua y al polvo, por lo que puede utilizarse en las condiciones climatológicas más extremas.  Las duras lentes de 2 mm están hechas de un policarbonato óptico resistente que garantiza la visibilidad, cubierto con un acabado mate para mantener un perfil de observación bajo.  Las gafas tácticas aislantes de observador del GAC incorporan un zoom manual para enfocar a distancia y ensanchar el campo visual y cuatro iluminadores de baja potencia para ver en la oscuridad.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">GAC気密式スカウトゴーグルは、高度な設計のデュアルレンズを採用した軍隊および警察向けの装備品である。飛散してくる破片への衝撃耐性と優れた視界を誇り、紫外線も100%カットする。スタイリッシュで装着感も良く、軽量な設計となっている。フレームは軽量で耐久性の高い合金製。顔の輪郭にフィットし、水やほこりを浸入させないため、厳しい天候下での使用にも耐えられる。厚さ2ミリのレンズは衝撃耐性の高い光学ポリカーボネート製で、クリアな視界を実現している。また敵による発見リスクを低下させるため、マット調の仕上げが施されている。GAC気密式スカウトゴーグルにはマニュアルズームが搭載されており、遠方に焦点を合わせたり、視界を広げることができる。また低光量照明が4灯内蔵されているため、真っ暗闇の状態でも使用することができる。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">GAC 전술 군용 고글은 두 개의 렌즈로 구성된 최첨단 디자인을 자랑합니다. 파편에 의한 강한 충격으로부터 착용자를 보호하며, 뛰어난 광학 성능과 100% 자외선 차단을 통해 군 병력과 기타 치안 요원들을 돕습니다. 경량의 편안한 착용감은 합금을 사용한 프레임에서 비롯되며, 얼굴의 윤곽에 정확히 들어 맞도록 설계되었습니다. 수분과 먼지를 차단하여 어떠한 기상 조건이나 환경에서도 제 성능을 발휘합니다. 2mm의 두꺼운 렌즈는 광학용 폴리카본으로 만들어져 시각적인 뚜렷함을 제공하며, 매트 소재로 마무리하여 외부의 빛을 거의 반사하지 않습니다. GAC 전술 군용 고글은 수동 줌 옵션과 넓은 시야각을 가지고 있습니다. 또한 네 개의 발광구를 사용하여 완전한 암흑 속에서도 시야를 확보해 줍니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The GAC Tactical Air Seal Scout Goggle is an advanced-design dual-lens goggle for Military and Law Enforcement, providing high-impact fragment protection, excellent optical performance and 100% UV protection packaged in a stylish, comfortable, lightweight design.  The frame is built from lightweight, durable alloy, moulded to fit the contours of the face, and sealed against water and dust for use in the most harsh climatic conditions.  2mm thick hard lenses are made of high impact, optical grade polycarbonate to ensure visual clarity, and coated with a matte finish for low visual profile.  The GAC Tactical Air Seal Scout Goggle comes with manual zoom option for ranged focus and extra-wide field of view, and 4 built-in low-light illuminators for use in complete darkness.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">GAC密透式偵察風鏡採用了精密的雙鏡面設計，是適合軍隊和警察使用的裝備，可以抵擋迎面飛散而來的碎片的衝擊力，確保視野不受阻礙，而且更100%防紫外線。除外觀設計有型外，風鏡的重量亦非常輕巧，確保佩戴舒服；鏡框以又輕又耐用的合金製成，緊貼臉部輪廓，不會讓水和塵埃進入，在嚴酷的天氣下亦可使用。鏡片厚度為2mm，使用可高度抵禦衝擊的光學聚碳酸酯製成，可經常保持視野清晰。此外，為了減低被敵方發現的危險，鏡面更經過磨砂處理。GAC密透式偵察風鏡搭載手動對焦機能，可以遠距離聚焦及做出超廣闊的視野；加上內置四個低光量照明，可在一片漆黑的環境下使用。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">GAC密透式偵察風鏡採用了精密的雙鏡面設計，是適合軍隊和警察使用的裝備，可以抵擋迎面飛散而來的碎片的衝擊力，確保視野不受阻礙，而且更100%防紫外線。除外觀設計有型外，風鏡的重量亦非常輕巧，確保佩戴舒服；鏡框以又輕又耐用的合金製成，緊貼臉部輪廓，不會讓水和塵埃進入，在嚴酷的天氣下亦可使用。鏡片厚度為2mm，使用可高度抵禦衝擊的光學聚碳酸酯製成，可經常保持視野清晰。此外，為了減低被敵方發現的危險，鏡面更經過磨砂處理。GAC密透式偵察風鏡搭載手動對焦機能，可以遠距離聚焦及做出超廣闊的視野；加上內置四個低光量照明，可在一片漆黑的環境下使用。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The GAC Tactical Air Seal Scout Goggle is an advanced-design dual-lens goggle for Military and Law Enforcement, providing high-impact fragment protection, excellent optical performance and 100% UV protection packaged in a stylish, comfortable, lightweight design.  The frame is built from lightweight, durable alloy, moulded to fit the contours of the face, and sealed against water and dust for use in the most harsh climatic conditions.  2mm thick hard lenses are made of high impact, optical grade polycarbonate to ensure visual clarity, and coated with a matte finish for low visual profile.  The GAC Tactical Air Seal Scout Goggle comes with manual zoom option for ranged focus and extra-wide field of view, and 4 built-in low-light illuminators for use in complete darkness.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>