<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LOOT™'s Sunset Yacht (With Home Theater)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Yacht Coucher de Soleil LOOT™ (Avec Home Cinéma)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sonnenuntergangs-Yacht (mit Heimkino) von LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sunset Yacht di LOOT™ (con Home Theater)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Puesta de sol en yate con LOOT™ (Con cine en casa)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LOOT™のサンセット・ヨット（ホーム・シアター付き）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LOOT™'s Sunset Yacht (With Home Theater)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Watch live events, videos, podcasts and exclusive content in your luxurious on-board theater while cruising along in a beautiful tropical lagoon. In addition, this upgraded Amaterasu yacht now offers the ability to set the mood of your cruise. Sunrise, sunset, day, night? It's your choice! Thrill to breathtaking views and host exclusive parties, or sit back and count the stars under the romantic moonlight. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Regardez des événements en direct, des vidéos, des podcasts, des exclusivités dans votre luxueux cinéma à bord de votre yacht, tout en naviguant dans un magnifique lagon tropical. Par ailleurs, ce yacht Amaterasu modernisé offre maintenant la possibilité de créer votre ambiance sur le bateau. Lever ou coucher de soleil, jour ou nuit ? À vous de choisir ! Admirez les vues à couper le souffle, organisez des fêtes ou reposez-vous en comptant les étoiles sous le romantique clair de lune. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schau dir Live-Events, Videos, Podcasts und exklusive Inhalte in deinem luxuriösen Heimkino an Bord an, während du durch wundervolle, tropische Lagunen schipperst. Außerdem bietet diese verbesserte Amaterasu-Yacht jetzt auch die Möglichkeit, die Tageszeit anzupassen. Sonnenaufgang, Sonnenuntergang, Tag, Nacht? Die Wahl liegt bei dir! Lass dich von atemberaubenden Ausblicken verzaubern, gib exklusive Partys oder lehn dich zurück und zähl die Sterne im romantischen Mondschein. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guarda eventi in diretta, video, podcast e contenuti esclusivi nel tuo lussuoso theater mentre navighi in una meravigliosa laguna tropicale. In questo yacht potenziato Amaterasu puoi regolare l'atmosfera del tuo viaggio: alba, tramonto, giorno, notte? Sta a te la scelta! Visuali mozzafiato faranno da cornice ai tuoi party esclusivi. In alternativa puoi sempre rilassarti alla luce della luna e ammirare il cielo stellato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Disfruta en directo de acontecimientos, vídeos, podcasts y contenidos exclusivos a través de tu lujoso cine a bordo mientras navegas por un hermoso lago tropical. Además, este yate Amaterasu mejorado te ofrece ahora la posibilidad de definir el ambiente de tu crucero. ¿Amanecer, puesta de sol, día, noche...? ¡Tú decides! Deja que la emoción te invada con estos impresionantes paisajes, y celebra fiestas exclusivas o relájate y cuenta estrella bajo la romántica luz de la luna. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステキなトロピカル・ラグーンでのクルージング中には、豪華絢爛オンボードシアターでライブイベント、ビデオ、ポッドキャスト、さらには限定コンテンツを視聴しましょう。そのうえ、アップグレード済みのアマテラス・ヨットならアナタのクルージングの雰囲気を自由につくり上げることができます。日の出、日の入り、昼夜を問わず、お望みのままに！息を呑むような景観のスリルを感じるもよし、限定パーティーを開催するもよし。ロマンティックな月あかりの下でのんびり星を数えるのもオツなものですよ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Watch live events, videos, podcasts and exclusive content in your luxurious on-board theater while cruising along in a beautiful tropical lagoon. In addition, this upgraded Amaterasu yacht now offers the ability to set the mood of your cruise. Sunrise, sunset, day, night? It's your choice! Thrill to breathtaking views and host exclusive parties, or sit back and count the stars under the romantic moonlight. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>