<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Red and White Swimsuit Set (Bikini Type, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set maillot de bain rouge et blanc (modèle bikini, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Rot-weißes Badeanzug-Set (Bikini, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set costume da bagno modello bikini (rosso e bianco, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de bañador rojo y blanco (tipo bikini, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">赤と白の水着セット（ビキニタイプ・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">Red and White Swimsuit Set (Bikini Type, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* 赤と白の水着セット（ビキニタイプ・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">Red and White Swimsuit Set (Bikini Type, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">Red and White Swimsuit Set (Bikini Type, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Red and White Swimsuit Set (Bikini Type, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Set of a big hat, bikini-type swimsuit, and short-type boots coordinated with red and white.\n
Defensive Strength: None~★\n
Sexiness: None~★★★\n
This set includes the following items:\n
\n
- Big Pom-pom Hat, Small (Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Big Pom-pom Hat, Medium (Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Big Pom-pom Hat, Large (Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Red Swimsuit with Boa (Bikini Type, Women) (Outfit)\n
- Red Boots with Boa (Short Type, Women) (Shoes)\n
\n
* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set accordé en rouge et blanc contenant un grand chapeau, un maillot de bain modèle bikini et des bottes courtes.\n
Défense : Sans~★\n
Sex-appeal : Sans~★★★\n
Ce set inclut les objets suivants :\n
\n
- Gros chapeau avec pompon, petit (femme) (Accessoire de tête)\n
- Gros chapeau avec pompon, moyen (femme) (Accessoire de tête)\n
- Gros chapeau avec pompon, grand (femme) (Accessoire de tête)\n
- Maillot de bain rouge avec boa (modèle bikini, femme) (Tenues)\n
- Bottes rouge avec boa (modèle court, femme) (Chaussures)\n
\n
* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein in rot und weiß gehaltenes Set bestehend aus einer großen Mütze, einem Bikini und kurzen Stiefeln.\n
Verteidigung: Keine~★\n
Sexappeal: Keine~★★★\n
Dieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n
\n
- Große Weihnachtsmütze mit Bommel, klein (für Frauen) (Kopfbedeckung)\n
- Große Weihnachtsmütze mit Bommel, mittelgroß (für Frauen) (Kopfbedeckung)\n
- Große Weihnachtsmütze mit Bommel, groß (für Frauen) (Kopfbedeckung)\n
- Roter Badeanzug mit Pelzrand (Bikini, für Frauen) (Kombination)\n
- Rote Stiefel mit Pelzrand (kurz, für Frauen) (Schuhe)\n
\n
* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set comprendente un cappello, un costume da bagno modello bikini e degli stivali corti, tutti coordinati in rosso e bianco.\n
Difesa: Nulla~★\n
Sensualità: Nulla~★★★\n
Nel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n
\n
- Cappello pompon, piccolo (da donna) (accessorio per la testa)\n
- Cappello pompon, medio (da donna) (accessorio per la testa)\n
- Cappello pompon, grande (da donna) (accessorio per la testa)\n
- Costume da bagno modello bikini (rosso con boa, da donna) (completo)\n
- Stivali corti (rossi con boa, da donna) (scarpe)\n
\n
* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettiva categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego con prendas rojas y blancas que incluye gorro grande, bañador tipo bikini y botas bajas.\n
Defensa: Ninguno~★\n
Sensualidad: Ninguno~★★★\n
Este juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n
\n
- Gorro grande con pompón, pequeño (mujer) (accesorio de cabeza)\n
- Gorro grande con pompón, mediano (mujer) (accesorio de cabeza)\n
- Gorro grande con pompón, grande (mujer) (accesorio de cabeza)\n
- Bañador rojo con boa (tipo bikini, mujer) (combinación)\n
- Botas rojas con boa (bajas, mujer) (zapatos)\n
\n
*Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">赤と白を基調とした大きな帽子、ビキニタイプの水着、ショートタイプのブーツのセット。\n
防御力：　（なし）～★\n
セクシー度：　（なし）～★★★\n
本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n
\n
・大きなポンポン帽・小（女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n
・大きなポンポン帽・中（女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n
・大きなポンポン帽・大（女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n
・ボアの付いた赤い水着（ビキニタイプ・女性）/組み合わせ\n
・ボアの付いた赤いブーツ（ショートタイプ・女性）/靴\n
\n
※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Set of a big hat, bikini-type swimsuit, and short-type boots coordinated with red and white.\n
Defensive Strength: None~★\n
Sexiness: None~★★★\n
This set includes the following items:\n
\n
- Big Pom-pom Hat, Small (Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Big Pom-pom Hat, Medium (Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Big Pom-pom Hat, Large (Women) (Head Accessory)\n
- Red Swimsuit with Boa (Bikini Type, Women) (Outfit)\n
- Red Boots with Boa (Short Type, Women) (Shoes)\n
\n
* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
