<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">FABULOUS Wedge Shoes - Black (for her)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">FABULOUS Talons Compensés - Noir (pour elle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">FABULOUS Plateau-Schuhe - Schwarz (für sie)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">FABULOUS Zeppe - Nero (per lei)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">FABULOUS Cuñas - Negro (para ella)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">FABULOUS Wedge Shoes - Black (for her)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">FABULOUS is our new fashion label! Go for the full colour block look or mix and match for a touch of individuality. Make an impression whatever the occasion! Look Fabulous! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">FABULOUS est notre nouvelle marque virtuelle de vêtements. Optez pour un ensemble coloré ou mélangez le tout selon vos envies pour une touche plus personnelle.  Ne passez plus jamais inaperçu, quelle que soit l’occasion !  Look fabuleux! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">FABULOUS ist unsere neue virtuelle Modemarke. Entschließen Sie sich für den vollständigen, einfarbigen Look oder mischen und stellen Sie sie für Ihren individuellen Touch zusammen.  Machen Sie Eindruck, zu jedem Anlass! Sehen fabelhaft! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">FABULOUS è il nostro marchio virtuale. Scegli un look a tinta unita o mescola i colori per un tocco più personale.  Fai sempre una buona impressione, qualunque sia l'occasione! Aspetto favoloso! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">FABULOUS es nuestra nueva firma de ropa. Elige prendas lisas o multicolores, combínalas para dar un toque de individualidad o conjúntalas. ¡Causa una buena impresión sea cual sea la ocasión! ¡Mira fabuloso! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">FABULOUS is our new fashion label! Go for the full colour block look or mix and match for a touch of individuality. Make an impression whatever the occasion! Look Fabulous! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>