<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Ocean View Dress - Coconut Shell (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Robe Ocean View - Noix de coco (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Ocean View Kleid - Kokosnuss (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Ocean View Vestito - Noce di cocco (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Ocean View Vestido - Color cáscara de coco (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our Sisters Of The Sun collection is a celebration of fashions that play up your natural beauty with their boho-chic vibe and warrior spirit. Alive with earthy colours and energy, each style easily transitions from days of soaking up the sun to nights spent dancing in the moonlight. This bustier style sundress brings you endless compliments with its sweetheart neckline and vivid aloha print. Special details include 5 pockets, smocking at back for a no-slip fit, and removable straps. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Notre collection Sisters Of The Sun fête la mode qui met en valeur votre beauté naturelle, avec un style chic et bohème tout en gardant un esprit guerrier. Avec ses couleurs ocrées et son énergie, chaque style s'adapte aux différents moments de la journée, du lever du soleil aux soirées au clair de lune. Cette robe avec bustier vous vaudra de nombreux compliments avec son encolure élégante et son imprimé de style hawaïen. Avec 5 poches, des smocks à l'arrière pour une tenue irréprochable et des bretelles amovibles. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unsere Sisters Of The Sun Kollektion akzentuiert Ihre natürliche Schönheit mit modischen Kreationen und einer Verschmelzung von Folklore-Chic und Kampfgeist. Der Stil in lebhaften Naturtönen und durchwachsen mit der Energie der Erde passt sich nahtlos an alle Anforderungen des Tages an - vom Sonnenbaden am Strand bis hin zum Tanzen im Mondschein. Dieses Sommerkleid für vollbusigere Damen sorgt mit seinem attraktiven Herzausschnitt und lebhaften Hawaiifarben für viele Komplimente. Zu besonderen Details zählen die fünf Taschen, das Smocking auf dem Rücken für einen perfekten Sitz und die abnehmbaren Träger. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La nostra collezione Sisters Of The Sun celebra la moda che mette in risalto la bellezza naturale grazie a uno stile boho-chic unito allo spirito guerriero. Pieno di energia e caratterizzato dai colori della natura, ogni stile passa elegantemente dalle giornate passate a prendere il sole alle notti trascorse a ballare sotto le stelle.  Questo vestito in stile bustier ti farà ricevere complimenti infiniti grazie alla scollatura a cuore e alla vivace stampa tropicale. Tra i dettagli speciali ci sono 5 tasche, arricciatura sulla schiena per la massima vestibilità e bretelle rimovibili. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nuestra colección Sisters Of The Sun es una exaltación de esa tendencia que realza tu belleza natural, con su toque bohemio-chic y su espíritu guerrero. De gran viveza gracias a sus colores terrosos y su energía, cada estilo se adapta con sencillez para pasar de un día de bronceado al sol a una noche bailando a la luz de la luna. Este vestido de verano tipo corpiño te llenará de piropos con su escote corazón y su vivaz estampado "aloha". Entre los detalles especiales se cuentan 5 bolsillos, frunce en espalda para un mejor ajuste y tirantes extraíbles. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Our Sisters Of The Sun collection is a celebration of fashions that play up your natural beauty with their boho-chic vibe and warrior spirit. Alive with earthy colors and energy, each style easily transitions from days of soaking up the sun to nights spent dancing in the moonlight. This bustier style sundress brings you endless compliments with its sweetheart neckline and vivid aloha print. Special details include 5 pockets, smocking at back for a no-slip fit, and removable straps. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>