<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Homing Spider Droid Prop</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Droïde araignée traqueur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spürspinnendroiden-Requisit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Oggetto Droide Ragno Autoguidato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Droide araña rastreador</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Homing Spider Droid Prop</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The vast, rock-laden deserts of Ryloth seem hostile to almost all forms of life. Life, as we know it, seems to only come to this land to die. Not true for the droid army, who look at the landscape with what I can only assume is a incredibly reflective smile. The terrain is nothing for their kind - they simply adapt and bring the only type of creature that would have an advantage in such a place - the Homing Spider Droid. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les vastes déserts rocheux de Ryloth semblent hostiles à pratiquement toutes les formes de vie. La vie, telle que nous la connaissons, ne semble venir dans ce pays que pour y mourir. Mais pas l'armée des droïdes, laquelle contemplait le paysage avec ce que je ne pouvais considérer que comme un sourire pensif. Le terrain ne signifie rien, pour eux, ils s'y adaptent simplement et font intervenir le seul type de créatures qui peut tirer parti d'un tel endroit : le droïde araignée traqueur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In den riesigen, steinigen Wüsten von Ryloth scheint kein Lebewesen wirklich gedeihen zu können. Leben, wie wir es kennen, kommt hier nur hin, um zu sterben. Aber nicht die Armee der Droiden, die, so stelle ich mir vor, über eine solche Zurückhaltung nur lachen kann. Ihnen ist das Terrain nicht wichtig: Sie passen sich einfach an und bringen die einzige Kreatur, die an einem solchen Ort einen Vorteil haben könnte - den Spürspinnendroiden. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le vaste e rocciose distese desertiche di Ryloth sembrerebbero ostili a qualsiasi forma di vita. Parrebbe che la vita che noi conosciamo possa venire in questi luoghi solo per morire. Ma non è cosi per l'armata dei droidi, che osservano questo paesaggio con quello che presumo essere un sorriso incredibilmente riflessivo. Il terreno non è nulla di che per quelli come loro - essi non fanno altro che trasformarsi nell'unico tipo di creatura che può ricevere un vantaggio da questo genere di luogo - il Droide Ragno Autoguidato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los vastos desiertos plagados de rocas de Ryloth parecen hostiles para casi todas las formas de vida. La vida, tal y como la conocemos, parece venir a estas tierras solo a morir. Eso no es así para el ejército droide, que observa el paisaje con lo que asumo no es más que una increíble mirada contemplativa. El terreno no es nada para los suyos, ellos se adaptan con facilidad y traen a las únicas criaturas que tendrían ventaja en un lugar así: los droides araña rastreadores. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The vast, rock-laden deserts of Ryloth seem hostile to almost all forms of life. Life, as we know it, seems to only come to this land to die. Not true for the droid army, who look at the landscape with what I can only assume is a incredibly reflective smile. The terrain is nothing for their kind - they simply adapt and bring the only type of creature that would have an advantage in such a place - the Homing Spider Droid. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>