<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Force Unleashed Poster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Poster du Pouvoir de la Force</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">The Force Unleashed-Poster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Poster de Il Potere della Forza</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Póster de El Poder de la Fuerza</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Force Unleashed Poster</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Between two great tales of our time, known as Episode III and Episode IV, there is a dark space. The story during this period had, for years, been left bare. Scholars spent years filling in small gaps, uncertain as to the exact happenings. How lucky that these scholars were able to unearth the period between war and redemption. Between death and rebirth. Between father and son. The years that the Force became Unleashed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Entre deux grands récits de notre temps, à savoir l'épisode III et l'épisode IV, il y a un espace obscur. L'histoire comprise dans cette période a été ignorée pendant des années. Des chercheurs ont passé des années à combler de petits intervalles, peu certains de ce qui s'était vraiment passé. Heureusement, ces chercheurs ont pu mettre à jour la période comprise entre la guerre et la rédemption. Entre la mort et la renaissance. Entre le père et le fils. Ces années où la Force a affirmé son pouvoir. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zwischen den beiden großen Geschichten unserer Zeit, bekannt als Episode III und Episode IV, gibt es eine dunkle Leere. Die Geschichte dieser Zeit wurde jahrelang ausgelassen. Gelehrte verbrachten Jahre damit, kleine Lücken auszufüllen, obwohl genaue Vorkommnisse ungewiss waren. Zum Glück konnten diese Gelehrten den Zeitraum zwischen Krieg und Erlösung enthüllen. Zwischen Tod und Geburt. Zwischen Vater und Sohn. Die Jahre, in denen die Macht freigesetzt wurde. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tra due grandi storie del nostro tempo, note come Episodio III ed Episodio IV, c'è uno spazio oscuro. Per anni, la cronaca di questo periodo è rimasta spoglia. Gli studiosi hanno speso anni nel tentativo di riempire questo spazio, ma rimanendo incerti sugli avvenimenti precisi. Per fortuna, questi studiosi sono riusciti a dissotterrare il periodo tra la guerra e la redenzione. Tra la morte e la rinascita. Tra padre e figlio. Gli anni in cui si è scatenato il Potere della Forza. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las dos grandes historias de nuestra era, conocidas como Episodio III y Episodio IV, comprenden un oscuro periodo entremedias. La historia de dicho tiempo había permanecido oculta durante años. Los eruditos dedicaron años a completar pequeñas lagunas, sin saber con certeza los sucesos exactos. Por suerte, dichos eruditos lograron desenterrar dicho periodo entre la guerra y la redención. Entre la muerte y el renacimiento. Entre el padre y el hijo. Los años del Poder de la Fuerza. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Between two great tales of our time, known as Episode III and Episode IV, there is a dark space. The story during this period had, for years, been left bare. Scholars spent years filling in small gaps, uncertain as to the exact happenings. How lucky that these scholars were able to unearth the period between war and redemption. Between death and rebirth. Between father and son. The years that the Force became Unleashed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>