<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Frozen Peak Palace Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack de meubles du Palais des cimes gelées</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Frostgipfelpalast: Möbelset</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto arredamento Palazzo glaciale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de muebles palacio invernal del pico helado</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">フローズンパレス家具セット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">얼어붙은 봉우리의 궁전 가구 번들</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Frozen Peak Palace Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">冰頂峰皇宮家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">冰頂峰皇宮家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Frozen Peak Palace Furniture Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fill your frosty Frozen Peak Palace with some chilly furniture items of its own. Bundle includes a bed, rug, couch, and table. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Décorez votre Palais des cimes gelées avec des meubles de glace. Le pack comprend un lit, un tapis, un canapé et une table. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Richte dich mit eisigen Möbelstücken ein in deinem Frostgipfelpalast. Das Set enthält ein Bett, einen Teppich, eine Couch und einen Tisch. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Riempi il tuo gelido Palazzo glaciale con appositi articoli di arredamento. Il pacchetto include letto, tappeto, divano e tavolo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Amuebla tu palacio invernal del pico helado con un refrescante mobiliario a juego. El conjunto incluye cama, manta, sofá y mesa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">フローズンパレスにぴったりなひんやりとした家具のセットです。\n\n本セットには以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n・「テーブル（フローズンパレス）」（テーブル）\n・「ラグ（フローズンパレス）」（ラグ）\n・「カウチ（フローズンパレス）」（ソファー）\n・「ベッド（フローズンパレス）」（アドバンスド家具）\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。\n\n※本セットには、アニメーションや機能が追加されているアドバンスド家具が含まれています。この種類のアイテムは配置できる数に制限があります。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">서리로 가득 찬 얼어붙은 봉우리의 궁전을 차가운 분위기의 가구로 채우십시오. 이 번들은 얼다음 아이템을 포함합니다.\n\n

●얼어붙은 봉우리의 궁전 침대\n
●얼어붙은 봉우리의 궁전양탄자\n
●얼어붙은 봉우리의 궁전소파\n
●얼어붙은 봉우리의 궁전탁자\n\n

* 구매 후 각 아이템은 해당 카테고리에 추가됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Fill your frosty Frozen Peak Palace with some chilly furniture items of its own.\n
This bundle includes the following items.\n\n

・Frozen Peak Palace Bed\n
・Frozen Peak Palace Rug\n
・Frozen Peak Palace Couch\n
・Frozen Peak Palace Table\n\n

*When purchased, each item is added to its respective category.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在您的冰頂峰皇宮內擺滿冰凍的家具。\n
本組合包包括以下道具：\n\n

●冰頂峰皇宮床\n
●冰頂峰皇宮小地毯\n
●冰頂峰皇宮長沙發\n
●冰頂峰皇宮桌子\n\n

※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別內。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在您的冰頂峰皇宮內擺滿冰凍的家具。\n
本組合包包括以下道具：\n\n

●冰頂峰皇宮床\n
●冰頂峰皇宮小地毯\n
●冰頂峰皇宮長沙發\n
●冰頂峰皇宮桌子\n\n

※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別內。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fill your frosty Frozen Peak Palace with some chilly furniture items of its own. Bundle includes a bed, rug, couch, and table. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>