<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mutt Williams Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble costume Mutt Williams</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mutt Williams-Outfit-Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Costume Mutt Williams Pacchetto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de Mutt Williams</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mutt Williams Costume Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">(Bundle) Once again the diner was in turmoil - a few greasers felt they had a right to the table they were at - one of the college guys felt otherwise, and here I was stuck in the middle of it all. I knew the cops would be here soon, and even though I hadn't gotten involved in the small-scale war that was taking place, I knew they'd bust me regardless. After all, I picked my side when I purchased the Mutt Williams avatar outfit. At least it looks like it'll be a good brawl. Includes the Mutt Williams Costume and Hair. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">(Ensemble) Une fois de plus le restaurant était en pleine agitation. Quelques ploucs pensaient avoir le droit d'être assis à leur table mais l'un des étudiants pensait le contraire, et moi je me retrouvais au milieu de tout ça. Je savais que les flics seraient là bientôt, et même si je n'étais pas mêlé à cette guéguerre, je savais qu'ils me coffreraient quand même. Après tout, j'ai choisi mon camp quand j'ai acheté la tenue de Mutt Williams. Au moins, il va y avoir une bonne bagarre. Comprend le costume et les cheveux de Mutt Williams. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">(Pack) Im Restaurant ging es wieder mal drunter und drüber. Ein paar Typen mit zu viel Haargel glaubten, ein Anrecht auf ihren Tisch zu haben. Einer der College-Jungs sah das anders, und ich saß mittendrin. Ich wusste, dass die Polizei bald da sein würde und dass sie mich festnehmen würden, auch wenn ich an dem Kleinkrieg nicht beteiligt war. Als ich mein Mutt-Williams-Avatar-Outfit gekauft habe, hab ich mich schließlich für eine Seite entschieden. Zumindest sieht's nach einer netten Schlägerei aus. Beinhaltet das Mutt-Williams-Kostüm und Haar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">(Pacchetto) Ancora una volta il locale era in subbuglio - un paio di bulli pensavano che quel tavolo gli spettasse di diritto - uno degli universitari la pensava diversamente, e così io mi trovai in mezzo. Sapevo che gli sbirri sarebbero arrivati presto, e anche se non ero coinvolto nella piccola guerra che era scoppiata, sapevo che mi avrebbero arrestato a prescindere. Dopotutto, ho scelto da che parte stare quando ho acquistato il completo avatar di Mutt Williams. Almeno pare che sarà una bella rissa. Include Costume e Capelli da Mutt Williams. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">(Conjunto) De nuevo fue una cena movidita… Unos trabajadores se pensaban que tenían derecho sobre la mesa en la que estaban sentados, pero uno de los universitarios no opinaba lo mismo, y yo me vi metido en medio de todo. Sabía que la Policía no tardaría en llegar. Y aunque yo no había tenido nada que ver, seguro que me pillaban a mí también. Bueno, después de todo ya me posicioné cuando me compré el traje de Mutt Williams. Al menos parece que será una buena pelea. Incluye el traje y el pelo de Mutt Williams. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">(Bundle) Once again the diner was in turmoil - a few greasers felt they had a right to the table they were at - one of the college guys felt otherwise, and here I was stuck in the middle of it all. I knew the cops would be here soon, and even though I hadn't gotten involved in the small-scale war that was taking place, I knew they'd bust me regardless. After all, I picked my side when I purchased the Mutt Williams avatar outfit. At least it looks like it'll be a good brawl. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>