<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Omnislayer Bundle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack omnitueur (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Omni-Töter - Paket (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completo distruttore (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de machacatodo (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">옴니슬레이어 세트 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Omnislayer Bundle (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">機械殺手服裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">機械殺手服裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Omnislayer Bundle (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Save the world from robots of the future in this mechanical outfit. Bundle includes helmet, top, bottom, boots, and gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sauvez le monde des robots du futur dans cette tenue mécanique. Le pack contient un casque, un haut et un bas de vêtement, des bottes et des gants. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In diesem mechanischen Outfit kann die Welt vor Robotern aus der Zukunft gerettet werden. Zum Paket gehören Helm, Oberteil, Unterteil, Stiefel und Handschuhe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Salva il mondo dai robot del futuro con questo costume meccanico. Il completo include elmo, parte superiore e inferiore, stivali e guanti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salva al mundo de los robots del futuro con este traje mecánico. El conjunto comprende casco, torso, perneras, guantes y botas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">기계화 갑옷을 입고 미래의 로봇으로부터 세계를 구하십시오. 이 세트에는 옴니슬레이어 헬멧, 옴니슬레이어 상의, 옴니슬레이어 하의, 옴니슬레이어 부츠, 그리고 옴니슬레이어 장갑이 포함됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Save the world from robots of the future in this mechanical outfit. Bundle includes the Omnislayer Helmet, Omnislayer Top, Omnislayer Bottom, Omnislayer Boots, and Omnislayer Gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">穿上這套機械套裝，從未來的機械人手裡拯救世界。服裝組包括機械殺手頭盔、機械殺手服裝-上身、機械殺手服裝-下身、機械殺手靴及機械殺手手套。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">穿上這套機械套裝，從未來的機械人手裡拯救世界。服裝組包括機械殺手頭盔、機械殺手服裝-上半身、機械殺手服裝-下半身、機械殺手靴及機械殺手手套。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Save the world from robots of the future in this mechanical outfit. Bundle includes helmet, top, bottom, boots, and gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>