<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Drey Relaxed Blue Cotton Shirt with Inner Vest</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chemise en Coton Assoupli Drey Bleue avec Veste Intérieure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blaues Drey Baumwollhemd mit Unterhemd</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Camicia blu di cotone semplice con canottiera Drey</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camisa azul relajada de algodón con camiseta interior de Drey</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">【Drey】インナー付きコットンシャツ　ブルー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"드레이" 릴랙스한 스타일의 청색 면 셔츠 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Drey Relaxed Blue Cotton Shirt with Inner Vest (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Drey休閒藍色棉上衣背心 （男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Drey休閒藍色棉上衣背心 （男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Drey Relaxed Blue Cotton Shirt with Inner Vest</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Show your relaxed side with this laid back shirt. The standing collar and vest add a modern edge, while the iconic golden button and logo tab create a sleek, stylish finish.\n\n Fabric: Relaxed cotton\n Care: Machine washable\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Affichez votre coté relax avec cette chemise décontractée. Le col montant et la veste contribuent à son aspect moderne tandis que les logo et bouton d'or emblématiques ajoutent classe et style à l'ensemble. Tissu : Coton Assoupli\n Entretien : Lavable en machine\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeig dich mit diesem lässigen Hemd von deiner entspannten Seite. Der Stehkragen und das Unterhemd verleihen der Kombination etwas Modernes, während der ikonische Goldknopf für einen coolen Chic sorgt.\n\n Stoff: Baumwolle\n Pflege: Waschmaschinenfest\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mostra il tuo lato più rilassato con questa camicia molto semplice. Il colletto rigido e la canottiera aggiungono un tocco moderno, mentre l'iconico bottone dorato e la targhetta con il logo sono due particolari alla moda.\n\n Tessuto: morbido cotone\n Istruzioni per il lavaggio: lavabile in lavatrice \n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Muestra el lado relajado de tu personalidad con esta tranquila camisa. El cuello y la camiseta le agregan un toque moderno, mientras que el emblemático botón dorado y el logotipo le dan un elegante acabado.\n\n Tela: algodón blando\n Cuidados: lavado a máquina\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">あなたのリラックスした一面をこれで表現しましょう。シャキッとした襟とヴェストがモダンさを、金のボタンとロゴがさらに日常の中にエレガントさを加えます。\n\n 素材：コットン\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 편안한 스타일의 셔츠로 당신의 느긋한 면을 보여 주세요. 세운 깃과 조끼가 옷에 모던함을 주고 있고, 산뜻한 황금색 단추와 로고 탭이 매끈하면서도 스타일 있는 마무리를 가능하게 합니다. .\n\n 직물: 편한 면제품\n 세탁: 세탁기 사용 가능\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Show your relaxed side with this laid back shirt. The standing collar and vest add a modern edge, while the iconic golden button and logo tab create a sleek, stylish finish.\n\n Fabric: Relaxed cotton\n Care: Machine washable\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這件休閒上衣，秀出你悠閒的一面。立領和背心增添現代風格，傳統的金鈕釦和金屬材質標誌，創造洗鍊、高雅的風格。\n\n 布料：休閒棉料\n 保養：可用洗衣機洗\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這件休閒上衣，秀出你悠閒的一面。立領和背心增添現代風格，傳統的金鈕釦和金屬材質標誌，創造洗鍊、高雅的風格。\n\n 布料：休閒棉料\n 保養：可用洗衣機洗\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Show your relaxed side with this laid back shirt. The standing collar and vest add a modern edge, while the iconic golden button and logo tab create a sleek, stylish finish.\n\n Fabric: Relaxed cotton\n Care: Machine washable\n [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>