<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Nis_Dots_No026</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Personnage 2D: Geoffrey</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドットオブジェ　紳士・執事好きのための…　じいや</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">도트 오브제 신사, 집사를 좋아하는 이들을 위한… 할아범</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Geoffrey: Old Gentleman" Sprite Statue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">像素雕像 給喜愛紳士與管家的玩家之GEOFFREY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">像素雕像 給喜愛紳士與管家的玩家之GEOFFREY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">2D Character Objects: Geoffrey</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nis_dot_No026</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Untitled</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La statuette d'un personnage que tu peux mettre dans ta chambre pour décorer.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「こんなこともあろうかと」紳士好き・執事好きのお客様のためにこちらのドットオブジェをご用意しておきました。年齢は不詳、ヒゲは間違いなく毎日ホットカーラー仕上げ。邪悪なココロの育成者”じいや”。純粋な悪のココロを見出しましたら、闇よりお仕えいたします。予知能力者の如き用意周到さではございますが、往々にして準備そのものが失敗である場合がございますので、何卒ココロよりのご信用を召されぬよう…。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">「이런 일이 생길 줄 알았어」 신사, 집사를 좋아하는 유저를 위해 이 도트 오브제를 준비했습니다. 나이는 불확실, 수염은 틀림없이 매일 곱슬곱슬하게 손질. 사악한 마음의 육성자 "할아범". 그가 당신에게서 순수한 악의 마음을 발견하면 그는 당신의 충신이 될 것입니다. 예지 능력자와 같은 용의주도함도 있습니다만 때때로 준비 그 자체가 실패일 때도 있기 때문에, 아무쪼록 마음 깊이 신용하지 않도록… .[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"I thought this might happen."This Sprite Statue is for all the guests who are especially fond of gentlemen and butlers. If he finds that you have a purely evil heart, he'll be your loyal servant. Geoffrey's age is unknown, and he curls his beard on a daily basis. As if psychic, Geoffrey is always fully prepared, but often his preparations fail. So don't trust him by any means. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這是為了喜愛紳士與管家的您所準備的像素雕像。Geoffrey，年齡不詳，毎日一絲不苟的用電熱捲髮器來整理鬍子，是邪惡之心的培訓者。一旦發現有人具備純粹邪惡之心的話，就會從黑暗世界前來侍奉。如預知能力者般事事準備周到，但往往他的準備還是失敗，還請不要衷心信賴他…[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這是為了喜愛紳士與管家的您所準備的像素雕像。Geoffrey，年齡不詳，毎日一絲不苟的用電熱捲髮器來整理鬍子，是邪惡之心的培訓者。一旦發現有人具備純粹邪惡之心的話，就會從黑暗世界前來侍奉。如預知能力者般事事準備周到，但往往他的準備還是失敗，還請不要衷心信賴他…[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A small character statue that you can place to decorate your own room.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>