<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Mini-skirt &amp; Socks 7-piece Set (Gray Checked, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set 7 pièces Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes (grise à carreaux, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Minirock &amp; Socken 7-teiliges Set (graukariert, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set 7 minigonne (a scacchi grigi, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de siete artículos de minifalda y calcetines (gris a cuadros, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ミニスカート＆ソックス７点セット（グレーチェック・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Mini-skirt &amp; Socks 7-piece Set (Gray Checked, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">7-piece set of checked grey mini skirts with different socks. No socks, 5 types of red socks (ankle, crew, knee, over-the-knee, thigh), and black tights. \nDefensive Strength: ★\nYouth Level: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Mini-skirt &amp; No Socks (Gray Checked, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Ankle Socks (Gray Checked &amp; Red, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Crew Socks (Gray Checked &amp; Red, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Knee Socks (Gray Checked &amp; Red, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Over-the-Knee Socks (Gray Checked &amp; Red, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Thigh High Socks (Gray Checked &amp; Red, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Tights (Gray Checked &amp; Black, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set 7 pièces de mini-jupes à carreaux grises avec différentes chaussettes. Sans chaussettes, et 5 types de chaussettes rouges (socquettes, chaussettes de sport, sous le genou, au-dessus du genou, aux cuisses) et des collants noirs. \nDéfense : ★\nNiveau de Jeunesse : ★★★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Mini-jupe Sans Chaussettes (grise à carreaux, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Socquettes (grise à carreaux &amp; rouges, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes de Sport (grise à carreaux &amp; rouges, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes sous le Genou (grise à carreaux &amp; rouges, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes au-dessus du Genou (grise à carreaux &amp; rouges, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes aux Cuisses (grise à carreaux &amp; rouges, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Collants (grise à carreaux &amp; noirs, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">7-teiliges Set eines graukarierten Minirocks ohne Socken und mit 5 verschiedenen Typen roter Socken (Söckchen, Waden, Knie, Overknee, Schenkel) und schwarzen Strumpfhosen. \nVerteidigung: ★\nJugendlichkeitslevel: ★★★\nDas Set beinhaltet die folgenden Kleidungsstücke:\n\n- Minirock ohne Socken (graukariert, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe) \n- Minirock &amp; Söckchen (graukariert &amp; rot, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe) \n- Minirock &amp; Wadensocken ( graukariert &amp; rot, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Minirock &amp; Kniestrümpfe ( graukariert &amp; rot, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Minirock &amp; Overknees ( graukariert &amp; rot, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Minirock &amp; Schenkelstrümpfe ( graukariert &amp; rot, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Minirock &amp; Strumpfhosen (graukariert &amp; schwarz, für Frauen) Unterteil, Schuhe)\n \n- Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set composto da 7 minigonne decorate con una trama a scacchi grigia accoppiate con 5 tipi di calzini rossi (alla caviglia, calzettoni, sotto le ginocchia, sopra le ginocchia, collant) e calze nere.\nDifesa: ★\nLivello giovinezza: ★★★\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Minigonna (a scacchi grigi, senza calzini, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi grigi con calzini alla caviglia rossi, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi grigi con calzettoni rossi, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi grigi con calzini sotto le ginocchia rossi, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi grigi con calzini sopra le ginocchia rossi, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi grigi con collant rossi, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de siete artículos con minifalda a cuadros grises con diferentes calcetines. Sin calcetines, cinco tipos de calcetines rojos (cortos, de deporte, a la altura de la rodilla, por encima de la rodilla y a la altura del muslo), y leotardos negros. \nDefensa: ★\nNivel de juventud: ★★★\nEste conjunto incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Minifalda y sin calcetines (gris a cuadros, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines cortos (gris a cuadros y rojo, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines de deporte (gris a cuadros y rojo, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines hasta la rodilla (gris a cuadros y rojo, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines por encima de la rodilla (gris a cuadros y rojo, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines hasta el muslo (gris a cuadros y rojo, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y leotardos (gris a cuadros y negros, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n\n*Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">グレーチェック柄のミニスカートの、足元違い７点セット。素足、赤ソックス５種（足首丈、スネ丈、膝下丈、膝上丈、太もも丈）、黒タイツ。\n防御力：　★\n青春度：　★★★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・ミニスカートと素足（グレーチェック・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n・ミニスカートとアンクルソックス（グレーチェック＆赤・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n・ミニスカートとクルーソックス（グレーチェック＆赤・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n・ミニスカートとハイソックス（グレーチェック＆赤・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n・ミニスカートとオーバーニーソックス（グレーチェック＆赤・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n・ミニスカートとサイハイソックス（グレーチェック＆赤・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n・ミニスカートとタイツ（グレーチェック＆黒・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">7-piece set of checked gray mini skirts with different socks. No socks, 5 types of red socks (ankle, crew, knee, over-the-knee, thigh), and black tights. \nDefensive Strength: ★\nYouth Level: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Mini-skirt &amp; No Socks (Gray Checked, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Ankle Socks (Gray Checked &amp; Red, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Crew Socks (Gray Checked &amp; Red, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Knee Socks (Gray Checked &amp; Red, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Over-the-Knee Socks (Gray Checked &amp; Red, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Thigh High Socks (Gray Checked &amp; Red, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Tights (Gray Checked &amp; Black, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category. [#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
