<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Star Trek™ TNG Starfleet operations officer costume (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Uniforme d'officier aux opérations de Starfleet dans Star Trek™ : La Nouvelle Génération (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Star Trek™ TNG Kostüm eines Sicherheitsoffiziers der Sternenflotte (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Star Trek™ TNG - Costume da ufficiale operativo della Flotta stellare (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Uniforme de Oficial de Operaciones de la Flota Estelar de Star Trek™ TNG (Mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Star Trek™ TNG Starfleet operations officer costume (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hey Trekkies, Star Trek™ has come to PlayStation®Home! You can now get yourself the official Star Trek™: The Next Generation Starfleet  operations officer costume. \n\nTM &amp; © 2013 CBS Studios Inc. Star Trek™ and all related marks and logos are trademarks of CBS Studios Inc. All Rights Reserved.\n\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avis à tous les Trekkers : Star Trek™ est arrivé sur PlayStation®Home ! Vous pouvez désormais vous offrir l'uniforme officiel d'officier aux opérations de Starfleet dans Star Trek™ : La Nouvelle Génération. \n\nTM &amp; © 2013 CBS Studios Inc. Star Trek™ et toutes les marques et logos associés sont des marques de CBS Studios Inc. Tous droits réservés.\n\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hallo Trekkies, Star Trek™ ist auf PlayStation®Home gelandet! Jetzt könnt ihr euch das offizielle Kostüm eines Sicherheitsoffiziers der Sternenflotte aus Star Trek™: Das nächste Jahrhundert besorgen.  \n\nTM &amp; © 2013 CBS Studios Inc. Star Trek™ sowie alle zugehörigen Marken und Logos sind Marken von CBS Studios Inc. Alle Rechte vorbehalten.\n\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ehi, Trekkie: Star Trek™ è arrivato su PlayStation®Home! Ora potrete indossare anche voi il costume da ufficiale operativo della Flotta stellare di Star Trek™: The Next Generation. \n\nTM &amp; © 2013 CBS Studios Inc. Star Trek™ e tutti i marchi e loghi collegati sono marchi di CBS Studios Inc. Tutti i diritti riservati.\n\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hola, Trekkies, ¡Star Trek™ llega a PlayStation®Home! Ahora puedes conseguir el uniforme oficial de Oficial de Operaciones de la Flota Estelar de la Federación de Star Trek™: La Nueva Generación.\n\nTM &amp; © 2013 CBS Studios Inc. Star Trek™ y todas las marcas y logos relacionados son marcas registradas de CBS Studios Inc. Todos los derechos reservados.\n\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hey Trekkies, Star Trek™ has come to PlayStation®Home! You can now get yourself the official Star Trek™: The Next Generation Starfleet  operations officer costume. \n\nTM &amp; © 2013 CBS Studios Inc. Star Trek™ and all related marks and logos are trademarks of CBS Studios Inc. All Rights Reserved.\n\n[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>