<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - New Order Camo Shorts - Cinnamon Red (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Short New Order Camo - Rouge cannelle (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - New Order Camo Shorts - Zimtbraun (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - New Order Camo Shorts - Rosso cannella (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - New Order Camo Pantalón corto - Rojo canela (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fight the good fight in the New Order camo print walkshort. It offers everything you look for in a well designed work wear styled chino. Detailed with a woven Billabong label above back pocket and embroidery at front pocket. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Choisissez le bon combat avec ce short de randonnée New Order avec imprimé camouflage. Il offre tout ce dont vous rêvez pour un chino au style fonctionnel bien conçu. Agrémenté d'un logo Billabong tissé au-dessus de la poche arrière et d'une broderie sur la poche avant. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kämpfen Sie den guten Kampf in dieser New Order Wandershorts in Tarnfarbe. Die Shorts hat alles, was Sie von einer optimal durchdachten Aktivshorts im Chinostil erwarten. Mit gewebtem Billabong-Etikett über der Gesäßtasche und Stickverzierungen an den Vordertaschen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Combatti per una buona causa con questi shorts New Order con stampa mimetica. Offrono tutto quello che cerchi in un paio di pantaloni da lavoro in stile chino. Presentano l'etichetta Billabong in tessuto sulla tasca posteriore e un ricamo sulla tasca frontale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Combate por una buena causa con este pantalón corto New Order con estampado de camuflaje. Ofrece todo lo que buscas en unos chinos de correcto diseño y estilo "pantalón de carga". Con detalle de etiqueta Billabong cosida sobre el bolsillo trasero y bordado en  bolsillo delantero. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>