<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tribus Papilio Tattoos [Female]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tatouages Tribus papilio [femme]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tribus Papilio-Tattoos [Weiblich]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tatuaggi Tribus Papilio [femminili]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tatuajes Tribus Papilio [mujer]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_49</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_49</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Tribus Papilio Tattoos [Female]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_49</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_49</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Tribus Papilio Tattoos [Female]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">What girl doesn't love butterflies and ink? Grab this bundle of female only tattoos! Includes: Obsidian Tribus Papilio Forearm and Calf Tattoos[F], Obsidian Tribus Papilio Lower Back Tattoo [F], Ivory Tribus Papilio Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F] and IvoryTribus Papilio Lower Back Tattoo [F].

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Y a-t-il une fille qui n’aime pas l’encre et les papillons ? Prenez cet ensemble de tatouages réservés aux femmes ! Comprend: Tatouages Tribus papilio Obsidienne pour avant-bras et mollet [femme], Tatouages Tribus papilio Obsidienne bas du dos et mollet [femme], Tatouages Tribus papilio Ivoire pour avant-bras et mollet [femme], et Tatouages Tribus papilio Ivoire bas du dos et mollet [femme].

Remarque : Tous les tatouages pour torse ou jambe ne sont pas égaux. Lors de l’achat de cet accessoire de tatouage, il est possible qu’il ne soit pas adapté à tous les habits. N’hésitez pas à prendre notre article gratuit « Torse nu » pour homme ou femme afin d’afficher correctement votre nouveau tatouage ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Welches Mädchen mag nicht Schmetterlinge und Tätowierungen? Hol dir dieses Paket mit ausschließlich weiblichen Tattoos! Es beinhaltet: Obsidian Tribus Papilio-Tattoos für Unterarm und Wade [Weiblich], Obsidian Tribus Papilio-Tattoos für den unteren Rücken und Wade [Weiblich], Ivory Tribus Papilio-Tattoos für Unterarm und Wade [Weiblich], und Ivory Tribus Papilio-Tattoos für den unteren Rücken und Wade [Weiblich].

Hinweis: Nicht alle Gegenstände für Oberkörper oder Beine sind gleich gestaltet. Wenn du dieses Tattoo-Zubehör kaufst, könnte es nicht mit allen Kleidungsstücken harmonieren. Gerne kannst du dir unseren kostenlosen “blanken” Oberkörper für Männer/Frauen holen, um deine neuen Tattoos angemessen zeigen zu können![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">A quale ragazza non piacerebbe farsi tatuare una farfalla? Afferra questo pacchetto di tatuaggi femminili che include: Tatuaggi Tribus Papilio nero ossidiana per avambraccio e polpaccio [femminili], Tatuaggi Tribus Papilio nero ossidiana avorio per la parte inferiore della schiena e polpaccio [femminili], Tatuaggi Tribus Papilio bianco per avambraccio e polpaccio [femminili], e Tatuaggi Tribus Papilio bianco avorio per la parte inferiore della schiena e polpaccio [femminili].

Nota: non tutti gli oggetti per torso o gamba sono creati allo stesso modo. Il tatuaggio che ti appresti ad acquistare potrebbe non andare bene su tutti gli articoli di abbigliamento. A questo scopo non esitare a scaricare gratuitamente l'oggetto unisex "Tela nuda" torso per visualizzare correttamente i tuoi nuovi tatuaggi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿A qué chica no le gustan los tatuajes y las mariposas? ¡Hazte con este conjunto de tatuajes solo para chicas! Incluye: Tatuaje Tribus Papilio obsidiana antebrazo y pantorrilla [mujer], Tatuajes Tribus Papilio obsidiana parte baja de la espalda y pantorrilla [mujer], Tatuaje Tribus Papilio marfil antebrazo y pantorrilla [mujer], y Tatuajes Tribus Papilio marfil parte baja de la espalda y pantorrilla [mujer].

Nota: no todos los objetos para torso y piernas se crean por igual. Cuando compres este accesorio para un tatuaje, quizá no quede bien con cualquier prenda de ropa. ¡Elige nuestro "Lienzo en blanco" de regalo para hombre o mujer y así podrás lucir tu nuevo tatuaje como se merece![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_49 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_49 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">What girl doesn't love butterflies and ink? Grab this bundle of female only tattoos! Includes: Obsidian Tribus Papilio Forearm and Calf Tattoos[F], Obsidian Tribus Papilio Lower Back Tattoo [F], Ivory Tribus Papilio Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F] and IvoryTribus Papilio Lower Back Tattoo [F].

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_49 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_49 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">What girl doesn't love butterflies and ink? Grab this bundle of female only tattoos! Includes: Obsidian Tribus Papilio Forearm and Calf Tattoos[F], Obsidian Tribus Papilio Lower Back Tattoo [F], Ivory Tribus Papilio Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F] and IvoryTribus Papilio Lower Back Tattoo [F].

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>