<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tribal Skulls Helmet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Casque de pilote à tête de mort tribale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tribal-Schädel-Pilotenhelm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Casco a teschi tribali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Casco con calaveras tribales</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">トライバルスカルヘルメット（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">해골 헬멧 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Tribal Skulls Helmet (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">部族骷髏頭盔(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">部族骷髏頭盔(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Tribal Skulls Helmet</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Deck your ship out in menacing war paint with the Tribal Skulls Paint-job! The Tribal Skulls Pilot's Helmet is included, so you can wear your skulls anywhere! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Faites arborer à votre vaisseau une peinture de guerre menaçante avec cette peinture de guerre à tête de mort tribale ! Le casque de pilote à tête de mort tribale est inclus, vous pourrez donc exhiber partout votre tête de mort ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schmücke Dein Schiff durch die Tribal-Schädel-Lackierung mit einer furchteinflößenden Kriegsbemalung! Der Tribal-Schädel-Pilotenhelm ist inklusive, so dass Du Deine Schädel überall tragen kannst! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dai un tono minaccioso e guerriero alla tua nave con la verniciatura a teschi tribali! Il casco in coordinato è incluso, per essere sempre pronti a combattere! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Adorna tu nave con una pintura de guerra feroz gracias a la pintura con calaveras tribales. Se incluye el casco de piloto con calaveras tribales para que muestres tu fiereza donde quieras. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">トライバルスカルペイントで戦争の恐ろしさを戦闘機に刻もう！トライバルスカルパイロット用ヘルメットも含まれているので、いつでもスカルを身に纏える！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">위협적인 전쟁 장식으로 부족 해골 도장을 함선에 칠하십시오! 해골 장식 조종사 헬멧이 포함되어 있어 언제라도 여러분만의 해골을 쓰고 다닐 수 있습니다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Deck your ship out in menacing war paint with the Tribal Skulls Paint-job! The Tribal Skulls Pilot's Helmet is included, so you can wear your skulls anywhere! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">以部族骷髏的船身油漆圖案，為你的太空船粉飾嚇人的戰爭油漆！附有部族骷髏的飛行員頭盔，讓你到處戴著骷髏！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">以部族骷髏的船身油漆圖案，為你的太空船粉飾嚇人的戰爭油漆！附有部族骷髏的飛行員頭盔，讓你到處戴著骷髏！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Deck your ship out in menacing war paint with the Tribal Skulls Paint-job! The Tribal Skulls Pilot's Helmet is included, so you can wear your skulls anywhere! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>