<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Novus Prime Stereo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaîne stéréo du Novus Prime</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Novus Prime Stereo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stereo Novus Prime</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estéreo Novus Prime</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムステレオ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임 스테레오</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Novus Prime Stereo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Novus Prime音響</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Novus Prime音響</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Novus Prime Stereo</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This sleekly-abstract stereo system plays tracks from the Novus Prime score, featuring a blend of epic orchestral peaks and intense space-age conflict. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette chaîne stéréo passe des morceaux du répertoire musical de Novus Prime aux accents orchestraux épiques et à l'intensité des combats de l'ère spatiale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese schnittig-abstrakten Stereoanlage spielt Stücke aus dem Novus Prime Soundtrack, eine gewaltige Mischung aus epischen orchestralen Höhepunkten und intensiven Science-Fiction Weltraumkonflikten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il raffinato impianto stereo riproduce brani dal repertorio della Novus Prime, in un mix di picchi epici orchestrali e intensi conflitti dell'era spaziale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este elegante y abstracto sistema estéreo reproduce las pistas de música de Novus Prime, con una combinación de épica orquesta con intenso conflicto de la era espacial. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この抽象芸術のようにスマートなステレオシステムはノーバス・プライムのサウンドトラックを再生してくれる。迫力あるオーケストラの音楽で宇宙時代の戦争を激しく表現。\n\n※このコンテンツは「プライベートラウンジのカスタマイズ/家具を追加する」内の「家電・器具」に追加されます。このアイテムは、アニメーションや機能が追加されているアドバンスド家具です。この種類のアイテムは配置できる数に制限があります。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">매끈하게 잘 빠진 이 스테레오 시스템은 노부스 프라임의 스코어를 재생합니다. 장대한 오케스트라 음악부터 우주시대의 분쟁을 그린 격렬한 음악까지 다양한 트랙을 즐기십시오. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This sleekly-abstract stereo system plays tracks from the Novus Prime score, featuring a blend of epic orchestral peaks and intense space-age conflict. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這台擁有光滑機身、抽象設計的音響系統可播放Novus Prime音樂，融合史詩式的管弦樂高潮及激烈的太空衝突旋律。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這台擁有光滑機身、抽象設計的音響系統可播放Novus Prime音樂，融合史詩式的管弦樂高潮及激烈的太空衝突旋律。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This sleekly-abstract stereo system plays tracks from the Novus Prime score, featuring a blend of epic orchestral peaks and intense space-age conflict. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>