<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MiniBots: Battlebox Ultimate Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble MiniBots : Battlebox ultime</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MiniBots: Das ultimative Battlebox-Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto avanzato di MiniBots: Battlebox</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El gran paquete de MiniBots: Battlebox</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MiniBots: Battlebox Ultimate Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Get the ultimate MiniBots Experience! The MiniBots: Battlebox active item will transform your favorite apartment into a custom third person shooter for 1 player. Bundle includes the Battlebox, 11 MiniBot scale furniture items (Modular Wall, R.A.M.P., Energy Bridge, Red and Blue Flags, Pillar, “Explosive” Barrel, Power Shield, Blast Shield, Platform, and Energy Barrier), male and female versions of the Rocket Boots and the GentleBot and LadyBot Helmet clothing items, the Pulse Field Chair, Teleport Beacon, and Stealth Sofa furniture items and the Turret and Sentry Companions. BONUS: unlocks all gadgets for use in MiniBots: Battlebox and MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Profitez au maximum de l'expérience MiniBots ! L'élément actif MiniBots: Battlebox transforme votre appartement préféré en jeu de tir objectif personnalisé pour 1 joueur. L'ensemble inclut la Battlebox, 11 éléments de mobilier MiniBot (mur modulaire, R.A.M.P.E., pont d'énergie, drapeaux rouge et bleu, pilier, tonneau "explosif", bouclier d'énergie, écran de protection, plateforme et barrière énergétique.), les versions homme et femme des bottes fusées, les casques gentleBot et ladyBot, le siège à champ pulsé, la balise de téléportation et le sofa de camouflage, ainsi que les compagnons tourelle et sentinelle. BONUS : Déverrouille tous les gadgets utilisables dans MiniBots : Battlebox et MiniBots multijoueur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sichern Sie sich das ultimative MiniBot-Erlebnis! Die MiniBots: Aktive Objekte der Battlebox verwandeln Ihre Lieblingswohnung in einen individuell gestalteten Third-Person-Shooter für 1 Spieler. Das Bundle enthält die Battlebox, 11 MiniBot-Möblierungsobjekte (Modulare Wand, R.A.M.P., Energiebrücke, rote und blaue Fahnen, Säule, „Sprengstoff“-Fass, Energieschild, Energiestoßschild, Plattform und Energiebarriere), Raketenstiefel für Damen und Herren sowie die GentleBot- und LadyBot-Helm-Kleidungsobjekte, die Möbelstücke Impulsfeldstuhl, Teleportationsblinkleuchte und Tarnsofa sowie die Gefährten Turm und Wache. BONUS: Gibt alle Gadgets zur Verwendung in MiniBots: Battlebox und MiniBots-Multiplayer-Modus frei. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vivi l'esperienza suprema in MiniBots! L'elemento attivo di MiniBots: Battlebox trasformerà il tuo appartamento preferito in uno sparatutto personalizzato in terza persona per 1 giocatore. Il pacchetto include il campo di battaglia, 11 arredi di gioco in scala per i MiniBot (Muro modulare, R.A.M.P., Ponte di energia, Bandiere rosse e blu, Colonna, Barile "esplosivo", Scudo di energia, Scudo blindato, Piattaforma e Barriera di energia), versioni per uomo e donna degli Stivali razzo e i capi di abbigliamento Elmo per lei e lui, gli arredi Sedia con campo a impulsi, Faro teletrasporto e Divano dell'invisibilità, nonché la Torretta e la Sentinella alleate. BONUS: sblocca tutti i gadget per l'utilizzo in MiniBots: Battlebox e modalità multigiocatore di MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Obtén la máxima experiencia MiniBots! El artículo activo de MiniBots:Battlebox transformará tu apartamento favorito en un disparador de terceros personalizado. El paquete incluye el Battlebox, 11 artículos de muebles a escala MiniBot (pared modular, P.R.M.A., puente de energía, banderas rojas y azules, pilar, barril "explosivo", escudo de poder, escudo explosivo, plataforma y barrera energética), versiones masculinas y femeninas de las botas espaciales, el casco GentleBot y LadyBot, la Silla de campo pulsante, el Faro de teletransporte, el Sofá sigiloso y los Compañeros Torreón y Centinela. BONUS: desbloquea todos los dispositivos para usarlos en MiniBots:Battlebox y el modo varios jugadores de MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Get the ultimate MiniBots Experience! The MiniBots: Battlebox active item will transform your favorite apartment into a custom third person shooter for 1 player. Bundle includes the Battlebox, 11 MiniBot scale furniture items (Modular Wall, R.A.M.P., Energy Bridge, Red and Blue Flags, Pillar, “Explosive” Barrel, Power Shield, Blast Shield, Platform, and Energy Barrier), male and female versions of the Rocket Boots and the GentleBot and LadyBot Helmet clothing items, the Pulse Field Chair, Teleport Beacon, and Stealth Sofa furniture items and the Turret and Sentry Companions. BONUS: unlocks all gadgets for use in MiniBots: Battlebox and MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>