<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Spacewalk Propulsion Boots (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bottes d'escapade spatiale (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schub-Stiefel für den Weltraumspaziergang (Herrenversion)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stivali a propulsione spaziale (per uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Botas de propulsión para paseo espacial (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">宇宙遊泳用推進力ブーツ（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">우주 유영 추진 부츠 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Spacewalk Propulsion Boots (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">太空漫步推進靴（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">太空漫步推進靴（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Spacewalk Propulsion Boots (male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">These boots utilize impulse thrusters to allow the wearer to move more quickly in zero-G environments. This also applies to those using the Zero-gravity Simulator to float within the station. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ces bottes sont dotées de propulseurs à impulsion afin de permettre à leur porteur d'effectuer des déplacements rapides dans les environnements à gravité zéro. Peuvent être également équipées par les utilisateurs de Simulateur d'apesanteur permettant de flotter à l'intérieur de la station [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese Stiefel verwenden Impuls-Schubdüsen, mit denen der Träger sich schneller in der Schwerelosigkeit bewegen kann. Auch benutzbar für alle, die den Schwerelosigkeitssimulator verwenden, um innerhalb der Station zu schweben. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questi stivali utilizzano la propulsione a impulsi, che permette a chi li indossa di muoversi più velocemente in assenza di gravità. Possono essere utilizzati anche con il simulatore di zero-G per fluttuare nella stazione. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estas botas emplean propulsores para que el usuario pueda desplazarse con mayor rapidez en entornos de gravedad cero. También se aplica a aquéllos que utilicen el simulador de gravedad cero para flotar dentro de la estación. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このブーツは無重力の環境で素早く移動できるためにインパルススラスターを使用している。無重力シミュレーターを使いステーション内を浮遊する時にも効果的。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">파동 추진기를 활용한 부츠로, 착용자가 무중력  환경에서 재빠르게 이동할 수 있게 해줍니다. 이러한 기능은 무중력 시뮬레이터를 이용해 정거장 내를 이동하는 사람에게도 유효합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">These boots utilize impulse thrusters to allow the wearer to move more quickly in zero-G environments. This also applies to those using the Zero-gravity Simulator to float within the station. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這對靴利用脈衝推動器，讓穿上它的人在零重力的環境下更迅速移動。亦能讓使用零重力模擬器在太空站內漂浮的人使用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這對靴利用脈衝推動器，讓穿上它的人在零重力的環境下更迅速移動。亦能讓使用零重力模擬器在太空站內漂浮的人使用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">These boots utilize impulse thrusters to allow the wearer to move more quickly in zero-G environments. This also applies to those using the Zero-gravity Simulator to float within the station. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>