<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rocking Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaise à bascule</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schaukelstuhl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sedia a dondolo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Balancín</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* RockingChair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* RockingChair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* RockingChair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* RockingChair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* RockingChair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rocking Chair</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There is no better furniture to place on your front porch than a bona fide rocking chair. This piece of furniture is perfect for relaxing and cleaning your shotgun, or for yelling at kids to get off your lawn. Use the momentum of your own body to rock back and forth. You'll never need to buy another chair again! This is an active item.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il n'y a pas de meilleur mobilier à mettre sous votre porche d'entrée que cette chaise à bascule. Elle est parfaite pour se reposer et nettoyer votre fusil à pompe, ou pour gronder les enfants qui labourent votre gazon. Utilisez l'élan de votre corps pour vous balancer d'avant en arrière. Vous n'aurez plus jamais besoin d'acheter une autre chaise ! C'est un objet actif. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es gibt kein besseres Möbelstück für Ihre Veranda als einen echten Schaukelstuhl. Dieses Möbelstück eignet sich ausgezeichnet, um sich zu entspannen und Ihre Schrotflinte zu säubern, oder um Kinder lauthals von Ihrem  Rasen zu vertreiben. Nutzen Sie die Schwungkraft Ihres eigenen Körpers, um hin und her zu schaukeln. Sie brauchen nie wieder einen anderen Stuhl zu kaufen! Hierbei handelt es sich um ein aktives Spiel.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non c'è niente di meglio che posizionare una sedia a dondolo sulla veranda. Quest'arredamento è perfatto per rilassarsi e pulire il vostro fucile da caccia, o per urlare ai bambini di andarsene dal tuo prato. Datevi una spinta per fare avanti e indietro. Non avrete bisogno di comprare un'altra sedia! Questo è un oggetto attivo.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No hay mejor mobiliario para tu porche que un buen balancín. Este mueble es perfecto para relajarse y limpiar tu escopeta o para gritarle a los niños que salgan de tu césped. Aprovecha un momento para ti y mécete adelante y atrás. Nunca más comprarás una silla nueva ! Este es un objeto activo.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized*  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized*  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized*  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized*  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized*  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">There is no better furniture to place on your front porch than a bona fide rocking chair. This piece of furniture is perfect for relaxing and cleaning your shotgun, or for yelling at kids to get off your lawn. Use the momentum of your own body to rock back and forth. You'll never need to buy another chair again! This is an active item.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>