<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Big Al Figure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Figurine de Al</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Big Al"-Figur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Modellino Big Al</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Muñeco del Gran Al</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ふとっちょアルのフィギュア</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">빅 앨 피규어</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Big Al Figure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Big Al 角色模型</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Big Al 角色模型</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Big Al Figure</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A pudgy computer geek with interests in electronics and all things Qwark. He owns a large Roboshack on planet Kerwan and has joined Ratchet on a few adventures. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un nerd grassouillet qui s'intéresse à l'électronique et à tout ce qui touche de près ou de loin à Qwark. Il possède un Roborama sur la planète Kerwan et il a accompagné Ratchet dans quelques-unes de ses aventures. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein pummeliger Computer-Freak mit einer Vorliebe für Elektronik und alles, was Qwark angeht. Er besitzt einen großen Roboshack auf dem Planeten Kerwan und hat Ratchet bereits bei ein paar Abenteuern zur Seite gestanden. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un genio del computer appassionato di elettronica e di qualunque cosa Qwark. Possiede un grosso Roboshack sul pianeta Kerwan e si è unito a Ratchet in alcune avventure. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un friki rellenito, fan de la electrónica y de las cosas con qwarks. Posee un gran robotaller en el planeta Kerwan, y ha acompañado a Ratchet en alguna aventura.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">まるまると太った、コンピュータのエキスパート。電子工学とクォークについても深い知識を持つ。惑星ケルバンの「Mr.アルのロボ工房」はいまや「ロボ＆ゲームスーパーストア」として小売業界の巨人に成長。過去にはラチェットの冒険に協力したことも [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">컴퓨터에 푹 빠진 모범생. 캡틴 쿼크의 광팬입니다. 어느 행성에 커다란 집이 있으며, 라쳇과 함께 모험을 하기도 했습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A pudgy computer geek with interests in electronics and all things Qwark. He owns a large Roboshack on planet Kerwan and has joined Ratchet on a few adventures.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">又矮又胖的電腦駭客，喜歡電子產品及任何有關魁克的事物。他在可宛星上擁有一間大機器屋，也曾經加入拉捷特的幾次冒險。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">又矮又胖的電腦駭客，喜歡電子產品及任何有關魁克的事物。他在可宛星上擁有一間大機器屋，也曾經加入拉捷特的幾次冒險。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A pudgy computer geek with interests in electronics and all things Qwark. He owns a large Roboshack on planet Kerwan and has joined Ratchet on a few adventures.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>