<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nerd Wear Bundle (female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vêtements de Nerd Ensemble (femelle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nerd Verschleiß  Bündel (weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nerd Vestiti Raccolta (femmina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Uso de Nerd Paquete (femenino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Nerd Wear Bundle (female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Who says you can't have it all.  With this bundle, you'll be nerd from head to toe.  Hunky boys without shirts love to hang out with nerdy chicks.  Nerd Glasses, Hair, Blouse, Pants, Socks and Sandals . . .there will be no confusing you with a normal person ever again.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Qui a dit qu'on ne peut pas tout avoir. Avec ce kit, vous serez nerd de la tête aux pieds. Garçons musclé sans shirts aiment se traîner avec des poussins ringards. Nerd lunettes, Cheveux, Blouse, Pantalon, Chaussettes et Sandales  . . . vous ne serez jamais être confondue avec une personne normale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer sagt, man kann nicht alles haben. Mit diesem bündel werden Sie nerd von kopf bis fuß. Jungen muskulös ohne der hemden liebe zu hängen mit nerdy Küken. Nerd Brille, Haare, Bluse, Hose, Socken und Sandalen  . . . es wird keine verwirrenden sie mit einer normalen person jemals wieder. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chi ha detto che non si può avere tutto. Con questo pacchetto, sarai nerd dalla testa ai piedi. Ragazzi muscoloso senza amore camicie per uscire con i pulcini nerd. Nerd Occhiali, Capelli, Camicetta, Pantaloni, Calze e Sandali  . . . non ci saranno ti confondere con una persona normale, mai più. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Quién dice que no se puede tener todo. Con este paquete, se le nerd de pies a cabeza. Muchachos muscular sin camisa encanta salir con chicas nerd. Nerd Gafas, Pelo, Blusa, Pantalones, Calcetines y Sandalias  . . . no habrá que confundir con una persona normal nunca más. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Who says you can't have it all.  With this bundle, you'll be nerd from head to toe.  Hunky boys without shirts love to hang out with nerdy chicks.  Nerd Glasses, Hair, Blouse, Pants, Socks and Sandals . . .there will be no confusing you with a normal person ever again.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>