<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Drey Classic Black Shimmer English Brogue Shoe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Richelieux classiques Drey noirs brillants</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schwarze klassische Drey Brogues</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scarpa sportiva classica inglese Drey nero lucido</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Zapato típico inglés de color blanco de Drey</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">【Drey】クラッシック英国風ブローグシューズ　（ブラックシマー）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"드레이" 클래식 블랙 드레스 슈즈 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Drey Classic Black Shimmer English Brogue Shoe (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Drey經典亮黑英式雕花皮鞋 (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Drey經典亮黑英式雕花皮鞋 (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Drey Classic Black Shimmer English Brogue Shoe</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stride into the new season in this classic English Brogue. In a leather finish with punch detailing, these shoes have timeless appeal. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avancez à grands pas dans la nouvelle saison avec ces richelieux classiques. Avec leur finition en cuir ornée de poinçons, ces chaussures ont une aura intemporelle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Betritt die neue Saison mit diesen klassisch englischen Brogues. Mit den Lochverzierungen im glänzenden Leder sind diese Schuhe zeitlose Klassiker. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Affronta la nuova stagione con passo deciso con queste classiche scarpe sportive inglesi. Pelle e punzonature danno a queste scarpe un fascino senza tempo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Deslízate hacia la nueva temporada con estos clásicos zapatos ingleses. Gracias a su acabado en cuero y a sus detalles perforados, estos zapatos tienen un atractivo atemporal. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このシューズで新しいシーズンに滑り込もう。レザーフィニッシュ済みのこの靴は永遠に輝き続けるでしょう。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">영국에서 온 클래식한 가죽 구두를 신고 새로운 시즌을 맞이하십시오. 펀치 장식에 가죽으로 마감된 이 구두의 가치는 시간이 지나도 변하지 않습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Stride into the new season in this classic English Brogue. In a leather finish with punch detailing, these shoes have timeless appeal. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這款經典的英式雕花鞋，讓你換季也有風。真皮上的雕花裝飾，讓這雙鞋散發永恆魅力。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這款經典的英式雕花鞋，讓你換季也有風。真皮上的雕花裝飾，讓這雙鞋散發永恆魅力。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Stride into the new season in this classic English Brogue. In a leather finish with punch detailing, these shoes have timeless appeal. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>