<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Octopoot Hat - Male</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chapeau Octopoot - Homme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Octopoot-Mütze - Männer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cappello Octopoot - uomo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sombrero Octopoot - Chico</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オクトプート帽子 - 男性用</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Octopoot Hat - Male</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Interwebz are made up of a network of tubes known as ‘intertubes.’ When the ‘intertubes’ are clogged then the internet slows!  The culprits? OCTOPOOTS! Living in the 'intertubes' and feeding on wiki searches, their waste sticks to the inside of the tubes, slowing down your precious connection! Our LOOT™ Scientists went into the intertubes and collected the Octopoots! Now we’re recycling them into hoodies and hats galore! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'Interwebz est constitué d'un réseau de tubes appelés "intertubes". Quand les "intertubes" sont bouchés, l'internet ralentit ! Et qui les bouche? Les coupables? Les OCTOPOOTS! Vivant dans les "intertubes" et se nourrissant de recherches wiki, leurs déjections se collent à l'intérieur des tubes ralentissant ainsi votre chère connexion! Nos Scientifiques de LOOT™ sont allés dans les intertubes et ont ramassé tous les Octopoots! Maintenant, on les recycle en une multitude de sweats à capuche et de chapeaux! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Internetz ist ein Gewebe aus lauter Röhren, die man 'Interrohre' nennt. Wenn diese 'Interrohre' verstopft sind, wird das Internet langsam! Und schuld daran sind nur die OKTOPUPSE! Sie kleben in den 'Interröhren' und fressen sich an Tippfehlern in Wikipediasuchanfragen satt. Ihr Auswurf verklebt die Rohre von innen, sodass wir wertvolle Bandbreite verlieren! Unsere LOOT™-Wissenschaftler sind durch die 'Interrohre' gekrochen und haben Oktopupse gesammelt! Und jetzt recyclen wir sie als Mützen und Kaputzenpullis. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Internet è fatto di tanti piccoli "intercavi". Quando questi sono intasati, la connessione rallenta significativamente! La colpa? È degli OCTOPOOT! che vivono negli "intercavi", si nutrono di wikiricerche e i cui scarti si accumulano sulle pareti dei cavi rallentando la tua preziosa connessione! I nostri scienziati LOOT™ sono scesi negli intercavi per raccogliere tutti gli Octopoot! Li stanno ora riciclando confezionando meravigliose felpe con cappuccio e tanti fantastici cappelli! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La Interwebz está formada por una red de tubos conocida como "Intertubos", y cuando los intertubos se atascan, la Internet va lenta. ¿Y quienes son los culpables? Los OCTOPOOTS! Viven en los intertubos y se alimentan de las búsquedas wiki, y sus deshechos se pegan al interior de los tubos ralentizando tu preciada conexión. Nuestros científicos de LOOT™ entraron en los intertubos y recogieron los Octopoots!. ¡Y ahora, los estamos convirtiendo en montones de sudaderas y sombreros! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LOOT™の似非科学レッスン#1：インターネットは「インターチューブ」というチューブ・ネットワークによって結成されている。インターチューブに生息するオクトプートのフンがネット接続を悪くする原因！LOOT™科学者チームがオクトプートを捕まえて、フード付きパーカーや帽子にリサイクル！私達って意外とエコでしょう？[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Interwebz are made up of a network of tubes known as ‘intertubes.’ When the ‘intertubes’ are clogged then the internet slows!  The culprits? OCTOPOOTS! Living in the 'intertubes' and feeding on wiki searches, their waste sticks to the inside of the tubes, slowing down your precious connection! Our LOOT™ Scientists went into the intertubes and collected the Octopoots! Now we’re recycling them into hoodies and hats galore! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>