<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ObjectName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Namco Museum™ Sweatshirt1 (Mens)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sweat-shirt 1 Namco Museum™ (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Namco Museum™ Sweatshirt1 (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Felpa1 Namco Museum™ (Per uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sudadera 1 Namco Museum™ (Masculina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">男性用パックマンジャージ1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">팩맨 저지 셔츠 1 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">PAC-MAN Shirt(Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">PAC-MAN 上衣 1（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">PAC-MAN 上衣 1（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">PAC-MAN® Zipper Jacket</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ObjectDescription</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A Sweatshirt featuring a new color. This item cannot be obtained as a Home Reward in Namco Museum. Wear this to stand out from the crowd! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un Sweat-shirt présentant une nouvelle couleur. Cet article ne peut être obtenu comme récompense Home dans Namco Museum. Portez-le pour vous démarquer des autres ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Sweatshirt mit brandneuer Farbe. Dieser Artikel kann nicht als Home-Gewinn im Namco Museum erworben werden. Tragen Sie ihn, um sich von anderen abzuheben! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una felpa di un colore nuovo. Questa maglia non può essere vinta in Namco Museum. Indossala e distinguiti dalla folla! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sudadera con un color nuevo. Este artículo no se puede obtener como premio Home en Namco Museum. ¡Póntelo para llamar la atención! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ナムコミュージアムリワードアイテムのニューカラージャージです。これを着用して他の人と差をつけよう！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">남코뮤지엄의 리워드 아이템인 뉴 컬러 저지 셔츠입니다. 남들하고는 달라야죠! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A Sweatshirt featuring a new color. This item cannot be obtained as a Home Reward in Namco Museum. Wear this to stand out from the crowd! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Namco Museum獎品的新色上衣，只可在這裡拿到。穿起它讓自己與別不同吧！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Namco Museum獎品的新色上衣，只能在這裡得到。穿起它讓自己與眾不同吧！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This two-tone jacket will keep you warm and stylish, but it's the attention to detail that sets this piece apart. The subtle yet charming Pac-Man zipper tab will show anyone that you're a true fan of the classics![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>