<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">JMX – 315 Flaming Red</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">JMX – 315 Rouge Flamboyant</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">JMX – 315 Flammend Rot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">JMX – 315 Rosso Fiammeggiante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">JMX – 315 Rojo Flamante</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It's time to get down with the Traffic Jam vibe.  Climb aboard our hover cars, the JMX-315, and discover this new way to travel in vehicular style!  In our flying transportation you can make the future of travel a reality in virtuality!  Choose from a range of styles and let your paint job do the talking, join the Traffic Jam now!Use square to move faster! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Laissez-vous porter par la vague Traffic Jam ! Grimpez à bord de notre aérovoiture, la JMX-315, et découvrez ce tout nouveau moyen de voyager avec classe !  Au volant de notre véhicule flottant, vous pourrez faire de l’avenir des transports une réalité virtuelle ! Choisissez parmi de nombreux styles et laissez votre peinture s’exprimer à votre place. Rejoignez Traffic Jam dès maintenant! Utiliser une équerre pour aller plus vite! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lasse dich von Traffic Jam davontragen! Steige in unsere Schwebe-Autos, die JMX-315, und entdecke die neue Art stilvoll in Fahrzeugen zu reisen! In unseren fliegenden Fortbewegungsmitteln kannst du die Zukunft des Reisens zur virtuellen Realität werden lassen! Wähle unter verschiedenen Stilen und lasse deine Lackierung sprechen. Schließe dich jetzt dem Traffic Jam an! Verwenden Sie eckige sich schneller zu bewegen! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lasciati trasportare dal movimento Traffic Jam! Salta a bordo delle nostre hover car, le JMX-315 e scopri questo nuovissimo modo di viaggiare con classe! Con i nostri veicoli volanti potrai rendere realtà in un mondo virtuale il futuro dei trasporti! Scegli tra una vasta gamma di stili e lascia che i colori della carrozzeria parlino per te. Unisciti subito a Traffic Jam! Utilizzare quadrato per muoversi più velocemente! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Déjate llevar por el movimiento Traffic Jam! Sube a bordo de nuestros aerovehículos, los JMX-315, y descubre una nueva forma de viajar con clase. ¡Con nuestros coches flotantes podrás convertir el transporte del futuro en una realidad virtual! Elige entre una amplia gama de estilos y deja que la pintura hable por ti. ¡Únete ya a Traffic Jam! Utilice el cuadrado para moverse más rápido![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">It's time to get down with the Traffic Jam vibe.  Climb aboard our hover cars, the JMX-315, and discover this new way to travel in vehicular style!  In our flying transportation you can make the future of travel a reality in virtuality!  Choose from a range of styles and let your paint job do the talking, join the Traffic Jam now! Use square to move faster! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>