<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Vixen Vicki Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vixen Vicki Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vixen Vicki Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vixen Vicki Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Vixen Vicki Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BrunetteBiker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BrunetteBiker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BrunetteBiker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BrunetteBiker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BrunetteBiker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Vixen Vicki Pin-up Girl</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Varoom-varoom… Vixen Vicki is ready to ride into Home as your sexy biker pin-up babe!  As a full character costume, she comes complete with retro pin-up hair, hat, make-up and skimpy black biker suit and boots.  She is sleeved with tats and sports sexy ab and leg art on her curvaceous frame... and just to take your RPM's to the limit, the sexy vixen comes with custom walk, run and pin-up pose animations.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Varoom-Varoom..Vixen Vicki est prête a cavaler a l'intérieur de Home comme ta sexy pin-up motard minette! Comme costume à part entière, elle vient complète avec des cheveux, chapeau, maquillage retro et une tenue de motard étriquées et bottes. Ses bras sont ornées de tatouages et elle affiche des abdos sexy et des figures de jambes artistiques sur son corps voluptueux..et juste pour conduire ta vitesse à la limite maximale, la Sexy Vixen vient avec une marche, course et pose animées de pin-up.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Varoom-varoom… Vixen Vicki ist als sexy Biker Pin-Up Babe bereit mit dir nach Hause zu fahren! Als komplettes Charakterkostüm kommt sie zusammen mit Retro Pin-Up Frisur, Hut, Make-Up, sowie knappem Biker-Anzug und Stiefeln. Ihre Ärmeltätowierungen schmeicheln der sexy Bauch- und Beinkunst auf ihrem kurvigen Körperbau... und um deine RPM's auf die Spitze zu treiben, bekommst du diese sexy Füchsin mit benutzerdefinierten Animationen für Gang, Lauf und Pin-Up Posen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Varoom-varoom… Vixen Vicki é pronta per andare a casa come la tua bambola motociclista sexy pin-up!  Come costume di personaggio completo, include capelli retro da pin-up, capello, trucco e abito succinto nero da motociclista con degli stivali.  Ha tanti lustrini, addominali sexy e arte sulle gambe sul suo corpo da urlo... e per portare le tue pulsazioni al limite, questa femmina sexy ha animazioni per una camminata particolare, corsa e pose da pin-up.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Varoom-varoom… Vixen Vicki esta lista para llevarte a Casa como tu nena  pin-up motociclista sexy!  Como disfraz de personaje completo, viene con  peinado retro de pin-up, sombrero, maquillaje y un traje negro de motociclista muy provocativo con botas.  Tiene varios motivos y abdominales sexys y arte en su pierna y en su complexión curveada... y esto llevará tus pulsaciones al limite, esta seductora sexy viene con animaciones de caminata especial, corrida y poses de pin-up.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BrunetteBiker [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BrunetteBiker [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BrunetteBiker [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BrunetteBiker [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BrunetteBiker [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Varoom-varoom… Vixen Vicki is ready to ride into Home as your sexy biker pin-up babe!  As a full character costume, she comes complete with retro pin-up hair, hat, make-up and skimpy black biker suit and boots.  She is sleeved with tats and sports sexy ab and leg art on her curvaceous frame... and just to take your RPM's to the limit, the sexy vixen comes with custom walk, run and pin-up pose animations.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>