<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">About Dolphies (4)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">À propos des Dolphies (4)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über Dolphys (4)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Informazioni sui Dolphy (4)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acerca de los Dolphies (4)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィーについて（４）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">About Dolphies (4)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">message</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If you are raising a Dolphy in your personal "Dolphy Room", you can enter it in races once you raise it into an adult.\nDolphy Rooms are peaceful areas where you can watch and raise your own Dolphy. Would you like to add 1 to your personal space?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si tu élèves un Dolphy dans ton "Dolphydrome", tu peux l'inscrire aux courses dès qu'il devient adulte.\nLe Dolphydrome est un endroit calme où tu pourras observer et élever ton Dolphy. Veux-tu en ajouter un à ton espace personnel ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn du in deinem persönlichen „Dolphy-Raum“ ein Dolphy großziehst, kannst du mit ihm an Rennen teilnehmen, sobald es erwachsen ist.\nDolphy-Räume sind friedliche Bereiche, in denen du dein eigenes Dolphy beobachten und großziehen kannst. Möchtest du deinem persönlichen Apartment eines hinzufügen?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se stai allevando un Dolphy nella tua "Stanza di Dolphy", puoi iscriverlo alle gare non appena diventa adulto.\nLe Stanze di Dolphy sono zone tranquille dove puoi osservare il tuo Dolphy mentre cresce. Vuoi aggiungerne 1 al tuo spazio personale?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si estás criando un Dolphy en tu propio "Cuarto de Dolphy", podrás inscribirlo en las carreras cuando llegue a la edad adulta.\nLos Cuartos de Dolphy son zonas tranquilas donde puedes observar y criar a tu propio Dolphy. ¿Quieres añadir uno a tu espacio personal?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">パーソナルスペース「ドルフィールーム」には、ドルフィーの育成機能があり、成体まで育てると、このハドソンゲートで行われるレースにエントリーできます。\n泳ぎまわるドルフィーを眺めながら、癒しのひとときも過ごせる「ドルフィールーム」を、あなたのパーソナルスペースの１つに加えてみませんか？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">If you are raising a Dolphy in your personal "Dolphy Room", you can enter it in races once you raise it into an adult.\nDolphy Rooms are peaceful areas where you can watch and raise your own Dolphy. Would you like to add 1 to your personal space?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CIRCLE]Close</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CIRCLE]Fermer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CIRCLE]Schließen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CIRCLE]Chiudi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CIRCLE]Cerrar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[CIRCLE]閉じる</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[CIRCLE]Close</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>