<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Get Ziggy With It Skirt - Black (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Jupe Get Ziggy With It - Noir (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Get Ziggy With It Rock - Schwarz (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Get Ziggy With It Gonna - Nero (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Falda Get Ziggy With It - Negro (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our Sisters Of The Sun collection is a celebration of fashions that play up your natural beauty with their boho-chic vibe and warrior spirit. Alive with earthy colors and energy, each style easily transitions from days of soaking up the sun to nights spent dancing in the moonlight. This knit mini skirt features a slim fit and a bold tribal print. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Notre collection Sisters Of The Sun fête la mode qui met en valeur votre beauté naturelle, avec un style chic et bohème tout en gardant un esprit guerrier. Avec ses couleurs ocrées et son énergie, chaque style s'adapte aux différents moments de la journée, du lever du soleil aux soirées au clair de lune. Cette mini-jupe en maille a une coupe près du corps avec un motif tribal surprenant. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unsere Sisters Of The Sun Kollektion akzentuiert Ihre natürliche Schönheit mit modischen Kreationen und einer Verschmelzung von Folklore-Chic und Kampfgeist. Der Stil in lebhaften Naturtönen und durchwachsen mit der Energie der Erde passt sich nahtlos an alle Anforderungen des Tages an - vom Sonnenbaden am Strand bis hin zum Tanzen im Mondschein. Dieses eng geschnittene Strick-Minikleid besticht durch sein augenfälliges Folkloremuster. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La nostra collezione Sisters Of The Sun celebra la moda che mette in risalto la bellezza naturale grazie a uno stile boho-chic unito allo spirito guerriero. Pieno di energia e caratterizzato dai colori della natura, ogni stile passa elegantemente dalle giornate passate a prendere il sole alle notti trascorse a ballare sotto le stelle.  Questa minigonna presenta taglio aderente e vivace stampa tribale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nuestra colección Sisters of the Sun es una celebración de la moda que resalta tu belleza natural gracias a su toque boho-chic y a su espíritu guerrero. Destila vida con tonos tierra y energía. Cada estilo pasa de los días sumergidos al sol a las noches de baile bajo la luz de la luna. Esta minifalda de punto es ajustada y tiene un llamativo estampado tribal. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>