<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Spinner Pullover - Blue (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Pull-over Spinner - Bleu (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Spinner Pullover - Blau (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Spinner Pullover - Blu (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Spinner Sudadera - Azul (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Spinner hoodie gets its distinct look from a heavy mix of colored stripes. Ultra soft in a premium cotton fleece fabric, details include a hood, pouch pockets, and a Billabong wave logo at the chest. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le sweat à capuche Spinner tire son look caractéristique d'un mélange chargé de bandes de couleur. Ultra doux grâce à un tissu polaire en coton, il comporte une capuche, des poches ventrales et un logo Billabong en forme de vague sur la poitrine. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aufwändig gestreifter Spinner Kapuzenpulli aus superweichem hochwertigem Baumwollfleece in leuchtenden Farben. Mit Kapuze, Seitentaschen und einem gewebten Billabong-Etikett auf der Brust [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il pullover con cappuccio Spinner prende il suo look distintivo da una forte combinazione di strisce colorate. In tessuto di cotone ultra morbido di alta qualità, il capo presenta un cappuccio, tascone e logo Billabong dell'onda sul petto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La sudadera Spinner se distingue por su potente serie de rayas en distintos tonos. Su tejido polar de algodón de primera calidad es de una suavidad extrema y tiene capucha, bolsillo de canguro y el logotipo de olas Billabong en el pecho. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>