<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rectangular Display Case </LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Boîte Rectangulaire </LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rechteckiger Schaukasten </LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vetrinetta Rettangolare </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Expositor Rectangular </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Rectangular Display Case </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rectangular Display Case </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Jam Jar was established in the 1940’s as THE place to go.  Discover the opulence and grandeur of this by gone era in a building rescued and restored to its rightful glory!  Whether you decide to return it to it's full boutique status, use it's exquisite detail as a backdrop for a gallery or as the venue of the latest fashion event, The Jam Jar will still prove to be THE place to be seen![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le 'Jam Jar' était considéré, dans les années 1940, comme le TOP dans endroits branchés. Découvrez la grandeur et richesse de ce bâtiment d'époque qui a été restauré pour retrouver sa splendeur d'antan !  Que vous décidiez d'en faire une boutique de mode ou d'utiliser ce cadre exceptionnel comme décor pour une exposition ou comme lieu de réception du dernier événement mode, le 'Jam Jar' sera, encore et toujours, au TOP![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das 'Jam Jar' wurde in den 1940ern gegründet und war DIE Anlaufstelle schlechthin. Entdecke die Opulenz und Pracht dieser vergangenen Ära in einem Gebäude, das zu seinem verdienten Ruhm restauriert wurde! Ob du es wieder zu seinem vollwertigen Status als Boutique bringen willst, es als Kulisse für eine Galerie oder als Veranstaltungsort für die neueste Modeschau verwenden willst, Das 'Jam Jar' wird weiterhin beweisen, dass es DER Ort ist, an dem man gesehen werden will! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il 'Jam Jar' fu fondato nel 1940 ed allora era IL locale per eccellenza.  Scopri l'opulenza e la decadenza di quest'epoca passata in un edificio restaurato e riportato alla sua antica gloria!  Che tu decida di riaprire la boutique che ospitava un tempo, utilizzare gli spazi squisitamente decorati per ospitare una galleria o una sfilata di moda di uno stilita di grido, il 'Jam Jar' sarà ancora IL luogo dove la gente che conta vorrà farsi vedere! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Jam Jar se creo en 1940 como el lugar a donde ir. Descubra la opulencia y grandeza de la era pasada en este edificio restaurado con la gloria que se merece! Usted decide si quiere convertirlo en lo que fue, utilice el exquisito detalle como telón para una galería o como un lugar para espectáculos, Jam Jar continuará demostrando que es el lugar donde hay que estar! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Jam Jar was established in the 1940’s as THE place to go.  Discover the opulence and grandeur of this by gone era in a building rescued and restored to its rightful glory!  Whether you decide to return it to it's full boutique status, use it's exquisite detail as a backdrop for a gallery or as the venue of the latest fashion event, The Jam Jar will still prove to be THE place to be seen![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Jam Jar was established in the 1940’s as THE place to go.  Discover the opulence and grandeur of this by gone era in a building rescued and restored to its rightful glory!  Whether you decide to return it to it's full boutique status, use it's exquisite detail as a backdrop for a gallery or as the venue of the latest fashion event, The Jam Jar will still prove to be THE place to be seen![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>