<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Red Poster 3 Yoda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Poster rouge 3 Yoda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rotes Poster 3 Yoda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Poster Rosso 3 Yoda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Póster rojo 3 Yoda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Red Poster 3 Yoda</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">I had set off to the local marketplace early in the morning. Once I arrived, the usual hustle and bustle of the area had seemingly been replaced by lethargic, slow, and distracted patrons. Not terribly uncommon - on Coruscant you find many small-time celebrities who can bring most any area of the city to a standstill. Pushing my way through towards the clothing district, I was resolved not to be yet another blank-eyed fan. In my haste, I pushed with too much gusto. The resulting succession of tumbling bodies poured outward from me in all directions, knocking more than a few people off the causeway, towards their death below. In a blur of green, I felt something fly overhead. Before I realized it, those falling were saved. And then he looked at me and spoke one sentence: “Hurry we must not. Muddled your mind becomes. A form of violence haste is. The dark side.” [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">J'étais parti tôt au marché. Sur place, l'habituel remue-ménage du lieu semblait avoir été remplacé par des clients léthargiques. Pas vraiment inhabituel : sur Coruscant, on trouve des tas de célébrités de troisième ordre qui peuvent paralyser n'importe quelle partie de la ville. Continuant vers le quartier des vêtements, j'étais bien résolu à ne pas être pris pour un fan fou. Mais, dans ma hâte, je me montrais un peu trop enthousiaste, précipitant plus d'une personne au bas de la chaussée, vers une mort certaine. Dans un flou vert, je sentis quelque chose voler au-dessus de moi. Il me regarda et dit : "Se hâter ainsi il ne faut. Confus devient votre esprit. Une forme de violence, la hâte se révèle. Le côté obscur." [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Am frühen Morgen hatte ich mich auf den Weg zum Marktplatz gemacht. Als ich ankam, waren alle abgelenkt. Das war nichts Außergewöhnliches - auf Coruscant kann man viele unwichtige Prominente finden, die ein Stadtviertel zum Stillstand bringen können. Ich war entschlossen, nicht einer dieser naiven Fans zu sein. Doch beeilte ich mich zu sehr und stieß mit Menschen zusammen. Manche wurden sogar vom Laufsteg geworfen, ein tödlicher Sturz. Verschwommen sah ich, wie über mir etwas Grünes flog. Bevor ich verstand, was passiert war, waren die Gefallenen gerettet. Und dann sah er mich an und sprach: “Beeilen dürfen wir nicht uns. Das deinen Geist verwirrt. Eine Form von Gewalt Hast ist. Die dunkle Seite.” [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ero partito per il mercato locale. Una volta lì, non c'era il solito caos, la folla era lenta e apatica. Nulla di insolito - su Coruscant ci sono molti VIP di poco conto capaci di paralizzare la città. Verso il distretto dell'abbigliamento, non volevo essere un ammiratore dallo sguardo spento. Nella fretta, spinsi con foga. Ne risultò una serie di corpi rotolanti in ogni direzione, molti caddero dalla strada sopraelevata verso una morte sicura. Un lampo di verde, e vidi qualcosa che volava su di me. Prima che me ne potessi rendere conto, le persone che stavano cadendo furono salvate. E poi lui mi guardò e disse: affrettarci non dobbiamo. Confusa la nostra mente diventa. La fretta è violenza. Il lato oscuro”. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salí hacia el mercado de buena mañana. Cuando llegué, el ajetreo habitual se había convertido en un ritmo letárgico y distraído. No era extraño: en Coruscant, sé de varios famosillos que consiguen frenar la actividad de casi todas las zonas de la ciudad. Avanzando por el barrio textil, decidí no ser un fanático más. Con las prisas, empujé con demasiado brío. Una sucesión de cuerpos comenzó a venirse abajo, varios iban a caerse del camino elevado, encontrando su muerte. Vi un destello de color verde, sentí que algo sobrevolaba mi cabeza. Antes de darme cuenta, los que caían estaban a salvo. Él me miró y dijo: "Darnos prisa no debemos. Confusa tu mente se vuelve. Una forma de violencia la prisa es. El lado oscuro". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">I had set off to the local marketplace early in the morning. Once I arrived, the usual hustle and bustle of the area had seemingly been replaced by lethargic, slow, and distracted patrons. Not terribly uncommon - on Coruscant you find many small-time celebrities who can bring most any area of the city to a standstill. Pushing my way through towards the clothing district, I was resolved not to be yet another blank-eyed fan. In my haste, I pushed with too much gusto. The resulting succession of tumbling bodies poured outward from me in all directions, knocking more than a few people off the causeway, towards their death below. In a blur of green, I felt something fly overhead. Before I realized it, those falling were saved. And then he looked at me and spoke one sentence: “Hurry we must not. Muddled your mind becomes. A form of violence haste is. The dark side.” [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>