<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">S.V.E.R. Expressionist Painting</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tableau expressionniste S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Expressionistisches S.V.E.R.-Gemälde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dipinto espressionista S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuadro expresionista de S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">表現派絵画 セイバー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">S.V.E.R. 인상파 그림</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SVER Expressionist Painting</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">SVER表現主義油畫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">SVER表現主義油畫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">SVER Expressionist Painting</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This unknown artist's painting of a S.V.E.R. warzone uses a dark palette to represent the struggle of the Shadow War. Own a piece of history that will look amazing in any apartment and prove that you're in touch with the movement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cet artiste anonyme dépeint une zone d'opération de S.V.E.R., privilégiant une palette sombre pour dépeindre la Guerre de l'ombre. Achetez ce fragment d'histoire et installez-le dans votre appartement. Montrez-leur que vous êtes dans le coup. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Gemälde eines unbekannten Künstlers spiegelt mit dunklen Farben ein S.V.E.R.-Einsatzgebiet wider, um die Kämpfe des Schattenkrieges darzustellen. Dieses Stück Geschichte macht sich hervorragend in jedem Apartment und zeigt, dass Sie dazugehören. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo dipinto di un artista sconosciuto raffigura una zona di guerra della S.V.E.R. con tonalità scure per meglio rappresentare la conflittualità della Guerra Ombra. Questo pezzo di storia si intonerà benissimo al vostro appartamento e dimostrerà la vostra affiliazione con il gruppo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este cuadro de autor desconocido muestra una zona de combate de S.V.E.R. y utiliza una gama de colores oscuros para representar las dificultades del Conflicto Global. Hazte con un pedazo de historia que quedará estupendo en tu apartamento y demostrará que eres un entendido del arte.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">暗いパレットを主に使用してセイバーの戦場を表現したこの絵画はシャドー戦争の苦闘を表している。 戦争の惨さも表現した無名の画家作。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">작자 미상의 이 그림은 어두운 색채로 그림자 전쟁 속의 투쟁을 형상화했습니다. 어느 아파트에서나 환상적으로 보일 역사의 한 부분을 지금 구입하십시오. 대세는 S.V.E.R.입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This unknown artist's painting of a SVER warzone uses a dark palette to represent the struggle of the Shadow War. Own a piece of history that will look amazing in any apartment, and prove that you're in touch with the movement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這是由一位不知名畫家所畫的SVER戰場油畫，使用暗色系的顏料以描繪戰爭的灰暗面。擁有歷史的一面可讓任何個人空間呈現不同的風貌，並且讓您體會時代的變遷。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這是由一位不知名畫家所畫的SVER戰場油畫，使用暗色系的顏料以描繪戰爭的灰暗面。擁有歷史的一面可讓任何個人空間呈現不同的風貌，並且讓您體會時代的變遷。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This unknown artist's painting of a SVER warzone uses a dark palette to represent the struggle of the Shadow War. Own a piece of history that will look amazing in any apartment, and prove that you're in touch with the movement. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>