<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Pearl Diver Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le pêcheur de perles appartement</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Perlentaucher: Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Appartamento Pescatore di perle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apartamento Buscador de perlas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">The Pearl Diver Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">펄 다이버 아파트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Pearl Diver Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">珍珠潛水員公寓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">珍珠潛水員公寓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Pearl Diver Apartment</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Spend some time beneath the waves in your own submarine, The Pearl Diver. Designed for combing through the sea floor, this underwater vessel is enclosed by glass to allow you to fully enjoy the aquatic sea life. Reward you and your friends with the exclusive Pearl Diver Mini-Fish Tank furniture item, only available in The Pearl Diver Apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Passez quelque temps sous les vagues dans votre sous-marin propre, Le pêcheur de perles. Conçu pour le peignage à travers le plancher de la mer, ce bateau sous-marin est fermé par un verre pour vous permettre de profiter pleinement de la vie marine aquatique. Récompense vous et vos amis dans le but exclusif Le pêcheur de perles Mini-Fish meuble réservoir, seulement disponible dans l'appartement Le pêcheur de perles. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verbringe in deinem eigenen U-Boot "Der Perlentaucher" etwas Zeit unterhalb der Wellen. Dieses Unterwassergefährt wurde dafür entwickelt, den Meeresboden zu durchkämmen, und hat eine Glashülle, damit du die Unterwasserwelt vollauf genießen kannst. Belohne dich und deine Freunde mit dem exklusiven Perlentaucher-Mini-Aquarium, das nur im Perlentaucher-Apartment erhältlich ist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Passa del tempo sotto le onde nel tuo personale sottomarino, il Pescatore di perle. Progettato per setacciare i fondali marini, questo vascello delle profondità è ricoperto di vetri, così da permetterti di godere della vista della vita sottomarina. Ricompensa te e i tuoi amici con un esclusivo oggetto d'arredamento Mini acquario Pescatore di perle, disponibile unicamente nell'Appartamento Pescatore di perle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pasa algo de tiempo bajo las olas en tu propio submarino, el Buscador de perlas. Diseñada para peinar el fondo marino, esta nave está recubierta de cristal para que disfrutes de la vida submarina en todo su esplendor. Premia a tus amigos y a ti también con el exclusivo Mini tanque de peces Buscador de perlas solo disponible en el apartamento Buscador de perlas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Spend some time beneath the waves in your own submarine, The Pearl Diver. Designed for combing through the sea floor, this underwater vessel is enclosed by glass to allow you to fully enjoy the aquatic sea life. Reward you and your friends with the exclusive Pearl Diver Mini-Fish Tank furniture item, only available in The Pearl Diver Apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">여러분의 잠수함, 펄 다이버를 타고 해수면 아래에서 시간을 보내세요. 해저를 이동할 수 있도록 디자인된 이 잠수함은 여러분이 수중 생활을 최대로 즐길 수 있도록 유리로 만들어져 있습니다. 펄 다이버 아파트에서만 제공되는 독점적인 펄 다이버 미니 어항으로 여러분과 여러분의 친구들에게 리워드를 선물하세요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Spend some time beneath the waves in your own submarine, The Pearl Diver. Designed for combing through the sea floor, this underwater vessel is enclosed by glass to allow you to fully enjoy the aquatic sea life. Reward you and your friends with the exclusive Pearl Diver Mini-Fish Tank furniture item, only available in The Pearl Diver Apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">乘坐您的私人潛水艇「珍珠潛水員」，在海底度過美好時光。這架潛水艇擅於在海床運行，船身以玻璃製造，讓您欣賞海底生態。獨家的珍珠潛水員迷你魚缸獎品道具只在珍珠潛水員公寓內才可獲得，用來送給自己和好友吧。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">乘坐您的私人潛水艇「珍珠潛水員」，在海底度過美好時光。這架潛水艇擅於在海床運行，船身以玻璃製造，讓您欣賞海底生態。獨家的珍珠潛水員迷你魚缸獎品道具只在珍珠潛水員公寓內才可獲得，用來送給自己和好友吧。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Spend some time beneath the waves in your own submarine, The Pearl Diver. Designed for combing through the sea floor, this underwater vessel is enclosed by glass to allow you to fully enjoy the aquatic sea life. Reward you and your friends with the exclusive Pearl Diver Mini-Fish Tank furniture item, only available in The Pearl Diver Apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>