<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Star Dolphy Figurine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Figurine de Dolphy étoilé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stern-Dolphy-Figur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Statuetta Dolphy stella</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Figurita de Dolphy de estrellas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">星のドルフィーフィギュア</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Star Dolphy Figurine</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Given to players who bet on the Dolphy that won 1st place in the Dolphy Race.\nPlayers who have their own “Dolphy room” can customise their Dolphy to be the same colour and design as this figurine.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Attribuée aux joueurs qui pronostiquent le Dolphy vainqueur d'une Course de Dolphies.\nTout joueur ayant un “Dolphydrome” peut personnaliser son Dolphy et lui donner la même couleur et les mêmes motifs que cette figurine.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wird an Spieler verliehen, die bei einem Dolphy-Rennen auf das Sieger-Dolphy gesetzt haben.\nSpieler, die ihren eigenen „Dolphy-Raum“ besitzen, können ihr Dolphy anpassen und ihm die Farbe und das Design dieser Figur verleihen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Viene assegnata ai giocatori che scommettono sul Dolphy che arriva primo in una Gara di Dolphy.\nI giocatori che hanno una "Stanza di Dolphy" possono personalizzare il proprio Dolphy con lo stesso colore e aspetto di questa statuetta.\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Se entrega a los jugadores que apuesten por el Dolphy que obtenga la 1ª posición en la carrera.\nLos jugadores que tengan un "cuarto de Dolphy" propio podrán personalizar su Dolphy para que sea del mismo color que esta figurita.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドルフィーレースで見事１位を当てたプレイヤーに贈られるフィギュアです。\n「ドルフィールーム」でドルフィー育成中の方は、このフィギュアと同じデザインがドルフィーのカスタマイズとして使用可能になります。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Given to players who bet on the Dolphy that won 1st place in the Dolphy Race.\nPlayers who have their own “Dolphy room” can customize their Dolphy to be the same color and design as this figurine.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>