<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sowfa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaire de Porc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Pig Stuhl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pig Sedia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Silla de Cerdo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sowfa</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Place pig in personal space. Rub with seasonings, oil and basil. Arrange the pig so that the desired view and can be soaked in. Sit on the pig for 2 to 2 and a half hours until your cheeks are tender.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Placez cochon dans l'espace personnel. Frottez-les avec les assaisonnements, l'huile et le basilic. Disposer le porc afin que la vue souhaitée et peut être trempé po ​​Asseyez-vous sur le porc pendant 2 à 2 heures et demie jusqu'à ce que votre joues soient tendres.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Legen Sie die Katze im persönlichen Bereich. Rub mit Gewürzen, Öl und Basilikum. Ordnen Sie das Schwein, so dass die gewünschte Ansicht und in. Setzen Sie sich auf das Schwein für 2 bis 2 und eine halbe Stunde kann eingeweicht werden, bis die Wangen zart sind.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Luogo di maiale nello spazio personale. Strofinare con condimenti, olio e basilico. Disporre il maiale in modo che la vista desiderata e possono essere messi a bagno in Sedersi sul maiale per 2 a 2 ore e mezzo fino a quando le guance sono teneri.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lugar de cerdo en el espacio personal. Frotar con los condimentos, aceite y albahaca. Organizar el cerdo para que la vista que desee y puede ser absorbido pulg Siéntese en el cerdo de 2 a 2 horas y media hasta que estén tiernas mejillas.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Place pig in personal space. Rub with seasonings, oil and basil. Arrange the pig so that the desired view and can be soaked in. Sit on the pig for 2 to 2 and a half hours until your cheeks are tender.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>