<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bundle: race-track construction kit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bundle: piste de course en kit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bundle: Rennbahn-Baukasten</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bundle: kit di costruzione di una pista</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bundle: kit de construcción de una pista de carreras</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Bundle: race-track construction kit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Build your own race tracks in any private space with this bundle containing 5 different sections: a start piece, a straight section, a turn, a bump, and a junction! The 5 elements come as flooring furniture that you can place wherever you like in your apartment or clubhouse. Design the race track of your dreams, equip your favourite locomotion object and challenge your friends to a race![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Construisez votre propre piste de course, dans n'importe quel espace privé, grâce à ce bundle contenant 5 sections différentes: une grille de départ, une ligne droite, un virage, une bosse et un croisement! Les 5 éléments sont des meubles que vous pouvez positionner où bon vous semble dans votre appartement ou Club-house. Construisez la piste de vos rêves, munissez-vous de votre moyen de locomotion favori, et invitez vos amis à faire la course![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bauen Sie Ihre eigene Rennstrecken in ihrem privaten Raum, mit diesem Bundle mit 5 verschiedenen Sektionen: ein Abfahrt, eine gerade Abschnitt, eine Drehung, eine Beule, und eine Kreuzung. Die 5 Elemente sind Möbeln, die Sie platzieren können, wo immer Sie wollen. Entwerfen Sie die Rennbahn Ihrer Träume, rüsten Sie Ihre Lieblings-Fahrzeug, und fordern Sie Ihre Freunde zu einem Rennen![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Costruisci la tua pista, in qualsiasi spazio privato, con questo bundle contenente cinque diverse sezioni: uno inizio, una linea retta, una curva, un dosso e un incrocio! I 5 elementi sono mobili che puoi posizionare dove si vuole nel vostro appartamento o club house. Costruire la pista dei tuoi sogni, afferrare il vostro modo preferito di trasporto, e invita i tuoi amici a correre [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Construye tus propias pistas de carreras en cualquier espacio privado con este bundle que contiene 5 secciones diferentes: una pieza de inicio, una sección recta, una curva, un golpe, y un cruce! Los 5 elementos vienen como muebles que se puede colocar donde quieras en tu apartamento o club-house. Diseñar el circuito de carreras de sus sueños, equipar su objeto locomoción favorito, y reta a tus amigos a una carrera! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Build your own race tracks in any private space with this bundle containing 5 different sections: a start piece, a straight section, a turn, a bump, and a junction! The 5 elements come as flooring furniture that you can place wherever you like in your apartment or clubhouse. Design the race track of your dreams, equip your favourite locomotion object and challenge your friends to a race![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>