<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Welcome</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to Audi Piano, below is how to become the best pianist and delight the patrons of the Audi Concert Hall with one of three fantastic symphonies.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue dans Audi Piano, vous découvrirez ci-dessous comment devenir le meilleur pianiste et ravir les patrons du Concert Hall Audi avec l'un de ces trois chefs-d'oeuvre fantastiques.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen bei Audi Piano 2.0! Es folgt eine Anleitung, wie Sie der beste Pianist werden und die Mäzene der Audi-Konzerthalle mit einer der drei fantastischen Symphonien begeistern.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuto ad Audi Piano. Scopri qui sotto come diventare il pianista migliore e deliziare i patroni della Sala Concerti Audi con una delle tre fantastiche sinfonie.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido a Audi Piano, abajo se muestra cómo convertirte en el mejor pianista y deleitar al público del Audi Concert Hall con una de estas tres excelentes sinfonías.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Aim</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Score by pressing the appropriate combination of buttons when each note is within the Hit Zone. The nearer the center of the Hit Zone the more points you will score. Hit as many notes as possible in a row to build your Streak, your Multiplier and ultimately your score.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Marquez des points en appuyant sur la bonne combinaison de touches lorsque chaque note se situe dans la zone de jeu. Appuyez le plus près possible du centre de la zone de jeu pour marquer le maximum de points. Frappez autant de notes que possible à la suite pour améliorer votre série, votre multiplicateur et, au final, votre score.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sobald sich die Note in der Treffer-Zone befindet, müssen Sie die richtige Tasten-Kombination drücken. So erhalten Sie Punkte! Je mehr Sie in die Mitte der Treffer-Zone treffen, desto mehr Punkte gibt es! Je mehr Noten Sie hintereinander treffen, desto höher fallen Ihre Serie, Ihr Multiplikator und - natürlich - Ihre Punktzahl aus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guadagna punti premendo la giusta combinazione di pulsanti non appena ciascuna nota si trova all'interno della Zona Obiettivo. Più ti avvicini al centro della Zona Obiettivo, più punti guadagni. Colpisci più note possibili una dopo l'altra per far aumentare la tua Serie, il tuo Moltiplicatore e, di conseguenza, il tuo punteggio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Consigue puntos presionando la combinación correcta de botones cuando cada nota se encuentre en la Zona de aciertos. Cuanto más en el centro estés de la Zona de aciertos, ganarás más puntos. Acierta el máximo de notas seguidas para aumentar tu Racha, tu Multiplicador y, en último lugar, tu puntuación.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Controls 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Hit Zone is indicated by the shaded area on the left. The notes will start scrolling in from the right. The next note to hit is shown as a thin vertical line passing through that note.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La zone de jeu est indiquée par la zone ombrée située sur la gauche. Les notes commencent à défiler par la droite. La prochaine note à presser est figurée par une ligne verticale fine qui traverse chaque note.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Treffer-Zone befindet sich links im schattierten Bereich. Der Notenlauf erfolgt von rechts. Durch die nächste Note, die Sie anschlagen müssen, verläuft eine dünne, senkrechte Linie.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Zona Obiettivo è indicata dall'area sfumata a sinistra. Le note inizieranno a entrare scorrendo da destra. La prossima nota da colpire appare come una sottile linea verticale che la attraversa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La Zona de aciertos es la zona oscura de la izquierda. Las notas empezarán a aparecer desde la derecha. La siguiente que hay que acertar aparece como una fina línea vertical por encima de esa nota.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Controls 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use #X (or  #D ) to hit the blue cross note.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez #X (ou #D ) pour presser une note barrée de couleur bleu.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit #X (oder #D ) schlagen sie eine blaue Kreuz-Note an.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usa #X (o #D) per colpire la nota con la croce azzurra.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Utiliza #C (o #D ) para acertar la nota de la cruz azul.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Controls 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use #S (or  #L ) to hit a pink square note.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez #S (ou #L ) pour presser une note carrée de couleur rose.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit #S (oder #L ) schlagen sie eine rosafarbene Quadrat-Note an.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usa #S (o #L ) per colpire una nota con il quadrato rosa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Utiliza #S (o #L ) para acertar la nota del cuadrado rosa.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Controls 4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use #T (or  #U ) to hit a green triangle note.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez #T (ou #U ) pour presser une note triangle de couleur verte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit #T (oder #U ) schlagen Sie eine grüne Dreieck-Note an.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usa #T (o #U ) per colpire una nota con il triangolo verde.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Utiliza #T (o #U ) para acertar la nota del triángulo verde.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Controls 5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use #C (or  #R ) to hit a red circle note.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez #C (ou #R ) pour presser une note ronde de couleur rouge.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit #C (oder #R ) schlagen Sie eine rote Kreis-Note an.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usa #C (o #R ) per colpire una nota con il cerchio rosso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Utiliza #C (o #R ) para acertar la nota del círculo rojo.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Controls 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">To play a chord hold any of the shoulder buttons ( #L1 , #L2 , #R1 or #R2 ) and then press the appropriate button as specified on the stave. Vertically stacked notes connected by a line represent a chord.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour jouer un accord, maintenez appuyée n'importe quelle touche #L1 , #L2 , #R1 or #R2 , et pressez ensuite la touche appropriée comme indiqué sur la portée. Les notes empilées verticalement reliées par une ligne représentent les accords.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Einen Akkord spielen Sie, indem Sie #L1 , #L2 , #R1 oder #R2 gedrückt halten und dann die auf der Notenlinie jeweils angegebene Taste  drücken. Übereinander liegende Noten, die mit einer Linie verbunden sind, stellen einen Akkord dar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per suonare un accordo, tieni premuto uno qualsiasi dei pulsanti laterali #L1 , #L2 , #R1 o #R2 e poi premi il pulsante indicato sul pentagramma. Una serie di note sovrapposte verticalmente e collegate da una linea rappresenta un accordo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Para tocar el acorde, mantén presionado cualquiera de los siguientes botones (#L1 , #L2 , #R1 o #R2 ) y luego presiona el botón que corresponda según indique el pentagrama. Las notas que aparecen juntas en vertical unidas por una línea representan un acorde.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">AllTimeScores</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">All Time High Scores</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Scores records absolus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rekord-Highscores</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tutti i punteggi elevati</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Altas puntuaciones</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TodaysScores</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Today's High Scores</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Meilleurs scores du jour</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tages-Highscores</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Punteggi elevati di oggi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Altas puntuaciones de hoy</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">YesterdaysScores</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Yesterday's High Scores</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Meilleurs scores d'hier</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vortages-Highscores</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Punteggi elevati di ieri</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Altas puntuaciones de ayer</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Friends</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Friends</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Amis</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Freunde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Amici</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Amigos</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Audi Concert Hall Scoreboards</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Audi Concert Hall Scoreboards</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Audi Concert Hall Scoreboards</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Audi Concert Hall Scoreboards</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Audi Concert Hall Scoreboards</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Audi Concert Hall Scoreboards [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Audi Concert Hall Scoreboards [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Audi Concert Hall Scoreboards [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Audi Concert Hall Scoreboards [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Audi Concert Hall Scoreboards [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>