<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Icaras Stool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Icaras Stool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tabouret Icaras</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Icaras-Hocker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sgabello Icaras</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Taburete de Icaras</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Icaras Stool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Icaras 의자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Icaras Stool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Icaras 腳凳</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Icaras 腳凳</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Icaras Stool</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Form, function and style were smashed together in the Icaras Apparel factory and out popped this beautiful stool. Offering the perfect, ergonomic support for your tired spinal column while you quaff your evening cocktail of choice. Icaras asks, are you sitting comfortably?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Form, function and style were smashed together in the Icaras Apparel factory and out popped this beautiful stool. Offering the perfect, ergonomic support for your tired spinal column while you quaff your evening cocktail of choice. Icaras asks, are you sitting comfortably? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Élégance, fonctionnalité et style ont été fusionnés dans l'usine d'accessoires d'Icaras pour façonner ce merveilleux tabouret. Il offrira un soutien ergonomique optimal à votre colonne vertébrale durement éprouvée pendant que vous engloutirez votre cocktail préféré. Icaras vous demande : êtes-vous vraiment bien assis ? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese wunderschöne Mischung aus Form, Funktionalität und Stil entstand in den Werken von Icaras Apparel. Der Hocker bietet dem müden Rückgrat die perfekte ergonomische Stütze, während man gemütlich seinen Lieblingscocktail schlürft. Icaras lässt fragen: Ist es bequem genug? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Forma, funzionalità e stile si fondono in questo bellissimo sgabello Icaras. Offre un supporto ergonomico perfetto che alla sera vi aiuterà a rilassare la colonna vertebrale mentre sorseggiate il vostro cocktail. La Icaras vorrebbe sapere se vi sembra abbastanza comodo... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La fábrica de equipamiento de Icaras ha fusionado los conceptos de forma, función y estilo para dar vida a este bello taburete. Te ofrece un sustento perfecto y ergonómico para la espalda cansada, mientras disfrutas de tu bebida favorita al final del día. Icaras te pregunta: ¿estás cómodo? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Form, function and style were smashed together in the Icaras Apparel factory and out popped this beautiful stool. Offering the perfect, ergonomic support for your tired spinal column while you quaff your evening cocktail of choice. Icaras asks, are you sitting comfortably? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Icaras Apparel 에서 제작한 이 의자는 멋과 기능성, 그리고 독특한 디자인을 접목시킨 명작입니다. 좋아하는 칵테일을 홀짝이며 이 의자에 앉으면 당신의 피곤한 허리와 등이 씻은듯이 나아집니다. 편안하시죠? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Form, function and style were smashed together in the Icaras Apparel factory and our popped this beautiful stool. Offering the perfect, ergonomic support for your tired spinal column while you quaff your evening cocktail of choice. Icaras asks, are you sitting comfortably? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">外形、功能和型格兼備的Icaras家具公司為您呈獻這個別出心裁的腳凳，讓您在暢飲美酒的同時為疲勞的脊骨帶來舒適的依靠。Icaras為您的坐姿帶來最貼心的照顧。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">外形、功能和型格兼備的Icaras家具公司為您呈獻這個別出心裁的腳凳，讓您在暢飲美酒的同時為疲勞的脊骨帶來舒適的依靠。Icaras為您的坐姿帶來最貼心的照顧。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Form, function and style were smashed together in the Icaras Apparel factory and out popped this beautiful stool. Offering the perfect, ergonomic support for your tired spinal column while you quaff your evening cocktail of choice. Icaras asks, are you sitting comfortably? [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>