<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">S.V.E.R. Footlocker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Malle S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">S.V.E.R.-Truhe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scarpiera S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Baúl de S.V.E.R.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ベッドトランクケース セイバー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">S.V.E.R. 락커</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SVER Footlocker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">SVER裝備箱</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">SVER裝備箱</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">SVER Footlocker</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">S.V.E.R. gear is as battle scarred as it comes, but they flaunt it like a badge of honour.  If you're not afraid of getting your boots dirty, S.V.E.R. invites you to try this footlocker.   [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'équipement S.V.E.R. est aussi abîmé que possible, mais les soldats en tirent une certaine fierté. Si vous n'avez pas peur de vous salir les bottes, S.V.E.R. vous invite à essayer cette malle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">S.V.E.R.-Ausrüstung trägt nicht selten die Narben unzähliger Schlachten, doch sie wirken nicht wie ein Makel, sondern vielmehr wie ein Ehrenorden. Wenn Staub und Dreck an Ihren Händen kein Problem darstellen, lädt Sie S.V.E.R. herzlich dazu ein, es mit dieser Truhe zu probieren.   [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'attrezzatura della S.V.E.R. porta i segni della battaglia ma anche questo è motivo di vanto.  Se non ti importa che gli stivali siano inzaccherati, la S.V.E.R. ti invita a provare questa scarpiera. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El equipo de S.V.E.R. está desgastadísimo después de tantos combates, pero a ellos les gusta lucirlo como si fuera una medalla de honor. Si no te importa que se te ensucien las botas, S.V.E.R. te anima a que pruebes su baúl. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">セイバーのギアはすべてボロボロで戦歴を物語っている。だがそれが誇りであり、セイバーの真骨頂だ。汚れるのが怖いなら他をあたれ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">S.V.E.R.의 모든 장비는 전투의 흉한 흔적을 하나씩 가지고 있습니다. 그러나 그들에게 상처란 훈장과도 같은 것. 신발을 더럽히는 것이 상관 없다면, S.V.E.R.의 락커를 시험해 보십시오. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SVER gear is as battle scarred as it comes, but they flaunt it like a badge of honor. If you're not afraid of getting your boots dirty, SVER invites you to try this footlocker. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">SVER的裝備常常佈滿戰鬥痕跡，但他們卻引以為傲。如果你不怕弄污靴子，SVER 誠邀你試用這款裝備箱。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">SVER的裝備常常佈滿戰鬥痕跡，但他們卻引以為傲。如果你不怕弄污靴子，SVER 誠邀你試用這款裝備箱。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">SVER gear is as battle scarred as it comes, but they flaunt it like a badge of honor. If you're not afraid of getting your boots dirty, SVER invites you to try this footlocker. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>