<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">High-neck Sweater &amp; Checkered Miniskirt Set (White &amp; Blue, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set pull à col roulé et minijupe à carreaux (blanc et bleu, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Rollkragenpullover &amp; Karierter Minirock Set (weiß &amp; blau, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set maglioncino a collo alto e minigonna con trama a scacchiera (bianco e blu, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de suéter de cuello alto y minifalda a cuadros (blanco y azul, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ハイネックセーターとミニスカートセット（ホワイト＆ブルー・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* ハイネックセット2</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* ハイネックセット2</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* ハイネックセット2</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* ハイネックセット2</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">High-neck Sweater &amp; Checkered Miniskirt Set (White &amp; Blue, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A three item set containing a white high-neck sweater, a blue checkered miniskirt, and a combination item of both.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nCuteness: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- High-neck Sweater (White, Women) (Tops)\n- Checkered Miniskirt (Blue, Women) (Bottoms)\n- High-necked Sweater &amp; Checkered Miniskirt (White &amp; Blue, Women) (Combination)\n\n*By purchasing this set, each item will be added its respective category. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de trois objets contenant un pull à col roulé blanc, une minijupe à carreaux bleue et une combinaison des deux objets.\nDéfense : ★\nCharme : ★★★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Pull col roulé (blanc, femme) (Hauts)\n- Minijupe à carreaux (bleue, femme) (Bas)\n- Pull à col roulé et minijupe à carreaux (blanc et bleu, femme) (Combinaison)\n\n*En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein dreiteiliges Set, bestehend aus einem weißem Rollkragenpullover, einem blau-karierten Minirock und einer Kombination aus beiden Kleidungsstücken.\nVerteidigung: ★\nNiedlichkeit: ★★★\nDas Set beinhaltet die folgenden Kleidungsstücke:\n\n- Rollkragenpullover (weiß, für Frauen) (Oberteile)\n- Karierter Minirock (blau, für Frauen) (Beinkleider)\n- Rollkragenpullover &amp; Karierter Minirock (weiß &amp; blau, für Frauen) (Kombination)\n\n*Mit dem Kauf dieses Sets wird jeder Gegenstand in die jeweilige Kategorie hinzugefügt. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set di 3 elementi contenente un maglioncino a collo alto bianco, una minigonna decorata con una trama a scacchiera blu e un completo comprendente entrambi i capi.\nDifesa: ★\nBellezza: ★★★\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Maglioncino a collo alto (bianco, da donna) (parti superiori)\n- Minigonna con trama a scacchiera (blu, da donna) (parti inferiori)\n- Set maglioncino a collo alto e minigonna con trama a scacchiera (bianco e blu, da donna) (completo)\n\n*Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Un paquete de tres artículos que consta de un suéter de cuello alto en color blanco, una minifalda azul a cuadros y la combinación de ambos.\nDefensa: ★\nTernura: ★★★\nEste conjunto incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Suéter de cuello alto (blanco, mujer) (torso)\n- Minifalda a cuadros (azul, mujer) (piernas)\n- Suéter de cuello alto y minifalda a cuadros (blanco y azul, mujer) (combinación)\n\n*Adquiriendo este paquete, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">白いハイネックセーターと、青いミニスカートと、それらを組み合わせたものの３点セット。\n防御力：　★\nかわいさ：　★★★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・ハイネックセーター（ホワイト・女性）（トップス）\n・チェックミニスカート（ブルー・女性）（ボトムス）\n・ハイネックセーターとチェックミニスカート（ホワイト＆ブルー・女性）（組み合わせ）\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A three item set containing a white high-neck sweater, a blue checkered miniskirt, and a combination item of both.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nCuteness: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- High-neck Sweater (White, Women) (Tops)\n- Checkered Miniskirt (Blue, Women) (Bottoms)\n- High-necked Sweater &amp; Checkered Miniskirt (White &amp; Blue, Women) (Combination)\n\n*By purchasing this set, each item will be added its respective category. [#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
