<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Spun'mas Tree</LANG>
	<LANG ID="de-DE">Spun‘mas-Baum</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-US">Spun'mas Tree</LANG>
	<LANG ID="es-ES">Árbol De Spun'mas</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Arbre De Spun'mas</LANG>
	<LANG ID="it-IT">Albero Di Spun'mas</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dances, shines and fills your apartment with Spun'mas cheer. Comes with a Countdown to Spun'mas wall hanging and a special present for all good Spunlings (and their friends) which can be opened on Spun'mas day only! [#Legal]</LANG>
	<LANG ID="de-DE">Tanzt, leuchtet und füllt dein Apartment mit Spun‘mas-Stimmung. Wird mit einem „Countdown bis Spun‘mas“-Wandbehang und einem besonderen Geschenk für alle braven Spunlings geliefert, das nur am Spun‘mas-Tag geöffnet werden kann! [#Legal]</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-US">Dances, shines and fills your apartment with Spun'mas cheer. Comes with a Countdown to Spun'mas wall hanging and a special present for all good Spunlings (and their friends) which can be opened on Spun'mas day only! [#Legal]</LANG>
	<LANG ID="es-ES">Baila, brilla y llena tu apartamento con la alegría de la Spun'mas. Viene con un cuenta atrás de pared para Spun'mas y un regalo especial para todos los Spunlings buenos (y sus amigos) que solo se puede abrir el día de Spun'mas. [#Legal]</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Il danse, il brille et remplit votre appartement de joyeux chants de Spun'mas. Fourni avec un calendrier mural qui compte les jours avant Spun'mas et un cadeau très spécial pour tous les Spunlings sages (et leurs amis), à ne pas ouvrir avant Spun'mas ! [#Legal]</LANG>
	<LANG ID="it-IT">Danza, luccica e riempie il tuo appartamento di gioioso spirito di Spun'mas. Fornito di un Calendario Spun'mas da muro e di un regalo speciale per tutti gli Spunling buoni (e per i loro amici) da aprire esclusivamente il giorno di Spun'mas! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">happy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Happy Spun'mas!</LANG>
	<LANG ID="de-DE">Frohe Spun'mas!</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-US">Happy Spun'mas!</LANG>
	<LANG ID="es-ES">¡Feliz Spun'mas!</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Joyeux Spun'mas!</LANG>
	<LANG ID="it-IT">Buon Spun'mas!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>