<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Glowing Death Mask Back Tattoo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tatouage du dos Masque embrasé de la mort</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rückentätowierung 'Leuchtende Todesmaske'</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tatuaggio brillante con Maschera della Morte sulla schiena</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tatuaje Brillante de Màscara de la Muerte en la espalda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_31</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_31</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_31</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_31</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_31</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Glowing Death Mask Back Tattoo</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Living Ink: Glowing Death Mask.  Behind this mask is the face of a man unlike any known to the living.  Gazing into the glowing eyes, however, you know he spells trouble.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Living Ink: Masque embrasé de la mort. Derrière ce masque ce trouve le visage d'un homme comme nul autre connu des vivants. Regardant dans les yeux embrasées, pourtant tu sais qu'il est a problèmes.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Living Ink: Glühende Todesmaske. Hinter dieser Maske verbirgt sich das Gesicht eines Mannes, der nicht unter den Lebenden weilt. Wenn du in seine leuchtenden Augen blickst, wirst du den Ärger spüren.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Living Ink: Maschera della Morte Brillante. Dietro questa maschera si nasconde il volto di un uomo sconosciuto  per qualsiasi creatura vivente. Sai che guardando dentro i suoi occhi brillanti, avrai problemi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Living Ink: Màscara de la Muerte Brillante. Detràs de èsta màscara se encuentra la cara de un hombre desconocido para cualquier creatura viviente. Si lo ves a los ojos brillantes que tiene, sabes que solo traerà problemas.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_31</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_31</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_31</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_31</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_31</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Living Ink: Glowing Death Mask.  Behind this mask is the face of a man unlike any known to the living.  Gazing into the glowing eyes, however, you know he spells trouble.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>