<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Legs_bi_soldier_Re</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Black Irem Brigade Trousers (Replica, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pantalon de la Brigade Noire Irem (Réplique, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Black Irem Brigade"-Hose (Replik, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pantaloni della Brigata Black Irem (replica, da uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pantalones del Escuadrón Irem Negro (réplica, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブラックアイレム団戦闘員　ボトムス（レプリカ・男性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블랙 아이렘단 팬츠（레플리카, 남성）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Combatant of the Black Irem Brigade - Bottom (Replica/Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">黑色Irem團戰鬥員 褲子（複製品/男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">黑色Irem團戰鬥員 褲子（複製品/男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Black Irem Brigade Trousers (Replica, M)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Legs_bi_soldier_Re_description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A pair of trousers worn by combatants in the Black Irem Brigade, with the posterior designed with a focus on permeability; they offer comfort even in the summer. The developers claim to have even succeeded in dramatically improving the athletic performance of the wearer by keeping the posterior cool. Strange.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un pantalon porté par les combattants de la Brigade Noire Irem, avec l'arrière conçu pour cibler la perméabilité; il offre du confort même en été. Les concepteurs prétendent avoir réussi à améliorer les performances athlétiques du sujet en gardant le postérieur à bonne température. Étrange. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine Hose, die von den Kämpfern der Black Irem Brigade getragen wird. Die luftdurchlässige Rückseite bietet auch im Sommer angenehmen Tragekomfort. Die Hersteller behaupten, dass die athletische Leistung des Trägers durch die kühlende Rückseite dramatisch angehoben wird. Sehr seltsam.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pantaloni indossati dai combattenti della Brigata Black Irem, con la zona posteriore pensata per una perfetta tenuta impermeabile: comfort assoluto anche in piena estate. I progettisti sostengono di aver decisamente migliorato le prestazioni atletiche senza per questo aver dovuto rinunciare alla freschezza delle zone posteriori. Strano.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pantalones que utilizan los combatientes del Escuadrón Irem Negro diseñados para aumentar la permeabilidad de la parte trasera. Son cómodos incluso en verano. Sus desarrolladores afirman que han sido capaces incluso de aumentar enormemente el rendimiento atlético de su portador, gracias a la refrigeración trasera.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブラックアイレム団の戦闘員たちが着用するパンツ。でん部の通気性確保に重点がおかれ、夏でも蒸れることがない。でん部を冷やすことで、なぜか運動能力を飛躍的に高めることに成功していると言う。不思議だ。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블랙 아이렘단의 전투원들이 착용하는 팬츠. 엉덩이의 통기성 확보에 중점을 두어, 여름에도 땀이 나지 않는다. 엉덩이를 시원하게 하면, 왠지 운동능력을 비약적으로 높일 수 있다고 한다. 신기한 일이다.[#Legal]
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The pants worn by Combatants of the Black Irem Brigade. With importance placed on backside breathability, it doesn't get very hot even in the summer. It's said that by keeping the backside cool, athletic performance is enhanced significantly. How mysterious.[#Legal]
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">黑色Irem團的戰鬥員們所穿的褲子。特別重視臀部的透氣性，即使是夏天也不會悶熱。臀部的涼爽不知為何能讓運動能力突飛猛進。簡直是太不可思議了。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">黑色Irem團的戰鬥員們所穿的褲子。特別重視臀部的透氣性，即使是夏天也不會悶熱。臀部的涼爽不知為何能讓運動能力突飛猛進。簡直是太不可思議了。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A pair of trousers worn by combatants in the Black Irem Brigade, with the posterior designed with a focus on permeability; they offer comfort even in the summer. The developers claim to have even succeeded in dramatically improving the athletic performance of the wearer by keeping the posterior cool. Strange.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>