<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Demon Hunter Armor Set (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble d’armure de chasseur de démons (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rüstungssatz Dämonenjäger (Männer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set di armatura da cacciatore di demoni (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de armadura del cazador de demonios (chico)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_18</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_18</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_18</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_18</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_18</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Demon Hunter Armor Set (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The prepared Demon Hunter is the one appropriately girded against the forces of Hell. Each piece of this iconic Demon Hunter armor is deadlier than the last. The set includes the Demon Hunter Hood, Demon Hunter Cloak, Demon Hunter Faulds, Demon Hunter Sabatons, and Demon Hunter Grips.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tout chasseur de démons entraîné se doit d’être correctement vêtu pour affronter les forces de l’Enfer. Chaque pièce de cet ensemble complet d’armure emblématique du chasseur de démons de Diablo III est plus mortelle que la précédente. Il comprend : chaperon de chasseur de démons, cape de chasseur de démons, braconnières de chasseur de démons, solerets de chasseur de démons, poignes de chasseur de démons.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der gerüstete Dämonenjäger ist perfekt gegen die Mächte der Hölle gewappnet. Jeder Teil dieser unverwechselbaren Dämonenjäger-Rüstung ist tödlicher als der vorherige. Der Rüstungssatz umfasst Dämonenjäger-Kapuze, Dämonenjäger-Umhang, Dämonenjäger-Diechlinge, Dämonenjäger-Sabatons und Dämonenjäger-Greifer.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I temibili cacciatori di demoni sono ben attrezzati contro le forze degli Inferi. Le parti del loro set di armatura sono una più letale dell'altra. Il set include Cappuccio da cacciatore di demoni, Mantello da cacciatore di demoni, Falda da cacciatore di demoni, Scarpe appuntate da cacciatore di demoni e Grinfie da cacciatore di demoni.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El cazador de demonios preparado es aquel que está presto y equipado como es debido contra las fuerzas del infierno. Cada elemento de esta simbólica armadura del cazador de demonios es más letal que el anterior. Este conjunto incluye la caperuza, el manteo, el faldar, los escarpes y los mitones del cazador de demonios.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_18 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_18 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_18 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_18 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_18 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The prepared Demon Hunter is the one appropriately girded against the forces of Hell. Each piece of this iconic Demon Hunter armor is deadlier than the last. The set includes the Demon Hunter Hood, Demon Hunter Cloak, Demon Hunter Faulds, Demon Hunter Sabatons, and Demon Hunter Grips.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>