<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Amaterasu Picture Frame</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cadre de l'Amaterasu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Amaterasu-Bilderrahmen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Marco de fotos Amaterasu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cornice per foto Amaterasu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「LOOT™パラダイス・クルーズ」フォトフレーム</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Amaterasu Picture Frame</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Finally, a picture frame you can hang on your boat without it falling off and into the great watery abyss below. This amazing new technology brought to you by science and the geniuses at Loot™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Enfin, voilà un cadre que vous pouvez accrocher sur votre bateau sans qu'il ne tombe à l'eau dans les profondeurs abyssales. Cet incroyable progrès technologique est le fruit de la science et des génies de LOOT™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Endlich kannst du Bilder auf deinem Boot sicher aufhängen, damit sie nicht herunterfallen und in den Tiefen der Meere verschwinden. Nutze diese fantastische neue Technologie, entwickelt von den Genies bei LOOT™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Por fin, un marco de fotos que puede colgarse en un barco sin que se caiga al abismo acuático por el que navegas. Esta novedosa tecnología llega de la mano de la ciencia y los genios de LOOT™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Finalmente una cornice da appendere nella tua barca senza che cada negli abissi dell'oceano. Questa tecnologia avanzatissima proviene dalle grandi abilità dei geni di LOOT™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">やっとできた、ボートに掛けても海に落ちたりしないフォトフレーム！現代科学とLOOT™の天才連中の協力によって提供しました。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Finally, a picture frame you can hang on your boat without it falling off and into the great watery abyss below. This amazing new technology brought to you by science and the geniuses at Loot™. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>