<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rock Reveller – Settee (corner piece)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rock Fêtard - Canapé d’angle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rock-Zecher – Sofa (Ecksitz)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vizi Rock – Divanetto (angolare)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Rockero – Sofá (esquina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rock Reveller – Settee (corner piece)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The time has come to hit the road and party. Take full advantage of the freedoms a virtual world provides, slip the bus into cruise control and join the party at full speed! Just remember… what goes on tour, stays on tour! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C’est l’heure de prendre la route et de faire la fête ! Jouissez des possibilités illimitées d’un monde virtuel ; laissez le chauffeur s’occuper de la route et foncez faire la fête. N’oubliez jamais : ce qui se passe en tournée, reste en tournée! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es ist an der Zeit auf die Pirsch zu gehen und Party zu feiern. Nutze den ganzen Vorteil der Freiheit, den eine virtuelle Welt bietet, schalte deinen Bus auf Autopilot und schließe dich der Party bei voller Geschwindigkeit an … was auf Tour geht, bleibt auf Tour! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">È giunto il momento di mettersi in viaggio e far festa. Approfitta della libertà che un mondo virtuale ti regala, innesta la quarta, un filo di gas e unisciti alla festa! Ricordati solo che... quello che succede durante il tour, riguarda solo il tour! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Ponte en marcha y ven a la fiesta! Aprovéchate de la libertad que te da un mundo virtual, activa el piloto automático del autobús y ¡únete a la fiesta a toda velocidad! Recuerda que... ¡lo que pase en la gira, se queda en la gira! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The time has come to hit the road and party. Take full advantage of the freedoms a virtual world provides, slip the bus into cruise control and join the party at full speed! Just remember… what goes on tour, stays on tour! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>