<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Scream Machine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Machine hurleuse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Warnschreier</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Macchina delle urla</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Máquina de gritos</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Scream Machine</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A Sneak Attack Sound Bank! Scare the bejeezus out of your friends with these frightening screams. Watch 'em jump out of their skin! (This item adds sounds to the free Sneak Attack audio trigger system and includes the male and female Scream Machine Hot Heads.) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Piste pour le répertoire Attaque furtive ! Donnez la trouille de leur vie à vos amis avec ces cris de terreur. Regardez-les sursauter comme jamais ! Également inclus : les Têtes brûlées Machine hurlante, modèles homme et femme. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Sounddatenbank für den perfekten Überraschungsangriff! Mit diesen markerschütternden Schreien wird deinen Freunden garantiert ein gehöriger Schrecken in die Glieder fahren. Ergötz dich an ihrer Panik! Mit geschlechtsspezifischen Warnschreier-Feuerköpfen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una valanga di suoni per i tuoi attacchi furtivi! Fai sobbalzare i tuoi amici con questi urli da brivido. Guardali saltare dallo spavento! In più, include anche le Teste calde Macchina delle urla per uomo e donna. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Una librería de sonidos para ataques sigilosos! Asusta como nunca a tus amigos con estos gritos aterradores. ¡Míralos saltar de miedo! ... e incluye la Máquina de gritos furiosos para hombres y mujeres. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A Sneak Attack Sound Bank! Scare the bejeezus out of your friends with these frightening screams. Watch 'em jump out of their skin! (This item adds sounds to the free Sneak Attack audio trigger system and includes the male and female Scream Machine Hot Heads.) [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>