<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">70" Moodlight LED TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">TV LED Moodlight 70"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">70" Moodlight LED-TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">TV LED 70" con luci d'atmosfera</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Televisión LED 70" con iluminación interactiva</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">７０型ムードライト液晶テレビ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">70인치 무드라이트 LED TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">70" Moodlight LED TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">70吋氣氛燈光液晶電視</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">70吋氣氛燈光液晶電視</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">70" Moodlight LED TV</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The latest model in LED TVs with moodlighting to create the best ambience in your apartment. It comes in various sizes! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce qui se fait de mieux en matière de TV LED ! Elle dispose même d'un éclairage d'ambiance vous permettant de créer une atmosphère chaleureuse dans votre salon. Existe en plusieurs dimensions ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das neueste LED-TV-Modell mit Stimmungslicht, um dein Apartment in eine wunderbare Atmosphäre zu tauchen. In unterschiedlichen Größen erhältlich! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'ultimo modello di TV LED con luci d'atmosfera per creare l'ambiente giusto nel vostro appartamento. Disponibile in diverse dimensioni.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El último modelo de televisiones LED con iluminación interactiva para crear la mejor atmósfera en tu hogar. ¡Disponible en varios tamaños! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この最新型の液晶テレビにはムードライト機能が付いているので最高の部屋の雰囲気を演出します。様々なサイズがあります！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">최신형의 LED TV로, 주거공간에서 최고의 분위기를 연출하기 위한 무드라이팅 기능이 포함됩니다. 다양한 화면 크기로 출시되었습니다![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The latest model in LED TVs with moodlighting to create the best ambience in your apartment. It comes in various sizes! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這款最新款的液晶電視附有氣氛燈光功能，能為房間營造最佳的氣氛，並有多種尺寸！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這款最新款的液晶電視附有氣氛燈光功能，能為房間營造最佳的氣氛，並有多種尺寸！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The latest model in LED TVs with moodlighting to create the best ambience in your apartment. It comes in various sizes! Note: This is a decorative item and not an actual functional TV! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>