<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Chaos Gloves (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Gants du Chaos (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Chaos Handschuhe (männlich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guanti Chaos (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guantes Chaos (masculino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Chaosグローブ（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Chaos글로브(남성용)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Chaos Gloves (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Chaos 手套 (男性用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Chaos 手套 (男性用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Chaos Gloves (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This item includes the Chaos Gloves (Male).\n\nDazzle friends and foes alike with the animated pandemonium of the Chaos clothing line!  Enjoy being the life of every party, and even confound dangerous predators when in a pinch.  There’s nothing that Chaos can’t handle! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cet article contient les gants du Chaos (Homme).\n\nMets-en plein la vue à tes amis ainsi qu'à tes ennemis grâce au pandemonium de la ligne de vêtements du Chaos. Amuses-toi à être un boute-en-train et même à déconcerter les dangereux prédateurs lors des mauvaises passes. Rien n'est impossible pour le Chaos! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser Gegenstand enthält den die Chaos Handschue (männlich).\n\nBlende Freunde und Feinde gleichermaßen mit dem animierten Pandämonium der Chaos Modelinie! Genieße es, im Mittelpunkt jeder Party zu stehen und im Notfall selbst gefährliche Jäger zu verwirren. Es gibt nichts, mit dem Chaos nicht fertig wird! [# Legal] [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo oggetto include i Guanti Chaos (Uomo).\n\nStupisci tutti i tuoi amici con l'allegro pandemonio della linea di vestiti Chaos! Goditi il piacere di essere l'attrazione di ogni festa, e confondi ogni pericoloso predatore! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este artículo incluye los guantes Chaos (masculino).\n\n¡Impresiona a tus amigos y enemigos con el pandemónium animado de la línea de ropa Chaos! Disfruta ser el punto de atención de cada fiesta, e incluso confundir a peligrosos depredadores si fuese necesario. ¡No hay nada que Chao 
no pueda manejar! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このアイテムにはChaosグローブ（男性用）が含まれています。\n\nChaosクローズラインの目も眩むほどのアニメーションで友達や敵をクラクラさせよう！危険なプレデターと遭遇したようなピンチの際でも、毎日のパーティを楽しんじゃおう。Chaosに扱えないものなどない！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 아이템에는 Chaos글로브(남성용)가 포함되어 있습니다. \n\nChaos클로즈 라인의 눈부신 애니메이션으로 친구나 적을 매료시키자!  위험한 Predator와 우연히 만나게 되는 위기에 있어도, 매일 파티를 즐기자. Chaos가 다루지 못하는 것 따위는 없다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This item includes the Chaos Gloves (Male).\n\nDazzle friends and foes alike with the animated pandemonium of the Chaos clothing line!  Enjoy being the life of every party, and even confound dangerous predators when in a pinch.  There’s nothing that Chaos can’t handle! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">这个物品包含 Chaos 手套(男性用)。\n\n穿着有如动画中一般的闪耀Chaos套装来让你的朋友和敌人们感到头晕目眩吧!就算遭遇危险的掠夺者，也能尽情享受生活。 Chaos系列套装让你战无不胜! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">这个物品包含 Chaos 手套(男性用)。\n\n穿着有如动画中一般的闪耀Chaos套装来让你的朋友和敌人们感到头晕目眩吧!就算遭遇危险的掠夺者，也能尽情享受生活。 Chaos系列套装让你战无不胜! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This item includes the Chaos Gloves (Male).\n\nDazzle friends and foes alike with the animated pandemonium of the Chaos clothing line!  Enjoy being the life of every party, and even confound dangerous predators when in a pinch.  There’s nothing that Chaos can’t handle! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>