<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Codebreaker (Hacker Class) (bundle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Codebreaker (Classe pirate) (lot)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Codebreaker (Hacker-Klasse) (Paket)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Codebreaker (classe hacker) (pacchetto)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Codebreaker (clase hacker) (paquete)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コードブレイカー（ハッカークラス）セット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">코드 브레이커 (해커 기체) 세트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Codebreaker (Hacker Class) (bundle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Codebreaker（黑客級)組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Codebreaker（黑客級)組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Codebreaker (Hacker Class) (bundle)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Outfitted with the latest in defensive shielding technology, the Codebreaker disrupts nearby AI systems, turning bot ships into allies. Powerful engines allow for escape when things go from bad to worse. The male and female versions of a special pilot’s helmet are included with the purchase of this ship. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pourvu de la dernière technologie en matière de blindage défensive, le Codebreaker perturbe les systèmes d'IA alentour, transformant les vaisseaux droïdes en alliés. Ses puissants propulseurs lui permettent de s'échapper facilement lorsque les choses tournent mal. Les versions homme et femme du casque de pilote spécial sont incluses avec l'achat de ce vaisseau. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ausgerüstet mit der neuesten Verteidigungsschild-Technologie, stört der Codebreaker nahe AI-Syteme und verwandelt Bot-Schiffe so in Verbündete. Kraftvolle Maschinen erlauben eine schnelle Flucht, wenn etwas schief geht. Die Herren- und Damenversionen eines speziellen Pilotenhelms sind beim Kauf dieses Schiffes inbegriffen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Grazie alle ultime tecnologie nel campo degli scudi difensivi, la Codebreaker neutralizza i sistemi IA vicini, trasformando le navi bot in alleati. I potenti motori permettono la fuga quando gli eventi precipitano. Incluso nell'acquisto della nave, uno speciale casco da pilota in versione per uomo e per donna. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Equipado con la tecnología de escudo defensivo más reciente, el decodificador afecta a los sistemas de IA cercanos, convirtiendo las naves robot en aliadas. Los potentes motores permiten escapar cuando las cosas se complican. Con la compra de esta nave, se incluyen las versiones masculina y femenina del casco de piloto especial. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">最新式の防御シールド技術を施したコードブレイカーは周辺のＡＩシステムを狂わせる。敵ボットの船を味方につけるのもお手の物。形勢不利な時には強力なエンジンで素早く脱出することもできる。\n※購入すると、ミニゲーム「ノーバス・プライム」内で戦闘機を使って遊ぶことができます。\n\n本セットには、アバターのカスタマイズ用の以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n・「コードブレイカーヘルメット（男性用）」（頭）\n・「コードブレイカーヘルメット（女性用）」（頭）\n※購入すると、「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">최신 방어막 기술을 적용한 코드 브레이커는 인접한 기체의 AI 시스템을 망가뜨리고 봇 함선을 아군으로 바꿔버립니다. 강력한 엔진을 이용해 좋지 않은 상황을 쉽게 탈출할 수 있습니다. 이 기체를 구입하면 특별한 조종사 헬멧이 남성용과 여성용 모두 제공됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Outfitted with the latest in defensive shielding technology, the Codebreaker disrupts nearby AI systems, turning bot ships into allies. Powerful engines allow for escape when things go from bad to worse. The male and female versions of a special pilot’s helmet are included with the purchase of this ship. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Codebreaker採用了最新的防衛科技，能干擾附近的AI系統，將機械太空船變成盟友。其強力引擎亦讓你在事態惡化時逃之夭夭。購買此太空船附送男用及女用的特別版飛行員頭盔。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Codebreaker採用了最新的防衛科技，能干擾附近的AI系統，將機械太空船變成盟友。其強力引擎亦讓你在事態惡化時逃之夭夭。購買此太空船附送男用及女用的特別版飛行員頭盔。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Outfitted with the latest in defensive shielding technology, the Codebreaker disrupts nearby AI systems, turning bot ships into allies. Powerful engines allow for escape when things go from bad to worse. The male and female versions of a special pilot’s helmet are included with the purchase of this ship. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>