<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Little Monster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Little Monster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Petit Monstre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kleine Teufel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Piccolo Mostro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Monstruito</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Little Monster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">꼬마 몬스터</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Little Monster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">小魔怪</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">小魔怪</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Little Monster</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">It is covered by small red hairs and has best-listening big ears. It likes to play a practical joke and to eat desserts such as candies and cookies. It often sneaks into human village to search for food.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It is covered by small red hairs and has best-listening big ears. It likes to play a practical joke and to eat desserts such as candies and cookies. It often sneaks into human village to search for food. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le petit monstre a des cheveux roux et des grandes oreilles excellentes, qui est espiègle. Il aime manger des confiseries, commes des bonbons et des biscuits. Il se faufile souvent dans le village des humains pour chercher des alimentations dans la nuit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die kleine Teufel, die ein rothaarige Körper und ein paar große Ohren mit gute Gehör hat, macht gerne Streich. Süßigkeiten wie Bonbons und Kekse sind bei ihr sehr beliebt, dass sie sich oft in der Nacht auf der Such nach Nahrung in die Dorfs der Menschen schleichen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ricoperto da sottilissimi peli rossi, il Piccolo Mostro è birichino, con due orecchi enormi che gli consentono di sentire lontano, ama i dolci, come caramelle e biscottini, spesso s’infiltra di notte nei villaggi degli esseri umani in cerca del cibo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cubierto de pelos rojos, un par de oídos excelentes, es el monstro atravieso, le gusta comer dulces como confides y galletas, se entra amenudo al aldea en la noche en búsqueda de alimentos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">&lt;none&gt; [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">빨간 털을 두르고 있으며 청력이 뛰어난 큰 귀를 갖고 있습니다. 장난기 많은 몬스터이며 캔디와 쿠키 같은 디져트를 좋아하고 컴컴한 밤에 몰래 인간 마을에 침입하여 음식을 찾습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">It is covered by small red hairs and has best-listening big ears. It likes to play a practical joke and to eat desserts such as candies and cookies. It often sneaks into human village to search for food. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">身披紅色細毛，有一對聽力極佳的大耳朵，是愛惡作劇的小魔物，喜歡吃糖果餅乾之類的甜食，經常在夜晚偷偷溜進人類村莊找尋食物。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">身披紅色細毛，有一對聽力極佳的大耳朵，是愛惡作劇的小魔物，喜歡吃糖果餅乾之類的甜食，經常在夜晚偷偷溜進人類村莊找尋食物。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">It is covered by small red hairs and has best-listening big ears. It likes to play a practical joke and to eat desserts such as candies and cookies. It often sneaks into human village to search for food. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>