<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Obsidian Pilot Suit (male) with Obsidian Blade Fighter Ship (bundle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Combinaison de pilote Obsidienne (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Obsidian-Piloten-Anzug (männliche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Uniforme da pilota Obsidian (per uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de Piloto Obsidian (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オブシディアンパイロットスーツ（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">옵시디언 블레이드 전함과 옵시디언 조종사용 수트 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Obsidian Pilot Suit (Men) with Obsidian Blade Fighter Ship</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">黑曜飛行員套裝(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">黑曜飛行員套裝(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Obsidian Pilot Suit (male) with Obsidian Blade Fighter Ship (bundle)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Harness technology from beyond the stars as an Obsidian fighter pilot!  These mysterious benefactors provided humanity with the Novus Prime space station, and they have finally arrived to take a direct hand in the conflict!  This outfit features custom animations utilizing advanced holographic generators.  An Obsidian Blade Fighter Ship is included, which may be used in the Novus Prime space combat game. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Exploitez la technologie au-delà des étoiles comme un pilote de chasse Obsidien! Ces mystérieux bienfaiteurs ont fourni à l'humanité la station spatiale Novus Prime et ils sont finalement arrivés pour prendre part au conflit! Cet équipement dispose d'animations personnalisées utilisant des générateurs holographiques avancés. Un navire de combat Obsidien "Blade" est inclus, qui peut être utilisé dans le jeu de combat spatial Novus Prime. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nutze als Obsidian-Kampfpilot die Technologie von weit hinter den Sternen! Diese mysteriösen Wohltäter haben der Novus Prime Raumstation Menschlichkeit gebracht und sind endlich gekommen, selbst in den Konflikt einzugreifen! Dieses Outfit ermöglicht benutzerspezifische Animationen, indem es fortgeschrittene Holographiegeneratoren nutzt. Dazu gehört ein Obidianklingen-Kampfschiff, welches im Kampf um Novus Prime verwendet werden kann. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La tecnologia delle galassie oltre le stelle a tua disposizione come pilota Obsidian! Questi misteriosi benefattori hanno fornito all'umanità la stazione spaziale Novus Prime, e adesso sono finalmente arrivati per prender parte di persona ai conflitti! Questa tuta vanta di decorazioni personalizzate grazie a dei generatori olografici personalizzati. Nel pacchetto c'è anche un caccia Obsidian, utilizzabile nei confronti a fuoco spaziali della Novus Prime. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Aprovecha la tecnología de más allá de las estrellas como un piloto de combate Obsidian! Estos misteriosos benefactores proveyeron a la humanidad con la estación espacial Novus Prime, ¡y finalmente han llegado para  tener participación directa en el conflicto! Este traje cuenta con animaciones personalizadas utilizando generadores holográficos avanzados. Una nave de combate Blade Obsidian está incluida, la cual puede ser usada en el juego de combate espacial Novus Prime. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">※購入すると、ミニゲーム「ノーバス・プライム」内でオブシディアンブレード戦闘機を使って遊ぶことができます。\n\n
オブシディアン戦闘機パイロットとしてアストロノミカルな技術を使いこなせ！謎のベネファクターは人類にノーバス・プライム宇宙ステーションを送り、ついに戦争に直接かかわることになった。このパイロットスーツは最新のホログラフィックジェネレーターを特徴とする。\n
+ユニークモーション対応[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">옵시디언 전투기 조종사로서 다른 세상의 기술을 활용해보세요! 이들 의문의 생명체들은 인류에게 노부스 프라임 우주 정거장을 제공했으며 그들은 드디어 의견 충돌에 직접 관여하고자 합니다! 이 의상은 고성능 홀로그래픽 생성기를 활용하여 사용자의 고유 애니메이션을 제공합니다. 노부스 프라임 스페이스 컴뱃 게임에서 쓸 수 있는 옵시디언 블레이드 전함도 포함되어 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Harness technology from beyond the stars as an Obsidian fighter pilot!  These mysterious benefactors provided humanity with the Novus Prime space station, and they have finally arrived to take a direct hand in the conflict!  This outfit features custom animations utilizing advanced holographic generators.  An Obsidian Blade Fighter Ship is included, which may be used in the Novus Prime space combat game. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">擁有未知技術的神祕人不只協助人類的Novus Prime宇宙太空站，並在戰爭中對人類伸出援手。這套自訂的特殊裝備配有先進的發電器，也包含了可以在Novus Prime宇宙作戰模式中使用的黑曜戰鬥機。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">擁有未知技術的神祕人不只協助人類的Novus Prime宇宙太空站，並在戰爭中對人類伸出援手。這套自訂的特殊裝備配有先進的發電器，也包含了可以在Novus Prime宇宙作戰模式中使用的黑曜戰鬥機。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Harness technology from beyond the stars as an Obsidian fighter pilot!  These mysterious benefactors provided humanity with the Novus Prime space station, and they have finally arrived to take a direct hand in the conflict!  This outfit features custom animations utilizing advanced holographic generators.  An Obsidian Blade Fighter Ship is included, which may be used in the Novus Prime space combat game. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Specials</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Specials</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Spéciaux</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Besonderheiten</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Speciali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Especiales</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スペシャル</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">스페셜</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Specials</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">特殊</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">特殊</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Specials</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Scan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Scan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Scanner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Scannen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Rileva</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Escanear</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スキャン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">스캔</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Scan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">掃描</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">掃描</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Scan</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Ship Check</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ship Check</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vérification du vaisseau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schiffsprüfung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Controllo della nave</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Revisar Nave</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">シップチェック</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">함선 체크</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ship Check</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">船艙檢查</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">船艙檢查</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ship Check</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>