<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Brokejaw the Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Brokejaw le zombi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Brokejaw die Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Brokejaw la Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Brokejaw the Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_19</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_19</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Brokejaw the Zombie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_19</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_19</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Brokejaw the Zombie</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Brokejaw is a dedicated marathon runner... She won't stop until she gets you, even with that broken jaw! Dress up in the full Brokejaw costume with this bundle. Includes Brokejaw the Zombie's Head, Brokejaw the Zombie's Torso, Brokejaw the Zombie's Legs, Brokejaw the Zombie's Hands, and Brokejaw the Zombie's Feet.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Brokejaw est un coureur de marathon dédié ... Elle ne s'arrêtera pas jusqu'à ce qu'elle vous mène, même avec cette mâchoire cassée! Habillez-vous avec le costume complet Brokejaw avec cet ensemble. Comprend Brokenjaw le zombi tête, Brokenjaw le zombi torse, Brokenjaw le zombi jambes, Brokenjaw le zombi mains, et Brokenjaw le zombi pieds.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Brokejaw ist ein engagierter Marathonläufer ... Sie wird nicht aufhören, bis sie dich bekommt, selbst mit dieser gebrochenen Kiefer! Dress up in voller Brokejaw Kostüm mit diesem Bundle. Inklusive Brokejaw der Zombie Head, Brokejaw der Zombie Torso, Brokejaw der Zombie Beine, Brokejaw der Zombie Hände und Brokejaw der Zombie Feet.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Brokejaw è un maratoneta dedicato ... Lei non si fermerà fino a quando non si ottiene, anche con quella mascella rotta! Dress up in costume Brokejaw pieno con questo pacchetto. Include Brokejaw Head Zombie, Brokejaw Torso del Zombie, Brokejaw gambe del Zombie, Brokejaw Mani del Zombie, e Brokejaw piedi del Zombie.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Brokejaw es un corredor de maratón dedicado ... Ella no se detendrá hasta que usted consigue, a pesar de que la mandíbula rota! Se visten con el traje completo Brokejaw con este paquete. Incluye Brokejaw cabeza del zombi, Brokejaw Torso del zombi, Brokejaw Piernas del zombi, Brokejaw Manos del zombi, y Brokejaw Pies del zombi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_19 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_19 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Brokejaw is a dedicated marathon runner... She won't stop until she gets you, even with that broken jaw! Dress up in the full Brokejaw costume with this bundle. Includes Brokejaw the Zombie's Head, Brokejaw the Zombie's Torso, Brokejaw the Zombie's Legs, Brokejaw the Zombie's Hands, and Brokejaw the Zombie's Feet.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_19 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_19 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Brokejaw is a dedicated marathon runner... She won't stop until she gets you, even with that broken jaw! Dress up in the full Brokejaw costume with this bundle. Includes Brokejaw the Zombie's Head, Brokejaw the Zombie's Torso, Brokejaw the Zombie's Legs, Brokejaw the Zombie's Hands, and Brokejaw the Zombie's Feet.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>