<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ethnic Clothing - Red (For Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tenue ethnique - Rouge (pour femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Trachtengewand – rot (für Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vestiti etnici - Rossi (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Atuendo étnico: rojo (para mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ethnic Clothing - Red (For Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ethnic clothing that has been dyed a vivid red and delicately embroidered with traditional patterns.\nThe light cape draped over the shoulders and purple flower corsage wrapped around the waist add the finishing touches to this cute design.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette tenue ethnique teinte en rouge vif arbore des motifs traditionnels délicatement brodés.\nLa cape légère qu'on enroule autour des épaules et le bouquet de fleurs violettes ceignant la taille mettent la touche finale à cette jolie tenue.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Trachtengewand in kräftigem Rot ist mit landestypischen zierlichen Mustern bestickt.\nDer leichte Schulterumhang und die lila Blumencorsage, die um die Taille geschnürt wird, ergänzen dieses hübsche Ensemble.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vestiti etnici tinti con un pigmento rosso vivo e ricamati con motivi tradizionali.\nLa mantellina coprispalle e i decori floreali viola attorno alla vita, sono i tocchi finali di questo grazioso completo.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El atuendo étnico está teñido en vivos tonos rojos y delicadamente bordado con motivos tradicionales.\nLa ligera capa que cubre los hombros y el cinturón de flor morada ponen los toques finales a este bonito diseño.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ethnic clothing that has been dyed a vivid red and delicately embroidered with traditional patterns.\nThe light cape draped over the shoulders and purple flower corsage wrapped around the waist add the finishing touches to this cute design.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>