<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Element - Move It Denim Overall with Noir Bralette - Vintage &amp; Natural (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Element - Salopette en jean Move It avec soutien-gorge à bandeau Noir - Vintage &amp; Naturel (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Element - Move It Jeansoverall mit Noir Bralette - Vintage &amp; Natur (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Element - Salopette di jeans Move It e Top Noir - Vintage e Naturale (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Element - Move It Mono vaquero con sostén bralette Noir - Vintage y natural (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Denim overall pant with pocket details, floral voile trim, cuffed hem, and metal logo trim. Over a knit bralette with adjustable strap details, contrast fabric bodice detail, center front zip closure, smocked back panel piecing, and metal logo plate. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Salopette en jean avec détails au niveau des poches, bordure florale, ourlet à revers et logo en métal. Sur un soutien-gorge à bandeau avec bretelles ajustables, corset contrasté, fermeture éclair centrale à l'avant, panneau arrière et logo en métal. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jeansoverall mit Taschen, Voileverzierungen mit Blumenmuster, ausgefranstem Saum und metallenen Logoverzierungen. Darunter eine Strickbralette mit verstellbaren Trägern, farblich abgesetztem Oberteil, Reißverschluss vorne, Smocking auf der Rückseite und metallener Logoplatte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Salopette di jeans con tasche, ricamo floreale in voile, orlo elasticizzato e targhetta in metallo con logo. Con sotto un top in maglia con spalline regolabili, corpetto in tessuto di colore contrastante, chiusura con zip al centro, arricciatura sulla schiena ed etichetta con logo in metallo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pantalón de mono vaquero con detalle de bolsillo, adornos de gasa floral y borde metálico con el logotipo. En la parte superior, un sostén bralette de punto con detalles de correa ajustable, detalle de corpiño de tela de contraste, cierre de cremallera frontal en el centro, con piezas en nido de abeja en la espalda y placa metálica con el logotipo. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>