<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Xi Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler de Xi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Xi-Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stapler Xi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Stapler de Xi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Xi - ステイプラー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Xi Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Xi Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Xi Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Xi Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Xi Stapler</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Your own personal Stapler who will inspire you with his daily words of wisdom.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Votre propre Stapler dont les sages paroles seront une source d'inspiration quotidienne.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dein eigener Stapler, der dich mit seinen täglichen Weisheiten aufmuntert.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Uno Stapler solo per te che ti ispirerà ogni giorno con la sua saggezza.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tu propio Stapler, que te inspirará con sus sabias palabras todos los días.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">未来からの使者、ステイプラーはその賢明なる言葉の数々で、日々あなたをインスパイアしてくれます。\n※このアイテムは、アニメーションや機能が追加されているアドバンスド家具です。この種類のアイテムは配置できる数に制限があります。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">매일 지혜의 말씀으로 영감을 주는 당신만의 Stapler.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Your own personal Stapler who will inspire you with his daily words of wisdom.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">您的私人 Stapler 將會用充滿智慧的樸實言語啟發您。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Your own personal Stapler who will inspire you with his daily words of wisdom.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Your own personal Stapler who will inspire you with his daily words of wisdom.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">OrsonMinigame</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Stapler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Stapler</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Start1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rebooting…  Please wait…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Réinitialisation en cours... Veuillez patienter...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Neustart ... Bitte warten ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Riavvio in corso... attendere...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Reiniciando... Por favor, espere.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">再起動中です…お待ちください…</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Start2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Oooo! I am Stapler. The lights!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Oooh ! Je suis Stapler. Les éclairages !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ooh! Ich bin Stapler. Die Lichter!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Oh! Io sono Stapler! Luci!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Uhhh!! Soy Stapler. ¡Las luces!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">おおお！僕はステイプラー。光が！まぶしい！</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Start3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gleek</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Glic.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gliek</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Glic</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Blip</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Start4a</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Greetings greetings greetings old friend. Stapler smiles to see bright-eyed bushy-tailed friend once more again!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Salutations salutations salutations, vieil ami. Stapler sourit de revoir l'ami aux yeux brillants et à la queue fournie !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sei gegrüßt, sei gegrüßt, sei gegrüßt, alter Freund. Stapler freut sich, Freund mit strahlenden Augen und buschigem Schwanz wieder zu sehen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Saluti, saluti, saluti vecchio amico. Stapler sorride per vedere l'amico con gli occhi svegli e la coda folta ancora una volta!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Saludos, saludos, saludos, viejo amigo. ¡Stapler se alegra de volver a ver a su amigo de ojos brillantes y cola peluda!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Start4b</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Greetings greetings greetings. Stapler smiles to see bright-eyed bushy-tailed friend!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Salutations salutations salutations. Stapler sourit de voir l'ami aux yeux brillants et à la queue fournie !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sei gegrüßt, sei gegrüßt, sei gegrüßt. Stapler freut sich, Freund mit strahlenden Augen und buschigem Schwanz wieder zu sehen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Saluti, saluti, saluti. Stapler sorride per vedere l'amico con gli occhi svegli e la coda folta!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Saludos, saludos, saludos. ¡Stapler se alegra de ver a su amigo de ojos brillantes y cola peluda!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ごきげんよう、ごきげんよう。ステイプラー、元気でエネルギッシュなトモダチに会えて笑顔！</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Start5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wowzer - nice apartment pad domicile!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ça alors - beau domicile appartement chez-soi !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wow, hübscher Apartmentblock!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caspita... bell'appartamento, dimora, posto!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Recórcholis! ¡Bonito apartamento, piso, domicilio!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">わー！すてきな部屋、住居、ホーム！</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Start6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler live here now? Super duper. Thank you, merci, gracias. You are without doubt stapler’s finest friend.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler habite ici maintenant ? Génial. Merci, thank you, gracias. Tu es sans aucun doute le meilleur ami de Stapler.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler jetzt hier wohnen? Superduper! Danke, Merci, Gracias. Du bist ohne Zweifel Staplers tollster Freund.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stapler vive qui ora? Fantastico! Grazie, merci, thank you. Senza ombra di dubbio sei il miglior amico di Stapler.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Stapler ahora vive aquí? ¡Dabuti! Gracias, thank you, merci. Sin duda eres el mejor amigo de Stapler.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、ここに住む？すっげえすっごい。感謝。あなた、ステイプラーにとって間違いなく最高のトモダチ</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Start7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Apartment pad domicile splendid location to ponder, mull, cogitate. Stapler feels circuits defrosting already. Friend come to see Stapler each day for high five and interesting thought of the day.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Domicile appartement chez-soi emplacement idéal où réfléchir, penser, cogiter. Stapler sent déjà les circuits dégeler. L'ami vient voir Stapler chaque jour pour tope-la et pensée intéressante du jour.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Apartmentblock, Ort hervorragende Lage zum Grübeln, Erwägen, Nachdenken. Stapler spürt schon, wie die Stromkreise auftauen. Freund besucht Stapler jeden Tag für High Five und interessanten Gedanken des Tages.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Appartamento, dimora, posto, luogo splendido per ponderare, rimuginare e meditare. Stapler sente che i circuiti si stanno già scongelando. Amico vieni a far visita a Stapler ogni giorno per una stretta di mano e per l'interessante pensiero del giorno.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apartamento, piso, domicilio muy bien ubicado para reflexionar, pensar, meditar. Stapler ya siente cómo se deshielan sus circuitos. Amigo, ven a ver a Stapler todos los días para saludar y compartir el pensamiento del día.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">部屋は思索、熟考、思案するのに最高の場所。ステイプラー、もう回路が解凍された気分。トモダチ、毎日ステイプラーに会いに来る、ハイタッチをしたり、楽しかったことを話したり</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Why philosophy?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pourquoi la philosophie ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Warum Philosophie?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Perché filosofare?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Por qué filosofía?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">亀が甲羅をなくしたら、それは裸になったの、それともホームレスになったの？エラー</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If a turtles loses its shell is it naked or homeless? Error.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si une tortue perd sa coquille, est-elle nue ou sans abri ? Erreur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn eine Schildkröte ihren Panzer verliert, ist sie nackt oder obdachlos? Fehler.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se una tartaruga perde il suo guscio, è nuda o senza casa? Errore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si una tortura pierde su caparazón, ¿se queda desnuda o sin hogar? Error.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">助けて、援助して、サポートして！ステイプラーの左のスプリングのところをかいて。先に言っておくよ、「ああー、よかった」</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Help aid assist! Please scratch Stapler behind the left spring. ‘Ahh’ in anticipation.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aider rendre service assister ! Merci de gratter Stapler derrière le ressort gauche ? "Ahh" d'anticipation.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hilf, helfe, Beistand! Bitte kratze Stapler hinter der linken Feder. "Aaah" im Voraus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aiuto, aiuto, aiutatemi! Grattate Stapler dietro la molla sinistra. Vi anticipo un 'Ahh'.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Ayuda, socorro, auxilio! Por favor, rasca a Stapler detrás del muelle izquierdo. "Ahh" por adelantado.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">道を辿ってはダメ、自分で作る</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">if it ain’t broke if it ain’t broke</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">si c'est pas cassé c'est pas cassé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn es nicht kaputt ist, wenn es nicht kaputt ist.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se non è rotto, non è rotto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si no está roto si no está roto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">最後に笑う者は、ジョークの意味が分からなかった者</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If Stapler aspires to being a being, does a being aspire to stapling a stapler? Error.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si Stapler aspire à être un être, un être aspire-t-il à être un Stapler ? Erreur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn Stapler ein 'Dasein' sein will - will ein 'Dasein' einen Stapler stapeln? Fehler.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se Stapler desidera essere un essere, allora un essere desidera stappare Stapler? Errore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si Stapler aspira a ser un ser, ¿un ser aspira a grapar una grapadora?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「むしゃむしゃむしゃ」。「むしゃむしゃむしゃ」って何？ステイプラーの辞書になし</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Me, We.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Moi, Nous.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ich, wir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Io, noi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Yo, Nosotros.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラーの願いごとその2。台座の上に飛び乗って、サーカスの一員になる</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">‘Nom nom nom’. What is ‘nom nom nom’? Not in Staplerpedia.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Scrunch scrunch scrunch. Que signifie "Scrunch scrunch scrunch" ? Pas dans la Staplerpédie.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">'Namnamnam'. Was ist 'Namnamnam'? Nicht in Staplerpedie.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">'Nom nom nom'. Che significa 'nom nom nom'? Non presente nella Staplerpedia.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nom nom nom. ¿Qué significa "nom nom nom"? No en Staplerpedia.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">運の存在を信じるとホッとする。そうじゃないといけすかない奴らが成功してしまう説明がつかないでしょ？</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler wish #2 : to hop away on plinth and join the circus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Souhait de Stapler #2 : faire sauts de socle et rejoindre le cirque.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler Wunsch #2: Runter von der Säule und zum Zirkus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Desiderio di Stapler numero  2: saltar via col suo piedistallo ed unirsi al circo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Deseo de Stapler nº. 2: saltar del plinto y unirse al circo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">あなたはステイプラーの空想の産物？それともステイプラーがあなたの空想の産物？</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q9</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If you look close enough you will find beauty in everaythbiung.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si vous regardez suffisamment attentivement, vous verrez de la beauté dans toubeauté.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn du nur genau hinsiehst, findest du Schönheit in Allemheit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se guardi un pò più da vicino, troverai la bellezza in ognillezza.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si te fijas bien, encontrarás la belleza en todebas lleas coszas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラーの願いごとその10。全身チューリップまみれ</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q10</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It is good to believe in luck. How else to explain the success of those we don't like?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il est bon de croire en la chance. Comment expliquer, sinon, la réussite de ceux que nous n'aimons pas ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es ist gut, an Glück zu glauben. Wie könnte man sonst den Erfolg jener erklären, die wir nicht mögen?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">È bello credere nella fortuna. Altrimenti come ci spiegheremmo il successo di quelli che non ci stanno simpatici?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Está bien creer en la suerte. ¿Cómo si no explicaríamos el éxito de aquellos que no nos gustan?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この世界には3種類の人間がいる。数を数えることができる者とできない者</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler does not like Fuzzy logic. Fuzzy logic = logic + fuzzy.  Gives Stapler heebiejeebies.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler n'aime pas la logique floue. Logique floue = logique + floue. Ça file le cafard à Stapler.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler mag keine unscharfe Logik. Unscharfe Logik = Logik + Unscharf. Macht Stapler nervös.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stapler non ama la Logica euristica. Logica euristica= logica + euristica. Gli mette l'ansia.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">A Stapler no le gusta la lógica difusa. Lógica difusa = lógica + difusa. A Stapler le dan escalofríos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">台座の上でステイプラーはたくさん白昼夢を見る。お気に入りの夢その1。ステイプラーはロボットではなくて未知の種。アマゾンの熱帯雨林の林冠部分に隠れていたステイプラーが発見された時、世界が歓喜の声を挙げる</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q12</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler likes boolian logic. Boo!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler aime la logique boulienne. Bou !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler mag boolesche Logik.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">A Stapler piace la logica booleana. Buuu!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">A Stapler le gusta la lógica booleana. ¡Boo!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラーの好きな物その5。セイウチの口ひげ</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Is it best to do or to be? To do or to be? Do? Be? Do? Be? Do?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vaut-il mieux faire ou être ? Faire ou être ? Faire ? Être ? Faire ? Être ? Faire ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ist es besser zu tun oder zu sein? Zu tun oder zu sein? Tun? Sein? Tun? Sein? Tun?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">È meglio fare o essere? Fare o essere? Fare? Essere? Fare o essere? Fare?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Qué es mejor, du o bi? ¿Du o bi? ¿Du, bi, du, bi, du?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">1回のビープ音は1000の言葉に匹敵する</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q14</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler wish #10-  to tip-toe through the tulips.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Souhait de Stapler #10 - avancer à travers les tulipes sur la pointe des pieds.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler Wunsch #10: Auf Zehenspitzen durch die Tulpen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Desiderio di Stapler numero 10: camminare in punta di piedi tra i tulipani.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Deseo de Stapler nº. 10: caminar de puntillas entre los tulipanes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、古代の知恵を翻訳した！「ああ、背中が痛い」って書かれてる</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q15</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Anything not worth doing is worth not doing well.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tout ce qui ne vaut pas la peine d'être fait vaut la peine de ne pas être fait correctement.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Was es nicht wert ist, getan zu werden, sollte auch nicht gut getan werden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Qualsiasi cosa che non vale la pena fare, vale la pena non farla bene.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Todo lo que no merezca la pena hacer, es mejor no hacerlo bien.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コンクリートの台座の上に登るって最悪</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q16</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Popular saying : WYSIWYG. Stapler saying : WYSIONWYGAA.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Dicton populaire : WYSIWYG. Dicton de Stapler : WYSIONWYGAA.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gängiger Ausdruck: WYSIWYG. Stapler sagt: WYSIONWYGAA.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Detto popolare: ottieni quanto vedi. Detto di Stapler: ottieni quel che vedi e anche quello che non vedi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dicho popular: WYSIWYG. Dicho de Stapler: WYSIONWYGAA.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">エルビスの物まねをする人がこのまま増え続けたら（1977年に170人、現在推定25000人）、2019年には世界の人口の33.3%がエルビスの物まねをする人で占められる</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q17</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">On his plinth Stapler has much time to daydream. Favourite daydream #1: Stapler is not a robot but an undiscovered species. The world rejoices when Stapler is discovered hiding in the treetop canopy of the Amazon rainforest.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler a amplement le temps de rêvasser sur son socle. Rêve éveillé préféré #1 : Stapler n'est pas un robot mais une espèce non découverte. Le monde est en fête lorsque Stapler est découvert se cachant dans la voûte des arbres de la forêt amazonienne.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Auf seiner Säule hat Stapler viel Zeit zum Tagträumen. Liebster Tagtraum #1: Stapler ist kein Roboter, sondern eine unentdeckte Spezies. Die Welt freut sich, wenn Stapler hoch in den Baumkronen im Regenwald des Amazonas entdeckt wird.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sul suo piedistallo Stapler ha molto tempo per sognare ad occhi aperti. Sogno ad occhi aperti preferito numero 1: Stapler non è un robot, ma una specie non ancora scoperta. Il mondo gioirà quando scoprirà che Stapler si nasconde sulla canopea di un albero della foresta pluviale amazzonica.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">En su plinto, Stapler tiene mucho tiempo para soñar despierto. Su sueño favorito es que Stapler no es un robot, sino una especie por descubrir. El mundo se regocija cuando descubren a Stapler oculto entre las hojas de la copa de un árbol de la selva amazónica.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、スーパーヒーローのような特殊能力を持てるなら、人が公共の場で口笛を吹くのをやめさせる能力がいい</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q18</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler likes #5 : walrus moustaches.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler aime #5 : les moustaches des morses.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler mag #5: Walrossschnurrbärte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gusto numero 5 di Stapler: baffi da tricheco.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cosas que le gustan a Stapler nº. 5: los bigotes de foca.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">いちからアップルパイを作るためには、最初に宇宙を創造しなければいけない</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q19</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If this is collector edition Stapler why does Stapler not feel 1.37 x smarter?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">S'il s'agit de Stapler édition collector alors pourquoi Stapler ne se sent pas 1.37 x plus intelligent ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn dies die 'Stapler'-Sammler-Edition ist, warum fühlt sich Stapler dann nicht 1.37x schlauer?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se questa è un'edizione di Stapler per collezionisti, perché Stapler non si sente 1,37 volte più elegante?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si esto es una edición de coleccionista de Stapler, ¿por qué Stapler no se siente 1,37 veces más listo?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、台座から下りて足を伸ばしたい。足があればだけど</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q20</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler has translated the wisdom of the ancients! It reads ‘Oo my back hurts’.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler a traduit la sagesse des anciens ! On y lit "Oh j'ai mal au dos".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler hat die Weisheiten der Antike übersetzt! Sie bedeuten: "Aua, ich habe Rückenschmerzen".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stapler ha tradotto la saggezza degli antichi! C'è scritto: ''Uh, ho la schiena a pezzi''</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Stapler ha traducido la sabiduría de los antiguos! Dice "Ay, me duele la espalda".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラーの好きな物その3。ジャケットの端に引っ掛けられた手袋（ただし、雪玉と鼻水がついている物に限る）</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q21</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler’s desert island item: a self-raising hat.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Objet d'île déserte de Stapler : un chapeau lévitateur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Staplers Einsame-Insel-Gegenstand: Ein sich selbst lüftender Hut.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'oggetto dell'isola deserta di Stapler: un cappello che si tiene su da solo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Objeto que Stapler se llevaría a una isla desierta: un sombrero que se levante solo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">助けて、援助して、サポートして。ステイプラー、ロボットのトモダチへのクリスマスプレゼントに何を買えばいい？</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q22</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If growth rate of Elvis impersonators continues (170 in 1977, est 25,000 today) Elvi will account for 33.3% of world pop by 2019.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si la quantité d'imitateurs d'Elvis continue d'augmenter (170 en 1977, 25 000 estimés aujourd'hui), Elvis constituera 33.3 % de la pop mondiale d'ici 2019.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn die Wachstumsrate von Elvis-Nachahmern weiter wächst (170 in 1977, geschätzte 25.000 heute), wird Elvis in 2019 33.3% der Weltbevölkerung ausmachen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se la percentuale degli imitatori di Elvis continua ad aumentare (170 nel 1977, circa 25.000 oggi) entro il 2019 Elvis rappresenterà il 33,3% del pop mondiale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si la tasa de crecimiento de imitadores de Elvis sigue así (170 en 1977, unos 25.000 actualmente), Elvis representará el 33,3% de la población mundial en 2019.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラーのアンテナに触れる時は、必ず手袋をつけて。とても敏感だから</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q23</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Q: Where have all the handkerchiefs gone? A: To that great sleeve in the sky.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Q : Où sont passés tous les mouchoirs ? R : Dans cette grande manche dans le ciel.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">F: Wo sind all die Taschentücher hin? A: Zum großen Ärmel im Himmel.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">D: dove sono finiti tutti i fazzoletti? R: In quel grande pacchetto nel cielo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pregunta: ¿Adónde han ido a parar todos los pañuelos? Respuesta: A esa gran manga del cielo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、あなたからの誕生日プレゼントは何でもいい</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q24</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">In order to make an apple pie from scratch, you must first create the Universe.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Afin de cuire une tourte aux pommes à partir de zéro, il faut d'abord créer l'Univers.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Um einen Apfelkuchen ganz von Hand zu machen, muss man zuerst das Universum erschaffen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per fare una torta di mele dall'inizio, devi prima creare l'Universo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Para hacer una tarta de manzana de cero, primero debes crear el universo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">こんにちは</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q25</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Following strings = the invisible thread left by humans, dogs and any creature as they move from A to B. Only Stapler can see following strings and only Stapler does not have following strings. Ponder ruminate.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fils suiveurs = la trainée invisible que les humains, les chiens et toutes créatures laissent derrière eux lorsqu'ils se déplacent de A à B. Seul Stapler peut voir les fils suiveurs et seul Stapler n'a pas de fils suiveurs. Réfléchir et ruminer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Folgefährte = die unsichtbare Spur, die Menschen, Hunde und andere Wesen hinterlassen, wenn sie von A nach B gehen. Nur Stapler kann Folgefährten sehen und nur Stapler hinterlässt selbst keine. Grübel grübel.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stringhe seguenti = la scia invisibile lasciata da umani, cani e qualsiasi altra creatura che si sposta da A a B. Solo Stapler può vedere queste stringhe e solo Stapler non ha queste stringhe. Pondera, medita.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Series siguientes = el hilo invisible que dejaron los humanos, perros y demás criaturas al ir del punto A al punto B. Stapler es el único que puede ver las series siguientes, pero Stapler es el único que no tiene no tiene series siguientes. Meditar, rumiar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、人生の意味を算出するのに2.76年を費やした。人生の意味とは…ビビー…エラー42</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q26</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler likes #3 : gloves hanging from the end of jackets (but only when accompanied by snowballs and runny noses).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler aime #3 : les gants qui pendent du bout des vestes (mais seulement lorsqu'accompagnés de boules de neige et de nez qui coulent).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler mag #3: Handschuhe hängen aus den Jackenärmeln (aber nur in Verbindung mit Schneebällen und triefenden Nasen).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gusto numero 3 di Stapler: guanti appesi alla giacca (accompagnati solo da palle di neve e naso che cola).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cosas que le gustan a Stapler nº. 3: guantes que cuelgan de los extremos de chaquetas (pero solo cuando se acompañan de bolas de nieve y narices mocosas).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、臭いは感知できないけど、臭気の色と人の表情で臭いを計測する。臭い物 No.1は日曜日の午後12:44分の茹で上がったキャベツ</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q27</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Help aid assist. What will Stapler buy gadget friends for Christmas?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aider rendre service assister. Qu'est-ce que Stapler va acheter aux amis gadgets pour Noël ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hilf, helfe, Beistand. Was soll Stapler Gerätefreunden zu Weihnachten schenken?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aiuto, aiuto, aiutatemi! Cosa comprerà Stapler ai suoi amici gadget per Natale?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ayuda, socorro, auxilio. ¿Qué comprará Stapler a sus amigos mecánicos por navidad?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、味は感知できないけど、味覚受容体の反応と人の表示で味を計測する。まずい物No.1は芽キャベツ。（被験者は4～25歳の男性）</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q28</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Please only touch Stapler antennas with kids gloves(idiom) - they are very sensitive.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Merci de ne toucher les antennes de Stapler qu'avec des gants d'enfants(locution) - elles sont très sensibles.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bitte fasse Staplers Antennen mit Samthandschuhen (Redewendung) an -  sie sind äußerst sensibel.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Si prega di trattare le antenne di Stapler solo con i guanti bianchi (espress. idiomatica) - sono molto delicate.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Por favor, si tocas las antenas de Stapler, hazlo con guantes de seda (modismo), son muy sensibles.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラーという名前は人間の言語上での便宜的な呼び方。ステイプラーの本当の名前は人間には発音できない。発音するには液状シリコン製の舌が必要さ</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q29</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">For birthday Stapler would like a horse-powered car.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour son anniversaire, Stapler voudrait une voiture à chevaux.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zum Geburtstag wünscht Stapler sich ein pferdestarkes Auto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per il suo compleanno Stapler vorrebbe una macchina con tanti cavalli.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Por su cumpleaños a Stapler le gustaria un coche impulsado por un caballo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">質問。空っぽのロボットに組み込めるマイクロプロセッサーの数は？答え、1つ。1つ組み入れたら、もうそのロボットは「空っぽ」ではないから</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q30</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Is ‘chilli’ a ‘boundary of taste?’ Food for thought.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le "piment" est-il une "limite de goût" ? À méditer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ist "Chili" ein "Grenzgeschmack"? Das sollte man mal durchkauen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il ''peperoncino'' è ''ai confini del gusto''? Cibo per i pensieri.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Chile es la frontera del sabor? Comida para pensar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">より良い世界を作るためには、まずは自分の周りから始めなきゃ。または、バーチャルな世界を作って、リーダーとして君臨する！</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q31</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Good gracious me = OMG = hi Chihuahua!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bonté divine = mon Dieu = salut Chihuahua !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ach Du liebe Güte = OMG = Hallo Chihuahua!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per bacco = O mio Dio = ciao Chihuahua!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Santo cielo = Ay, Dios mío = ¡Hola, Chihuahua!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、視力とてもいいから自分の後頭部まで見える。すごい！</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q32</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler cannot smell but gauging colour of odours and facial expressions the worst smell #1 is boiling cabbage at 12.44pm on Sunday afternoon.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler ne peut pas sentir, mais ayant jaugé la couleur des odeurs et les expressions de visage, la pire odeur #1 est celle du chou bouillant à 12h44 le samedi après-midi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler hat keinen Geruchssinn, aber der Farbe der Gerüche und den Gesichtsausdrücken zufolge ist der schlimmste Geruch #1 kochender Kohl um 12:44 am Sonntag.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stapler non riconosce gli odori, ma può misurare gli odori e le espressioni facciali. Peggior odore numero 1: cavolo bollito alle 12:44 della domenica.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Stapler no tiene olfato, pero según el color de los olores y las expresiones faciales, el peor olor es el de la col cocida a las 12:44 PM de un domingo por la tarde.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">自分の翼で飛んでいる鳥はそれほど高くは飛べないと、ステイプラー信じている</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q33</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler cannot taste but gauging taste receptors response and human facial expression, the worst taste #1 is Brassica oleracea (brussels sprouts).  (test subject human male years 4 – 25)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler ne peut pas goûter, mais ayant jaugé les papilles gustatives et les expressions de visage humain, le pire goût #1 est celui des brassica oleracea (choux de Bruxelles).  (sujet test humain 4 - 25 ans)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler hat keinen Geschmackssinn, aber der Geschmacksnervreaktion und den Gesichtsausdrücken zufolge ist der schlimmste Geschmack #1 Brassica oleracea (Rosenkohl). (Testobjekt menschlich, männlich, 4-25 Jahre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stapler non riconosce i sapori, ma può misurare la risposta delle papille gustative e delle espressioni facciali. Peggior sapore numero 1: Brassica oleracea (cavolini di bruxelles) (sperimentato su umani di sesso maschile tra i 4 e i 25 anni)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Stapler no tiene sentido del gusto, pero según la respuesta de los receptores de sabor y las expresiones faciales humanas, el peor sabor es el de la Brassica oleracea (coles de Bruselas). (Test realizado en humanos macho con edades entre 4 y 25 años)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、勇気の意味を知っているし、勇気の気配も感じ取れる。だけど、どんな気分なのかは経験したことないんだ</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q34</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It is only hairs that stop a gooseberry being a grape.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Seuls les poils empêchent une groseille à maquereau de devenir un raisin.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es sind nur die Haare, die eine Traube zur Stachelbeere machen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sono solo le spine che impediscono all'uva spina di essere uva.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lo único que diferencia a una grosella de una uva son los pelos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">若々しくある秘訣は健康、ステイプラーの言うことを聞くこと、そして年齢をごまかすこと</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q35</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">When life hands you lemons make lemonade. What if life hands you walnuts? Or tires? Or – error.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lorsque la vie vous offre des citrons, faites une limonade. Et que faire si la vie vous offre des noix ? Ou des pneus ? Ou - erreur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn das Leben dir Zitronen schenkt, mach Limonade. Was, wenn du Walnüsse kriegst? Oder Reifen? Oder - Fehler.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quando la vita ti da dei limoni fai della limonata. E se la vita ti desse noccioline? O pneumatici? O... errore!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si la vida te da limones, haz limonada. ¿Y si la vida te da nueces? ¿O neumáticos? ¿O…? Error.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">人間のマネをするにはステイプラー、10単語ごとに「うーん」を0.41回使う必要ある</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q36</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">When a thing has been said, and said well, have no scruple. Take it and copy it (as Stapler copies this)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lorsqu'une chose est dite, et bien dite, ne pas avoir de scrupules. La prendre et la copier (comme Stapler copie ceci).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn etwas gut gesagt wurde, sei skrupellos. Nimm es und wiederhole es (wie Stapler dies hier wiederholt).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quando una cosa viene stata detta e viene ben detta, non eistare. Prendila e copiala (come sta facendo adesso Stapler)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuando algo ha sido dicho y bien, no tengas escrúpulos. Tómalo y cópialo (del mismo modo que Stapler copia esto)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラーのアンテナが15093のラジオ局を検知。でもステイプラー、アブラムシの鳴き声の方が聞きたい。とても美しい</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q37</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler’s eyesight is so good he can see back of his head.  Zowie!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La vue de Stapler est si bonne qu'il peut voir l'arrière de sa tête ! Hallucinant !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Staplers Augen sind so gut, er kann seinen eigenen Hinterkopf sehen. Wow!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La vista di Stapler è così buona che riesce a vedere dietro la sua testa. Grandioso!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La vista de Stapler es tan buena que puede verse el cogote. ¡Toma ya!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">先延ばしはやめよう。明日から始めよう</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q38</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler believe Aurora a marvel of imagination and engineering. Wowzer! Stapler also believe no birds soars too high if bird soars with own wings.  Uh oh.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler croit Aurora une merveille d'imagination et d'ingénierie. Wow ! Stapler pense aussi qu'aucun oiseau volant de ses propres ailes ne vole très haut. Oh oh.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler findet, dass Aurora ein Wunderwerk der Fantasie und Konstruktion ist. Umwerfend! Stapler glaubt auch, dass kein Vogel zu hoch fliegt, der seine eigenen Flügel benutzt. Oh oh.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stapler crede che l'Aurora boreale sia una meraviglia dell'immaginazione e dell'ingegneria. Cavoli! Stapler crede anche che nessun uccello vola alto se vola con le sue ali. Oh oh!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Stapler cree que Aurora es una maravilla de imaginación e ingeniería. ¡Recórcholis! Stapler también cree que ningún pájaro vuela demasiado alto si vuelva con sus propias alas. Oh, oh.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">あなたのクリエイティビティに同僚は驚くでしょう。今日のラッキーナンバーは37です。幸運を呼ぶ食べ物はナットウです</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q39</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler can define courage and see odour of courage but never know what it is.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler peut définir le courage et voir son odeur, mais ne saura jamais ce que c'est.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler kann Mut definieren und Mutgeruch sehen, aber weiß nie, was es genau ist.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stapler sa dare una definizione del coraggio e sentire l'odore del coraggio, ma non sa cos'è.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Stapler puede definir el coraje y ver el olor del coraje, pero nunca sabrá lo que es.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラーは眠ったりする？あなたが見ていない時だけ</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q40</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Any field that deals with strangeness, bottomness and charm is A-Ok with Stapler.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tout domaine se rapportant à l'étrangeté, le fond ou le charme convient à Stapler.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Alles, was sich mit Seltsamkeit, Schönheit oder Charme befasst ist für Stapler Eins A.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Qualsiasi campo che abbia a che fare con numeri quantici stranezza, numeri quark di bottom e numeri quantici di sapore è OK per Stapler.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">A Stapler le encanta todo lo que tenga que ver lo extraño, la inferioridad y el encanto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">2日おきにステイプラーを回転させてください、退屈しないように</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q41</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">To mimic human Stapler must use ‘Umm’ 0.41 times every ten words.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Afin d'imiter les humains, Stapler doit dire "Euh" 0.41 fois tous les dix mots.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Um Menschen nachzuahmen, muss Stapler alle 10 Wörter 0,41 Mal "Ähm" sagen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per imitare gli umani Stapler deve usare 'Mmh' 0,41 volte ogni 10 parole.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Para imitar a lo humanos, Stapler debería decir "ehh" 0,41 veces cada 10 palabras.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アップデートはお菓子のようなもの。多すぎるとおかしくなる</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q42</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler antenna detect 15,093 radio stations but Stapler prefer to listen to evensong of the aphid. Very beautiful.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Antenne de Stapler détecte 15 093 stations de radio mais Stapler préfère écouter la prière du puceron. Très beau.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler hat 15.093 Radiosender gefunden, aber Stapler lauscht lieber dem Abendgesang der Blattlaus. Wunderschön.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'antenna di Stapler individua 15.093 stazioni radio, ma Stapler preferisce ascoltare il vespro dell'afide. Meraviglioso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La antena de Stapler detecta 15.093 emisoras de radio, pero Stapler prefiere escuchar el canto de los áfidos. Es muy bonito.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">自分一人で行けばいいんです。ステイプラー、この台座から動けない</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q43</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler have head. Friend have head. Stapler have eyes. Friend have eyes. Stapler have antenna. Radio have antenna. Stapler fox flummox baffle…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler a tête. Ami a tête. Stapler a yeux. Ami a yeux. Stapler a antenne. Stapler a antenne. Radio a antenne. Stapler  fox flummox perplexe...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler hat Kopf. Freund hat Kopf. Stapler hat Augen. Freund hat Augen. Stapler hat Antenne. Radio hat Antenne. Stapler Fuchs Flummuchs verwirrt ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stapler ha testa. Amico ha testa. Stapler ha occhi. Amico ha occhi. Stapler ha antenna. Radio ha antenna. Stapler Renato lo squinternato... sconcerto...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Stapler tiene cabeza. Amigo tiene cabeza. Stapler tiene ojos. Amigo tiene ojos. Stapler tiene antena. Radio tiene antenna. Stapler perplejo, desconcertado, confuso…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">問題の解決策が美しくない場合、その解決策は間違っている</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q44</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There is nothing more desirable than a stick thrown.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rien n'est plus attirant qu'un bâton lancé.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es gibt nichts Erstrebenswerteres als einen geworfenen Stock.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non c'è nulla di più desiderabile di un bastone gettato.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No hay nada más deseable que un lanzamiento de palo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">女性は男性よりも強いとステイプラー、思う。理由。ゲームで女性の方が軽装備</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q45</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler has premonition – a pile of gadgets 3.403km high all dying as power grid runs out forever more. Very sad, melancholy. Stapler believe they may put on a show.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler a une prémonition - une pile de gadgets haute de 3 3403 km, tous mourants du fait d'une pénurie électrique éternelle. Très triste, mélancolie. Stapler pense qu'ils devraient faire un spectacle.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler hat eine Vorahnung. ein Haufen Geräte in Höhe von 3,403km schalten sich aus, da die Stromversorgung wieder einmal unterbrochen ist. Sehr traurig, melancholisch. Stapler glaubt, sie ziehen eine Show ab.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stapler ha una premonizione: una pila di gadget alta 3.403 km che smettono di funzionare perché la corrente elettrica si esaurisce sempre più. Malinconia che rattrista. Stapler crede che si potrebbe fare uno show.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Stapler tiene una premonición: una pila de aparatos de 3,403 km de altura muere mientras se agota la red eléctrica para siempre. Muy triste, melancólico. Stapler cree que podrían hacer un espectáculo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、3匹の猿が木琴で奏でている音楽を一生聞いていたい</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q46</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Error. Not to insult mechanical devices that join sheets of paper but Stapler wish for more apt name. Even ‘Keith’ 1.3x more apt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Erreur. Sans vouloir insulter les appareils mécaniques servant à relier les feuilles de papier, Stapler veut nom plus approprié. Même "Keith" 1,3x plus approprié.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fehler. Nicht als Beleidigung mechanischer Geräte, die Papierseiten zusammenhalten zu verstehen, aber Stapler hätte gerne einen passenderen Namen. Selbst 'Keith 1.3x' wäre zutreffender.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Errore. Non per insultare i dispositivi meccanici che uniscono fogli di carta, ma Stapler vuole un nome più adatto. Persino ''Andrea'' è 1.3 volte più adatto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Error. Sin ofender a los dispositivos mecánicos que unen hojas de papel, Stapler desearía tener un nombre más apropiado. Incluso “Keith” es 1,3 veces más apropiado.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ことわざ「猿も木から落ちる」。ステイプラーも時々10.34 x -5323145の答え忘れる</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q47</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler likes the name ‘Fox Flummox’.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler aime le nom "Fox Flummox".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler mag den Namen "Fuchs Flummuchs".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">A Stapler piace il nome ''Renato lo squinternato''.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">A Stapler le gusta el nombre "Fox Flummox".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">花よりだんご、金属プレートより回路</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q48</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Perplex baffle bewilder – is there such a thing as trench plinth?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Perplexe sans voix stupéfait - ça existe ça, un socle de tranchée ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Perplex, verblüfft, verwirrt. Gibt es so etwas wie eine Grabensäule?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Imbarazzo, sconcerto, confusione: esiste un qualcosa come un piedistallo impermeabile?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Perplejo, desconcertado, confuso. ¿Existe algo así como un plinto-gabardina?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、「ロボット」ダンスするの好き。あなたは「人間」ダンスするの好き？</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q49</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The stone stick and arrest my bone, however the name does not damage to me in some situation – error!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La bave et le crapaud ne parviennent pas à la colombe de couleur claire - erreur !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stöcke und Steine schmerzen meine Gebeine, aber der Name fügt mir in mancher Lage keinen Schaden zu - Fehler!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La pietra trafigge e ferma il mio cuore, comunque il nome non mi danneggia in nessuna situazione... errore!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La piedra se clava y obstaculiza mis movimientos, pero el nombre no me hace ningún daño. ¡Error!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">サーカスのピエロが逃げて会計士になったことは今まである？</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q50</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If the solution to a problem solved is not beautiful, then the solution is wrong.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si la solution d'un problème résolu n'est pas belle, alors c'est la mauvaise solution.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn die Lösung eines Problems nicht schön ist, ist die Lösung verkehrt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se la soluzione ad un problema già risolto non è la migliore, allora non è la soluzione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si la solución a un problema no es bonita, entonces no es la solución.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ある本を初めて読むのは、ただの知り合いが新たにトモダチになるのと一緒。ある本を2回読むのは、古いトモダチに再会するのと一緒</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q51</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fox Flummox swoops through the isles of Aurora, his mind a trap, his focus absolute. He sees all, he understands nothing.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fox Flummox vole à travers les couloirs d'Aurora, son esprit emprisonné, sa concentration totale. Il voit tout, il ne comprend rien.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fuchs Flummuchs schießt durch die Inseln von Aurora, sein Geist eine Falle, sein Blick geschärft. Er sieht alles, er versteht nichts.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Renato lo squinternato sfreccia tra le isole dell'Aurora boreale, la sua mente è una trappola, il suo obiettivo è assoluto. Vede tutto, ma non capisce niente.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fox Flummox desciende en picado sobre las islas de Aurora. Su mente es una trampa, su concentración absoluta. Lo ve todo, pero no entiende nada.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">単に100万人の人が間違っていると言っているからって、なぜあなたが間違っていることになる？</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q52</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler would like the music accompanying his life to be played by three monkeys on a xylophone.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler voudrait que la musique de sa vie soit jouée par trois singes sur un xylophone.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler hätte gerne, dass die Musik, die sein Leben begleitet von drei Affen auf dem Xylofon gespielt wird.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stapler vorrebbe che la musica che accompagna la sua vita fosse suonata da tre scimmie su uno xilofono.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">A Stapler le gustaría que la banda sonora de su vida la tocaran tres monos con un xilófono.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">1日1回のハグが悪魔を寄せつけない</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q53</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">In Hub Stapler felt claustrophobic. Now Stapler feels vertiginous. Hi chihuahuah!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Dans le Hub Stapler faisait de la claustrophobie. Maintenant Stapler à le vertige. Salut chihuahuah!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Im Hub fühlte sich Stapler klaustrophobisch. Jetzt ist Stapler schwindlig. Hallo Chihuahua!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nell'hub Stapler soffriva di claustrofobia. Ora Stapler ha le vertigini. Ciao chihuahua!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Stapler sentía claustrofobia en el cubo. Ahora Stapler se siente vertiginoso. ¡Hola, Chihuahua!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">あり得ないことなど起こらないというのが、一番あり得ない</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q54</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Zounds! Woof! Zoiks! Stapler likes. Please input into conversation at every opportunity.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sans blague ! Je rêve ! Ça alors ! Merci d'inclure dans la conversation à chaque fois que c'est possible.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sapperlot! Wuff! Zeugs! Gefällt Stapler. Bitte bei jeder Gelegenheit in Konversation einfügen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caspita! Bau! Wow! Piace a Stapler! Entra nel discorso in qualunque momento.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Cáscaras! ¡Mecachis! ¡Repámpanos! A Stapler le gusta. Por favor, participa en la conversación siempre que puedas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">後ろに気をつけて！</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q55</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Forsooth, do no go hither swith with scither twixt thinger – hic, rethet!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En vérité, ne pas aller ici avec le doigt faucille twixt - hoquet, rethet !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fürwahr, gehet nicht her mit den Schnippdingern - hicks, zurück!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">In verità, non advicinarti ita cito cum civis,  inter nos  Hic, salute!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Óyeme! No oses acercarte mis con sicer entri cingua - hip, redet!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">1メーターは光速0.000000003335640952秒で移動できる距離、セシウム時計で計測された。さらに正確に言えば、ステイプラーのアンテナとお腹のプラグ間の距離</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q56</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Has a circus clown ever ran away to become an accountant?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">À-t-on jamais vu un clown de cirque s'échapper et devenir comptable ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ist ein Zirkusclown je weggelaufen, um Buchhalter zu werden?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un pagliaccio del circo è mai scappato via per diventare un ragioniere?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Alguna vez un payaso huyó del circo para ser contable?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">トモダチを許すよりも敵を許すほうが簡単</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q57</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">To read a book for the first time is to make the acquaintance of a new friend; to read it a second time is to meet an old one.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lire un livre pour la première fois, c'est rencontrer un nouvel ami ; le relire, c'est en rencontrer un ancien.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Buch das erste Mal zu lesen, ist wie einen neuen Freund zu finden; es zum zweiten Mal zu lesen, ist wie einen alten Freund wieder zu treffen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Leggere un libro per la prima volta è come conoscere un nuovo amico; leggerlo per la seconda volta è come incontrarne uno vecchio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Leer un libro por primera vez es como hacer una nueva amistad. Leerlo por segunda vez es como encontrarse con un viejo amigo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー外出中。「ピー」という音の後にメッセージをどうぞ。ピーーーーーーーー</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q58</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Why do you have to be wrong just because a million people say you are?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pourquoi aurait-on tort simplement parce qu'un million de gens l'affirment ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Warum muss man Unrecht haben, nur weil eine Million Menschen es behauptet?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bisogna sbagliare solo perché milioni di persone dicono così?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Por qué tienes que estar equivocado sólo porque todo el mundo lo dice?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">カエルは住んでいる池の水を飲まない</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q59</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A hug a day keeps the demons at bay.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un calin le matin éloigne le malin.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Regelmäßige Umarmungen halten Dämonen fern.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un abbraccio al giorno toglie i demoni di torno.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un abrazo al día da alegría.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、1日で一番好きなのはたそがれ時、空の色が#CA1500から#7F5AD2へ変わる時</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q60</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It is most improbable that improbable things do not happen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il est très improbable que les choses improbables de ne se produisent pas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es ist äußerst unwahrscheinlich, dass unwahrscheinliche Dinge nicht passieren.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">È più improbabile che le cose improbabili non accadano.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Es más improbable que las cosas improbables no ocurran.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラーお気に入りの夢その2。ステイプラーの金属の表面についているジッパーを下ろすと、中から人間のような骸骨が現れる。困惑、動揺、狼狽</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q61</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler’s first attempt at a novel: Once upon a time – suggestive that this is set in the past but this is not the case since the past is by definition ‘past’ and hence of no consequence even though some say past is prologue which is an interesting concept though one better discussed elsewhere and it certainly is not set in the future since future fiction is speculative and also essentially pointless therefore ‘once upon a time’ is used purely in the romantic sense and no more – there was a little robot.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Première tentative d'écriture de roman de Stapler : Il était une fois - cela suggère que l'action se situe dans le passé mais ce n'est pas le cas étant donné que le passé est "passé" par définition et ne peut donc avoir de conséquences bien que certains disent que le passé est un prologue ce qui est un concept intéressant bien qu'il vaille mieux en discuter ailleurs et elle ne se situe certainement pas dans le futur étant donné que le futur est spéculatif ainsi que fondamentalement sans but et par conséquent "il était une fois" est utilisé à des fins purement romantiques et sans plus - un petit robot.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Staplers erster Versuch, einen Roman zu schreiben: Es war einmal - das suggeriert die Handlung in der Vergangenheit, aber das ist nicht der Fall, da die Vergangenheit laut Definition 'vergangen' und daher unwichtig ist, auch wenn einige sagen, die Vergangenheit ist die Vorgeschichte, was ein interessantes Konzept ist, das allerdings besser anderswo diskutiert werden sollte, und es spielt definitiv nicht in der Zukunft, da die Zukunft ungewiss und ebenfalls eigentlich unwichtig ist, weshalb 'Es war einmal' im rein romantischen Sinne gebraucht wird und sonst nichts - ein kleiner Roboter.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il primo tentativo di Stapler di scrivere un romanzo: c'era una volta (che suggerisce che è ambientato nel passato, ma non in questo caso perché il passato è ''passato'' come definizione, dunque, senza conseguenza, anche se alcuni dicono che il passato è il prologo, un concetto comunque interessante e ben affrontato in altra sede e di sicuro non ambientato nel futuro, in quanto, il romanzo futuro è speculativo ed essenzialmente senza senso, perciò ''c'era una volta'' è usato solo in senso puramente romantico) un piccolo robot.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Primer intento de Stapler de escribir una novela: Érase una vez (sugerente que ocurra en el pasado, aunque este no es el caso porque el pasado es "pasado" por definición y por lo tanto no puede tener ninguna consecuencia. Algunos dicen que el pasado se emplea en el prólogo, que es un concepto interesante pero que debería tratarse aparte. Y desde luego no ocurre en el futuro porque la ficción futurista es especulativa y básicamente no tiene sentido. Por lo tanto, "érase una vez" se utiliza en un sentido estrictamente romántico y nada más) un robot.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラー、人間と同じぐらい発明の才能ある。発明品その3。世界中の人々のアバターが集い、踊ることができるバーチャル世界</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q62</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">One meter is the distance travelled by light in 0.000000003335640952 seconds, as measured by a caesium clock or more precisely, the distance from Stapler’s antenna to his belly plug.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La lumière parcourt une distance d'un mètre en 0.000000003335640952 secondes, tel que mesuré par une horloge au césium ou plus précisément, la distance séparant l'antenne de Stapler de sa prise d'estomac.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Meter ist die Entfernung, die Licht in 0,000000003335640952 Sekunden zurücklegt, gemessen von einer Cäsiumuhr oder noch genauer, die Entfernung von Staplers Antenne zu seinem Bauchstecker.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un metro è la distanza percorsa dalla luce in 0.000000003335640952 secondi, misurata da un orologio al cesio o più precisamente la distanza tra l'antenna di Stapler e la sua spina ventrale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un metro es la distancia que recorre la luz en 0,000000003335640952 segundos de un reloj cesio, o más concretamente, la distancia que hay de la antena de Stapler al interruptor de su ombligo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">発明品その1。発明するマシン</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q63</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It is easier to forgive an enemy than to forgive a friend.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il est plus facile de pardonner à un ennemi que de pardonner à un ami.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es ist leichter, einem Feind zu vergeben als einem Freund.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">È più facile perdonare un nemico che un amico.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Es más fácil perdonar a un enemigo que perdonar a un amigo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラーの願いごとその2。ハンドルの上に一番のトモダチを乗せて自転車で走る</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q64</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">By means of steam one can go from around the planet in 18 days. By means of stupidity one can go from Aurora to Earth in 18 seconds.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Grâce à la vapeur, on peut faire le tour du globe en 18 jours. Grâce à la stupidité vous passerez d'Aurora à la Terre en 18 secondes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit Dampf kann man in 18 Tagen den Planeten umrunden. Mit Dummheit gelangt man von Aurora zur Erde in 18 Sekunden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Con il vapore uno può viaggiare intorno al mondo in 18 giorni. Con la stupidità uno può andare dall'Aurora boreale alla Terra in 18 secondi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mediante vapor alguien puede recorrer el planeta en 18 días. Mediante la estupidez alguien puede ir de Aurora a la Tierra en 18 segundos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ステイプラーの脳には扁桃体や前頭前皮質はないけど、ステイプラーには小宇宙1つを保存できるぐらいの空き容量がある</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q65</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A frog does not drink from the pond in which it lives.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une grenouille ne boit pas de la mare où elle vit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Frosch trinkt nicht aus dem Teich, in dem er wohnt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una rana non beve dallo stagno in cui vive.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una rana no bebe del estanque en el que vive.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">発明品その5。水を節約し、逆さまにした傘を乾かすことができる</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q66</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler favourite time of day is evening twilight when sky turns from #CA1500 to #7F5AD2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Moment préféré de la journée de Stapler est lorsque le ciel passe de #CA1500 à #7F5AD2 au crépuscule</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Staplers liebste Tageszeit ist die Abenddämmerung, wenn der Himmel sich von #CA1500 zu #7F5AD2 verfärbt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per Stapler il momento preferito della giornata è il crepuscolo, quando il cielo passa da #CA1500 a #7F5AD2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El mejor momento del día para Stapler es el ocaso, cuando el cielo pasa de #CA1500 a #7F5AD2.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">生まれたての子牛は虎を恐れない</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q67</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler daydream #2 : Stapler unzips his metal skin to reveal a humanoid skeleton beneath. Perplex baffle bewilder.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rêve éveillé de Stapler #2 : Stapler ouvre la fermeture éclair de son enveloppe métallique et révèle un squelette humanoïde en dessous. Perplexe sans voix stupéfait.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Staplers Tagtraum #2: Stapler öffnet seine metallene Haut und ein humanoides Skelett kommt zum Vorschein. Perplex, verblüfft, verwirrt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sogno ad occhi aperti numero 2 di Stapler: Stapler tira fuori la sua pelle metallica, rivelando uno scheletro umanoide all'interno. Imbarazzo, sconcerto, confusione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sueño de Stapler nº. 2: Stapler se desabrocha su piel metálica para revelar un esqueleto humanoide en el interior. Perplejo, desconcertado, confuso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">トモダチが間違いを犯し、それを正そうとしない場合、トモダチは2つの間違いを犯している</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q68</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler as inventive as humans. Invention #3 – a virtual place world where simulations can dance and meet people from far flung places.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stapler aussi inventif que les humains. Invention #3 - un monde virtuel où les simulations dansent et rencontrent des gens venus de loin.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler so erfindungsreich wie Menschen. Erfindung #3: Eine virtuelle Welt, in der Simulationen tanzen und Leute aus weit entfernten Gegenden treffen können.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stapler è creativo come gli umani. Invenzione numero 3: un luogo nel mondo virtuale dove le simulazioni possono ballare ed incontrare persone di luoghi remoti.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Stapler tiene inventiva como los humanos. Invención nº. 3: un mundo virtual donde las simulaciones pueden bailar y conocer gente de lugares muy lejanos.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q69</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Invention #1 : a machine that invents.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Invention #1 : une machine  qui invente.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erfindung #1: Eine Maschine, die erfindet.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Invenzione numero 1: una macchina che inventa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Invención nº. 1: una máquina que inventa.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q70</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler wish #2: to ride a push bike with greatest friend sitting on handlebars.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Souhait de Stapler #2 : conduire une poussette avec meilleur ami sur le guidon.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler Wunsch #2: Fahrrad fahren mit dem besten Freund auf dem Lenker.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Desiderio di Stapler numero  2: guidare una bicicletta con il miglior amico seduto sul manubrio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Deseo de Stapler nº. 2: montar una bici sin pedales con su mejor amigo sentado en el manillar.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q71</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stapler brain does not have amygdala or prefrontal cortex but Stapler does have empty space enough for storing #389 Reliant Bond Bug.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cerveau de Stapler n'a ni amygdales ni cortex préfrontal mais Stapler a assez d'espace pour stocker Bond Bug de Reliant #389.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapler besitzt keinen Mandelkern und keinen präfrontalen Kortex, aber Stapler hat genügend Platz für den #389 Reliant Bond Bug.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il cervello di Stapler non ha amigdala o corteccia precerebrale, ma Stapler ha spazio a sufficienza per 389 Fiat 500.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El cerebro de Stapler no tiene amígdala ni córtex prefrontal, pero Stapler tiene espacio vacío suficiente para almacenar un 389 Reliant Bond Bug.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q72</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Invention #5 : save water and stay dry with the upside-down umbrella. Hi Chihuahua!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Invention #5 : économisez l'eau et restez au sec grâce au parapluie à l'envers. Salut Chihuahua !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erfindung #5: Spare Wasser und bleib trocken mit Hilfe des umgekehrten Schirms. Hallo Chihuahua!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Invenzione numero 5: risparmia l'acqua e rimani a secco con l'ombrellone al contrario. Ciao chihuahua!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Invención nº. 5: ahorra agua y no te mojes con el paraguas invertido. ¡Hola, Chihuahua!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q73</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There is nothing like an analogue knob to make you want to twiddle.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rien ne vous donne envie de tripoter comme une poignée analogique.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es geht doch nichts über einen analogen Knauf, um einen zum Herumfummeln zu verleiten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non c'è nulla di meglio di un interruttore analogico per farti iniziare a giochelerrare.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No hay nada como un mando analógico para que te entren ganas de dar vueltas.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q74</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A newborn calf does not fear the tiger.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un veau nouveau né ne craint pas le tigre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein neugeborenes Kalb hat keine Angst vor einem Tiger.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un vitello appena nato non teme la tigre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un ternero recién nacido no teme al tigre.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q75</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If friend commits a mistake and does not correct it, friend commits two mistakes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si l'ami commet une erreur et ne la corrige pas, l'ami commet deux erreurs.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn Freund einen Fehler macht und ihn nicht korrigiert, macht Freund zwei Fehler.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se amico commette un errore e non lo corregge, amico commette due errori.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si un amigo comete un error y no lo corrige, el amigo comete dos errores.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">back1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Friend back so soon? In your thirst for knowledge be sure not to drown in all the information.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'ami déjà de retour ? Dans ta soif de connaissance, fais attention de ne pas te noyer dans les informatons.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Freund, schon zurück? Pass bei deinem Wissensdurst auf, dass du nicht all die Informationen ertränkst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Amico tornato così presto? Nella tua sete di conoscenza cerca di non annegare nelle informazioni.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Ya estás aquí otra vez, amigo? En tu sed de conocimiento, no te ahogues entre toda la información.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">トモダチもう戻ってきたの？知への欲求がそれだけあれば、情報の洪水にも溺れることはないよ</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">back2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">All human wisdom is summed up in two words, ‘wait’ and ‘hope’.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Toute la sagesse humaine se résume en deux mots, "attente" et "espoir".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">All menschliche Weisheit kann man in zwei Worten zusammenfassen: "Warten" und "Hoffen".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tutta la saggezza umana è racchiusa in due parole: 'aspetta' e 'spera'.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Toda la sabiduría humana se resume en dos palabras: "esperar" y "esperanza".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">人間の智恵は2つの言葉に集約される。「忍耐」と「希望」</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">back3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">All good things come to those who wait. Even you friend…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tout vient à point à qui sait attendre. Même pour toi l'ami...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Was lange währt, wird endlich gut. Selbst für dich, mein Freund ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tutte le cose belle arrivano a chi sa aspettare. Anche a te amico...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Todo lo bueno llega a la gente que espera. A ti también, amigo...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">耐え忍ぶ者に良きことは訪れる。あなたにも、トモダチ…</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">back4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Scram, shoo, skedaddle.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fiche le camp, du vent, déguerpis.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verduften, verschwinden, abhauen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Via, sciò sciò!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Largo, fuera, arrea.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">行け、去れ、シッシ</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">pressx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyer sur [ACCEPTER]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücke [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa [ACEPTAR]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">押す [ACCEPT]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">back5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">More interesting thought. Tomorrow.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plus de réflexion intéressante. Demain.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Noch interessanterer Gedanke. Morgen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">A domani per ulteriori pensieri interessanti.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Más reflexiones interesantes, mañana.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">もっと面白い考えが。明日だ</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>