<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Loco Woolly Hat (Kulche/women's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bonnet de laine Loco (Kulche/femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Loco-Wollmütze (Kulche/Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Berretto di lana Loco (Kulche) da donna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Loco gorro de lana (Kulche/mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ロコニット帽(クルチェ・女性用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">로코 비니(크루체/여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Loco Woolly Hat (Kulche/women's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">樂克針織帽(克魯傑/女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">樂克針織帽(克魯傑/女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LocoBeanie (Kulche/women's)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This woolly hat is designed after the ever-cheerful, inexhaustible Kulche.
This simple, mischievous design is perfect for anybody who wants to stand out in the crowd!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce bonnet de laine s'inspire de l'infatigable et toujours joyeux Kulche.
Ce design simple et malicieux conviendra à quiconque veut se démarquer de la foule !\n\nAcheter cet objet ajoute 1 LocoRoco à ton espace personnel de l'île Loco.
Tu peux ajouter jusqu'à 20 LocoRoco à l'île Loco. Une fois le maximum atteint, tu ne peux plus ajouter d'unités.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese Wollmütze ist nach dem immer heiteren, unerschöpflichen Kulche gestaltet.
Das einfache, schelmische Design ist perfekt für alle, die aus der Masse herausstechen wollen!\n\nDieser Gegenstand fügt deinem Loco-Insel-Apartment 1 LocoRoco hinzu.
Du kannst bis zu 20 LocoRoco hinzufügen. Ist das Maximum erreicht, können keine weiteren Einheiten hinzugefügt werden.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo berretto è ispirato all'allegro e vivace Kulche.
Il design semplice e sbarazzino è perfetto per chiunque voglia distinguersi dalla folla!\n\nAcquistando questo oggetto, aggiungerai un LocoRoco al tuo spazio personale su Loco Island.
Puoi aggiungere fino a 20 LocoRoco su Loco Island. Una volta raggiunto il numero massimo, non potrai aggiungerne altri.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este gorro de lana está inspirado en el incansable y siempre animado Kulche. 
¡Este diseño sencillo y atrevido es perfecto para todo aquel que quiera ser diferente al resto!\n\nComprar este objeto añade 1 LocoRoco a tu espacio personal en la Loco Isla.
Puedes añadir un máximo de 20 LocoRoco a la Loco Isla. Cuando hayas alcanzado este número, no podrás añadir más unidades.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">いつも明るく元気なロコロコ”クルチェ”がデザインされたニット帽。\n
シンプルでありながらアクが強いデザインは、周りに流されたくないあなたにピッタリです！\n\nこのアイテムを購入するとパーソナルスペース”ロコアイランド”に\n”ロコロコ”が１匹追加されます。”ロコアイランド”には最大20匹まで”ロコロコ”を追加できます。最大数に達した場合は、それ以上の追加はされません。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">언제나 밝고 명랑한 로코로코 '크루체'가 디자인된 비니.\n
심플하면서도 엣지 있는 디자인은, 자신만의 길을 걷는 당신에게 딱 이에요!\n\n이 아이템을 구입하면 퍼스널 스페이스 '로코 아일랜드'에 '로코로코'가 1마리 추가됩니다. '로코 아일랜드'에는 최대 20마리까지 '로코로코'를 추가할 수 있습니다.  최대치에 다다르면 더 이상은 추가할 수 없습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This woolly hat is designed after the ever-cheerful, inexhaustible Kulche.
This simple, mischievous design is perfect for anybody who wants to stand out in the crowd!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">以總是開朗有朝氣的樂克樂克”克魯傑”為設計的針織帽。\n
簡單卻很有味道的設計，最適合不落俗套的你！\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">以總是開朗有朝氣的樂克樂克”克魯傑”為設計的針織帽。\n
簡單卻很有味道的設計，最適合不落俗套的你！\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This beanie is designed after the ever-cheerful, inexhaustible Kulche.
This simple, mischievous design is perfect for anybody who wants to stand out in the crowd!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your LocoIsland personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to LocoIsland. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>