<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Active Object - Fortune Cookie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Objet interactif - Biscuit chinois</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aktives Objekt - Glückskeks</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Oggetto attivo - Biscotto della fortuna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Objeto activo: galleta de la fortuna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Active Item - Fortune Cookie</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">What will your fortune be? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Que vous réserve l'avenir ? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Was wird Ihr Schicksal bringen? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cosa ti riserva il futuro? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Qué te deparará la fortuna? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">What will your fortune be? [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">speaker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fortune Cookie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Biscuit chinois</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Glückskeks</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Biscotto della fortuna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">galleta de la fortuna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fortune Cookie</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Are you really looking for advice inside of a cookie?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous cherchez vraiment des conseils dans un gâteau ?!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Suchst du wirklich in einem Keks um Rat?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stai davvero cercando consiglio dentro un biscotto?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿De verdad buscas consejo en el interior de una galleta?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Are you really looking for advice inside of a cookie?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Help! I'm being held prisoner inside a Chinese fortune cookie factory.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">À l'aide ! Je suis retenu prisonnier dans une usine de gâteaux chinois !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hilfe! Ich werde in einer chinesischen Glückskeksfabrik gefangen gehalten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aiuto! Sono tenuto prigioniero dentro una fabbrica di biscotti della fortuna cinesi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Que alguien me ayude! Estoy encerrado en una fábrica china de galletas de la fortuna.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Help! I'm being held prisoner inside a Chinese fortune cookie factory.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Don't try to fix what isn't broken.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">N'essayez pas de réparer ce qui n'est pas cassé.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Repariere nichts, das nicht kaputt ist.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non tentare di riparare ciò che non è rotto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No trates de arreglar lo que no está roto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Don't try to fix what isn't broken.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Everything is only as important in your life as you make it.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Dans la vie, les choses ont l'importance qu'on leur donne.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Alles im Leben ist nur so wichtig, wie du es nimmst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ogni cosa nella vita assume l'importanza che tu gli attribuisci.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Todo en esta vida tiene la importancia que tú le des.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Everything is only as important in your life as you make it.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You can always find happiness at work on Friday.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La joie est toujours au rendez-vous au bureau le vendredi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Freitags macht Arbeit immer Freude.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Puoi sempre trovare la felicità in un venerdì di lavoro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Siempre podrás encontrar la felicidad en el trabajo... los viernes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You can always find happiness at work on Friday.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Is it me or do you look like you have a case of the Mondays?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C'est moi ou vous êtes allergique au début de semaine ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Liegt es an mir oder hast du dir einen schlimmen Fall von Montag eingefangen?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sbaglio o tu hai la sindrome del lunedì mattina?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Es cosa mía o tienes cara de lunes?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Is it me or do you look like you have a case of the Monday's?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Never lose the ability to find beauty in ordinary things.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il faut savoir trouver la beauté dans les choses simples.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verliere nie die Fähigkeit, Schönheit in einfachen Dingen zu finden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non perdere mai la capacità di scorgere la bellezza nelle cose di ogni giorno.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No pierdas la capacidad de encontrar la belleza en las cosas cotidianas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Never lose the ability to find beauty in ordinary things.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Humour usually works best in awkward moments.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'humour est la meilleure façon de détendre l'atmosphère.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In peinlichen Momenten funktioniert Humor am besten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'umorismo in genere funziona meglio nelle situazioni imbarazzanti.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El humor funciona mejor en los momentos incómodos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Humor usually works best in awkward moments.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply9</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You love Chinese food.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous, vous aimez la cuisine chinoise.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du liebst chinesisches Essen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tu adori il cibo cinese.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te encanta la comida china.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You love Chinese food.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply10</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You will be hungry again in one hour.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous aurez de nouveau faim dans une heure.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du wirst in einer Stunde wieder hungrig sein.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tra un'ora avrai di nuovo fame.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Volverás a tener apetito dentro de una hora.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You will be hungry again in one hour.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Actually, we were wondering if you had any advice for us?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En fait, on se demandait si vous aviez des conseils à nous donner ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eigentlich haben wir uns gefragt, ob du uns einen Rat geben kannst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ci stavamo per l'appunto chiedendo se avessi un consiglio da darci.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">En verdad, nos preguntábamos si nos podrías aconsejar tú a nosotros.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Actually, we were wondering if you had any advice for us?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply12</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fear is just excitement in need of an attitude adjustment.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La peur n'est qu'excitation mal dosée.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Furcht ist nur Spannung, die ihre Einstellung ändern muss.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La paura non è altro che eccitazione con l'atteggiamento sbagliato.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El miedo no es más que emoción que necesita un cambio de actitud.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fear is just excitement in need of an attitude adjustment.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There is no mistake so great as that of being always right.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il n'y a pas d'erreur plus grave que d'avoir toujours raison.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es gibt keinen Fehler, der größer wäre als der, immer Recht zu haben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non esiste errore più grande dell'avere sempre ragione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No hay error más grave que tener siempre la razón.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">There is no mistake so great as that of being always right.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply14</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Having money is not everything, not having it is.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avoir de l'argent n'est pas tout. Ne pas en avoir, l'est.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Geld zu haben ist nicht alles, es nicht zu haben schon.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I soldi non sono tutto, non averne lo è.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tener dinero no lo es todo; no tenerlo, sí.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Having money is not everything, not having it is.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply15</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If an alien shows up on your doorstep, don't say we didn't warn you.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si un extraterrestre débarque chez vous, au moins, on vous aura prévenu.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn ein Alien vor deiner Haustür steht, dann sag nicht, wir hätten dich nicht gewarnt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se un alieno si presenta alla tua porta, non dire che non ti avevamo avvisato.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si se presenta un extraterrestre en tu casa no digas que no te avisamos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">If an alien shows up on your doorstep, don't say we didn't warn you.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply16</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Picture this…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Imaginez un peu...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stell dir das vor ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Immagina che...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Imagina...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Picture this…</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply17</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Isn't it ironic that Chinese fortune cookies originated in the U.S?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous ne trouvez pas ça ironique que les gâteaux chinois viennent des États-Unis ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ist es nicht ironisch, dass chinesische Glückskekse in den USA entstanden sind?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non è un'ironia della sorte che i biscotti della fortuna cinesi siano nati negli Stati Uniti?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿No es curioso que las galletas chinas de la fortuna se crearan en EE. UU.?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Isn't it ironic that Chinese fortune cookies originated in the U.S?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply18</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If life hands you a lemon, ask for a receipt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si la vie vous envoie des citrons...demandez le ticket de caisse.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn das Leben dir eine Zitrone gibt, dann verlange eine Quittung.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se la vita non ti sorride, tu raccontale una barzelletta.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si la vida te da sorpresas, pide un recibo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">If life hands you a lemon, ask for a receipt.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply19</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take a good look at the person on your left, now hand them a breath mint!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Regardez bien la personne à votre gauche... Et donnez-lui un chewing-gum !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schau dir die Person zu deiner Linken gut an. Jetzt gib ihr ein Pfefferminzbonbon!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guarda bene la persona alla tua sinistra e offrile una mentina per l'alito!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mira bien a la persona a tu izquierda, ahora, dale un caramelo de menta para el mal aliento.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Take a good look at the person on your left, now hand them a breath mint!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply20</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There's really not much left to say, just make sure to tip your server.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il n'y a pas grand-chose à ajouter... Ah si, n'oubliez pas le pourboire en partant.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Viel mehr gibt es eigentlich nicht zu sagen, aber geh auf Nummer sicher und gib deiner Bedienung Trinkgeld.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non c'è rimasto molto da dire, ma non dimenticare di lasciare la mancia al cameriere.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No hay mucho más que decir... Quizás que no olvides de darle una propina al camarero.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">There's really not much left to say, just make sure and tip your server.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply21</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Good sense is the master of human life." - Source Unknown</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Le bon sens est la base de la vie." Source inconnue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Gute Einsicht ist der Meister des menschlichen Lebens." – Quelle unbekannt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Il buon senso è il maestro di vita di tutti gli uomini." - Anonimo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“El sentido común es la clave del ser humano”. - Anónimo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Good sense is the master of human life." - Source Unknown</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply22</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Go home and check all your trouser pockets for some extra cash, you're going to need it.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rentrez chez vous et fouillez toutes vos poches : vous allez avoir besoin de monnaie.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Geh heim und durchsuche all deine Hosentaschen nach zusätzlichem Bargeld. Du wirst es brauchen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vai a casa e guarda se hai lasciato soldi nelle tasche dei pantaloni: ti serviranno.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ve a casa y rebusca en todos los bolsillos de tus pantalones a ver si encuentras unas monedillas; te van a hacer falta.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Go home and check all your pants pockets for some extra cash, you're going to need it.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply23</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Pray for what you want, but work for the things you need." - General Fortune Cookie Saying</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Priez pour les choses que vous voulez, mais travaillez pour celles dont vous avez besoin." Proverbe de gâteau chinois</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Bete, wofür du willst, aber arbeite für die Dinge, die du brauchst." – Allgemeine Glückskeks-Weisheit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Prega per ottenere ciò che desideri, ma lavora per ottenere ciò di cui hai bisogno." - Detto popolare dei biscotti della fortuna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Reza por lo que deseas y trabaja por lo que necesitas”. - Refrán de galleta de la fortuna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Pray for what you want, but work for the things you need." - General Fortune Cookie Saying</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply24</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Nature, time and patience are the three best physicians." - General Fortune Cookie Saying</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"La nature, le temps et la patience sont les meilleurs remèdes." Proverbe de gâteau chinois</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Natur, Zeit und Geduld sind die drei besten Ärzte." – Allgemeine Glückskeks-Weisheit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Natura, tempo e pazienza curano qualsiasi male." - Detto popolare dei biscotti della fortuna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“La naturaleza, el tiempo y la paciencia todo lo curan". - Refrán de galleta de la fortuna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Nature, time and patience are the three best physicians." - General Fortune Cookie Saying</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply25</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It's important to always plan ahead, just make sure you check back with your past.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il faut savoir se projeter dans l'avenir ; mais n'oubliez pas de consulter votre passé d'abord.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es ist wichtig, immer vorauszuplanen, aber geh auf Nummer sicher und kläre das mit deiner Vergangenheit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">È importante fare programmi per il futuro senza dimenticare di fare i conti con il passato.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Es importante hacer planes para el futuro, pero no te olvides de consultar con tu pasado.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">It's important to always plan ahead, just make sure and check back with your past.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply26</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Many of life's failures are people who did not realise how close they were to success when they gave up." - Thomas Edison</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Beaucoup de gens ont échoué car ils n'ont pas su voir à quel point la réussite était proche quand ils ont abandonné." Thomas Edison</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Viele, die im Leben gescheitert sind, haben bloß nicht bemerkt, wie nahe sie dem Erfolg waren, als sie aufgaben." – Thomas Edison</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Molti falliscono perché nel momento della resa non si rendono conto di quanto siano vicini al successo." - Thomas Edison</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“Muchos fracasos ocurren en personas que no se dieron cuenta lo cerca del éxito que se encontraban cuando desistieron". - Thomas Edison</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Many of life's failures are people who did not realize how close they were to success when they gave up." - Thomas Edison</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply27</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"The positive thinker sees the invisible, feels the intangible, and achieves the impossible." - Source Unknown</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Le penseur positif voit l'invisible, sent l'intangible et fait l'impossible." Source inconnue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Wer positiv denkt, sieht das Unsichtbare, fühlt das Unberührbare und erreicht das Unmögliche." – Quelle unbekannt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"L'ottimista vede l'invisibile, avverte l'intangibile e raggiunge l'impossibile." - Anonimo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“El optimista ve lo invisible, siente lo intangible y logra lo imposible”. - Anónimo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"The positive thinker sees the invisible, feels the intangible, and achieves the impossible." - Source Unknown</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply28</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wondering how you got somewhere will never tell you where it's going to end up.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce n'est pas en vous demandant comment vous en êtes arrivé là que vous saurez où vous allez finir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Darüber nachzudenken, wie du irgendwo hinkamst, wird dir nie verraten, wo es enden wird.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chiedersi come si è arrivati ad un punto non dirà mai dove si andrà a finire.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pensar en cómo has llegado a una situación nunca te indicará cómo va a terminar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Wondering how you got somewhere will never tell you where it's going to end up.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply29</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Laughter is the best medicine.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le rire est le meilleur des remèdes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lachen ist die beste Medizin.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ridere è la migliore medicina.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La risa es la mejor medicina.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Laughter is the best medicine.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply30</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">That wasn't chicken.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce n'était pas du poulet...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das war kein Hühnchen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non era pollo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lo que has comido no era pollo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">That wasn't chicken.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply31</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">What would you do with a million pounds? Okay, now go and get your million pounds.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Que feriez-vous avec un million d'Euro ? Très bien, maintenant allez chercher votre million.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Was würdest du mit einer Million Euro tun? Okay, jetzt geh und verdien dir deine Million Euro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cosa faresti con un milione di dollari? Ok, ora va' a guadagnarti il tuo milione di dollari.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Qué harías si tuvieras un millón de euros?... Muy bien, pues ahora ve y consigue ese milloncete.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">What would you do with a million dollars? Okay, now go get your million dollars.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply32</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Have you looked in the mirror lately? Because you look awesome.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous devriez vous regarder plus souvent dans la glace : vous avez une mine superbe !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hast du in der letzten Zeit mal in den Spiegel geschaut? Du siehst nämlich klasse aus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ti sei guardato allo specchio ultimamente? Perché hai un aspetto fantastico.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Te has mirado en el espejo últimamente? Porque estás genial.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Have you looked in the mirror lately? Because you look awesome.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply33</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Could you order me a broccoli beef takeaway please? I'm really hungry.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous pourriez me commander du bœuf aux brocolis ? Je meurs de faim.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Könntest du mir Brokkoli-Rindfleisch zum Mitnehmen bestellen? Ich habe wirklich Hunger.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Potresti ordinarmi un piatto di carne e broccoli a portar via? Ho una fame pazzesca.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Podrías pedirme una ternera con verduras para llevar? Es que me muero de hambre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Could you order me a broccoli beef to go please? I'm really hungry.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply34</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Do you have any idea how dark it was in there?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous savez à quel point il faisait sombre là-dedans ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hast du eigentlich eine Ahnung, wie dunkel es da drin war?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai idea di quanto fosse buio lì dentro?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Tienes idea de lo oscuro que estaba ahí dentro?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Do you have any idea how dark it was in there?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply35</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If you find yourself in deep waters, hold your breath.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si vous vous retrouvez en eaux profondes, retenez votre souffle.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn du dich im tiefen Wasser wiederfindest, halt die Luft an.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se ti trovi in brutte acque, trattieni il fiato.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si te encuentras en aguas turbulentas, aguanta la respiración.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">If you find yourself in deep waters, hold your breath.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply36</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sarcasm is for winners.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le sarcasme, c'est pour les gagnants.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sarkasmus ist etwas für Sieger.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il sarcasmo è dei vincitori.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El sarcasmo es de ganadores.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sarcasm is for winners.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply37</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">He who throws dirt is losing ground.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Celui qui jette de la boue perd du terrain.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer mit Staub wirft, verliert an Boden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chi lancia fango, perde terreno.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Quien echa tierra, pierde terreno.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">He who throws dirt is losing ground.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply38</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">He who laughs at himself never runs out of things to laugh at.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Celui qui se moque de lui-même, aura toujours de quoi rigoler.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer über sich selbst lachen kann, hat immer etwas zu lachen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chi ride di sé stesso non esaurisce mai i motivi per ridere.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Quien sabe reírse de sí mismo siempre tendrá algo de lo que reír.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">He who laughs at himself never runs out of things to laugh at.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply39</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The world may be your oyster, but it doesn't mean you'll get its pearl.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le monde peut être votre huître, mais ça ne veut pas dire que vous aurez sa perle.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Selbst, wenn dir die Welt zu Füßen liegt, wirst du nicht unbedingt ihre Schätze in den Händen halten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mondo può essere la tua ostrica, ma non significa che ti regalerà la sua perla.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Puede que te aburras como una ostra, pero como una sin perla.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The world may be your oyster, but it doesn't mean you'll get its pearl.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply40</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Don't wait for your ship to come in, swim out to it.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il faut battre le fer pendant qu'il est chaud.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Warte nicht darauf, dass dein Schiff zu dir kommt. Schwimm zu ihm.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non aspettare che la nave venga a salvarti, ma nuota verso di essa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No esperes que llegue tu tren, corre a por él.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Don't wait for your ship to come in, swim out to it.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply41</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It's not over until you're dead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce n'est pas fini tant que vous n'êtes pas mort.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es ist erst vorbei, wenn du tot bist.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non è finita finché non sei morto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nada acaba hasta la muerte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">It's not over until you're dead.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply42</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Become the person your dog already thinks you are.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Devenez la personne que votre chien voit en vous.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Werde die Person, für die dich dein Hund bereits hält.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Diventa la persona che il tuo cane pensa tu sia già.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conviértete en la persona que tu perro cree que eres.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Become the person your dog already thinks you are.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply43</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">People won't miss you if you won't go away.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous ne manquerez pas aux gens si vous restez là.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Leute können dich nicht vermissen, wenn du nicht fortgehst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non mancherai a nessuno se non te ne vai.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nadie te echará de menos si no te vas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">People won't miss you if you won't go away.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply44</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There's an old saying when it comes to telling fortunes, we just wish we could remember it.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il y a un vieux proverbe à propos des voyants... Mais j'ai bien peur de l'avoir oublié.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es gibt ein altes Sprichwort über Wahrsagerei. Wenn wir uns doch nur daran erinnern könnten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">C'è un vecchio detto sul predire il futuro, solo che non ce lo ricordiamo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hay un viejo dicho sobre las galletas de la fortuna... Ojalá pudiéramos acordarnos de cuál es.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">There's an old saying when it comes to telling fortunes, we just wish we could remember it.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply45</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">They say you don't know how much you've got until it's gone, then make sure you get it appraised.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">On dit qu'on ne connaît pas la valeur d'une chose avant de l'avoir perdue alors appréciez ce que vous avez.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Man sagt, man kennt erst den Wert von etwas, wenn es weg ist. Also geh besser und lass es schätzen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Si dice che uno non apprezza quel che ha finché non lo ha perso, perciò cerca di apprezzarlo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dicen que uno no se da cuenta de lo que tiene hasta que lo pierde, así que mejor que te lo tasen cuanto antes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">They say you don't know how much you've got until it's gone, then make sure and get it appraised.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply46</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">He who laughs last really didn't get the punch line.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Celui qui rit en dernier n'a pas dû bien comprendre la blague.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer zuletzt lacht, hat den Witz wirklich nicht verstanden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chi ride ultimo... non ha capito la battuta.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Quien ríe el último es que no ha pillado el chiste.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">He who laughs last really didn't get the punch line.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply47</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The greatest danger could be your stupidity</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le plus grand des dangers est parfois la stupidité.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Deine Dummheit könnte die größte Gefahr sein.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il più grande pericolo potrebbe essere la tua stupidità.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El mayor peligro puede ser tu estupidez.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The greatest danger could be your stupidity</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">reply48</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The difference between fiction and reality? Fiction has to make sense.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La différence entre réalité et fiction? La fiction, elle, doit être vraisemblable.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Unterschied zwischen Fiktion und Realität ist der, dass Fiktion Sinn ergeben muss.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La differenza tra finzione e realtà? La finzione deve avere un senso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿La diferencia entre realidad y ficción? La ficción tiene que ser lógica.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The difference between fiction and reality? Fiction has to make sense.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>