<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">What the Bleep Peep - Heavy Pet - Blazing Blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">What the Bleep Peep - Blue éclatant</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">What the Bleep Peep - Leuchtblau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">What the Bleep Peep - Blu acceso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">What the Bleep Peep - Azul Encendido</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_34</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">What the Bleep Peep - Heavy Pet - 불타는 블루</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">What the Bleep Peep - Heavy Pet - Blazing Blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">What the Bleep Peep - Heavy Pet - 閃電藍</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">What the Bleep Peep - Heavy Pet - 閃電藍</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">What the Bleep Peep - Heavy Pet - Blazing Blue</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">What the Bleep Peep is bad to the Bone!  This naughty little Peep will bring you hours of fun in your apartment!   You can control your Peep with custom animations and special Peep moves![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">What the Bleep Peep est profondément mauvais! Ce vilain petit Peep sera  à l'origine d'heures de bon temps dans ton appartement. Tu peux le contrôler avec des animations personnalisées et des manœuvres spéciales Peep![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">What the Bleep Peep ist ein ungezogener Begleiter! Dieses freche kleine Peep wird dir in deiner Wohung unendlich viel Spaß bereiten! Du kannst dein Peep mit benutzerdefinierten Animationen und speziellen Peep-Bewegungen steuern![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">What the Bleep Peep é cattivissimo!  Questo piccolo Peep tepistello ti porterá ore di divertimento nel tuo appartamento!  Puoi controllare il tuo Peep con animazioni fatte a posta e movimenti speciali Peep![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">What the Bleep Peep es bien rudo!  Este Peep malportado te dará horas de diversión en tu departamento!  Puedes controlar tu Peep con animaciones personalizadas y movimientos Peep especiales![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_34 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">What the Bleep Peep은 심술궂은 친구랍니다!  이 건방지고 작은 Peep을 아파트에 데려와 즐겁게 놀아 보세요!   사용자 지정 애니메이션과 특수 Peep 모션으로 컨트롤할 수 있습니다![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">What the Bleep Peep is bad to the Bone!  This naughty little Peep will bring you hours of fun in your apartment!   You can control your Peep with custom animations and special Peep moves![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">What the Bleep Peep壞透了！這頑皮的 Peep會為您帶來無窮的歡樂！您可以用自訂動態和專屬Peep動作來控制Peep！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">What the Bleep Peep壞透了！這頑皮的 Peep會為您帶來無窮的歡樂！您可以用自訂動態和專屬Peep動作來控制Peep！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">What the Bleep Peep is bad to the Bone!  This naughty little Peep will bring you hours of fun in your apartment!   You can control your Peep with custom animations and special Peep moves![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>