<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Chair Empire</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaise Empire</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stuhl Reich</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sedia Empire</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Silla Imperial</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>    
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This furniture is perfect for large rooms and bright spaces. Its neoclassical style combines elegance and quality. Completely handmade with the highest quality material, each individual piece is unique. An innovative design with classical influences that will make your space live up to your expectations. Don’t settle for less. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce meuble est parfait pour les grandes pièces et les espaces lumineux. Son style néoclassique combine élégance et qualité. Entièrement fait main avec les matériaux de la plus haute qualité, chaque pièce est unique. Une conception innovante avec des influences classiques qui mettra votre espace de vie au plus au haut niveau de vos attentes. Ne vous contentez pas du minimum. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Möbel eignen sich hervorragend für große Räume und helle Plätze. Der neoklassizistische Stil vereint Qualität und Eleganz. Jedes Stück ist ein Unikat, denn die Stücke sind handgemacht und ausschließlich qualitativ hochwertiger Materialien wurden zur Herstellung verwendet. Das innovative Design mit klassischen Einflüssen wird Ihren Ansprüchen gerecht werden. Geben Sie sich nicht mit weniger zufrieden. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo pezzo d’arredamento è perfetto per le stanze ampie e gli spazi luminosi. Il suo stile neoclassico combina eleganza e qualità. Completamente fatto a mano con materiali di altissima qualità, ciascun pezzo è unico. Un design innovativo con influenze classiche che rende onore ai tuoi spazi. Non pretendere di meno. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estos muebles son perfectos para grandes salones y espacios luminosos. Su estilo neoclásico combina la elegancia y la calidad. Totalmente hechos a mano con materiales de primera calidad, cada uno de ellos representa una pieza única. Un diseño innovador con influencias clásicas que harán de tu espacio un lugar a la altura de tus expectativas. No te conformes con menos. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>