<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blaster's Paradise - Sodium Personal Space</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Blaster's Paradise - Espace Personnel Sodium</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blaster's Paradise - (Sodium) Persönlicher Lebensraum</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Blaster's Paradise: spazio personale Sodium</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paraíso del disparo: espacio personal de Sodium</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Blaster's Paradise - Sodiumパーソナルスペース</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블래스터의 천국 - Sodium 퍼스널 스페이스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Blaster's Paradise - Sodium Personal Space</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">爆破者的天堂 - Sodium個人空間</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">爆破者的天堂 - Sodium個人空間</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blaster's Paradise - Sodium Personal Space</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blast your way to an epic score with the awesome TankTop shooter in this stunning sub-tropical personal space. With spectacular waterfalls, a mysterious abandoned mill, and the addictive TankTop shooter, this waterside hang-out will be the envy of all your friends. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Grimper jusqu'à un score épique grâce au jeu de tir génial Tanktop dans cet étonnant espace personnel sous-tropical. Avec des chutes d'eau spectaculaires, un moulin abandonné mystérieux, et le jeu de tir addictif TankTop, cette balade au bord de l'eau ren. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erkämpfe dir mit dem fantastischen Tanktop-Shooter ein episches Ergebnis in diesem atemberaubenden subtropischen persönlichen Bereich. Um diesen Unterschlupf am Strand mit spektakulären Wasserfällen, einer mysteriösen verlassenen Mühle und dem fesselnden TankTop-Shooter werden dich all deine Freunde beneiden. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Batti tutti i record in TankTop, l'incredibile sparatutto dello spazio personale sub-tropicale. Cascate spettacolari, una misteriosa miniera abbandonata e il coinvolgente sparatutto TankTop, questo ritrovo sarà l'invidia di tutti i tuoi amici. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Diviértete destruyendo lo que se interponga en tu camino en el espacio personal del paraíso subtropical de TankTop. Compite en espectaculares cataratas o un molino abandonado en este adictivo shooter que será la envidia de todos tus amigos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">トロピカルなパーソナルスペース内で行われるTankTopシューターを是非体験してください！綺麗な滝、ミステリアスな廃水車、それにこのやみつきになりそうなTankTopシューター…この自然のほとりに皆が嫉妬するはず？！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이처럼 기막힌 아열대의 개인공간에서 벌어지는 멋진 TankTop 슈팅 게임에서 역사에 남을 점수를 기록해보세요. 엄청난 규모의 폭포와 미스테리한 버려진 제재소, 그리고 중독성있는 TankTop 슈팅 게임까지, 당신 친구들 모두가 부러워하게 될 해변가에서의 즐거움이죠. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Blast your way to an epic score with the awesome TankTop shooter in this stunning sub-tropical personal space. With spectacular waterfalls, a mysterious abandoned mill, and the addictive TankTop shooter, this waterside hang-out will be the envy of all your friends. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在風景優美的亞熱帶個人空間，用TankTop Shooter的強大火力炸出最高分。 這裡有壯觀的瀑布、神秘的無人磨坊，還有讓人無法自拔的TankTop Shooter，讓眾家好友都羨慕你這個海角樂園。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在風景優美的亞熱帶個人空間，用TankTop Shooter的強大火力炸出最高分。 這裡有壯觀的瀑布、神秘的無人磨坊，還有讓人無法自拔的TankTop Shooter，讓眾家好友都羨慕你這個海角樂園。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blast your way to an epic score with the awesome TankTop shooter in this stunning sub-tropical personal space. With spectacular waterfalls, a mysterious abandoned mill, and the addictive TankTop shooter, this waterside hang-out will be the envy of all your friends. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>