<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Skull Dolphy Frame</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cadre Dolphy "crâne"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schädel-Dolphy-Rahmen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cornice Dolphy teschio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Marco de Dolphies de calaveras</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スカルのドルフィーフレーム</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Skull Dolphy Frame</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A picture frame featuring skull Dolphies.\nUse this frame with any picture or image you like.\nPlayers who have their own “Dolphy room” can customise their Dolphy to be the same colour and design as this frame.\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cadre photo orné de Dolphies "crâne".\nUtilise ce cadre avec la photo ou l'image de ton choix.\nTout joueur ayant un “Dolphydrome” peut personnaliser son Dolphy et lui donner la même couleur et les mêmes motifs que ce cadre.\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Bilderrahmen mit Schädel-Dolphys.\nDu kannst jedes beliebige Bild in diesen Rahmen einfügen.\nSpieler mit einem eigenen Dolphy-Raum können ihr Dolphy mit der Farbe und dem Design des Rahmens ausstatten.\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cornice raffigurante due Dolphy teschio.\nUsa questa cornice con le foto o immagini che preferisci.\nI giocatori che hanno la propria "Stanza di Dolphy" possono personalizzare il loro Dolphy in modo che abbia lo stesso colore e aspetto del modello proposto nella cornice.\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Marco de fotos con Dolphies de calaveras.\nUtiliza este marco con cualquier foto o imagen que desees.\nLos jugadores que tengan su propio "Cuarto de Dolphy" podrán personalizar su Dolphy para que tenga el mismo color y diseño que este marco.\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スカルマークのドルフィーがあしらわれたピクチャーフレームです。\n好きな写真や画像を入れて飾ることができます。\n「ドルフィールーム」でドルフィー育成中の方は、同じデザインがドルフィーのカスタマイズとして使用可能になります。\n[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A picture frame featuring skull Dolphies.\nUse this frame with any picture or image you like.\nPlayers who have their own “Dolphy room” can customize their Dolphy to be the same color and design as this frame.\n[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>