<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dark Blue Bikini with Animated Gold Chain Bundle (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble bikini bleu marine avec chaîne en or animée (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kostümpaket "Dunkelblauer Bikini mit animierter Goldkette" (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completo bikini blu scuro con catena d'oro animata (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de bikini azul oscuro con cadena de oro animada (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">다크 블루 비키니와 움직이는 골드 체인 번들 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Dark Blue Bikini with Animated Gold Chain Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">附動態金鏈的深藍色比堅尼服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">附動態金鏈的深藍色比基尼服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dark Blue Bikini with Animated Gold Chain Bundle (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dress to impress with this dark blue bikini bundle held together by gold loops. Bundle includes a top, bottom, and heels. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Soyez sûre d'impressionner avec ce bikini bleu marine avec anneaux en or. L'ensemble comprend un haut, un bas et des chaussures à talon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Kostümpaket "Dunkelblauer Bikini mit animierter Goldkette", das von soliden goldenen Kettchen gehalten wird, garantiert einen großen Auftritt. Das Paket enthält Oberteil, Unterteil und Pumps. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cattura gli sguardi con questo completo bikini blu scuro impreziosito da anelli d'oro. Include reggiseno, slip e sandali alti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Impresiona a todos, con este conjunto de bikini azul oscuro, unido por aros dorados. El conjunto incluye las partes superior e inferior del bikini y zapatos de tacón. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">골드 체인으로 연결된 다크 블루 비키니 번들과 함께 해변의 스타가 되어 보십시오. 이 번들은 상의, 하의, 그리고 하이힐을 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Dress to impress with this dark blue bikini bundle held together by gold loops. Bundle includes a top, bottom, and heels. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">穿上這套配有金環的深藍色比堅尼服裝組來盛裝登場，艷壓全場。服裝組包括上身、下身及高跟鞋。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">穿上這套配有金環的深藍色比基尼服裝組來盛裝登場，艷壓全場。服裝組包括上半身、下半身及高跟鞋。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dress to impress with this dark blue bikini bundle held together by gold loops. Bundle includes a top, bottom, and heels. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>