<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Casino: Budget Room</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">The Casino: Budget chambre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">The Casino: niedrigen Wert Hotel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">The Casino: valore di hotel a basso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">The Casino: Presupuesto de habitaciones</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Casino: Budget Room</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">We hope you enjoyed playing at The Casino. As a first time player we've managed to find a spare room in section B3 in our former hotel space. We're happy to offer one of our VIP Suites as soon as you've shown the true card shark you are. Good Luck!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nous espérons que vous avez aimé jouer au casino. En tant que joueur première fois que nous avons réussi à trouver une chambre libre dans la section B3 dans notre espace ancien hôtel. Nous sommes heureux d'offrir l'une de nos suites VIP dès que vous avez montré le requin carte vrai que vous êtes. Bonne chance!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wir hoffen, Sie genießen Spielen im Casino. Als erster Spieler Zeit haben wir es geschafft, ein Zimmer in Abschnitt B3 in unserem ehemaligen Hotel Platz finden. Wir freuen uns, einem unserer VIP-Suiten, sobald du den wahren Kartenhai Sie unter Angebot. Viel Glück!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Speriamo vi siate divertiti a giocare al casinò. Come giocatore prima volta siamo riusciti a trovare una stanza libera in B3 sezione nel nostro spazio ex hotel. Siamo lieti di offrire uno dei nostri VIP Suites appena hai mostrato il vero squalo carta sei. Buona fortuna!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esperamos que haya disfrutado de jugar en el casino. Como jugador de la primera vez que hemos logrado encontrar una habitación libre en B3 sección en nuestro espacio antiguo hotel. Estamos encantados de ofrecer uno de nuestros VIP Suites tan pronto como se ha demostrado que el tiburón tarjeta de verdad eres. ¡Buena suerte!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">We hope you enjoyed playing at The Casino. As a first time player we've managed to find a spare room in section B3 in our former hotel space. We're happy to offer one of our VIP Suites as soon as you've shown the true card shark you are. Good Luck!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>