<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Element - Boston Sweater Over Lillo Dress  - Camel and Black (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Element - Sweat-shirt Boston sur une robe Lillo - Chameau et noir (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Element - Boston Pullover über Lillo Kleid  - Kamelfarben und Schwarz (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Element - Boston Maglione e Vestito Lillo - Cammello e Nero (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Element - Boston Sudadera sobre Lillo vestido  - Color Camello y Negro (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Crew neck sweater with intarsia verbiage artwork on chest, rib details, cotton voile details, and metal logo plate.
And sleeveless all-over jersey dress with drop back detail and woven logo label. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sweat-shirt ras de cou avec verbiage décoratif incrusté sur la poitrine, détails côtelés, ornements en voile et plaque logo métallique.
Et une robe sans manche en jersey avec ourlet plongeant à l'arrière et étiquette logo tissée. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gerippter Pullover mit Rundhalsausschnitt, Intarsia-Beschriftung auf der Vorderseite, Verzierungen aus Baumwollschleierstoff und metallener Logoplatte. Darunter ein ärmelloses Strickkleid mit ausgeschnittenem Rücken und gewebtem Logoetikett. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maglione con scollo tondo, scritta intarsiata sul petto, dettagli a costine e in cotone voile e targhetta in metallo con logo.
E vestito senza maniche in jersey con stampa all-over, scollo profondo sulla schiena ed etichetta con logo in tessuto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sudadera de cuello redondo con inscripción gráfica en el pecho mediante técnica de intarsia, detalles de canalé, gasa de algodón y placa metálica con el logotipo.
Y vestido de punto de jersey sin mangas con detalle de caída en espalda y etiqueta cosida con el logotipo. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>