<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Novus Prime Concept: The Codebreaker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Concept de Novus Prime : Le Codebreaker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Novus Prime Konzept: The Codebreaker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Design Novus Prime: Codebreaker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Concepto de Novus Prime: Codebreaker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムのコンセプト：コードブレイカー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임 컨셉: 코드 브레이커</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Novus Prime Concept: The Codebreaker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Novus Prime概念畫：Codebreaker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Novus Prime概念畫：Codebreaker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Novus Prime Concept: The Codebreaker</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. Specialized in AI manipulation, the Codebreaker hacks into nearby bot ships, changing them into unwitting allies in the middle of a dogfight. The tide of battle can quickly turn once a Codebreaker enters the field. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ornez vos murs de peintures conceptuelles de Novus Prime. Spécialisé dans la manipulation d'intelligences artificielles, le Codebreaker pirate les droïdes alentours, les transformant en alliés involontaires en plein combat. L'issue d'une bataille peut rapidement changer quand le Codebreaker entre en jeu. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schmücke deine Wände mit den Konzeptzeichnungen von Novus Prime. Der Codebreaker ist auf die Manipulation von KIs spezialisiert. So kann er sich in Bot Schiffe in der Nähe hacken und sie mitten im Kampf zu willenlosen Verbündeten machen. Das Blatt kann sich schnell wenden, sobald ein Codebreaker ins Spiel kommt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Decora le tue pareti con il design della Novus Prime. Specializzata nella manipolazione di IA, la Codebreaker può prendere il controllo di una nave bot nelle vicinanze, trasformandola in un alleato nel bel mezzo di una battaglia aerea. Le sorti di un conflitto possono cambiare velocemente appena una Codebreaker scende in campo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Adorna tus paredes con las pinturas conceptuales de Novus Prime. Especializado en la manipulación de IA, Codebreaker intenta controlar las naves robot cercanas, convirtiendo éstas en aliados durante el combate aéreo. El clímax de la batalla puede cambiar rápidamente con la entrada de Codebreaker en el campo de batalla. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムのコンセプト絵画を壁に飾ろう。ＡＩを巧みに操るコードブレイカーは近くのボット船に侵入し気付かれないうちに敵ボットを味方に変えてしまう。たとえ戦闘中であったとしてもだ。コードブレイカーの登場で一転、逆転勝利もありうる。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임의 컨셉화로 벽을 장식합니다. AI 조작에 특화된 코드 브레이커는 인근 봇 함선을 해킹해 난전 중 적을 아군으로 바꿔놓습니다. 이러한 관계로 코드 브레이커의 존재는 승패의 흐름을 순식간에 뒤바꿀 수 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. Specialized in AI manipulation, the Codebreaker hacks into nearby bot ships, changing them into unwitting allies in the middle of a dogfight. The tide of battle can quickly turn once a Codebreaker enters the field. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用Novus Prime的概念繪畫裝飾你的牆壁。Codebreaker擅長操控人工智能系統，能在近距離空戰裡入侵附近機械太空船的系統，化敵為友。Codebreaker一旦進入戰場，可迅速扭轉戰局。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用Novus Prime的概念繪畫裝飾你的牆壁。Codebreaker擅長操控人工智能系統，能在近距離空戰裡入侵附近機械太空船的系統，化敵為友。Codebreaker一旦進入戰場，可迅速扭轉戰局。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. Specialized in AI manipulation, the Codebreaker hacks into nearby bot ships, changing them into unwitting allies in the middle of a dogfight. The tide of battle can quickly turn once a Codebreaker enters the field. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>