<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stealth Sofa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sofa de camouflage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tarnungssofa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Divano dell'invisibilità</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sofá sigiloso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Stealth Sofa</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This prototype stealth field generator renders whatever it is attached to (mostly) invisible. Unfortunately, it got lost in the sofa cushions. BONUS: unlocks the Stealth Field gadget for use in MiniBots: Battlebox and MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce prototype de générateur de champ de camouflage rend (presque) invisible tout ce qui y est attaché. Malheureusement, on l'a perdu au milieu des coussins. BONUS : déverrouille le gadget Champ de camouflage utilisable dans MiniBots : Battlebox et dans MiniBots multijoueur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser Prototyp eines Tarnungsfeldgenerators sorgt dafür, dass das, woran er befestigt ist (fast) unsichtbar wird. Leider ging er in den Sofakissen verloren. BONUS: Schaltet das Tarnungsfeld-Gadget für die Anwendung in MiniBots: Battlebox und MiniBots-Multiplayer-Modus frei. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo generatore prototipo di campo di invisibilità rende (per lo più) invisibile qualunque cosa venga attaccata. Sfortunatamente, è andato perso tra i cuscini del divano. BONUS: sblocca il gadget Campo di invisibilità per usarlo in MiniBots: Battlebox e modalità multigiocatore di MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este generador de campo sigiloso prototípico convierte en (casi) invisible casi todo lo que está junto a él. Desgraciadamente, se perdió entre los cojines del sofá. BONUS:  libera el dispositivo Campo sigiloso para utilizarlo en MiniBots: Battlebox y el modo varios jugadores de MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This prototype stealth field generator renders whatever it is attached to (mostly) invisible. Unfortunately, it got lost in the sofa cushions. BONUS: unlocks the Stealth Field gadget for use in MiniBots: Battlebox and MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>