<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Midnight Glade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La Clairière de Minuit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Mitternachtslichtung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Radura a mezzanotte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Claro de medianoche</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">夜が更けた森林の奥</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">한밤중 숲 속의 빈 터</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Midnight Glade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">午夜暮林</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">午夜暮林</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Midnight Glade</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A secluded  glade under a moonlit starry sky. Gather around the solitary tree and warm yourself by the glow of the fire. It's the perfect place for a fireworks party.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une clairière retirée sous un ciel étoilé au clair de lune. Rassemblez-vous autour de cet arbre solitaire et profitez de la chaleur du feu de camp. L'endroit idéal pour une soirée de feux d'artifice.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine abgelegene Lichtung unter einem vom Mond erleuchteten Sternenhimmel. Setz dich unter den einsamen Baum und wärme dich am Feuer. Der perfekte Ort für ein Feuerwerk.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una radura appartata sotto un cielo stellato da cui fa capolino la luna. Raccoglietevi intorno all'albero solitario e riscaldatevi al tepore del fuoco. È il posto perfetto per una festa con i fuochi d'artificio.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un claro apartado bajo un cielo estrellado iluminado por la luna. Reuniros en torno al árbol solitario y caliéntate con el resplandor del fuego. Es el lugar perfecto para una fiesta con fuegos artificiales.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">都会の喧騒から離れたそこはまさしく、癒しの森林オアシスであるのです。しかし、時には花火遊びをして森の木達をびっくりさせましょう。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">별빛이 쏟아지는 달밤의 호젓한 숲 속의 빈 터. 큰 나무 주위에 모여 앉아 따스한 불로 몸을 녹이세요. 불꽃놀이 파티를 열기에 딱 어울리는 곳이죠.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A secluded  glade under a moonlit starry sky. Gather around the solitary tree and warm yourself by the glow of the fire. It's the perfect place for a fireworks party.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">明月照星辰，荒野立孤林。聚到這棵孤木旁，點起營火，暖和每個人的心。到這邊辦花火節最適合了。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">明月照星辰，荒野立孤林。聚到這棵孤木旁，點起營火，暖和每個人的心。到這邊辦花火節最適合了。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A secluded  glade under a moonlit starry sky. Gather around the solitary tree and warm yourself by the glow of the fire. It's the perfect place for a fireworks party.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>