<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Space Crash arcade cabinet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Borne d'arcade Space Crash</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Space Crash Arcade-Automat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cabinato arcade "Space Crash"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Gabinete de la arcada "Space Crash"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Space Crash arcade cabinet</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You can place this cabinet anywhere in your personal space or club-house: it contains a simple 2D score-chaser arcade game. Play this addictive infinite scroller, where you have to avoid colliding with obstacles to travel as far as possible, and beat your high-score. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous pouvez placer cette borne d'arcade n'importe ou dans un espace personnel ou un club-house. Il contient un jeu d'arcade tout simple. Jouez à ce jeu addictif, dont le but est d'éviter les obstacles le plus longtemps possible, pour obtenir un score toujours meilleur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie können diesen Arcade-Automat überall in Ihrem persönlichen Raum oder Clubhaus stellen: es eine einfache 2D-Score-Chaser Arcade-Spiel enthält. Spielen Sie dieses süchtig mach unendlich Scroller, wo Sie vermeiden Kollision mit Hindernissen, so weit wie möglich zu reisen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">È possibile inserire questo cabinato arcade ovunque in uno spazio personale o clubhouse. Esso contiene un semplice gioco arcade. Gioca a questo gioco coinvolgente, l'obiettivo è quello di evitare gli ostacoli più a lungo possibile, per ottenere un punteggio ancora migliore. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Usted puede colocar este gabinete de la arcada en cualquier lugar en un espacio personal o casa club. Contiene un juego arcade sencillo. Juega a este adictivo juego, el objetivo es evitar los obstáculos, siempre y cuando sea posible, para obtener un resultado aún mejor. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You can place this cabinet anywhere in your personal space or club-house: it contains a simple 2D score-chaser arcade game. Play this addictive infinite scroller, where you have to avoid colliding with obstacles to travel as far as possible, and beat your high-score. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>