<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">VEEMEE Ultimate Clothing Bundle - Women</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot de vêtements VEEMEE Ultime - Femmes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">VEEMEE - Das Ultimative Bündel - Damenkleidung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set eccezionale di abbigliamento VEEMEE - Donna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Pack definitivo de ropa VEEMEE - Mujer</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This bundle contains 44 female clothing items from VEEMEE's The Original V-Store.\n
This bundle contains clothing from the 2000 AD, Foam Hand Guns, Island Records, Joystick Junkies, Tops and Tails and Worn Free ranges. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce lot contient 44 vêtements pour femmes du magasin The Original V-Store de VEEMEE.\n
Ce lot contient des vêtements de collections 2000 AD, Foam Hand Guns, Island Records, Joystick Junkies, Tops and Tails et Worn Free. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Bündel enthält 44 Kleidungsstücke für Damen aus dem VEEMEE The Original V-Store.\n
Dieses Bündel enthält Kleidungsstücke aus den Kollektionen von 2000 AD, Foam Hand Guns, Island Records, Joystick Junkies, Tops and Tails und Worn Free. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il set comprende 44 articoli di abbigliamento da donna dal The Original V-Store di VEMEE.\n
Il set comprende capi di abbigliamento delle collezioni 2000 AD, Foam Hand Guns, Island Records, Joystick Junkies, Tops and Tails e Worn Free. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este pack contiene 44 artículos de ropa para mujer de The Original V-Store de VEEMEE.\n
Este pack contiene ropa de las gamas 2000 AD, Foam Hand Guns, Island Records, Joystick Junkies, Tops and Tails y Worn Free. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>