<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Platinum Bomb Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Platinum Bomb Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Platinum Bomb Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Platinum Bomb Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Platinum Bomb Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Blonde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Blonde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Blonde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Blonde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Blonde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Platinum Bomb Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Do blondes have more fun?  Find out with this sexy retro pin-up babe full character costume, wearing a periwinkle blue swim dress with delicate white flowers, she's a breath of fresh air!  This platinum bomb comes complete from head-to-toe with sexy pin-up hair, retro swim dress, custom tats, and animations that will be sure to solve the mystery.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les blondes ont-elles plus de fun? Découvre-le avec cette sexy retro pin-up minette dans son costume, Platinum Bomb porte une robe de bain bleu pervenche avec de délicates fleurs blanches, C'est un souffle d'air frais! Cette Platinum bomb vient complète de la tête au pieds avec des cheveux pin-up sexy, une robe de bain retro, tatouages personnalisées, et animations qui sur résoudront l'énigme.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Haben Blondinen mehr Spaß? Finde es heraus mit diesem kompletten Charakterkostüm des sexy Pin-Up Babes.  Platinum Bomb trägt einen lavenderblauen Badeanzug mit zierlichen weißen Blumen, sie ist wie ein Hauch frischer Luft! Diese Platinbome kommt komplett von Kopf bis Fuß mit sexy Pin-Up Frisur, Retro-Badeanzug, selbstformbaren Tätowierungen und Animationen, die mit Sicherheit das Geheimnis lüften.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le bionde si divertono di piú?  Scoprilo con questo costume completo del personaggio retro da bambola sexy pin -up, Platinum Bomb porta un vestito blu pervinca con dei fiori bianchi molto delicati, é una boccata d'aria fresca!  Questa bomba platinata viene dalla testa ai piedi con capelli sexy da pin-up, costume da bagno retro, lustrini particolari, ed animazioni che sicuramente risolveranno il mistero.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las rubias se divierten mas? Descúbrelo con éste  disfraz completo de muñeca sexy retro pin-up, Platinum Bomb lleva un traje de baño azul marino con pequeñas flores blancas, es un respiro de aire fresco!  Esta bomba platinada viene completa de pies a cabeza con cabello sexy de pin-up, traje de baño retro, motivos a la medida, y animaciones que seguramente resolverán el misterio.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Blonde [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Blonde [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Blonde [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Blonde [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup01_Blonde [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Do blondes have more fun?  Find out with this sexy retro pin-up babe full character costume, wearing a periwinkle blue swim dress with delicate white flowers, she's a breath of fresh air!  This platinum bomb comes complete from head-to-toe with sexy pin-up hair, retro swim dress, custom tats, and animations that will be sure to solve the mystery.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>