<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Novus Prime Private Hangar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Hangar privé du Novus Prime</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Novus Prime Privathangar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hangar privato della Novus Prime</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hangar de soldados Novus Prime</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライム個人用格納庫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임 개인 격납고</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Novus Prime Private Hangar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Novus Prime私人太空船船庫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Novus Prime私人太空船船庫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Novus Prime Private Hangar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is a fully functional hangar for your Novus Prime Officer's Quarters.  With this hangar you can play missions with friends, use the workshop, and collect salaries.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Hangar toutes options pour vos quartiers d'officier du Novus Prime. Avec ce hangar, vous pourrez faire des missions avec vos amis, utiliser l'atelier et récolter des salaires. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dies ist ein voll funktionstüchtiger Hangar für dein Novus Prime Offiziersquartier. Mit diesem Hangar kannst du Missionen mit deinen Freunden spielen, den Workshop benutzen, und Gehalt bekommen.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un hangar completamente funzionale per il tuo alloggio ufficiale della Novus Prime. Con questo hangar puoi intraprendere missioni con gli amici, usare l'officina e ritirare lo stipendio. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este es un hangar completamente funcional para tu cuartel de oficiales Novus Prime. Con este hangar puedes jugar misiones con tus amigos, usar el taller y recolectar salarios.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムの士官棟用の全機能を備えた格納庫をアンロックできる。これさえあれば友達が遊びに来た時に一緒にミッションプレーをしたり、ワークショップを利用したり、サラリーを受け取ったりすることができる。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임 장교 생활구역에 설치할 수 있는, 기능적 차이 없이 완전히 작동하는 격납고입니다. 이 격납고를 통해 친구와 임무를 즐기거나, 작업실을 사용하거나, 보수를 받을 수 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This is a fully functional hangar for your Novus Prime Officer's Quarters.  With this hangar you can play missions with friends, use the workshop, and collect salaries.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這是你的Novus Prime官員府第的實用太空船船庫，讓你跟朋友挑戰任務、使用工作坊及領取薪金。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這是你的Novus Prime官員府第的實用太空船船庫，讓你跟朋友挑戰任務、使用工作坊及領取薪金。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This is a fully functional hangar for your Novus Prime Officer's Quarters.  With this hangar you can play missions with friends, use the workshop, and collect salaries.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>