<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Earth Bug Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack Insecte De Terre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erdkäfer-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pack Insetti Di Terra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack Bicho De Tierra</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The earth bug is a stalwart that can withstand heavy punishment from hostile plants. This pack gives you immediate access to all 3 types of earth bug for use in Killer Plants from Outer Space. Also included in this pack is an earth bug T-shirt (both male and female versions included), access to the earth worm liveries for all of your ships and a large slow pot plant to decorate your apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'insecte de terre est un vaillant soldat qui peut supporter de lourds dégâts infligés par des plantes hostiles. Ce pack vous donne accès aux trois types d'insectes de terre à utiliser dans Killer Plants From Outer Space, à un t-shirt insecte de terre (versions homme et femme incluses), aux livrées Earth Worm pour tous vos vaisseaux et à une grande plante ralentissante en pot pour décorer votre appartement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Erdkäfer ist ein robuster Gefährte, der schweren Angriffen feindlicher Pflanzen widerstehen kann. Dieses Paket verleiht sofortigen Zugriff auf alle 3 Erdkäfer-Arten in "Killer Plants from Outer Space". Es enthält ebenfalls ein Erdkäfer-Shirt (Damen und Herren) und gewährt Zugriff auf die Regenwurm-Lackierung für alle Schiffe, sowie eine große Verlangsamungs-Topfpflanze für Ihr Apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il coriaceo Insetto di Terra riesce a incassare una gran quantità di danni inflitti dalle piante ostili. Questo pack fornisce accesso immediato a tutti i 3 tipi di Insetti di Terra utilizzabili in Killer Plants from Outer Space. Il pack include anche una t-shirt Insetto di Terra (in doppia versione per uomo e donna), l'accesso alle livree Earth Worm per tutte le tue navicelle e una grande pianta rallentante in vaso per decorare il tuo appartamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Es bicho de tierra es inquebrantable y puede resistir cualquier castigo de las plantas hostiles. Este pack garantiza el acceso a los tres tipos de bicho de tierra para usarlos en Killer Plants from Outer Space. También se incluye en este pack una camiseta de bicho de agua y una gorra de béisbol (versiones para hombre y mujer) y una planta ralentizadora en maceta grande para decorar tu apartamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>