<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Dragon Year Mercenary Woman Full Body Suit (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dragon Year Mercenary Woman Full Body Suit (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Costume de Soldat Féminin de l'année du Dragon (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Anzug der Soldatin für Jahr des Drachen (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Abito Mercenaria dell’Anno del Drago (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Vestido de Mercenaría año dragon (Mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Female01_FullBodySuit_MercenaryW</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">용의해 용병 여전사 의상 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Dragon Year Mercenary Woman Full Body Suit (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">龍年女傭兵套裝(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">龍年女傭兵套裝(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dragon Year Mercenary Woman Full Body Suit (Women)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">This is the special edition of Mercenary Woman Full Body Suit for Dragon Year. The subject of it is dragon and phoenix. It combines masculine dragon scales and feminine phoenix head decorations. With these two eastern holy beasts together, this suit creates attractive power.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is the special edition of Mercenary Woman Full Body Suit for Dragon Year. The subject of it is dragon and phoenix. It combines masculine dragon scales and feminine phoenix head decorations. With these two eastern holy beasts together, this suit creates attractive power. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Costume de Soldat Féminin est une collection spéciale de l'année du Dragon, qui une thème du Dragon est du Phénix, compose des écailles du Dragon masculin et l'armure en métal, aussi la décoration féminine de la tête du Phénix. Elle compose les deux sacrés orientals ensemble, qui a la charme incomparable. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sonderausgabe von Anzug der Soldatin für Jahr des Drachen. Zum Thema Drachen und Phönix zeigen die Drachenschuppen und die Metall Rüstung die Männlichkeit von Drachen, während die Phoenix-förmigen Kopfdeko die Weiblichkeit von Phönix zeigt. Die zwei östlichen heiligen Tiere versprühen zusammen einen einzigartigen Charme. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per l’edizione speciale dell’Abito Mercenaria per l’anno del Drago, i temi principali sono il drago e la fenice. Si accostano la mascolinità delle squame del drago e dell’armatura metallica e la femminilità della decorazione a forma della testa della fenice, affascinante accoppiamento dei due mostri sacri dell’Oriente. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Vestido de Mercenaría versión especial del año dragón, con el tema de dragón y felix, escalas del dragón y armaduras representan la parte  masculina, unión junto con la decoración de la cabeza la cual se representa la parte femelina. La unión de dos bestias sagradas orientales está lleno de atracciones. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Female01_FullBodySuit_MercenaryW [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">용병 여전사 의상 용의해 스페셜 버전으로 용과 봉황을 테마로 단단한 용의 비늘조각과 메탈 투구 갑옷 그리고 봉황의 음유한 두형 데코레이션으로 동방의 두 가지 성수를 융합하여 무엇과도 비교할 수 없는 매력을 발산합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This is the special edition of Mercenary Woman Full Body Suit for Dragon Year. The subject of it is dragon and phoenix. It combines masculine dragon scales and feminine phoenix head decorations. With these two eastern holy beasts together, this suit creates attractive power. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">女傭兵套裝的龍年特別版，以龍與鳳為主題，結合陽剛的龍的鱗片與金屬盔甲，以及鳳的陰柔頭形裝飾，將兩種東方的聖獸融合在一起，散發無與倫比的魅力。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">女傭兵套裝的龍年特別版，以龍與鳳為主題，結合陽剛的龍的鱗片與金屬盔甲，以及鳳的陰柔頭形裝飾，將兩種東方的聖獸融合在一起，散發無與倫比的魅力。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This is the special edition of Mercenary Woman Full Body Suit for Dragon Year. The subject of it is dragon and phoenix. It combines masculine dragon scales and feminine phoenix head decorations. With these two eastern holy beasts together, this suit creates attractive power. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>