<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nerd Wear Bundle (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vêtements de Nerd Ensemble (mâle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nerd Verschleiß Bündel (männlich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nerd Vestiti Fascio (maschio)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Uso de Nerd Paquete (masculino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Nerd Wear Bundle (male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">We know what you're saying: "I want it all." With this bundle, you'll be nerd from head to toe.  No more embarrassing cool clothes at your Slide Rule Club Meetings.  Nerd Glasses, Hair, Shirt, Slacks and Shoes . . .there will be no confusing you with a normal person ever again.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nous savons ce que vous dites: "Je veux tout." Avec ce kit, vous serez nerd de la tête aux pieds. Pas plus de vêtements embarrassants-cool lors de vos Réunions Slide Club Règle. Nerd Lunettes, Cheveux, Chemise, Pantalons et Chaussures  . . . vous ne serez jamais être confondue avec une personne normale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wir wissen, was du sagst: "Ich will alles." Mit diesem bündel werden sie nerd von kopf bis fuß. Nicht mehr peinlich coole klamotten an Ihrem rechenschieber Clubtreffen. Nerd Brille, Haare, Hemd, Hose und Schuhe  . . . es wird keine verwirrenden sie mit einer normalen person jemals wieder. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sappiamo quello che stai dicendo: "voglio tutto." Con questo pacchetto, sarai nerd dalla testa ai piedi. Senza vestiti più imbarazzante cool al vostro Regolo Riunioni del Club. Nerd Occhiali, Capelli, Camicia, Pantaloni e Scarpe  . . . non ci sarà si confonde con una persona normale, mai più. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sabemos lo que estás diciendo: "Lo quiero todo." Con este paquete, se le nerd de pies a cabeza. No hay ropa fresca más embarazoso en su regla de cálculo Reuniones del Club. Gafas de Nerd, Pelo, Camisa, Pantalones y Zapatos  . . . no habrá que confundir con una persona normal nunca más. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">We know what you're saying: "I want it all." With this bundle, you'll be nerd from head to toe.  No more embarrassing cool clothes at your Slide Rule Club Meetings.  Nerd Glasses, Hair, Shirt, Slacks and Shoes . . .there will be no confusing you with a normal person ever again.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>