<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fallen Leaves Tile Set</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble de carreaux à motif de feuilles tombées</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kacheln mit Laub</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set di mattonelle con foglie gialle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de baldosas de hojas caídas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fallen Leaves Tile Set</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A set of fallen leaves tiles.
\n
\nThis set includes the following items for customizing your personal space.
\nFallen Leaves Tile - Big Pile (Ornaments)
\nFallen Leaves Tile - Small Pile (Ornaments)
\n
\n*Each item will be added to their relevant wardrobe and furniture category. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Des carreaux à motif de feuilles tombées.\n\nComprend les éléments de personnalisation de l'espace personnel suivants :\nCarreau à motif de feuilles tombées - Grand tas (Décoration)\nCarreau à motif de feuilles tombées - Petit tas (Décoration)\n\n*Chaque objet sera ajouté à la catégorie garde-robe ou mobilier correspondante. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kacheln mit Laub.\n\nDas Set enthält folgende Objekte, mit denen du dich ausstatten kannst.\nKachel mit Laub – großer Haufen (Ornamente)\nKachel mit Laub – kleiner Haufen (Ornamente)\n\n*Jedes Objekt wird der entsprechenden Kleiderschrank- und Möbel-Kategorie hinzugefügt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un set di mattonelle con foglie gialle.\n\nQuesto set include i seguenti elementi per la personalizzazione del tuo spazio personale.\nMattonella con foglie gialle - Pila grande (decorazioni)\nMattonella con foglie gialle - Pila piccola (decorazioni)\n\n*Ogni oggetto verrà aggiunto alla rispettiva categoria all'interno del guardaroba e dei mobili. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un conjunto de baldosas de hojas caídas.\n\nEste conjunto incluye los siguientes elementos para personalizar tu espacio personal.\nBaldosa de hojas caídas: montón grande (adornos)\nBaldosa de hojas caídas: montón pequeño (adornos)\n\n*Cada objeto se añadirá a la categoría de vestuario o mobiliario correspondiente. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A set of fallen leaves tiles.
\n
\nThis set includes the following items for customizing your personal space.
\nFallen Leaves Tile - Big Pile (Ornaments)
\nFallen Leaves Tile - Small Pile (Ornaments)
\n
\n*Each item will be added to their relevant wardrobe and furniture category. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>