<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ice Bug Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack Insecte De Glace</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eiskäfer-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pack Insetti Di Ghiaccio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack Bicho De Hielo</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The ice bug excels at both attack and defence, freezing Ginger's plant life with its deadly ice blast attack. This pack gives you access to all 3 types of ice bug for use in Killer Plants from Outer Space. Also included in this pack is an ice bug T-shirt and baseball cap (both male and female versions included). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'insecte de glace excelle en attaque comme en défense. Il gèle les plantes de Ginger avec son explosion de glace mortelle. Ce pack vous donne accès aux trois types d'insectes de glace à utiliser dans Killer Plants From Outer Space, à un t-shirt insecte de glace et une casquette de base-ball (versions homme et femme incluses). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Eiskäfer verfügt über herausragende Angriffs- und Verteidigungswerte. Er gefriert Gingers Pflanzen mit seinem tödlichen Eisangriff. Dieses Paket verleiht Zugriff auf alle 3 Eiskäfer-Arten in "Killer Plants from Outer Space". Es enthält ebenfalls ein Eiskäfer-Shirt und eine Baseballkappe (Damen und Herren). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'Insetto di Ghiaccio è efficace sia in fase di attacco che di difesa, essendo in grado di congelare le piante di Ginger con il suo letale attacco glaciale. Questo pack ti consente di accedere a tutti i 3 tipi di Insetti di Ghiaccio utilizzabili in Killer Plants from Outer Space. Il pack include anche una t-shirt Insetto di Ghiaccio e un cappellino da baseball (in doppia versione per uomo e donna). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este bicho de hielo es excelente para atacar y defender, congelando a la planta de Ginger con su rayo de hielo mortal. Este pack garantiza el acceso a los tres tipos de bicho de hielo para usarlos en Killer Plants from Outer Space. También se incluye en este pack una camiseta de bicho de hielo y una gorra de béisbol (versiones para hombre y mujer). [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>