<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">HEAVY RAIN™: Evidence Analysis</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">HEAVY RAIN™ : analyse de preuves</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">HEAVY RAIN™: Beweisanalyse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">HEAVY RAIN™: Analisi delle prove</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">HEAVY RAIN™: Análisis de pruebas</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Deduce who hasn't visited the scene</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Déterminez qui n'est pas venu sur les lieux.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Folgern Sie, wer nicht am Schauplatz war.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Deduci chi non ha visitato la scena</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Deduce quién no ha estado en el escenario.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_1_Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Pill Container</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Boîte à pilules</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tablettenbehälter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Contenitore di pillole</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pastillero</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_1_Fact</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Object empty. Name and contents unclear. Which character would need to take pills? Does this point at someone in particular?</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Objet vide. Propriétaire et contenu indéfinis. Quel personnage aurait besoin de médicaments ? Cet indice est-il lié à quelqu'un en particulier ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Leeres Objekt. Name und Inhalt unbekannt. Welcher Charakter könnte diese Tabletten brauchen? Deutet dies auf eine bestimmte Person hin?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Oggetto vuoto. Nome e contenuto incerti. Quale personaggio potrebbe aver bisogno di pillole? Ti suggerisce qualcuno in particolare?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Objeto vacío. Nombre y contenido desconocidos. ¿Qué personaje necesitaría pastillas? ¿Incrimina esto a alguien en particular?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>  
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_2_Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hotel Receipt</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Note d'hôtel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hotelrechnung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ricevuta hotel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ticket de hotel</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_2_Fact</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Information on receipt water-stained and therefore unable to read. Who would be staying at a hotel?</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette note a été exposé à l'eau et est par conséquent illisible. Qui peut bien séjourner dans un hôtel ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Rechnung hat Wasserflecken und ist unlesbar. Wer könnte in einem Hotel gewesen sein?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scritte su una ricevuta bagnata, quindi illeggibile. Chi potrebbe aver pernottato in hotel?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La información del ticket está borrada por el agua y resulta ilegible. ¿Quién se hospedaría en el hotel?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_3_Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Red Material</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Tissu rouge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rotes Material</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Materiale rosso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Material rojo</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_3_Fact</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cotton material looks likely to come from a red clothing item. Most likely a shirt/blouse.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Morceau de tissu en coton qui semble provenir d'un vêtement rouge. Probablement un chemisier.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Baumwollmaterial scheint von einem roten Kleidungsstück zu stammen. Wahrscheinlich von einem Hemd oder einer Bluse.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Frammento di cotone, appartenente ad un capo di abbigliamento rosso. Probabilmente una camicia o una maglia.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Material de algodón, posiblemente de una prenda roja. Seguramente, una camisa o blusa.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>  
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_4_Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Coffee Cup</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Tasse de café</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kaffeetasse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tazza da caffè</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Taza de café</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_4_Fact</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Pink lipstick traces found on cup. Does this point at someone in particular? Is this significant?</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Traces de rouge à lèvres rose relevées sur la tasse. Cet indice est-il lié à quelqu'un en particulier ? Est-ce pertinent ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Auf der Tasse sind rosa Lippenstiftspuren. Deutet dies auf eine bestimmte Person hin? Eine relevante Spur?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tracce di rossetto rosa rilevate sulla tazza. Ti suggeriscono qualcuno in particolare? Sarà un elemento rilevante?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Restos de pintalabios rosa en la taza. ¿Incrimina esto a alguien en particular? ¿Tiene alguna relevancia?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_5_Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Coat Button</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Bouton de manteau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mantelknopf</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bottone cappotto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Botón de abrigo</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_5_Fact</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Button found with some cotton thread and traces of another waterproof brown material. Not leather. Most likely an outdoor jacket/raincoat. </LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Bouton auquel sont restés attachés du fil de coton et un morceau de tissu imperméable marron. Il provient probablement d'une veste ou d'un vêtement de pluie.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Knopf mit Baumwollfäden und Spuren eines wasserdichten braunen Materials gefunden. Kein Leder. Wahrscheinlich eine Outdoor-Jacke oder ein Regenmantel.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bottone con qualche filo di cotone e tracce di un altro materiale marrone impermeabile. Non pelle. Dev'essere di una specie di giaccone/impermeabile.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Botón hallado con restos de hilo de algodón y de otro material marrón impermeable. No es cuero. Posiblemente, de un abrigo o chubasquero. </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_6_Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Grey Hair</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Cheveu blanc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Graues Haar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Capello grigio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pelo gris</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_6_Fact</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A grey hair. Initial analysis points in the direction of a person approximately 40 years old. Is this relevant?</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un cheveu blanc. L'analyse initiale indique qu'il appartient à une personne d'une quarantaine d'années. Est-ce pertinent ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein graues Haar. Erste Analyse deutet auf eine Person von rund 40 Jahren hin. Ist das relevant?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un capello grigio. Le prime analisi puntano a una persona di circa 40 anni. È un elemento rilevante?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un pelo gris. El análisis preliminar indica una persona de unos 40 años de edad. ¿Es relevante?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>  
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_7_Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Photograph</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Photographie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Foto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fotografia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fotografía</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_7_Fact</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Picture of a young boy with “Love you Daddy, Shaun” written on it.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Photo d'un jeune garçon sur laquelle il est écrit : "Je t'aime, papa. Shaun".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bild eines kleinen Jungen mit der Aufschrift "Daddy, ich hab dich lieb! Shaun".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Foto di un bambino con sopra la scritta "Ti voglio bene papà, Shaun".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Imagen de un joven con la inscripción "Te quiero, papá. Shaun".</LANG>
  </PHRASE>  
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_8_Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Leather Material</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Morceau de cuir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lederstück</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Frammento di pelle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Material de cuero</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_8_Fact</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Piece of brown leather material. Extended exposure to water visible. Most likely from an item of outdoor clothing. </LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Morceau de cuir marron. Traces d'exposition prolongée à l'eau. Provient probablement d'un vêtement d'extérieur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Stück braunes Leder. Offensichtlich längere Zeit dem Wasser ausgesetzt. Stammt wahrscheinlich von einem Outdoor-Kleidungsstück.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Frammento di pelle marrone. Mostra una prolungata esposizione all'acqua. Probabilmente proviene da un capo da esterno.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fragmento de cuero marrón. Presenta una exposición continuada al agua. Posiblemente, de una prenda usada en exteriores. </LANG>
  </PHRASE>  
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_9_Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Inhaler</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Inhalateur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Inhalator</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Inalatore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Inhalador</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_9_Fact</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A standard inhaler/puffer commonly used by asthma sufferers. Is this item relevant?</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un inhalateur standard couramment utilisé par les personnes souffrant d'asthme. Cet objet constitue-t-il une preuve ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein gewöhnlicher Inhalator, wie ihn Asthmatiker benutzen. Ist dieser Gegenstand wichtig?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tipico inalatore spray usato da soggetti asmatici. Sarà un elemento rilevante?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un inhalador estándar utilizado habitualmente por asmáticos. ¿Es relevante?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_10_Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Newspaper</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Journal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeitung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quotidiano</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Periódico</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_10_Fact</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A page from a newspaper. Some water damage so the name is illegible. Any relevance? </LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Une page d'un journal. Son exposition à l'eau l'a rendue illisible. S'agit-il d'un indice déterminant ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine Zeitungsseite. Da sie dem Wasser ausgesetzt war, ist der Name unlesbar. Von Bedeutung?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pagina di un quotidiano. Il nome è illeggibile a causa dell'acqua. È di qualche interesse?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una página de periódico parcialmente dañada por el agua. El nombre es ilegible. ¿Es relevante? </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_11_Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Club Flyer</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Flyer de boîte de nuit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Club-Flyer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Volantino club</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Panfleto de club</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Item_11_Fact</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This flyer is promoting a club called the Blue Lagoon. Is this significant in finding out who was here?</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce flyer fait la publicité d'une boîte de nuit appelée "Blue Lagoon". Cet indice permet-il de déduire qui est venu sur ces lieux ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser Flyer wirbt für einen Club namens "Blue Lagoon". Ist das wichtig, um herauszufinden, wer hier war?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo volantino pubblicizza il club Blue Lagoon. Che possa servire a scoprire chi ci è stato?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este panfleto anuncia un club llamado Blue Lagoon. ¿Tiene importancia para averiguar quién estuvo aquí?</LANG>
  </PHRASE> 
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Intro Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">HEAVY RAIN™: Evidence Analysis</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">HEAVY RAIN™ : analyse de preuves</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">HEAVY RAIN™: Beweisanalyse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">HEAVY RAIN™: Analisi delle prove</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">HEAVY RAIN™: Análisis de pruebas</LANG>
  </PHRASE>  
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Intro Body 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Three of the playable characters from HEAVY RAIN™ have visited this scene.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Trois des personnages jouables de HEAVY RAIN™ sont venus ici.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drei der spielbaren Charaktere aus HEAVY RAIN™ waren am Schauplatz.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tre dei personaggi giocabili di HEAVY RAIN™ hanno visitato questa scena.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tres de los personajes jugables de HEAVY RAIN™ han visitado la escenario.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Intro Body 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You must use your powers of deduction to work out which three of the four possible characters these are.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez votre pouvoir de déduction pour découvrir de quels personnages il s'agit, parmi les quatre possibles.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie müssen Ihre deduktiven Fähigkeiten einsetzen, um herauszufinden, welche drei der vier möglichen Charaktere dies sind.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Devi utilizzare le tue capacità di deduzione per scoprire quali siano questi tre fra i quattro personaggi possibili.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Debes usar tus dotes de deducción para averiguar quiénes son los tres de los cuatro posibles.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Intro Body 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Scattered around this scene are a number of clues. Using the camera you have been given, take photos of the six clues that signify that three of the characters have definitely been here. You only have space for six photos so choose wisely.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Plusieurs indices sont dispersés dans cet espace. Grâce à l'appareil photo qui vous a été remis, prenez en photo les six indices vous permettant de déterminer avec certitude que trois des personnages sont venus ici. Vous ne pouvez prendre que six photos alors réfléchissez bien.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">An diesem Schauplatz sind verschiedene Hinweise verteilt. Fotografieren Sie mit der Kamera, die Sie erhalten haben, die sechs Hinweise, die beweisen, dass drei der Charaktere tatsächlich hier waren. Sie haben nur Platz für sechs Fotos, also entscheiden Sie mit Bedacht.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sparsi per la scena ci sono vari indizi. Utilizzando la fotocamera che hai ricevuto, scatta le foto di sei indizi che dimostrino che tre personaggi sono sicuramente stati qui. Hai spazio solo per sei foto, quindi scegli attentamente.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">En el escenario hay diversas pistas. Utiliza la cámara que has recibido, haz fotos de las seis pistas que prueban la presencia de los tres personajes. Solo tienes espacio para seis fotos, así que escógelas sabiamente.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Intro Body 4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Some clues point at more than one possible character so these should be ignored as they are inconclusive. Some clues have been placed to confuse. Will they confuse you?</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Certains indices sont liés à plusieurs personnages. Étant peu concluants, il convient donc de les ignorer. D'autres indices ont pour but de vous troubler. Atteindront-ils leur objectif ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Einige Hinweise deuten auf mehr als einen möglichen Charakter hin. Sie sollten ignoriert werden, da sie nicht schlüssig sind. Einige Hinweise wurden platziert, um Sie zu verwirren. Werden Sie sich verwirren lassen?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Alcuni indizi si ricollegano a più di un personaggio, quindi vanno ignorati perché inconcludenti. Alcuni indizi sono intenzionalmente fuorvianti. Ti lascerai fuorviare?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Algunas pistas apuntan a más de un posible personaje, así que deberías ignorarlas por no ser concluyentes. Otras se han colocado para confundirte. ¿Lograrán hacerlo?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Intro Body 5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Once satisfied that you have captured the six shots required, return the camera to this location and find out if you have deduced correctly.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Une fois satisfait des six clichés que vous avez pris, ramenez l'appareil photo ici et découvrez si vous avez vu juste.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sobald Sie der Meinung sind, dass Sie die sechs benötigten Bilder aufgenommen haben, bringen Sie die Kamera hierher zurück und finden Sie heraus, ob Sie die richtigen Schlussfolgerungen gezogen haben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quando pensi di aver scattato le sei foto richieste, riporta qui la fotocamera e scopri se le tue deduzioni sono state corrette.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una vez realizadas las seis fotografías que necesitas, devuelve la cámara aquí y averigua si has deducido correctamente.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Intro Body 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If you capture an incorrect shot then you will need to exit the game and collect a new camera from this point.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Si vous avez pris un cliché non concluant, vous devrez quitter le jeu et reprendre un nouvel appareil photo ici.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn Sie ein falsches Foto aufgenommen haben, müssen Sie das Spiel verlassen und sich hier eine neue Kamera holen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se scatti la foto sbagliata dovrai uscire dal gioco e raccogliere una nuova fotocamera in questo punto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Su realizas una fotografía incorrecta, deberás salir del juego y hacerte con una nueva cámara aquí.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Intro Body 7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Good luck.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Bonne chance.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Viel Glück.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Buona fortuna.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Buena suerte.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] Continue</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] Continuer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] Fortfahren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] Continua</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] Continuar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">More Info</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] More Info</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] Plus d'info</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] Weitere Infos</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] Altre informazioni</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] Más información</LANG>
  </PHRASE> 
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Door</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You need to be wearing the HEAVY RAIN™ "Access All Areas" Shirt to go through this door</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous devez porter le T-shirt HEAVY RAIN™ "V.I.P." pour franchir cette porte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie müssen das "HEAVY RAIN™ - Access All Areas"-T-Shirt tragen, um durch diese Tür zu gehen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Devi indossare la maglietta "Accesso a tutte le aree" di HEAVY RAIN™ per attraversare questa porta.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Necesitas llevar la camiseta de "acceso a todas las areas" de HEAVY RAIN™ para atravesar esta puerta.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Ethan 1</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">ETHAN MARS</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">ETHAN MARS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">ETHAN MARS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">ETHAN MARS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">ETHAN MARS</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Ethan Caption</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] ETHAN MARS</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] ETHAN MARS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] ETHAN MARS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] ETHAN MARS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] ETHAN MARS</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Ethan 2</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Ethan Mars is a young architect, living on the east coast of America. Two years ago, he lost his eldest son in a car accident that left him in a coma. Once a successful and happy family man, Ethan is now grief-stricken and depressed; separated from his wife, and distant from his other son, Shaun.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Ethan Mars est un jeune architecte résidant sur la côte est des États-Unis. Il y a deux ans, il a perdu son fils aîné dans un accident de voiture qui l'a lui-même plongé dans le coma. Autrefois un architecte brillant et un père de famille heureux, Ethan est aujourd'hui rongé par le chagrin et en proie à la dépression. Séparé de sa femme, il éprouve des difficultés à communiquer avec son autre fils, Shaun.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ethan Mars ist ein junger Architekt, der an der amerikanischen Ostküste lebt. Vor zwei Jahren starb sein ältester Sohn bei einem Autounfall, bei dem er selbst ins Koma fiel. Ethan war früher ein erfolgreicher und glücklicher Familienmensch, jetzt ist er traurig und depressiv. Er lebt von seiner Frau getrennt und hat ein distanziertes Verhältnis zu Shaun, seinem anderen Sohn.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ethan Mars è un giovane architetto che vive sulla costa orientale degli Stati Uniti. Due anni fa, perse il figlio maggiore in un incidente stradale che lo lasciò in coma. Da felice padre di famiglia e uomo di successo, Ethan è ora affranto dal dolore e depresso, anche a causa della separazione dalla moglie e della lontananza dall'altro suo figlio, Shaun.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ethan Mars es un joven arquitecto que vive en la costa Este de Estados Unidos. Hace dos años, perdió a su hijo mayor en un accidente de coche que lo dejó en coma. Ethan, que fue una vez un hombre con una familia feliz, es ahora presa del dolor, deprimido, separado de su esposa y distanciado de su otro hijo, Shaun.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Ethan 3</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Still suffering from the after-effects of the accident, Ethan is thrown into a nightmare when he discovers that Shaun may become the next victim of the Origami Killer. He will be forced to confront just how far he is prepared to go to rescue his son – and in doing so, he may be able to finally find redemption from the guilt and grief he feels.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Souffrant encore des séquelles de l'accident, Ethan plonge en plein cauchemar en découvrant que Shaun pourrait être la prochaine victime du tueur aux origamis. Bientôt contraint de prouver jusqu'où il est prêt à aller pour sauver son fils, Ethan trouvera peut-être le moyen de se libérer de la culpabilité et du chagrin qui l'accablent.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ethan leidet noch unter den Auswirkungen des Unfalls, und als er entdeckt, dass Shaun das nächste Opfer des Origami-Killers werden könnte, findet er sich in einem Albtraum wieder. Er muss sich der Frage stellen, wie weit er gehen würde, um seinen Sohn zu retten. Und vielleicht wird er dabei endlich von seinen Schuldgefühlen und seiner Trauer erlöst ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ethan sprofonda in un incubo quando scopre che Shaun potrebbe essere la prossima vittima dell'assassino dell'origami. Per salvare suo figlio sarà costretto a scoprire quanto è disposto a rischiare di sé. E nel farlo, potrebbe finalmente riuscire a riscattarsi dal dolore e dai sensi di colpa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Él, que aún sufre los efectos secundarios del accidente, vive ahora una pesadilla al descubrir que Shaun puede convertirse en la próxima víctima del Asesino del Origami. Se verá forzado a descubrir hasta dónde llegaría para salvar a su hijo y así redimirse tal vez de la culpa y el dolor que siente.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Scott 1</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">SCOTT SHELBY</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">SCOTT SHELBY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">SCOTT SHELBY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">SCOTT SHELBY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">SCOTT SHELBY</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Scott Caption</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] SCOTT SHELBY</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] SCOTT SHELBY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] SCOTT SHELBY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] SCOTT SHELBY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] SCOTT SHELBY</LANG>
  </PHRASE>  
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Scott 2</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Scott Shelby, 44 years old, is former cop who turned private investigator after 20 years with the local police department. Two decades on the streets have left him tough and cynical, but despite his sometimes hard demeanour, he has a sense of honour and compassion that shines through under pressure.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Scott Shelby, 44 ans, est un ancien policier reconverti en détective privé après vingt ans de service au sein de la police locale. Sa longue expérience de la rue l'a endurci jusqu'au cynisme, mais malgré une attitude parfois bourrue, il est habité par un sens de l'honneur et une bonté qui se révèlent sous la pression.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Scott Shelby ist 44 Jahre alt und ein ehemaliger Polizist, der nach 20 Jahren bei der örtlichen Polizei Privatdetektiv wurde. Die zwei Jahrzehnte auf den Straßen der Stadt haben ihn hart und zynisch gemacht, aber trotz seiner harten Schale verfügt er auch in gefährlichen Situationen über Ehrgefühl und Mitleid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scott Shelby, 44 anni, è un ex-poliziotto, ora investigatore privato dopo 20 anni di servizio al dipartimento di polizia locale. Due decenni sulla strada lo hanno reso duro e cinico. Tuttavia, nonostante qualche comportamento brusco, ha un senso dell'onore e della compassione che traspare anche sotto pressione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Scott Shelby, de 44 años, es un ex policía que se convirtió en investigador privado después de servir 20 años en el cuerpo de policía local. Dos décadas en las calles lo han convertido en un tipo duro y cínico. Sin embargo, a pesar de su carácter, su sentido del honor y de la compasión salen a relucir cuando está bajo presión.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Scott 3</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Shelby has been hired by the families of previous victims of the Origami Killer, and he is now conducting a parallel investigation into the case, searching for clues and leads that the authorities may have missed.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Shelby a été engagé par les familles des victimes du tueur aux origamis. Il mène sa propre enquête sur l'affaire, à la recherche d'indices et de pistes qui auraient pu échapper à la police.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Shelby wurde von den Angehörigen früherer Opfer des Origami-Killers angeheuert und führt jetzt eine parallele Untersuchung des Falls durch. Er sucht nach Hinweisen und Spuren, die der Polizei entgangen sein könnten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Shelby è stato ingaggiato dalle famiglie delle precedenti vittime dell'assassino dell'origami, e ora sta conducendo un'indagine parallela sul caso, ricercando indizi e piste che potrebbero essere sfuggiti alle autorità.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las familias de las últimas víctimas del Asesino del Origami han contratado a Shelby para que realice una investigación paralela del caso, buscando pistas que las autoridades hayan podido pasar por alto.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>  
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Madison 1</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">MADISON PAIGE</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">MADISON PAIGE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MADISON PAIGE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">MADISON PAIGE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">MADISON PAIGE</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Madison Caption</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] MADISON PAIGE</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] MADISON PAIGE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] MADISON PAIGE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] MADISON PAIGE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] MADISON PAIGE</LANG>
  </PHRASE>  
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Madison 2</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Madison Paige is a young reporter, living alone in the city. Suffering from crippling insomnia and nightmares, she often finds herself checking into local motels for the night – seemingly the only place she can rest and relax. </LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Madison Paige est une jeune journaliste, vivant seule en ville. Souffrant d'insomnie et en proie à de terribles cauchemars, elle trouve souvent refuge pour la nuit dans des motels, le seul endroit où elle puisse se détendre et se reposer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Madison Paige ist eine junge Journalistin, die allein in der Stadt lebt. Sie leidet unter schwerer Schlaflosigkeit und Albträumen und bucht sich häufig über Nacht in den örtlichen Motels ein, da sie anscheinend nur dort Ruhe und Entspannung findet.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Madison Paige è una giovane giornalista che abita da sola in città. Soffrendo gravemente di insonnia e incubi, spesso si trova a pernottare nei motel locali, apparentemente gli unici luoghi in cui riesce a riposare e rilassarsi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Madison Paige es una joven periodista que vive sola en la ciudad. Sufre insomnio y pesadillas constantes. Con frecuencia acude a moteles baratos del lugar para pasar la noche. Es, al parecer, el único lugar donde puede descansar y reponer fuerzas. </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Madison 3</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Though she has no apparent connection with the Origami Killer case, she will soon find herself unexpectedly drawn into the investigation; when she does, she will show courage and commitment, placing herself in great danger to find out the truth.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Bien qu'elle n'ait aucun lien apparent avec l'affaire du tueur aux origamis, elle se retrouvera bientôt mêlée à l'enquête. Elle fera alors preuve de courage et d'audace, allant jusqu'à risquer sa vie pour faire éclater la vérité.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Obwohl sie anscheinend nichts mit dem Fall des Origami-Killers zu tun hat, wird sie unerwartet in die Untersuchung hineingezogen. Dabei zeigt sie Mut und Einsatz. Sie setzt sich großer Gefahr aus, um die Wahrheit herauszufinden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Anche se non sembra avere legami con il caso dell'assassino dell'origami, si troverà inaspettatamente risucchiata nelle indagini. Quando succederà, darà prova di coraggio e dedizione, mettendosi in grave pericolo per scoprire la verità.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pese a no tener una conexión aparente con el caso del Asesino del Origami, pronto se verá envuelta en la investigación de forma inesperada. Llegado el momento, mostrará valor y compromiso, y no dudará en exponerse a grandes peligros para averiguar la verdad.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Norman 1</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">NORMAN JAYDEN</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">NORMAN JAYDEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">NORMAN JAYDEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">NORMAN JAYDEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">NORMAN JAYDEN</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Norman Caption</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] NORMAN JAYDEN</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] NORMAN JAYDEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] NORMAN JAYDEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] NORMAN JAYDEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] NORMAN JAYDEN</LANG>
  </PHRASE>  
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Norman 2</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Norman Jayden is a dedicated and thorough FBI profiler, sent into this unfamiliar city to support the police force with their investigation into the Origami Killer. Jayden specialises in utilising an experimental device called ARI (‘Added Reality Interface’), which allows him to investigate crime scenes and analyse evidence in a unique way.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Norman Jayden est un profiler du FBI appliqué et consciencieux, envoyé dans une ville qui lui est inconnue pour renforcer l'équipe d'investigation en charge de l'affaire du tueur aux origamis. La spécificité de Jayden est d'utiliser un système expérimental appelé ARI (interface de réalité augmentée) lui permettant d'analyser une scène de crime et des indices sous un angle novateur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Norman Jayden ist ein engagierter und gründlicher Profiler des FBI, der in diese ihm unbekannte Stadt geschickt wird, um die Polizei bei der Untersuchung des Origami-Killer-Falls zu unterstützen. Jayden kennt sich besonders gut mit einem experimentellen Gerät namens ARI (Added Reality Interface) aus, mit dem er Tatorte und Beweise auf einzigartige Weise untersuchen kann.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Norman Jayden è uno scrupoloso criminologo dell'FBI, inviato in questa inospitale città per affiancare le forze di polizia nelle indagini sull'assassino dell'origami. Jayden è specializzato nell'uso di un dispositivo sperimentale chiamato ARI ("Added Reality Interface"), che gli consente di esaminare le scene dei crimini analizzando gli indizi in modo ineguagliabile.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Norman Jayden es un criminólogo del FBI concienzudo y perseverante llegado a esta ciudad para ayudar a la policía en el caso del Asesino del Origami. Jayden se especializa por utilizar un dispositivo experimental llamado ARI ("Interfaz de Realidad Aumentada"), que le permite investigar en los escenarios del crimen y analizar pruebas de una forma única.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">BIOG Norman 3</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">With the local cops resentful of both his methods and his very presence, he struggles urgently to piece together the evidence before it is too late, and another victim is discovered.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Malgré l'hostilité des policiers de la ville lui reprochant ses méthodes et sa présence, il mène une lutte acharnée pour assembler les pièces du puzzle avant qu'il ne soit trop tard et que le tueur ne fasse une autre victime.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Während die örtliche Polizei sowohl seine Methoden als auch seine bloße Anwesenheit ablehnt, bemüht er sich mit aller Kraft, die Beweise zusammenzutragen, bevor es zu spät ist und ein weiteres Opfer entdeckt wird. </LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Con i poliziotti locali infastiditi tanto dai suoi metodi quanto dalla sua presenza, si affretta a raccogliere prove prima che sia troppo tardi e venga scoperta un'altra vittima.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con la policía local molesta por sus métodos y su mera presencia, Jayden se esfuerza por encajar las piezas del rompecabezas antes de que sea demasiado tarde y el asesino se cobre una nueva víctima.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Well Done Title</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Conclusive Evidence!</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Preuves irréfutables !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beweise schlüssig!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prove inconfutabili!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Pruebas concluyentes!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
    <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Well Done Body</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Congratulations, you have captured the correct shots. Your powers of deduction are strong. Please accept these rewards for your expert investigative prowess.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Félicitations, vous avez pris les bons clichés. Votre pouvoir de déduction est très développé. Veuillez accepter cette récompense pour avoir mené cette enquête avec brio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Herzlichen Glückwunsch, Sie haben die richtigen Aufnahmen gemacht. Ihre deduktiven Fähigkeiten sind ausgezeichnet. Bitte nehmen Sie für Ihre professionellen ermittlungstechnischen Fähigkeiten diese Belohnung an.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Congratulazioni, hai eseguito gli scatti corretti. Le tue capacità di deduzione sono notevoli. Accetta questa ricompensa per la tua raffinata abilità investigativa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Enhorabuena, has obtenido las fotografías correctas. Tienes grandes dotes de deducción. Acepta esta recompensa por tu gran destreza investigadora.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Fail Title</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Inconclusive Evidence</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Preuves peu concluantes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beweise nicht schlüssig</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prove inconcludenti</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pruebas inconcluyentes</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Fail Body 1</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Unfortunately you haven’t captured the correct shots. You obtained %i of 6. You need to take your time and piece the information together correctly. </LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Malheureusement, vous n'avez pas pris les bons clichés. Vous en avez obtenu %i sur 6. Prenez votre temps pour assembler les pièces du puzzle.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Leider haben Sie nicht die richtigen Aufnahmen gemacht. Sie haben %i von 6. Sie müssen sich Zeit lassen und die Informationen richtig zusammenfügen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Purtroppo non hai eseguito gli scatti corretti. Ne hai ottenuti %i su 6. Devi operare con calma e raccogliere le informazioni corrette.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lamentablemente, no has tomado todas las fotografías correctas. Has obtenido %i de 6. Tómate tu tiempo y reúne la información correcta. </LANG>
  </PHRASE>  
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Fail Body 2</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Would you like to try again?</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Voulez-vous réessayer ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Möchten Sie es erneut versuchen?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Desideri riprovare?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Quieres volver a intentarlo?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
    <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Fail Legend</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] Yes, [CIRCLE] Exit game</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] Oui [CIRCLE] Quitter le jeu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] Ja [CIRCLE] Spiel verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] Sì [CIRCLE] Esci dal gioco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] Sí [CIRCLE] Salir del juego</LANG>
  </PHRASE> 
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Take Photo</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Press [CROSS] to take a photo or [TRIANGLE] to exit camera mode</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyez sur [CROSS] pour prendre une photo ou sur [TRIANGLE] pour quitter le mode Appareil photo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücken Sie [CROSS], um ein Foto aufzunehmen, oder [TRIANGLE], um den Kamera-Modus zu verlassen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi [CROSS] per scattare una foto o [TRIANGLE] per uscire dalla modalità fotocamera.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa [CROSS] para hacer una foto o [TRIANGLE] para salir del modo cámara.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Exit Camera</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Press [TRIANGLE] to exit camera mode</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyez sur [TRIANGLE] pour quitter le mode Appareil photo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücken Sie [TRIANGLE], um den Kamera-Modus zu verlassen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi [TRIANGLE] per uscire dalla modalità fotocamera.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa [TRIANGLE] para salir del modo cámara.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Camera Mode</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Press [TRIANGLE] to enter camera mode</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyez sur [TRIANGLE] pour entrer dans le mode Appareil photo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücken Sie [TRIANGLE], um den Kamera-Modus aufzurufen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi [TRIANGLE] per entrare in modalità fotocamera.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa [TRIANGLE] para entrar en el modo cámara.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Submit Title</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Submit Film?</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Soumettre la pellicule ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Film abgeben?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Consegnare rullino?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Entregar rollo?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Submit Body 1</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">You have collected 6 shots.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez pris 6 clichés.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben 6 Aufnahmen gemacht.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai raccolto 6 scatti.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Has tomado 6 fotografías.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
    <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Submit Body 2</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Would you like to submit your camera?</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Souhaitez-vous soumettre vos clichés ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Möchten Sie Ihre Kamera abgeben?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Desideri consegnare la fotocamera?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Quieres entregar la cámara?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Submit Legend</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS]Yes, [CIRCLE] No</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] Oui [CIRCLE] Non</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] Ja [CIRCLE] Nein</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] Sì [CIRCLE] No</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] Sí [CIRCLE] No</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Submit Fail Body 1</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">You have not collected the 6 shots required for submission.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous n'avez pas pris les 6 clichés requis.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben nicht die zur Abgabe erforderlichen 6 Aufnahmen gemacht.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non hai raccolto i 6 scatti richiesti per la consegna.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No has tomado las 6 fotografías necesarias para entregar la cámara.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Submit Fail Body 2</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Please continue your investigation. </LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Veuillez poursuivre votre enquête.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bitte setzen Sie Ihre Untersuchung fort.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prosegui le tue indagini.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Retoma tu investigación. </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Submit Fail Body 3</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Which three of the four potential characters have been in this space? Take a shot of a piece of evidence that indicates the presence of a particular character. Each character has two pieces of evidence that places them in this space. We need 6 shots in total.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Lesquels des quatre personnages possibles sont venus dans cet espace ? Prenez en photo les preuves de la venue d'un personnage en particulier. Chaque personnage compte deux indices prouvant son passage ici. Vous avez besoin d'un total de 6 clichés.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Welche drei der vier möglichen Charaktere waren hier? Fotografieren Sie jeden Beweis, der auf die Anwesenheit eines bestimmten Charakters hindeutet. Je zwei Beweisstücke weisen auf jeden Charakter hin. Wir brauchen insgesamt 6 Aufnahmen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quali tre dei quattro potenziali personaggi sono stati in questo spazio? Scatta la foto di un elemento indiziario che indichi la presenza di un particolare personaggio. Ciascun personaggio è ricollegato a questo luogo da due elementi indiziari. Ci servono 6 scatti in totale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Qué tres de los cuatro personajes posibles han estado en este espacio? Toma una fotografía de cada prueba que indique la presencia de un personaje en particular. Cada personaje ha dejado dos pruebas que lo sitúan en el espacio. Necesitamos 6 fotografías en total.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Processing Title</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Processing Photos</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Analyse des photos</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fotos werden analysiert.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Elaborazione foto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Procesando fotos</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Processing Body</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">Processing</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Analyse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Analyse läuft.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Elaborazione</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Procesando
</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
	<LANG ID="REF">Collected Body</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-GB">You have collected 6 shots. You should now return to the stage and submit your camera.</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez pris 6 clichés. Vous devriez regagner la scène pour soumettre vos clichés.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben 6 Aufnahmen gemacht. Sie sollten jetzt Ihre Kamera an der Plattform abgeben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai raccolto 6 scatti. Devi tornare sul palco e consegnare la fotocamera.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Has tomado 6 fotografías. Ahora deberías volver al lugar donde obtuviste la cámara para devolverla.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>  
</LOCALISATION>