<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bandana - Guns (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bandana - Armes à feu (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Halstuch - Knarren (Weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bandana - Pistole (Femmina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bandana-Pistolas (Mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Bandana - Guns (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Bandana - Guns (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Bandana - Guns (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Bandana - Guns (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Bandana - Guns (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Bandana - Guns (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Only the best bandits have the coolest bandana's to cover their faces. This bandana has a super cool gun pattern on it so people will know you mean business when you tell them to reach for the sky. Robbing banks will be a breeze when you wear this. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les meilleurs bandits seulement ont les bandanas les plus cool pour couvrir leur visage. Ce bandana a un motif d'armes à feu pour que les gens savent à qui ils ont affaire quand vous leur demanderez de mettre les mains en l'air. Dévaliser les banques deviendra aussi simple que de porter ce bandana. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nur die besten Banditen haben die coolsten Halstücher, um ihre Gesichter zu bedecken. Das Halstuch hat eine super cooles Knarren Muster, damit die Leute wissen, dass du es ernst meinst, wenn du ihnen bedeutest, auf den Himmel zu zeigen. Bankraub wird ein Kinderspiel sein, wenn du dies trägst. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Solo i migliori banditi hanno una bandana che gli copre la faccia. Questa bandana ha sopra un super modello di pistola, cosicchè le persone sapranno che hai serie intenzioni. Rapire le banche sarà una passeggiata quando la indosserete. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sólo los mejores bandidos tienen las bandanas más molonas para cubrirse el rostro. Esta bandana tiene un tremendo estampado con una pistola que hará que la gente sepa que vas en serio cuando dices que tocarás el cielo.Atracar bancos será un plis mientras la lleves puesta. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Bandana - Guns (Female) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Bandana - Guns (Female) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Bandana - Guns (Female) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Bandana - Guns (Female) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Bandana - Guns (Female) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Only the best bandits have the coolest bandana's to cover their faces. This bandana has a super cool gun pattern on it so people will know you mean business when you tell them to reach for the sky. Robbing banks will be a breeze when you wear this. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>