<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Beamblade Bundle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack lamedacier (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Strahlenklinge - Paket (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completo Lamafulgida (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de espada de luz (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">빔 블레이드 세트 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Beamblade Bundle (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">激光劍服裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">激光劍服裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Beamblade Bundle (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Realise your dungeon slaying dreams with this enchanted armour. Bundle includes helmet, top, bottom, boots, and gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Réalisez vos rêves de preux chevalier avec cette armure enchantée. Le pack contient un casque, un haut et un bas de vêtement, des bottes et des gants. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese verzauberte Rüstung lässt Träume von Kämpfen im Kerker aufkommen. Zum Paket gehören Helm, Oberteil, Unterteil, Stiefel und Handschuhe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I tuoi sogni fantasy sono diventati realtà grazie a questa armatura incantata. Il completo include elmo, parte superiore e inferiore, stivali e guanti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Haz realidad tus sueños heroicos con esta armadura encantada. El conjunto comprende casco, torso, perneras, guantes y botas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">던전을 탐험하는 당신의 꿈을 실현시켜 줄 수 있는 갑옷입니다. 이 세트는 빔 블레이드 헬멧, 빔 블레이드 상의, 빔 블레이드 하의, 빔 블레이드 부츠, 그리고 빔 블레이드 장갑을 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Realize your dungeon slaying dreams with this enchanted armor. Bundle includes the Beamblade Helmet, Beamblade Top, Beamblade Bottom, Beamblade Boots, and Beamblade Gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用這套施了魔法的盔甲來實現你的揮刀地牢的夢想。服裝組包括激光劍頭盔、激光劍服裝-上身、激光劍服裝-下身、激光劍靴及激光劍手套。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用這套施了魔法的盔甲來實現你的揮刀地牢的夢想。服裝組包括激光劍頭盔、激光劍服裝-上半身、激光劍服裝-下半身、激光劍靴及激光劍手套。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Realize your dungeon slaying dreams with this enchanted armor. Bundle includes helmet, top, bottom, boots, and gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>