<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sapphire Suit Bundle (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack costume saphir (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Saphiranzug: Paket (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto tenuta zaffiro (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de traje zafiro (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사파이어 수트 세트 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sapphire Suit Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">藍寶石服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">藍寶石服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sapphire Suit Bundle (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This chic outfit displays an impressive radiance of blue on its clothing and from the sapphire on its cane. Bundle includes a jacket, cane, trousers, and shoes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le bleu de l'ensemble et de la pierre ornant la canne illuminent littéralement cette tenue. Le pack comprend une veste, une canne, un pantalon et des chaussures. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Von der Kleidung und dem Spazierstock dieses schicken Outfits geht ein beeindruckendes blaues Strahlen aus. Das Paket umfasst Jacke, Stock, Hose und Schuhe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tenuta chic, che irradia luce blu dai capi di vestiario e dallo zaffiro montato sul bastone. Il pacchetto include giacca, bastone, pantaloni e scarpe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este conjunto chic luce un azul radiante de impresión en el tejido, y en el zafiro del bastón. El conjunto incluye chaqueta, pantalones, zapatos y bastón. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">놀라운 광채를 발산하는 푸른색 의상입니다. 사파이어로 장식된 지팡이와 함께 격조 높은 모습을 자랑하세요. 이 세트는 재킷, 지팡이, 바지, 그리고 구두를 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This chic outfit displays an impressive radiance of blue on its clothing and from the sapphire on its cane. Bundle includes a jacket, cane, pants, and shoes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這套時髦的服裝和權杖上的藍寶石展現著令人讚嘆的耀眼藍光。服裝組包括件外套、權杖、褲子和鞋子。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這套時髦的服裝和權杖上的藍寶石展現著令人讚嘆的耀眼藍光。服裝組包括件外套、權杖、褲子和鞋子。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This chic outfit displays an impressive radiance of blue on its clothing and from the sapphire on its cane. Bundle includes a jacket, cane, pants, and shoes. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>