<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Drey White Wedge Ankle Boot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bottines compensées Blanche Drey</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weiße Drey Absatzstiefeletten</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stivaletti a zeppa bianchi Drey</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Botines de cuña blancos de Drey</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">【Drey】ウェッジブーツ（ホワイト・女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"드레이" 흰색 웻지 발목 부츠 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Drey White Wedge Ankle Boot (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Drey白色楔型踝靴 （女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Drey白色楔型踝靴 （女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Drey White Wedge Ankle Boot</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This  suede boot with its wedge platform heel, embossed emblem and sleek shaping is sure to be seen on next season's catwalk. A definite mix-and-match must-have for any wardrobe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette bottine en suede avec son talon compensé, avec l'emblême imprimé et une forme lisse est sûr d'être vue sur la passerelle la saison prochaine. Un must-have qui va avec n'importe quelle garde-robe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese Wildleder-Stiefeletten mit Plateau-Absatz, Emblem und schlanker Passform werden nächste Saison sicher auf allen Laufstegen vertreten sein. Ein absolutes Muss für jede Garderobe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questi stivaletti di camoscio con il loro tacco a zeppa, emblema in rilievo e forma elegante verranno sicuramente notati sulle passerelle della prossima stagione. Un accessorio imprescindibile per ogni guardaroba da abbinare e combinare. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estos botines de ante con tacón de cuña portan el emblema de Drey, además de un estilo y distinción dignos de la próxima pasarela de la moda. ¡Son el complemento perfecto para tu armario! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ウェッジプラットフォーム、刻印、洗練されたスタイル。あなたの足元に皆の視線が釘付け。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">웻지 플랫폼 힐과 양각된 문양 및 매끈한 외양의 이 스웨이드 부츠는 다음 시즌의 패션쇼 무대에서 분명 볼 수 있을 겁니다. 이리저리 골라 맞춰 입는, 어떤 의상에도 반드시 있어야 하는 필수품입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This  suede boot with its wedge platform heel, embossed emblem and sleek shaping is sure to be seen on next season's catwalk. A definite mix-and-match must-have for any wardrobe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這雙楔型厚底高跟麂皮靴有標誌浮雕，造型高雅，絕對會在下一季的伸展台上亮相。無敵的混搭好道具，每個女人的鞋櫃都該有一雙。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這雙楔型厚底高跟麂皮靴有標誌浮雕，造型高雅，絕對會在下一季的伸展台上亮相。無敵的混搭好道具，每個女人的鞋櫃都該有一雙。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This  suede boot with its wedge platform heel, embossed emblem and sleek shaping is sure to be seen on next season's catwalk. A definite mix-and-match must-have for any wardrobe. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>