<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Monk Armor Set (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble d’armure de moine (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rüstungssatz Mönch (Männer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set di armatura da monaco (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de armadura del monje (chico)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_30</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_30</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_30</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_30</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_30</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Monk Armor Set (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You are a holy warrior. Decimate foes with your physical and spiritual prowess in this iconic Monk armor set from Diablo III. The set includes the Monk's Master Crown, Monk Cuirass, Monk Legwraps, Monk Treads, and Monk Fists.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous êtes un guerrier saint. Utilisez vos prouesses physiques et spirituelles pour décimer vos ennemis grâce à cet ensemble complet d’armure emblématique du moine de Diablo III. Il comprend : couronne de maître de moine, cuirasse de moine, couvre-jambes de moine, bottines de moine, poings de moine.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie sind ein heiliger Krieger. Lichten Sie die Reihen Ihrer Feinde mithilfe Ihrer physischen und geistigen Fähigkeiten, die in diesem unverwechselbaren Mönchsrüstungssatz aus Diablo III verborgen sind. Der Rüstungssatz umfasst die Mönchskrone des Großmeisters, Mönchskürass, Mönchsbeinwickel, Mönchstreter und Mönchsfäuste.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sei un guerriero sacro. Annienta i nemici grazie alla tua potenza fisica e spirituale con questo set di armatura da monaco di Diablo III. Il set include Corona del Maestro da monaco, Corazza da monaco, Cosciali da monaco, Stivaletti da monaco e Pugni da monaco.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Eres un guerrero sagrado. Tus enemigos sucumbirán a tu poderío físico y espiritual con este simbólico conjunto de armadura del monje de Diablo III. El conjunto incluye la corona de maestro, la coraza, las perneras, los botines y los puños del monje.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_30 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_30 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_30 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_30 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_30 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You are a holy warrior. Decimate foes with your physical and spiritual prowess in this iconic Monk armor set from Diablo III. The set includes the Monk's Master Crown, Monk Cuirass, Monk Legwraps, Monk Treads, and Monk Fists.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>