<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cauldron of the Sunless Kingdom (Active Object)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaudron du Royaume Sans-Soleil (Objet Actif)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kessel des Sonnenlosen Königreichs (Aktives Objekt)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Calderone del Regno Tetro (Oggetto attivo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Caldero del Reino sin sol (Objeto activo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">太陽無き王国の大釜（アドバンスド家具）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">햇볕이 들지 않는 왕국의 가마솥(액티브 아이템)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Cauldron of the Sunless Kingdom (Active Object)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">蔽日王國神鼎（動態道具）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">蔽日王國神鼎（動態道具）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cauldron of the Sunless Kingdom (Active Object)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Former treasure of the rulers of the Sunless Kingdom, legend tells that the cauldron could bestow plentiful rewards upon those who use it. Collect ingredients and fuel for the fire, watch the display as your spells are unleashed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ancien Trésor des maitres du Royaume Sans-Soleil, la légende raconte que le chaudron offrira d'abondantes récompenses à ceux qui l'utilisent. Récupérez des ingrédients et combustibles pour le feu et observez vos sorts se déchaîner. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein ehemaliger Schatz der Herrscher des Sonnenlosen Königreichs. Die Legenden besagen, dass der Kessel jede Person, die ihn benutzt, mit Reichtümern überhäuft. Sammele Zutaten, entfache das Feuer und sieh zu, wie deine Zauber entfesselt werden. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un tempo tesoro dei sovrani del Regno Tetro, la leggenda vuole che il calderone possa elargire ricompense a Coloro che lo usano. Raccogli ingredienti e combustibile per il fuoco e goditi lo spettacolo dei tuoi incantesimi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Antiguo tesoro de los gobernadores del Reino sin sol, la leyenda cuenta que el caldero puede ofrecer infinitas recompensas a aquellos que lo utilizan. Recoge los ingredientes y aviva el fuego, observa qué sucede mientras vas liberando tus hechizos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">太陽無き王国の歴代統治者に受け継がれてきたお宝。伝説によれば、これを使った者は有り余る程の贈り物を授かるとある。材料と燃料を集めて火をおこし、呪文が効力を発揮する様子を眺めよう。\n\nこのアイテムは、アニメーションや機能が追加されているアドバンスド家具です。\nこの種類のアイテムは配置できる数に制限があります。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">망자의 왕국을 지배하던 이들이 소유하던 보물입니다. 전설에 따르면 사용하는 자에게 많은 보물을 선사한다고 합니다. 재료를 모아 불을 붙이고, 자신의 마법이 실현되는 것을 확인하세요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Former treasure of the rulers of the Sunless Kingdom, legend tells that the cauldron could bestow plentiful rewards upon those who use it. Collect ingredients and fuel for the fire, watch the display as your spells are unleashed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">蔽日王國統治者以前的珍寶。據傳使用神鼎之人可獲得豐厚報酬。只要收集烹煮所用的材料和生火燃料，就能看到法術的神奇效果。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">蔽日王國統治者以前的珍寶。據傳使用神鼎之人可獲得豐厚報酬。只要收集烹煮所用的材料和生火燃料，就能看到法術的神奇效果。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Former treasure of the rulers of the Sunless Kingdom, legend tells that the cauldron could bestow plentiful rewards upon those who use it. Collect ingredients and fuel for the fire, watch the display as your spells are unleashed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>