<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Black Mana T-shirt (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">T-shirt mana noir (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">T-Shirt „Schwarzes Mana“ (für Männer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">T-shirt del Mana Nero (maschio)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta de maná negro (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Black Mana T-Shirt (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Black Mana T-Shirt (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Black Mana T-Shirt (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Black Mana T-Shirt (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Black Mana T-Shirt (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Black Mana T-shirt (male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Declare your allegiance to the mana colour that best expresses your character in this stylish T-shirt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Déclarez votre allégeance à la couleur de mana qui exprime le mieux votre personnalité grâce à ce t-shirt cool.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeige allen mit diesem schicken T-Shirt, welche Manafarbe am ehesten deinem Charakter entspricht.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dichiara la tua devozione al colore di mana che meglio esprime il tuo carattere con questa elegante T-shirt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Declara tu lealtad al color de maná que mejor expresa tu personalidad con esta camiseta.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Pledge allegiance to the mana colour that best expresses your character, in this stylish T-shirt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Pledge allegiance to the mana colour that best expresses your character, in this stylish T-shirt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Pledge allegiance to the mana colour that best expresses your character, in this stylish T-shirt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Pledge allegiance to the mana colour that best expresses your character, in this stylish T-shirt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Pledge allegiance to the mana colour that best expresses your character, in this stylish T-shirt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Declare your allegiance to the mana color that best expresses your character in this stylish T-shirt.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>