<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ObjectName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Namco Museum™ Shorts1 (Mens)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bermuda 1 Namco Museum™ (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Namco Museum™-Shorts1 (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pantaloncini1 Namco Museum™ (Per uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">pantalones cortos 1 Namco Museum™ (Masculinos)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">男性用ナムコミュージアムショートパンツ1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">남코 뮤지엄 반바지 1 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">NAMCO MUSEUM Shorts1 (Mens)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">NAMCO MUSEUM 短褲 1（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">NAMCO MUSEUM 短褲 1（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Namco Museum™ Strap Shorts</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ObjectDescription</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Shorts featuring a new color. This item cannot be obtained as a Home Reward in Namco Museum. Wear this to stand out from the crowd! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un short présentant une nouvelle couleur. Cet article ne peut être obtenu comme récompense Home dans Namco Museum. Portez-le pour vous démarquer des autres ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Shorts in brandneuer Farbe. Dieser Artikel kann nicht als Home-Gewinn im Namco Museum erworben werden. Tragen Sie ihn, um sich von anderen abzuheben! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pantaloncini di un colore nuovo. Questo articolo non può essere vinto in Namco Museum. Indossalo e distinguiti dalla folla! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pantalones corots con un color nuevo. Este artículo no se puede obtener como premio Home en Namco Museum. ¡Póntelo para llamar la atención! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ナムコミュージアムリワードアイテムのニューカラーショートパンツです。これを着用して他の人と差をつけよう！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">남코뮤지엄의 리워드 아이템인 뉴 컬러 반바지입니다. 남들하고는 달라야죠! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Shorts featuring a new color. This item cannot be obtained as a Home Reward in Namco Museum. Wear this to stand out from the crowd! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Namco Museum獎品的新色短褲，只可在這裡拿到。穿起它讓自己與別不同吧！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Namco Museum獎品的新色短褲，只能在這裡得到。穿起它讓自己與眾不同吧！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Suspenders on the shoulder are so mid-nineteenth century! Get into this year's relaxed look with these casual suspender shorts sporting the words "NAMCO MUSEUM" in gold embroidery.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>