<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dovchenko Hat &amp; Hair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chapeau &amp; cheveux Dovchenko</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dovchenko Hut &amp; Frisur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cappello e Capelli Dovchenko</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sombrero y Pelo de Dovchenko</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dovchenko Hat &amp; Hair</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">(Hat/Hair) The sun was beating down on us outside of the Warehouse. Dovchenko was barking orders at us as Jones struggled to escape. We would not let him - our mission was clear. We had one relic we needed to find in this place, and we could not fail. She would not allow us. As we discovered the location, Jones broke free and began chasing our men. Swinging through the rafters, taking us down one punch at a time. I drove the jeep frantically, attempting to escape with Dovchenko safely. Good thing I was wearing my Russian Soldier avatar item, giving me that edge over Jones that I needed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">(Chapeau/cheveux) Le soleil brûlait au-dessus de nos têtes. Dovchenko nous gueulait ses ordres alors que Jones essayait de s'enfuir. Nous ne le laisserions pas faire - nos ordres étaient clairs. Il nous fallait trouver une relique, et nous ne pouvions échouer. Elle ne nous le permettrait pas. Alors que nous découvrions l'endroit, Jones s'échappa et poursuivit nos hommes. Il frappa et cogna, assommant un homme après l'autre. Je conduisais la Jeep comme un fou, afin de sauver Dovchenko. Heureusement que je portais un costume de l'armée russe, ce qui me permit d'obtenir l'avantage sur Jones. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">(Hut/Frisur) Die Sonne brannte außerhalb des Lagers auf uns herab. Dovchenko brüllte seine Befehle, während Jones sich zu befreien versuchte. Wir würden das nicht zulassen - unsere Mission war eindeutig. Wir mussten an diesem Ort ein Artefakt finden und Versagen war undenkbar. Sie würde uns das nie verzeihen. Als wir den Standort gefunden hatten, konnte sich Jones befreien und begann, unsere Leute zu jagen. Er schwang sich an den Balken entlang, und schaltete einen nach dem anderen aus. Ich raste mit dem Jeep davon und versuchte, Dovchenko in Sicherheit zu bringen. Zum Glück trug ich meinen Russischer Soldat-Avatar-Gegenstand, mit dem ich mir gegenüber Jones einen entscheidenden Vorteil verschaffen konnte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">(Cappello/capelli) Il sole picchiava duro su di noi fuori dal Magazzino. Dovchenko ci urlava ordini mentre Jones si divincolava per cercare di fuggire. Non glielo permettemmo - la nostra missione era chiara. Dovevamo trovare una reliquia in questo posto, e non potevamo fallire. Lei non ce lo avrebbe permesso. Mentre cercavamo di scoprire l'oggetto, Jones si liberò e iniziò a inseguire i nostri uomini. Si dondolò da una trave all'altra e ci annientò un pugno per volta. Io guidai freneticamente la jeep nel tentativo di fuggire in salvo con Dovchenko. Meno male che indossavo il mio completo avatar da Soldato Russo. Grazie ad esso, avevo ancora un vantaggio nei confronti di Jones. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">(Sombrero/pelo) El sol nos daba de lleno fuera del almacén. Dovchenko no dejaba de gritarnos órdenes mientras Jones buscaba la manera de escapar. Pero nosotros no se lo íbamos a permitir, nuestra misión era clara. Teníamos que encontrar la reliquia del almacén y no íbamos a fallar. Aunque ella nos lo pondría difícil. Mientras descubrimos la localización del lugar, Jones consiguió escaparse y empezó a perseguir a nuestros hombres. Iba de viga en viga y golpeando a los nuestros uno a uno. Yo conducía el jeep como un loco, intentando escapar sano y salvo con Dovchenko. Menos mal que llevaba mi traje avatar de soldado ruso, que me daba la ventaja que necesitaba para escapar de Jones. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">(Hat/Hair) The sun was beating down on us outside of the Warehouse. Dovchenko was barking orders at us as Jones struggled to escape. We would not let him - our mission was clear. We had one relic we needed to find in this place, and we could not fail. She would not allow us. As we discovered the location, Jones broke free and began chasing our men. Swinging through the rafters, taking us down one punch at a time. I drove the jeep frantically, attempting to escape with Dovchenko safely. Good thing I was wearing my Russian Soldier avatar item, giving me that edge over Jones that I needed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>