<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">KIF - Casual Wear 2-piece Set (Kitchen-wear, Lt. Suzumiya Model, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">FIK - Set 2 pièces déc. (cuisine, modèle Ltn. Suzumiya, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">2-teiliges KUF - Alltagskleidungs-Set (Küchenkleidung, Modell Lt. Suzumiya, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">FLK - Set abbigliamento informale con grembiule da cucina 2 elementi (modello del ten. Suzumiya, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">FIK - Juego de 2 piezas de ropa casual (ropa de cocina, modelo teniente Suzumiya, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">金沢独立戦線・普段着２点セット（調理中・スズミヤ中尉モデル・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">KIF - Casual Wear 2-piece Set (Kitchen-wear, Lt. Suzumiya Model, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 2-piece set of casual wear (kitchen-wear) and slippers modeled after Lt. Sachiko G. Suzumiya in the "Kanazawa Independence Front" 4-panel comic series on the Granzella website.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- KIF - Casual Wear (Kitchen-wear, Lt. Suzumiya Model, Women) (Outfits)\n- KIF - Slippers (Lt. Suzumiya Model, Women) (Feet)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 2 pièces de vêtements décontractés (vêtements de cuisine) et de chaussons basé sur le Lieutenant Sachiko G. Suzumiya dans la bande dessinée à 4 vignettes "Front d'Indépendance de Kanazawa" sur le site web de Granzella.\nDéfense : ★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- FIK - Tenue décontractée (cuisine, modèle Ltn. Suzumiya, femme) (Tenues)\n- FIK - Chaussons (modèle Ltn. Suzumiya, femme) (Pieds)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">2-teiliges Set, das Alltagskleidung (Küchenkleidung) und Hausschuhe von Lt. Sachiko G. Suzumiya aus der 4-Panel-Comicreihe "Kanazawa Unabhängigkeitsfront" auf der Webseite von Granzella enthält.\nVerteidigung: ★\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- KUF - Alltagskleidung (Küchenkleidung, Modell Lt. Suzumiya, für Frauen) (Outfits)\n- KUF - Hausschuhe (Modell Lt. Suzumiya, für Frauen) (Füße)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set formato da 2 elementi comprendente un abbigliamento informale con grembiule da cucina e delle pantofole - oggetti del dal tenente Sachiko G. Suzumiya nella storia a fumetti "Fronte di liberazione di Kanazawa" pubblicata sul sito di Granzella.\nDifesa: ★\nQuesto set comprende i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- FLK - Abbigliamento informale con grembiule da cucina (modello del ten. Suzumiya, da donna) (aspetti)\n- FLK - Pantofole (modello del ten. Suzumiya, da donna) (piedi)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, gli oggetti elencati verranno aggiunti nella loro categoria specifica.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de 2 piezas de ropa casual (ropa de cocina) y zapatillas de andar por casa basado en la teniente Sachiko G. Suzumiya en el cómic de 4 paneles del "Frente por la Independencia de Kanazawa" en el sitio web de Granzella.\nDefensa: ★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- FIK - Ropa casual (modelo teniente Suzumiya, mujer) (traje)\n- FIK - Zapatillas de andar por casa (modelo teniente Suzumiya, mujer) (pies)\n\n* Al adquirir este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su categoría correspondiente.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">グランゼーラのウェブサイトにて連載中の４コマ漫画「金沢独立戦線」に登場するサチコ・G・スズミヤ中尉モデルの、普段着（調理中）とスリッパの２点セット。\n防御力：　★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・金沢独立戦線・普段着（調理中・スズミヤ中尉モデル・女性）/組み合わせ\n・金沢独立戦線・スリッパ（スズミヤ中尉モデル・女性）/足\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 2-piece set of casual wear (kitchen-wear) and slippers modeled after Lt. Sachiko G. Suzumiya in the "Kanazawa Independence Front" 4-panel comic series on the Granzella website.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- KIF - Casual Wear (Kitchen-wear, Lt. Suzumiya Model, Women) (Outfits)\n- KIF - Slippers (Lt. Suzumiya Model, Women) (Feet)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
