<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack Aquarium Ultime</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acuario extremo pequeño</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ultimatives Aquarium Bündel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Acquario Supremo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ultimate Aquarium Bundle Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ultimate Aquarium Bundle Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cet aquarium est le nec plus ultra de la technologie aquariophile. En utilisant la puissance de la nanotechnologie, nous avons créé un bassin dont vous pouvez modifier la taille afin de pouvoir remplir n'importe quel espace de votre pièce. Il est vendu avec Trouver Pack de poissons et Sous Le Pack Décoration océan. Si vous cherchez à rénover votre appartement avec un nouveau mur fait d'eau et de poissons, cet aquarium est fait pour vous. Les poissons sont inclus: Clownfish, Royal Gramma, Yellow Tang, Moorish Idol et Blue Tang. Décorations inclus: Diffuseur de Bulles Invisible, Coquille, Château Englouti, Oursin et Colonnes. Il s'agit d'un élément animé actif. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este acuario es el último modelo en tecnología de acuarios. Usando el poder de la nano-tecnología hemos creado un acuario que puedes cambiar de tamaño para que quepa en cualquier espacio de tu cuarto. Viene en un lote de Encontrar Paquete de Peces y Under The Ocean Paquete Decoración. Si buscas renovar tu apartamento con una pared hecha de agua y peces, este es tu acuario.  El pescado se incluyen: Clownfish, Royal Gramma, Yellow Tang, Moorish Idol and Blue Tang. Decoraciones incluido: Burbujeador invisible, Concha de caracol, Castillo hundido, Erizo de mar y Columnas. Este es un elemento activo animado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Aquarium ist der Höhepunkt der Aquariumstechnologie. Mit den Möglichkeiten der Nano-Technologie haben wir ein Aquarium geschaffen, das Sie in der Größe anpassen können, damit es in jedes Ihrer Zimmer passt. Es wird mit Finding Fish Pack und Unter dem Ozean Dekopaket. Falls Sie vorhaben, Ihre Wohnung mit einer neuen Wand aus Wasser und Fischen zu renovieren, ist dies Ihr Aquarium. Der Fisch enthalten sind: Clownfish, Royal Gramma, Yellow Tang, Moorish Idol and Blue Tang. Dekorationen enthalten: Unsichtbarer Bubbler, Muschelschale, Versunkenes Schloss, Seeigel und Säulen. Dies ist eine animierte aktive Element. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa vasca è il top nella tecnologia degli acquari. Usando il potere della nano-tecnologia abbiamo creato un acquario che è possibile ridimensionare e adattare ad ogni ambiente nel vostro spazio. Viene fornita in abbinamento a Trovare pacchetto dei pesci e Sotto il pacco decorazione Ocean. Se volete  rinnovare l'appartamento con un nuovo muro di acqua e pesci, questo è l'acquario che fa per voi. I pesci sono inclusi: Butterflyfish, Clownfish, Royal Gramma, Yellow Tang, Moorish Idol and Blue Tang. Decorazioni incluso: Aeratore Invisibile, Conchiglia, Castello Sommerso, Riccio di Mare e Colonne. Questo è un elemento animato attiva. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This tank is the ultimate in aquarium technology. Using the power of nano-technology we have created an aquarium that you can resize to fit any room in your space. It comes bundled with the Finding Fish Pack and the Under The Ocean Decoration Pack. If you're looking to renovate your apartment with a new wall made of water and fish, this is your aquarium. The fish included are: Clownfish, Royal Gramma, Yellow Tang, Moorish Idol and Blue Tang. Decorations included: Invisible Bubbler, Conch Shell, Sunken Castle, Sea Urchin and Columns. This is an animated active item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This tank is the ultimate in aquarium technology. Using the power of nano-technology we have created an aquarium that you can resize to fit any room in your space. It comes bundled with the Finding Fish Pack and the Under The Ocean Decoration Pack. If you're looking to renovate your apartment with a new wall made of water and fish, this is your aquarium. The fish included are: Clownfish, Royal Gramma, Yellow Tang, Moorish Idol and Blue Tang. Decorations included: Invisible Bubbler, Conch Shell, Sunken Castle, Sea Urchin and Columns. This is an animated active item. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>