<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Witch Doctor Armor Set (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble d’armure de féticheuse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rüstungssatz Hexendoktor (Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set di armatura da sciamana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de armadura de la médica bruja</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_48</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_48</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_48</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_48</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_48</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Witch Doctor Armor Set (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Command armies of the dead in this iconic set of Witch Doctor armor from Diablo III. The set includes the Witch Doctor Voodoo Mask, Witch Doctor Voodoo Armor, Witch Doctor Vodoo Tassets, Witch Doctor Voodoo Trail, and Witch Doctor Voodoo Vambraces.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Commandez les armées des morts grâce à cet ensemble complet d’armure emblématique de la féticheuse de Diablo III. Il comprend : masque vaudou de féticheuse, armure vaudoue de féticheuse, tassettes vaudoues de féticheuse, pisteuses vaudoues de féticheuse, protège-bras vaudous de féticheuse.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Befehligen Sie Armeen von Toten in diesem unverwechselbaren Hexendoktor-Rüstungssatz aus Diablo III. Der Rüstungssatz umfasst Hexendoktor-Voodoomaske, Hexendoktor-Voodoorüstung, Hexendoktor-Voodootassetten, Hexendoktor-Voodoopfad und Hexendoktor-Voodoostulpen.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Comanda armate di defunti con questo set di armatura da sciamana tratto da Diablo III. Il set include Maschera vudù da sciamana, Corazza vudù da sciamana, Fiancali vudù da sciamana, Sandali vudù da sciamana e Antibracci vudù da sciamana.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dirige a los ejércitos de los muertos con este simbólico conjunto de armadura de la médica bruja de Diablo III. El conjunto incluye la máscara de vudú, la armadura de vudú, las escarcelas de vudú, el rastro de vudú y los avambrazos de vudú de la médica bruja.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_48 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_48 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_48 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_48 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_48 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Command armies of the dead in this iconic set of Witch Doctor armor from Diablo III. The set includes the Witch Doctor Voodoo Mask, Witch Doctor Voodoo Armor, Witch Doctor Vodoo Tassets, Witch Doctor Voodoo Trail, and Witch Doctor Voodoo Vambraces.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>