<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Novus Prime Concept: The Kunai</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Concept de Novus Prime : Le Kunai</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Novus Prime Konzept: The Kunai</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Design Novus Prime: Kunai</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Concepto de Novus Prime: Kunai</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムのコンセプト：クナイ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임 컨셉: 쿠나이</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Novus Prime Concept: The Kunai</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Novus Prime概念畫：Kunai</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Novus Prime概念畫：Kunai</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Novus Prime Concept: The Kunai</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. Built for speed and deadly precision, the Kunai serves as a scout and assassin for the Earth Fleet. With its sophisticated cloaking matrix, enemies can be eliminated before a threat is even detected. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ornez vos murs de peintures conceptuelles de Novus Prime. Construit pour la vitesse, le Kunai sert aussi bien pour la reconnaissance que pour les missions d'assassinat de la flotte Terrestre. Avec sa matrice de camouflage, les ennemis sont éliminés avant même qu'ils ne détectent le danger. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schmücke deine Wände mit den Konzeptzeichnungen von Novus Prime. Wegen seiner Schnelligkeit und tödlichen Präzision dient der Kunai als Kundschafter und Attentäter für die Erdenflotte. Dank seiner ausgereiften Tarnvorrichtung können Feinde eliminiert werden, noch bevor überhaupt eine Bedrohung registriert wird. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Decora le tue pareti con il design della Novus Prime. Costruita per essere veloce e mortalmente precisa, la Kunai serve la Flotta Terrestre in ricognizione e in attacco. Con la sua sofisticata matrice di occultamento può eliminare i nemici ancor prima che il pericolo sia rilevato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Adorna tus paredes con las pinturas conceptuales de Novus Prime. Construido para la velocidad y tener una precisión mortal, Kunai sirve como un explorador y asesino para la Flota de la Tierra. Con su sofisticada capa matriz, los enemigos pueden ser eliminado antes de que sea detectado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムのコンセプト絵画を壁に飾ろう。超高速で正確無比、それがクナイ。時には地球軍のスパイ、時には暗殺者。洗練されたクローキングマトリックス技術で気付かれる前に敵を倒してしまう驚異的な存在。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임의 컨셉화로 벽을 장식합니다. 속도와 치명적인 정확도를 중심으로 설계된 함선으로, 지구 함대의 정찰 및 기습 역할을 수행합니다. 매우 섬세한 은폐 매트릭스를 이용해 적에게 탐지되기도 전에 적을 제거할 수 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. Built for speed and deadly precision, the Kunai serves as a scout and assassin for the Earth Fleet. With its sophisticated cloaking matrix, enemies can be eliminated before a threat is even detected. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用Novus Prime的概念繪畫裝飾你的牆壁。Kunai以速度和非凡的精準度見稱，是地球艦隊的偵察機和暗殺者。其出色的隱形功能能在敵人探測到威脅前先發制人，消滅敵人。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用Novus Prime的概念繪畫裝飾你的牆壁。Kunai以速度和非凡的精準度見稱，是地球艦隊的偵察機和暗殺者。其出色的隱形功能能在敵人探測到威脅前先發制人，消滅敵人。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. Built for speed and deadly precision, the Kunai serves as a scout and assassin for the Earth Fleet. With its sophisticated cloaking matrix, enemies can be eliminated before a threat is even detected. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>