<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Teleport Beacon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Balise de téléportation</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Teleportations-Leuchtbake</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Faro teletrasporto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Faro de teletransporte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Teleport Beacon</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Using barely understood quantum flux technology, this item allows MiniBots to teleport to the beacon. Can also be used as a lamp. BONUS: unlocks the Teleport Beacon gadget for use in MiniBots: Battlebox and MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisant la mystérieuse technologie des flux quantiques, cet objet permet aux MiniBots de se téléporter jusqu'à la balise. Elle peut aussi servir de lampe. BONUS : déverrouille le gadget Balise de téléportation utilisable dans MiniBots : Battlebox et MiniBots multijoueur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mithilfe der noch kaum erforschten Quantum-Flux-Technologie können sich die MiniBots zur Leuchtbake teleportieren. Sie kann zudem als Lampe verwendet werden. BONUS: Schaltet das Teleportations-Leuchtbaken-Gadget für die Anwendung in MiniBots: Battlebox und MiniBots-Multiplayer-Modus frei. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usando questa misteriosa tecnologia di flusso quantistico, i MiniBot possono teletrasportarsi verso il faro. Può essere usato anche come lampada. BONUS: sblocca il gadget Faro teletrasporto per usarlo in MiniBots: Battlebox e modalità multigiocatore di MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mediante la desconocida tecnología del flujo cuántico, este elemento permite a los MiniBots teletransportarse al faro. También puede ser usado como lámpara. BONUS:  libera el dispositivo Faro de teletransporte para utilizarlo en MiniBots: Battlebox y el modo varios jugadores de MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Using barely understood quantum flux technology, this item allows MiniBots to  teleport to the beacon. Can also be used as a lamp. BONUS: unlocks the Teleport Beacon gadget for use in MiniBots: Battlebox and MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>