<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Street Style - Bundle Outfit Pack 04 - White (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Street Style - Lot pack tenue 04 - Blanc (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Street Style - Outfit Paket 04 - Weiß (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Street Style - Pacchetto Vestiti 04 - Bianco (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Street Style - Conjunto Vestimenta Pack 04 - Blanco (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wear the whole package with this Street Style Outfit Pack!\n\n
This bundle contains\n
(1) Street Style - Hot Pants and Knee Highs - Blue (Women)\n
(2) Street Style - Leather and fur jacket - White (Women)\n
(3) Street Style - Fedora Fringe - Black (Women) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Portez le lot complet avec ce pack tenue Street Style Outfit !\n\n
Ce lot contient\n
(1) Street Style - Minishort avec bottes cuissardes - Bleu (femme)\n
(2) Street Style - Blouson cuir et fourrure - Blanc (femme)\n
(3) Street Style - Borsalino à frange - Noir (femme) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tragen Sie Street Style von Kopf bis Fuß - mit diesem kompletten Street Style Outfit Paket!\n\n
Dieses Paket enthält\n
(1) Street Style - Hotpants und kniehohe Stiefel - Blau (Damen)\n
(2) Street Style - Leder-/Pelzjacke - Weiß (Damen)\n
(3) Street Style - Fedora mit Pony - Schwarz (Damen) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Indossa tutti i capi con questo Pacchetto di Abbigliamento Street Style!\n\n
Il set comprende\n
(1) Street Style - Pantaloncini e Stivali al ginocchio - Blu (Donna)\n
(2) Street Style - Giacca di pelle e pelliccia - Bianco (Donna)\n
(3) Street Style - Borsalino con Frangia - Nero (Donna) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Ponte todo el conjunto con este pack de vestimenta Street Style!\n\n
Este pack contiene\n
(1) Street Style - Culote y botas altas - Azul (Mujer)\n
(2) Street Style - Chaqueta de cuero y pelo - Blanco (Mujer)\n
(3) Street Style - Sombrero de fieltro y flequillo - Negro (Mujer) [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>