<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Classic Pinup Bombs</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Classic Pinup Bombs</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Classic Pinup Bombs</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Classic Pinup Bombs</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Classic Pinup Bombs</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* PinupSet01</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* PinupSet01</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* PinupSet01</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* PinupSet01</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* PinupSet01</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Classic Pinup Bombs</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Try out the Pinup Bomb Bundle: Cherry, Brownie and Platinum. Check out their classic swim dress outfits, stylized hair and make-up, and custom walk, run and pose animations. Grab these girls and explode onto the scene![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Essayez le bundle Pin-up Bomb : Cherry, Brownie et Platinum. Découvrez leurs maillots de bain, leurs coiffures et maquillage stylés, ainsi que leurs démarches et animations personnalisées. Incarnez l’une de ces filles et devenez une véritable star![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erlebe das Pin-up Bomb Bundle: Cherry, Brownie und Platinum. Wirf einen Blick auf ihre klassischen Badeanzüge, ihre stylischen Frisuren und Make-ups sowie ihre individuellen Geh-, Lauf- und Posing-Animationen. Schnapp dir diese Girls und stiehl allen die Show![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prova il nuovo Pin-up Bomb Bundle: Cherry, Brownie e Platinum; troverai le pin-up nel classico costume da bagno con pettinature e make-up stilosi e animazioni personalizzate per camminata, corsa e pose da top model. Scegli la tua ragazza e fai scintille![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Prueba el Pin-up Bomb Bundle: Cherry, Brownie y Platinum. Echa un vistazo a sus conjuntos clásicos de baño, estilizados peinados y maquillajes, y animaciones personalizadas para caminar, correr y posar. ¡Consigue a estas chicas y dejarás huella allá donde vayas![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Try out the Pinup Bomb Bundle: Cherry, Brownie and Platinum. Check out their classic swim dress outfits, stylized hair and make-up, and custom walk, run and pose animations. Grab these girls and explode onto the scene![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>