<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Glasses_qmask_02</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dark Lily's Mask (Red, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Masque de Dark Lily  (Rouge, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dark Lilys Maske (Rot, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maschera di Dark Lily (rossa, da uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Máscara de Dark Lily (roja, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ダークリリーの仮面（赤・男性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">다크 릴리 가면（빨강, 남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Dark-Lily Mask (Red/Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Dark-Lily的面具（紅色/男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Dark-Lily的面具（紅色/男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dark Lily's Mask (Red, M)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Glasses_qmask_02_description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A replica of the mask worn by Dark Lily Matsushima, top lieutenant of the Black Irem Brigade. As red is her favorite color after black, Lily can often be seen wearing this particular mask. Just wearing this mask seems to imbue the wearer with Lily's sensual beauty.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une réplique du masque porté par Dark Lily Matsushima, lieutenant chef de la Brigade Noire Irem. Comme le rouge est sa couleur préférée après le noir, c'est ce masque que Lily porte le plus souvent. Le simple fait de porter ce masque semble imprégner le porteur de la beauté sensuelle de Lily. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine Replik der von Dark Lily Matsushima, Oberleutnant der Black Irem Brigade, getragenen Maske. Da Rot ihre Lieblingsfarbe nach Schwarz ist, trägt sie diese Maske häufig. Das Tragen dieser Maske scheint den Träger mit der sinnlichen Schönheit von Lily zu durchtränken.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Replica della maschera indossata da Dark Lily Matsushima, alto ufficiale della Brigata Black Irem. Questa maschera viene molto usata, dal momento che il rosso è il suo colore preferito dopo il nero. Tutta la femminilità di Dark Lily fluirà nel vostro corpo nel momento stesso in cui l'appoggerete sugli occhi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una réplica de la máscara que llevaba Dark Lily Matsushima, teniente en jefe del Escuadrón Irem Negro. Como el rojo es su color preferido después del negro, es muy habitual ver a Lily con esta máscara en particular. El mero hecho de ponerse esta máscara parece impregnar a su portador con la belleza sensual de Lily.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブラックアイレム団の幹部ダークリリー松嶋が愛用している仮面のレプリカ。「赤」は「黒」の次に彼女が好む色で着用していることが多い。この仮面だけで彼女の色香が漂ってくるようだ。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블랙 아이렘단의 간부 다크 릴리 마츠시마가 애용하던 가면 레플리카.「빨강」은 그녀가「검정」다음으로 좋아하는 색으로, 자주 착용한다. 이 가면만으로도 그녀의 미색이 느껴지는 것 같다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A replica of the mask worn and loved by Dark-Lily Matsushima, leader of the Black Irem Brigade. Red is her next favorite color to black, and she wears this one often as well. The mask alone seems to evoke her charm.[#Legal]
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">黑色Irem團的幹部Dark-Lily Matsushima愛用面具的複製品。「紅色」是她僅次於「黑色」所喜愛的顏色所以也經常使用。光有這個面具就彷彿能夠聞到她的香味。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">黑色Irem團的幹部Dark-Lily Matsushima愛用面具的複製品。「紅色」是她僅次於「黑色」所喜愛的顏色所以也經常使用。光有這個面具就彷彿能夠聞到她的香味。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A replica of the mask worn by Dark Lily Matsushima, top lieutenant of the Black Irem Brigade. As red is her favorite color after black, Lily can often be seen wearing this particular mask. Just wearing this mask seems to imbue the wearer with Lily's sensual beauty.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>