<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hollywood Hills House Daytime Clubhouse (with Home Theatre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Club-house de jour de Hollywood Hills (avec home cinéma)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Klubhaus eines Hauses in Hollywood Hills bei Tag (mit Heimkino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Circolo diurno Casa di Hollywood Hills (con Home Theater)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Casa Hollywood Hills, clubhouse de día (con Home Cinema)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Hollywood Hills House Daytime Clubhouse (with Home Theater)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Hollywood Hills House Daytime Clubhouse (with EOD)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Hollywood Hills House Daytime Clubhouse (with EOD)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Hollywood Hills House Daytime Clubhouse (with EOD)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Hollywood Hills House Daytime Clubhouse (with EOD)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hollywood Hills House Daytime Clubhouse (with Home Theater)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Entertain and meet with your club in this ultra-exclusive clubhouse, set in the Hollywood Hills above the LA skyline! Features include:\n
• Built-in Entertainment On Demand theater system;\n
• A swimming feature for the infinity pool!\n
THIS is the ultra-exclusive retreat for the discerning club owner. Purchase of this clubhouse comes bundled with the LOOT™ Active Camera and Active Light, so you can film your parties and upload them to YouTube!\n\n PLEASE READ:  Due to contractual and rights agreements, all content may not be available in all countries. Content availability is dependent on the geolocation of the device. CRACKLE content is only available in US, CA, UK, and AU. RADIOIO is only available in US and CA. Only one LOOT™ TV or LOOT™ Radio can be active at a time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Divertissez-vous et réunissez votre club dans cette club house ultra-exclusive située à Hollywood Hills avec un panorama sur tout Los Angeles ! Les fonctions comprennent : \n 
• Un Système Ciné de Loisirs à la Demande Intégré ; \n
• Une fonction natation pour la piscine panoramique ! \n
VOILÀ un refuge ultra-exclusif pour un propriétaire de club perspicace. L'achat de ce club-house vient avec les lots Caméra Active LOOT™ et Lumière Active, pour que vous puissiez filmer vos fêtes et les télécharger sur YouTube. \n
\n 
Veuillez lire :  En raison d'accords contractuels et juridiques, les contenus ne sont pas disponibles dans tous les pays. La disponibilité du contenu dépend de la géolocalisation du système.  Le contenu Crackle est disponible uniquement aux USA, au Canada, en Grande-Bretagne et en Australie. RadioIO est disponible UNIQUEMENT aux USA et au Canada. Vous ne pouvez faire fonctionner qu'une Télé LOOT™ ou qu'une Radio LOOT™ à la fois. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Empfange und unterhalte in diesem ultra-exklusiven Klubhaus in Hollywood Hills über der Skyline von Los Angeles deine Klubmitglieder! Das Paket enthält:\n
• Integriertes EOD-Heimkino\n
• Schwimmfunktion für den Unendlichkeits-Swimmingpool!\n
DIES ist der ultra-exklusive Zufluchtsort für den anspruchsvollen Klubbesitzer. Dieses Klubhauspaket enthält auch die aktive LOOT™-Kamera und das aktive LOOT™-Licht, damit du deine Parties ohne weitere Kosten filmen und auf YouTube hochladen kannst!\n\n BITTE LESEN:
Aufgrund vertraglicher und rechtlicher Vereinbarungen sind einige EOD-Kanäle auf bestimmte Länder beschränkt. Inhalt von Crackle ist NUR in den Vereinigten Staaten, in Kanada, im Vereinigten Königreich und in Australien verfügbar. RadioIO ist NUR in den Vereinigten Staaten und in Kanada verfügbar. Darüber hinaus ist es aus rechtlichen Gründen möglich, dass bestimmte Länder innerhalb der Kanäle nicht dieselben Inhaltsauswahlen erhalten. Der Inhalt ist nur in englischer Sprache verfügbar. Falls Freunde aus anderen Ländern bei dir sind, kann nur Inhalt angezeigt werden, der in allen Ländern verfügbar ist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Incontra il tuo club e divertiti in questo circolo ultra esclusivo di Hollywood Hills, proprio sopra Los Angeles! Sono incluse le seguenti funzionalità:\n
• Sistema cinematografico di intrattenimento su richiesta integrato;\n
• Funzionalità di nuoto per la piscina a sfioro!\n
QUESTO è un rifugio ultra esclusivo per i proprietari di club più esigenti. Con l'acquisto di questo circolo sono disponibili gli oggetti di LOOT™ Telecamera attiva e Illuminazione attiva che ti permetteranno di filmare le tue feste e di caricarle su YouTube!\n\n LEGGERE:
A causa di accordi contrattuali e sui diritti, alcuni canali EOD sono disponibili solo per determinate nazioni. I contenuti Crackle sono disponibili SOLAMENTE per Stati Uniti, Canada, Regno Unito e Australia. RadioIO è disponibile SOLAMENTE per Stati Uniti e Canada. Inoltre, alcuni paesi potrebbero non ricevere le stesse selezioni di contenuto per i vari canali. I contenuti sono disponibili solo in lingua inglese. Se con te ci sono amici provenienti da altre nazioni, possono essere visualizzati solo contenuti disponibili per tutti i paesi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Invita a tu club y reúnete con ellos en esta ultra exclusiva clubhouse, ¡situada en Hollywood Hills, en lo alto del horizonte de Los Ángeles! Incluye:\n
• Entertainment On Demand con sistema Home Cinema;\n
• ¡Función de natación para la piscina infinita!\n
ESTO es un retiro ultra exclusivo para los propietarios de club más exigentes. La compra de esta clubhouse incluye en el lote la Active Camera y la Active Light de LOOT™, ¡para que puedas filmar tus fiestas y subirlas a YouTube sin coste adicional!\n
\n 
LEER DETENIDAMENTE:
Debido a acuerdos contractuales y derechos, algunos canales solo se emiten en determinados países. El contenido Crackle SOLO está disponible en Estados Unidos, Canadá, Reino Unido y Australia. RadioIO SOLO está disponible en Estados Unidos y Canadá. Además, los derechos hacen que cada país pueda recibir selecciones de contenidos diferentes en los canales. Contenidos solo disponibles en inglés. Si estás con amigos de otros países, solo se verán los contenidos disponibles en todos los países. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Entertain and meet with your club in this ultra-exclusive clubhouse, set in the Hollywood Hills above the LA skyline! Features include:
• Built-in Entertainment On Demand theater system;
• A swimming feature for the infinity pool!
THIS is the ultra-exclusive retreat for the discerning club owner. Purchase of this clubhouse comes bundled with the LOOT Active Camera and Active Light, so you can film your parties and upload them to YouTube! PLEASE READ:  Due to contractual and rights agreements, all content may not be available in all countries. Content availability is dependent on the geolocation of the device. CRACKLE content is only available in US, CA, UK, and AU. RADIOIO is only available in US and CA. Only one LOOT TV or LOOT Radio can be active at a time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">【For Ages 18 and Above】\n
Entertain and meet with your club in this ultra-exclusive clubhouse, set in the Hollywood Hills above the LA skyline! Features include:\n
• Built-in Entertainment On Demand theater system;\n
• A swimming feature for the infinity pool!\n
THIS is the ultra-exclusive retreat for the discerning club owner.\n\n PLEASE READ:  Due to contractual and rights agreements, all content may not be available in all countries. Content availability is dependent on the geolocation of the device. CRACKLE content is only available in US, CA, UK, and AU. RADIOIO is only available in US and CA. Only one LOOT™ TV or LOOT™ Radio can be active at a time. ※Please note, in order to access the clubhouse you will need to have purchased the Club Slot. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">【For Ages 18 and Above】\n
Entertain and meet with your club in this ultra-exclusive clubhouse, set in the Hollywood Hills above the LA skyline! Features include:\n
• Built-in Entertainment On Demand theater system;\n
• A swimming feature for the infinity pool!\n
THIS is the ultra-exclusive retreat for the discerning club owner.\n\n PLEASE READ:  Due to contractual and rights agreements, all content may not be available in all countries. Content availability is dependent on the geolocation of the device. CRACKLE content is only available in US, CA, UK, and AU. RADIOIO is only available in US and CA. Only one LOOT™ TV or LOOT™ Radio can be active at a time. ※Please note, in order to access the clubhouse you will need to have purchased the Club Slot. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">【For Ages 18 and Above】\n
Entertain and meet with your club in this ultra-exclusive clubhouse, set in the Hollywood Hills above the LA skyline! Features include:\n
• Built-in Entertainment On Demand theater system;\n
• A swimming feature for the infinity pool!\n
THIS is the ultra-exclusive retreat for the discerning club owner.\n\n PLEASE READ:  Due to contractual and rights agreements, all content may not be available in all countries. Content availability is dependent on the geolocation of the device. CRACKLE content is only available in US, CA, UK, and AU. RADIOIO is only available in US and CA. Only one LOOT™ TV or LOOT™ Radio can be active at a time. ※Please note, in order to access the clubhouse you will need to have purchased the Club Slot. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">【For Ages 18 and Above】\n
Entertain and meet with your club in this ultra-exclusive clubhouse, set in the Hollywood Hills above the LA skyline! Features include:\n
• Built-in Entertainment On Demand theater system;\n
• A swimming feature for the infinity pool!\n
THIS is the ultra-exclusive retreat for the discerning club owner.\n\n PLEASE READ:  Due to contractual and rights agreements, all content may not be available in all countries. Content availability is dependent on the geolocation of the device. CRACKLE content is only available in US, CA, UK, and AU. RADIOIO is only available in US and CA. Only one LOOT™ TV or LOOT™ Radio can be active at a time. ※Please note, in order to access the clubhouse you will need to have purchased the Club Slot. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Entertain and meet with your club in this ultra-exclusive clubhouse, set in the Hollywood Hills above the LA skyline! Features include:\n
• Built-in Entertainment On Demand theater system;\n
• A swimming feature for the infinity pool!\n
THIS is the ultra-exclusive retreat for the discerning club owner. Purchase of this clubhouse comes bundled with the LOOT™ Active Camera and Active Light, so you can film your parties and upload them to YouTube!\n\n PLEASE READ:  Due to contractual and rights agreements, all content may not be available in all countries. Content availability is dependent on the geolocation of the device. CRACKLE content is only available in US, CA, UK, and AU. RADIOIO is only available in US and CA. Only one LOOT™ TV or LOOT™ Radio can be active at a time. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>