<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Scout's Honor Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Scout's Honor Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Scout's Honor Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scout's Honor Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Scout's Honor Pin-up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BlondeBiker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BlondeBiker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BlondeBiker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BlondeBiker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BlondeBiker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Scout's Honor Pin-up Girl</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Scout's Honor she's the hottest girl in Home!  This sexy pin-up girl is a full character costume, complete from head to toe in a patent-red leather biker suit, hat and boots.  Her sexy tattoos adorn her arms, abs and legs and she'll be sure to earn a merit badge with her custom walk, run and pin-up poses - Scout's Honor![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Scout's Honor est la fille la plus belle dans Home! Cette sexy pin-up nana est un costume a part entière, complet de la tête au pieds en tenue motard cuir  rouge-vernis, chapeau et bottes. Son tatouage sexy orne son bras, abdos et jambes et elle est sure de remporter l'insigne de mérite avec sa marche personnalisée, sa course et poses de pin-up Scout's Honor![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Großes Ehrenwort, sie ist das heißeste Mädchen im Haus! Dieses sexy Pin-Up Girl kommt als komplettes Charakterkostüm mit einem quietschroten Lederanzug, Hut und Stiefeln. Ihre sexy Tätowierungen schmücken ihre Arme, ihren Bauch und Beine. Mit ihrem benutzerdefinierten Gang, Lauf und Pin-Up Posen ist sie ein Verdienstabzeichen wert - Großes Ehrenwort![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scout's Honor é la bambola piú sexy della Casa!  Questa bambola sexy pin-up é un costume completo del personaggio, coperta dalla testa ai piedi in un abito da motociclista in pelle rossa , capello e stivali.  I suoi tatuaggi sexy abelliscono le sue braccia, adomminali e gambe e sicuramente conseguirá una medaglia per il merito con la sua camminata particolare, corsa e pose da pin-up - Onore di Scout! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Scout's Honor es la mas guapa de la Casa!  Esta niña sexy pin-up es un disfraz completo del personaje, viene de la cabeza a los pies con traje de motociclista en piel, sombrero y botas.  Sus tatuajes sexys adornan sus brazos, abdomen y piernas seguramente se ganará una medalla al mérito con su caminata especial , corrida y poses de pin-up - Palabra de Scout! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BlondeBiker [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BlondeBiker [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BlondeBiker [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BlondeBiker [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup03_BlondeBiker [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Scout's Honor she's the hottest girl in Home!  This sexy pin-up girl is a full character costume, complete from head to toe in a patent-red leather biker suit, hat and boots.  Her sexy tattoos adorn her arms, abs and legs and she'll be sure to earn a merit badge with her custom walk, run and pin-up poses - Scout's Honor![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>