<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dirk the Daring Outfit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Panoplie Dirk l'Audacieux</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dirk der Waghalsige - Outfit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completo da Dirk l'Audace</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Atuendo de Dirk el Temerario</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_DirkCostume</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_DirkCostume</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_DirkCostume</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_DirkCostume</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_DirkCostume</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dirk the Daring Outfit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It was late at night, a cool breeze had blown through the window. A window which I hadn't opened. Somewhat panicked   I look to my right, Princess Daphne has been kidnapped...again. I couldn't believe it, how many times can I possibly go through this castle! Good thing I purchased my Dirk the Daring outfit to take on the Evil Wizard and Singe. I really must get better locks. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il faisait nuit, il était tard, une brise soufflait à travers la fenêtre. Une fenêtre que je n'avais pas ouverte. Un peu paniqué, je regarde à ma droite...la princesse Daphné a été kidnappée... de nouveau. Je ne pouvais pas le croire, mais combien de fois devrais-je retourner dans ce château ! Heureusement pour moi, j'ai acheté ma panoplie de Dirk le valeureux pour combattre le magicien maléfique et Singe. Il faut que je change les serrures, ça devient urgent ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es war spät nachts - ein kalter Hauch wehte durchs Fenster. Ein Fenster, das ich nicht geöffnet hatte. Panisch schaute ich rechts neben mich - Prinzessin Daphne wurde gekidnapped....ein weiteres Mal! Ich fragte mich, wie oft ich durch dieses Schloss wandern kann, um sie zu retten. Gott sei Dank habe ich mir das "Dirk der Waghalsige"-Outfit gekauft, um den bösen Zauberer Mordroc und den feuerspeienden Drachen zu besiegen. Damit kann mir nichts mehr passieren. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Era notte fonda, una brezza gelata sbuffava dalla finestra. Una finestra che non avevo aperto. In preda al panico guardo alla mia destra, la Principessa Daphne era stata rapita… di nuovo. Non ci potevo credere, quante volte devo mai tornare in questo castello! Meno male che ho comprato il completo da Dirk l'Audace in modo da affrontare il Mago Malvagio e Singe. Devo veramente montare delle serrature migliori. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Era tarde en la noche, una brisa fresca soplaba a través de la ventana. Una ventana que yo no había abierto. Con algo de pánico miré a mi derecha y la princesa Daphne había sido secuestrada... otra vez. No podía creerlo, ¿cuántas veces es posible que pueda revisar este castillo? Lo bueno es que he comprado mi traje de Dirk el Temerario para encargarme del Malvado Mago y de Singe. Realmente debo conseguir mejores cerraduras. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_DirkCostume [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_DirkCostume [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_DirkCostume [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_DirkCostume [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_DirkCostume [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">It was late at night, a cool breeze had blown through the window. A window which I hadn't opened. Somewhat panicked   I look to my right, Princess Daphne has been kidnapped...again. I couldn't believe it, how many times can I possibly go through this castle! Good thing I purchased my Dirk the Daring outfit to take on the Evil Wizard and Singe. I really must get better locks. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>