<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MiniBots Training Facility</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Centre d'entraînement MiniBots</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MiniBots-Trainingsanlage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Struttura di addestramento MiniBot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Instalaciones de entrenamiento de los MiniBots</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MiniBots Training Facility</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This personal space allows you to design and control a custom MiniBot in a fast-paced multiplayer third person shooter for 2-8 players. Battle it out in a last-bot standing Free-for-all brawl or  group with friends for Team Arena mode! Complete hidden achievements to unlock unique rewards!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cet espace personnel laisser vous créez et contrôlez un MiniBot personnalisé dans ce jeu pour 2-8 joueurs. S'affronter lors d'un combat à mort ou se rassembler avec les amis sans un jeu d'équipe. peuvent Récupérez des trophées cachés afin de déverrouiller récompenses uniques.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In dieser persönlichen Umgebung können Sie einen individuellen MiniBot in einem schnellen und aktionsgeladenen Multiplier-Third Person-Shooter für 2-8 Spieler entwerfen und steuern. Kämpfen Sie es aus in einem kostenlosen Kampf, bei dem es am Ende nur einen geben kann - oder tun Sie sich für eine Schlacht im Team-Arena-Modus mit Freunden zusammen! Führen Sie verborgene Aufgaben aus, um einzigartige Belohnungen freizuschalten!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo spazio personale ti consente di progettare e controllare un MiniBot personalizzato in uno sparatutto in terza persona in modalità multigiocatore dal ritmo adrenalinico dai 2 agli 8 giocatori. Combatti in una lotta all'ultimo robot Tutti contro tutti o alleati con altri amici per utilizzare la modalità gioco di squadra. Completa obiettivi nascosti per sbloccare premi unici!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este espacio personal te permite diseñar y controlar un MiniBot personalizado en un rápido disparador de terceros para varios jugadores (de 1 a 8 jugadores). Lucha hasta el final en una pelea hasta que caiga el último robot o únete a tus amigos para el modo Equipo Arena. ¡Completa logros ocultos para liberar recompensas exclusivas!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This personal space allows you to design and control a custom MiniBot in a fast-paced multiplayer third person shooter for 2-8 players. Battle it out in a last-bot standing Free-for-all brawl or  group with friends for Team Arena mode! Complete hidden achievements to unlock unique rewards!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>