<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Leotard with Tights Set (Blue, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de body et collants (Bleus, Femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Gymnastikanzug und Stockings-Set (blau, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set body e collant (blu, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de leotardos y medias (Azules, Mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">タイツ付きレオタードセット（青・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">타이츠와 레오타드 세트 (파란색, 여성)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Leotard with Tights Set (Blue, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">緊身衣和緊身褲組合包（藍色/女用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">緊身衣和緊身褲組合包（藍色/女用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Leotards and Tights Set (Blue, Female)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Blue leotards with brown tights. Set contains leotard wearable with shoes and leotard with socks down to the feet. \nThis set contains the following items with which to customize your avatar.\n\n・Leotard with Tights to be Worn with Shoes (Blue, Women) (Combination/Women)\n・Leotard with Tights (Blue, Women) (Combination/Women)\n\nWhen purchased, each item is added to the appropriate category in your "Avatar Customization" screen.  [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Body bleu et collants marrons. A porter ou non avec des chaussures.\nCe set inclus les articles suivants pour customizer votre avatar.\n\nBody et collants à porter avec des chaussures (Bleu, Femme)(combi/Femme)\nBody et collants (Bleu, Femme)(combi/Femme)\n\nAprès l’achat, chaque article sera ajouté dans sa catégorie de “Avatar Customization”[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Blaue Gymnastikanzüge und braune Stockings. Solche, worüber man Schuhe anziehen kann, und solche, bei denen dies nicht geht, in einem Set.\nIn diesem Set sind folgende Gegenstände für Avatar-Personalisierung inbegriffen.\n\nGymnastikanzug und Stockings, worüber Schuhe angezogen werden können (blau, für Frauen)(Kombination/Frau)\nGymnastikanzug und Stockings (blau, für Frauen)\n\nBei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand in entsprechende Kategorie der "Avatar-Personalisierung" hinzugefügt.  [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un body blu e dei collant marroni. Abbinabili con delle scarpe.\nQuesto set include i seguenti oggetti per la personalizzazione dell'avatar.\n\nBody e collant da abbinare a delle scarpe (blu, da donna / completo da donna)\nBody e collant (blu, da donna / completo da donna)\n\n*Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella categoria "Personalizza avatar".  [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de leotardos azules y medias marrones. Se puede usar con o sin zapatos.\nEste juego incluye los siguientes objetos para adaptar al avatar.\n\nLeotardo y medias para vestir con zapatos (Azul, Mujer)(Combinación/Mujer)\nLeotardo y medias (Azul, Mujer)(Combinación/Mujer)\n\nDespués de la compra, cada objeto será agregado a la categoría de "Personalización del avatar" a la que aplica.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">青いレオタードとブラウンのタイツ。上から靴を履くとき用と履かないとき用がセットになっている。\n本セットには、アバターカスタマイズ用の下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・タイツ付きレオタード・靴重ね履き用（青・女性）（組み合わせ/女性）\n・タイツ付きレオタード（青・女性）（組み合わせ/女性）\n\n※購入すると、「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">파란색 레오타드와 갈색 타이츠. 위에 신발을 신는 것과 신지 않는 것이 세트로 되어 있다.\n\n●타이츠와 레오타드, 신발 덧신기용（파란색, 여성）（의상）\n●타이츠와 레오타드（파란색, 여성）（의상）\n\n※구입하면「옷장」안의 해당 카테고리에 각 아이템이 추가됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Blue leotards with brown tights. Set contains leotard wearable with shoes and leotard with socks down to the feet. \nThis set contains the following items with which to customize your avatar.\n\n・Leotard with Tights to be Worn with Shoes (Blue, Women) (Outfit)\n・Leotard with Tights (Blue, Women) (Outfit)\n\nWhen purchased, each item is added to the appropriate category in your "Wardrobe" screen.  [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">藍色緊身衣和啡色緊身褲。組合包包括穿鞋及不穿鞋的兩款緊身衣。 \n組合包包括以下用於自訂分身角色的物品。\n\n●緊身衣和緊身褲/可配穿鞋子（藍色/女用）（套裝）\n●緊身衣和緊身褲（藍色/女用）（套裝）\n\n※購買後，各物品被添加到「衣帽間」內的相應類別中。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">藍色緊身衣和褐色緊身褲。組合包包括穿鞋及不穿鞋的兩款緊身衣。 \n組合包包括以下用於自訂分身角色的物品。\n\n●緊身衣和緊身褲/可配穿鞋子（藍色/女用）（套裝）\n●緊身衣和緊身褲（藍色/女用）（套裝）\n\n※購買後，各物品被添加到「更衣室」內的相應類別中。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Blue leotards and brown tights. Possible to wear shoes on top or not.\nThis set includes the following items for avatar customization.\n\nLeotards and Tights for Wearing with Shoes (Blue, Female)(combination/Female)\nLeotards and Tights (Blue, Female)(combination/Female)\n\nUpon purchasing, each item in the applicable category of "Avatar Customization" will be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
