<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Outcurl Straight and Star Earrings 3-item Set (Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de 3 pièces Coupe droite bouclée à l'arrière et Boucles d'oreille étoile (femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Frisur mit abstehenden Spitzen und Sternenohrringe, 3-teiliges Set (für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set 3 elementi con acconciatura e orecchini (da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de tres artículos de alisado con ondas y pendientes de estrella (mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">外ハネストレート＆スターイヤリング３点セット（女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">Outcurl Straight and Star Earrings 3-item Set (Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* 魔女のウィッグ・イヤリングセット</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">Outcurl Straight and Star Earrings 3-item Set (Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">Outcurl Straight and Star Earrings 3-item Set (Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Outcurl Straight and Star Earrings 3-item Set (Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 3-item set with a cute hair style curled out in the back and large star-shaped earrings.\nDefensive Strength: None~★\nMagic Power: ★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Outcurl Straight Hairstyle (Women) (Head)\n- Star Earring (Left Ear, Women) (Jewelry, Left Ear)\n- Star Earring (Right Ear, Women) (Jewelry, Right Ear)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 3 objets contenant une coupe de cheveux mignonne bouclée à l'arrière et de grandes boucles d'oreille en forme d'étoile.\nDéfense : Sans~★\nPouvoir Magique : ★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Coupe de cheveux droite bouclée à l'arrière (femme) (Tête)\n- Boucle d'oreille étoile (oreille gauche, femme) (bijoux, oreille gauche)\n- Boucle d'oreille étoile (oreille droite, femme) (bijoux, oreille droite)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">3-teiliges Set mit niedlicher Frisur mit abstehenden Spitzen und großen Ohrringen in Sternenform.\nVerteidigung: Keine~★\nMagie: ★\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Frisur mit abstehenden Spitzen (für Frauen) (Kopfbedeckung)\n- Sternenohrring (linkes Ohr, für Frauen) (Schmuck, linkes Ohr)\n- Sternenohrring (rechtes Ohr, für Frauen) (Schmuck, rechtes Ohr)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set di 3 elementi con una graziosa acconciatura la cui parte posteriore ha le punte dei capelli arricciate all'infuori e un paio di grandi orecchini a forma di stella. Questo set è composto da 3 elementi.\nDifesa: Nulla~★\nPotere magico: ★\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti elementi:\n\n- Acconciatura liscia con le punte arricciate (da donna) (testa)\n- Orecchino a forma di stella (orecchio sinistro, da donna) (gioielli, orecchio sinistro)\n- Orecchino a forma di stella (orecchio destro, da donna) (gioielli, orecchio destro)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de tres artículos bonito peinado, ondulado en la parte posterior, y pendientes grandes en forma de estrella.\nDefensa: Ninguno~★\nPoder mágico: ★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Peinado alisado con ondas (mujer) (cabeza)\n- Pendiente de estrella (oreja izquierda, mujer) (joya, oreja izquierda)\n- Pendiente de estrella (oreja derecha, mujer) (joya, oreja derecha)\n\n*Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">後ろ髪が外にハネたキュートなヘアスタイルと、大きな星型のイヤリングの３点セット。\n防御力：　なし～★\n魔力：　★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・外ハネストレートヘアスタイル（女性）/頭\n・スターイヤリング（左耳・女性）/ジュエリー・左耳\n・スターイヤリング（右耳・女性）/ジュエリー・右耳\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 3-item set with a cute hair style curled out in the back and large star-shaped earrings.\nDefensive Strength: None~★\nMagic Power: ★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Outcurl Straight Hairstyle (Women) (Head)\n- Star Earring (Left Ear, Women) (Jewelry, Left Ear)\n- Star Earring (Right Ear, Women) (Jewelry, Right Ear)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
