<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blueprint: Home - City Penthouse Environment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Blueprint: Home - Environnement Appartement de ville</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blueprint: Home - Umgebung: Stadt-Penthouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Blueprint: Home - Ambiente Attico in città</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Blueprint: Home, entorno de ático en la ciudad</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Blueprint: Home - 都会のペントハウス</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블루프린트: 홈 - 시티 펜트하우스 환경</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Blueprint: Home - City Penthouse Environment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Blueprint: Home - 城市頂層公寓環境</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Blueprint: Home - 城市頂層公寓環境</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blueprint: Home - City Penthouse Environment</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Build your home atop a huge skyscraper in the middle of a thriving city. Your luxury penthouse will benefit from the best view money can buy. Note - You will need to own Blueprint: Home to access this content once it has been purchased. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bâtissez votre domicile au-dessus d’un immense gratte-ciel, en plein cœur d’une ville en pleine effervescence. Votre luxueux appartement bénéficiera de la meilleure vue sur le marché. Remarque - vous devrez posséder Blueprint: Home pour accéder au contenu une fois que vous l'aurez acheté. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bauen Sie Ihr Zuhause auf der Spitze eines riesigen Wolkenkratzers. Ihr Luxus-Penthouse wird Sie mit einem unbezahlbaren Ausblick verwöhnen. Achtung - Sie benötigen Blueprint: Home, um diese Inhalte nach dem Kauf verwenden zu können. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Costruisci la tua casa in cima a un grattacielo altissimo nel mezzo di una città fiorente. Il tuo attico di lusso avrà una vista fantastica. Nota: una volta acquistato questo contenuto, per accedervi dovrai possedere Blueprint: Home. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Construye tu hogar en el ático de un enorme rascacielos en el centro de una próspera ciudad. Tu ático lujoso tendrá la mejor vista del mundo. Nota: necesitarás tener Blueprint: Home para acceder a este contenido una vez que lo hayas comprado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">※このアイテムはパーソナルスペース「Blueprint: Home」専用アイテムです。購入すると、Blueprint: Home内の背景を変更できます。\n\n人でごった返す都会のど真ん中、そびえ立つビルの最上階にあなたの家を建てましょう。豪華絢爛なペントハウス、お金を出せばこれだけの最高の景色が手に入るんです。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">번영하는 도시 한가운데에 있는 거대한 고층건물 꼭대기에 집을 지으세요. 당신의 럭셔리한 펜트하우스는 돈으로 살 수 있는 가장 멋진 경관을 선사합니다. 주의 - 구입한 후에 이 컨텐츠를 사용하려면 블루프린트: 홈을 보유하고 있어야 합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Build your home atop a huge skyscraper in the middle of a thriving city. Your luxury penthouse will benefit from the best view money can buy. Note - You will need to own Blueprint: Home to access this content once it has been purchased. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在繁華都市中央的巨型摩天樓之頂構建家園。豪華的頂層公寓可讓您欣賞金錢可買得到的迷人風景。註：購買此內容後，您需要擁有Blueprint: Home才可使用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在繁華都市中央的巨型摩天樓之頂構建家園。豪華的頂層公寓可讓您欣賞金錢可買得到的迷人風景。註：購買此內容後，您需要擁有Blueprint: Home才可使用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Build your home atop a huge skyscraper in the middle of a thriving city. Your luxury penthouse will benefit from the best view money can buy. Note - You will need to own Blueprint: Home to access this content once it has been purchased. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>