<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Leather Bikini Bundle (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack bikini cuir (pour Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lederbikini-Paket (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Bikini in pelle (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de bikini de cuero (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">가죽 비키니 번들 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Leather Bikini Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">皮革比堅尼服裝組(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">皮革比基尼服裝組(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Leather Bikini Bundle (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This strikingly seductive outfit has mayhem and mischief written all over it. Bundle includes top, bottom with thigh-high boots, and gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette tenue remarquablement aguichante sèmera le trouble partout où vous irez. Le pack comprend un top, un bas avec cuissardes et des gants. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses unglaublich verführerische Outfit riecht nach Chaos und Ärger. Im Paket enthalten sind ein Oberteil, ein Unterteil mit hohen Stiefeln und Handschuhe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un completo altamente seducente che grida maliziosamente "furore" dalla testa ai piedi. Il pacchetto include top, guanti e parte sotto con stivali alla coscia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este atuendo descaradamente seductor pide a gritos sembrar el caos y hacer diabluras. El conjunto comprende las partes superior e inferior, botas altas y guantes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">치명적인 매력을 자랑하는 고혹적인 의상입니다. 이 번들은 가죽 비키니 상의, 하의, 장갑, 그리고 부츠를 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This strikingly seductive outfit has mayhem and mischief written all over it. Bundle includes Leather Bikini Top, Leather Bikini Bottom with thigh-high boots, and Leather Bikini Gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這套誘惑的服裝充滿著混亂和淘氣的氣息。組合包包括皮革比堅尼上衣、皮革比堅尼下身連高筒長靴及皮革手套。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這套誘惑的服裝充滿著混亂和淘氣的氣息。組合包包括皮革比基尼上衣、皮革比基尼下半身連高筒長靴及皮革手套。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This strikingly seductive outfit has mayhem and mischief written all over it. Bundle includes top, bottom with thigh-high boots, and gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>