<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Assaulter (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le fusil d'assaut (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Angreifer (Weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fucile d'assalto (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Atacante (femenino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Assaulter (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Assaulter spews forth ballistic fun with reckless abandon. Also features a zoom and 5 round burst for those who like to aim. BONUS: Unlocks the Assaulter for use in MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le fusil d'assaut crache sans compter son déchaînement balistique. Il dispose également d'un zoom et d'un mode rafale pour ceux qui aiment viser. BONUS : Déverrouille le fusil d'assaut utilisable dans MiniBots multijoueur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Angreifer versprüht gnadenlos ballistischen Fun im Übermaß. Bietet zudem einen Zoom- und einen 5-Runden-Strahl für diejenigen, die lieber genauer zielen. BONUS: Gibt den  Angreifer für den Einsatz im MiniBots-Multiplayer-Modus frei. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Fucile d'assalto erutta piacere balistico con una carica sconsiderata. È anche dotato di zoom e di una modalità di sparo a 5 raffiche per chi ama mirare. BONUS: sblocca il Fucile d'assalto per l'uso in modalità multigiocatore in MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Atacante arroja regalitoos balísticos con imprudente abandono. Cuenta además con un zoom y 5 ráfagas redondas para aquellos a los que les gusta apuntar. BONUS: Desbloquea el Atacante para usarlo en modo de varios jugadores de los MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Assaulter spews forth ballistic fun with reckless abandon. Also features a zoom and 5 round burst for those who like to aim. BONUS: Unlocks the Assaulter for use in MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>