<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Playstation®Home Mansion - Ground Floor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Manoir PlayStation®Home - Rez-de-chaussée</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Playstation®Home-Villa: Erdgeschoss</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Villa PlayStation®Home - Piano terra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mansión de PlayStation®Home: planta baja</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">PlayStation®Home 맨션 - 1층</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">PlayStation®Home Mansion - First Floor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">PlayStation®Home豪華別墅 －1樓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">PlayStation®Home豪華別墅 －1樓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">PlayStation®Home Mansion - First Floor</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to the PlayStation®Home Mansion, an extravagant space filled with some of the rarest items around. On the ground floor you’ll find your mansion comes equipped with the best security money can buy: a live tiger! An Imperial staircase will lead you to the first floor while your kitchen comes fully stocked with gold appliances to fit your cooking needs and an adjacent dining room for you and your guests. Best of all, you’ll be able to walk around while wearing your very own 100 % gold-virtual-thread lounge-wear that comes as a reward for purchasing the new space. And for an added bonus the PlayStation®Home Mansion also allows for up to 5 gold rewards for each of your guests. Enjoy your time in the good life! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue dans le manoir PlayStation®Home, un espace extravagant rempli des articles les plus rares. Au rez-de-chaussée, vous allez découvrir que votre manoir est équipé du meilleur système de sécurité imaginable : un véritable tigre ! Vous y trouverez également un escalier impérial menant au premier étage, une cuisine entièrement équipée d'appareils en or pour réaliser toutes vos idées de recettes, ainsi qu'une salle à manger pour vous et vos invités. Pour couronner le tout, vous pourrez arpenter votre salon vêtu de la magnifique tenue d'intérieur virtuelle en or massif offerte pour l'achat du nouvel espace. Et en bonus, le manoir PlayStation®Home vous permettra aussi de gagner jusqu'à 5 récompenses en or pour chacun de vos invités. Profitez de la vie de star !  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen in der PlayStation®Home-Villa, einem extravaganten Apartment, das mit einigen der seltensten Gegenstände eingerichtet ist. Im Erdgeschoss werden Sie feststellen, dass die Villa über das beste Sicherheitssystem verfügt, das für Geld zu haben ist: einen echten Tiger! Eine Doppeltreppe führt über eine Galerie zum ersten Stock. Ihre komplett mit Geräten in Gold ausgestattete Küche erfüllt selbst höchste Ansprüche, um sich und Ihre Gäste im angrenzenden Esszimmer kulinarisch zu verwöhnen. Außerdem können Sie Ihre Villa in Ihrer Freizeitkleidung aus 100 % virtuellen Goldfäden genießen, die Sie als Belohnung für den Erwerb Ihres neuen Apartments erhalten. Als zusätzlichen Bonus gestattet die PlayStation®Home-Villa darüber hinaus noch bis zu 5 Goldbelohnungen für jeden Ihrer Gäste. Schwelgen Sie in Ihrem neuen Luxusleben! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ecco a te la villa PlayStation®Home, uno spazio stravagante pieno di straordinarie rarità. Al piano terra troverai il miglior sistema di sorveglianza che si possa avere: una tigre viva! Uno scalone imperiale conduce al primo piano, mentre la cucina, completamente arredata con elettrodomestici in oro, comunica con una sala da pranzo riservata a te e ai tuoi ospiti. Acquistando questo nuovo spazio avrai anche una spettacolare ricompensa: un abito da casa in tessuto d'oro al 100%, da indossare per passeggiare tra le tue lussuose stanze. E come se non bastasse, la villa PlayStation®Home contiene anche fino a 5 ricompense in oro per ciascuno dei tuoi ospiti. Goditi la bella vita! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te damos la bienvenida a la mansión de PlayStation®Home, un espacio extravagante, lleno de los objetos más exclusivos que puedas encontrar. En la planta baja podrás encontrar el mejor guardián que pueda pagar el dinero: ¡un tigre! Una escalera imperial te llevará a la primera planta, mientras que en la cocina podrás disfrutar de los electrodomésticos de oro, con los que podrás saciar tus necesidades culinarias en el comedor anexo, para ti y tus invitados. Lo mejor de todo, podrás lucir tus mejores galas, tejidas en hilo virtual de oro 100%, que recibirás como premio por adquirir este nuevo espacio. Además, la mansión de PlayStation®Home incluye hasta cinco premios de oro para tus invitados. ¡Disfruta de la buena vida! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">PlayStation®Home 맨션에 오신 것을 환영합니다. 가장 희귀한 아이템들로 채워진 럭셔리 스페이스입니다. 맨션의 1층은 돈으로 구할 수 있는 가장 강력한 보안 장치가 마련되어 있습니다. 바로 살아 있는 호랑이입니다! 황실 스타일의 계단을 통해 2층으로 갈 수 있으며, 부엌은 여러분에 취향에 어울리는 황금 주방용품이 준비되어 있고, 부엌과 연결된 식당에서는 손님들과 만찬을 열 수도 있습니다. 더 나아가, 이 스페이스를 구입하시면 자동으로 주어지는 100% 황금실로 짠, 황금 실내복을 입고 집안을 활보해 보십시오. 또한 추가 보너스로는 PlayStation®Home 맨션을 방문하는 친구들에게 최대 4개의 황금 리워드를 각기 선물할 수 있습니다. 환상적인 삶을 누리십시오! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Welcome to the PlayStation®Home Mansion, an extravagant space filled with some of the rarest items around. On the first floor you’ll find your mansion comes equipped with the best security money can buy: a live tiger! An Imperial staircase will lead you to the second floor while your kitchen comes fully stocked with gold appliances to fit your cooking needs and an adjacent dining room for you and your guests. Best of all, you’ll be able to walk around while wearing your very own 100 % gold-virtual-thread lounge-wear that comes as a reward for purchasing the new space. And for an added bonus the PlayStation®Home Mansion also allows for up to 4 gold rewards for each of your guests. Enjoy your time in the good life! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">歡迎來到PlayStation®Home豪華別墅，這個奢華的空間放滿了最奇異的物品。在一樓，你會發現你的Mansion配備了金錢能買到最好的保安：一頭活生生的老虎！一條充滿皇室貴氣的樓梯連接到二樓，那裡的廚房齊備了金色的器具來配合你的下廚需要，而旁邊的飯廳讓你和你的賓客用膳。最好的是，購買這個新空間附送100%金色虛擬縫線的家居服，讓你穿著四處走。PlayStation®Home豪華別墅亦額外讓你送出最多4份黃金獎品道具給予你的賓客。請好好享受美好的生活時光！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">歡迎來到PlayStation®Home豪華別墅，這個奢華的空間放滿了最奇異的物品。在一樓，你會發現你的Mansion配備了金錢能買到最好的保安：一頭活生生的老虎！一條充滿皇室貴氣的樓梯連接到二樓，那裡的廚房齊備了金色的器具來配合你的下廚需要，而旁邊的飯廳讓你和你的賓客用膳。最好的是，購買這個新空間附送100%金色虛擬縫線的家居服，讓你穿著四處走。PlayStation®Home豪華別墅亦額外讓你送出最多4份黃金獎品道具給予你的賓客。請好好享受美好的生活時光！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome to the PlayStation®Home Mansion, an extravagant space filled with some of the rarest items around. On the first floor you’ll find your mansion comes equipped with the best security money can buy: a live tiger! An Imperial staircase will lead you to the second floor while your kitchen comes fully stocked with gold appliances to fit your cooking needs and an adjacent dining room for you and your guests. Best of all, you’ll be able to walk around while wearing your very own 100 % gold-virtual-thread lounge-wear that comes as a reward for purchasing the new space. And for an added bonus the PlayStation®Home Mansion also allows for up to 5 gold rewards for each of your guests. Enjoy your time in the good life! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>