<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MotorStorm® Tool Chest</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MotorStorm® Tool Chest</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Caisse à outils MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MotorStorm®-Werkzeugkiste</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cassetta degli attrezzi MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Caja de herramientas de MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">MotorStorm® 道具箱</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">MotorStorm® 공구상자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">MotorStorm™ Tool Chest</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">MotorStorm™ 工具箱</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">MotorStorm™ 工具箱</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MotorStorm® Tool Chest</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Every MotorStormer needs a tool chest? Oh yeah, ‘cos it’s a tool chest – well, if you’re really enthusiastic, you could keep a few tools in it too. We've lost the keys so it doesn't actually open, sorry...[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tous les pilotes ont besoin d'une caisse à outils ? Oh ouais, parce que c'est une caisse à outils. Bien, si vous êtes vraiment passionné, vous pouvez même y ranger quelques outils. Par contre, on a perdu les clés et on ne peut pas l'ouvrir, pardon...[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jeder MotorStorm®-Fan braucht eine Werkzeugkiste. Und weil das hier eine Werkzeugkiste ist, kannst du sogar Werkzeug darin aufbewahren – wenn dir danach sein sollte. Wir haben nur leider den Schlüssel verloren … Sie geht also nicht auf … Sorry![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">C'è una cosa di cui ogni fan di MotorStorm® non può fare a meno: la sua cassetta degli attrezzi! Oh sì, e puoi anche tenerci degli attrezzi dentro! Purtroppo abbiamo perso le chiavi e quindi non si può aprire... le nostre scuse![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Todos los pilotos de MotorStorm® necesitan una caja de herramientas? Claro, pues es una caja de herramientas. Si eres un auténtico entusiasta podrías usarla para guardar algunas herramientas. Hemos perdido las llaves así que no se abre, lo sentimos…[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">レーサーにとって道具箱は必須。箱の中身にはレンチなどの道具もちゃんと入っているだろう。しかし、申し訳ないことにこの道具箱を開ける鍵を無くしてしまった・・・[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">MotorStorm 레이서는 공구상자가 필요하다구요? 물론 필요하지요. 정말 정비할 생각이 있는 레이서들은 공구도 몇 개 갖출지 모르겠네요. 그렇지만 이 상자의 열쇠는 사라진지 오래라서 열리지가 않아요.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Every MotorStormer needs a tool chest? Oh yeah, ‘cos it’s a tool chest – well, if you’re really enthusiastic, you could keep a few tools in it too. We've lost the keys so it doesn't actually open, sorry...[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">每一個MotorStorm玩者都需要一個工具箱？也對啦。如果你真的有心的話，也可以放幾件工具進去。但我們弄丟了鑰匙，所以它其實不能打開，抱歉…。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">每一個MotorStorm玩者都需要一個工具箱？也對啦。如果你真的有心的話，也可以放幾件工具進去。但我們弄丟了鑰匙，所以它其實不能打開，抱歉…。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Every MotorStormer needs a tool chest? Oh yeah, ‘cos it’s a tool chest – well, if you’re really enthusiastic, you could keep a few tools in it too. We've lost the keys so it doesn't actually open, sorry...[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>