<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hornet DX Hover Engine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Réacteur de suspension Hornet DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hornet DX - Hover-Triebwerk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Motore Hover Hornet DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Motor de planeador Hornet DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Hornet DX ホバーエンジン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Hornet DX 호버 엔진</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Hornet DX Hover Engine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Hornet DX 漂浮引擎</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Hornet DX 漂浮引擎</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hornet DX Hover Engine</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Improved stability will allow your Sodium2 racer to stay on course at high speed and handle crashes better. A decent set of air brakes to counteract the reduced turning circle is highly recommended. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une stabilité améliorée permettra à votre engin Sodium2 de rester en course aux plus hautes vitesses et de mieux supporter les accidents. Une bonne paire d'aérofreins pour contrebalancer la réduction de maniabilité est hautement recommandée. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Durch die erhöhte Stabilität bleibt dein Sodium2-Gleiter auch bei hohen Geschwindigkeiten auf der Strecke und ist weniger anfällig für Kollisionen. Es werden gute Luftbremsen empfohlen, um das veränderte Kurvenverhalten auszugleichen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una maggiore stabilità permetterà al tuo veicolo Sodium2 di rimanere in pista ad alte velocità e di gestire meglio le collisioni. Si raccomanda un buon sistema di aerofreni per compensare la ridotta capacità di sterzata. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La estabilidad mejora permitirá que tu corredor de Sodium2 no se salga de la pista a altas velocidades y que pueda soportar mejor los golpes. Recomendamos el uso de un conjunto de frenos de aire decente para contrarrestar la reducción del ángulo de giro. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">あなたのSodium2 racerにより安定性を。ハイスピードによってもブレない事によりクラッシュもコントロールし易くなります。エアブレーキの作用によってスピンの危険性が減るのはお勧めですよ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">향상된 안정성은 고속으로 달릴 때도 여러분의 Sodium2 레이서가 코스를 벗어나지 않게 하고 충돌사태 시에도 더욱 잘 대처할 수 있게 해줄 겁니다. 줄어든 회전 서클을 보완할 적절한 에어 브레이크 세트를 강력히 추천합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Improved stability will allow your Sodium2 racer to stay on course at high speed and handle crashes better. A decent set of air brakes to counteract the reduced turning circle is highly recommended. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">改善穩定性，讓Sodium2賽車在高速下仍能維持方向，撞擊後也更容易操控。建議加購一組空氣制動器，彌補過彎半徑縮小的缺憾。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">改善穩定性，讓Sodium2賽車在高速下仍能維持方向，撞擊後也更容易操控。建議加購一組空氣制動器，彌補過彎半徑縮小的缺憾。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Improved stability will allow your Sodium2 racer to stay on course at high speed and handle crashes better. A decent set of air brakes to counteract the reduced turning circle is highly recommended. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>