<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Rexford Denim Jeans - Vintage Fade (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Jean denim Rexford - décoloré vintage (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Rexford Jeans - Klassisch ausgebleichtes Blau (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Rexford Jeans - Vintage Fade (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Rexford Vaqueros - Vintage difuminado (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cleanly styled, classic details, and a great regular fit. There's a lot to like about the Rexford denim pants. Everything you appreciate about a great pair of jeans is here, including 5 pockets, metal hardware, subtle stitching detail at the back pockets, a zip fly, and a leather logo patch at the back waist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Style pur, détails classiques et très belle coupe régulière. Le jean denim Rexford ne manque pas d'atouts. Tout ce que vous appréciez dans un excellent jean est là, y compris les 5 poches, les accessoires métalliques, les coutures raffinées aux poches arrière, la braguette zippée et un logo en cuir à la taille. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit ihrem geraden Schnitt, klassischen Stil und optimaler Passform ist die Rexford Jeans die perfekte Jeans schlechthin, denn sie hat einfach alles, was eine Qualitätsjeans unbedingt haben muss: fünf Taschen, Metallverzierungen, feine Stickarbeit an den Gesäßtaschen, Reißverschluss und Lederetikett hinten am Bund. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dallo stile pulito, con dettagli classici e taglio normale con ottima vestibilità. C'è molto da apprezzare in un paio di jeans Rexford. Tutto quello che cerchi in un paio di jeans lo troverai in questo modello, tra cui 5 tasche, finiture in metallo, dettaglio con cucitura sottile sulle tasche posteriori, zip con patta e toppa di pelle con logo nella parte posteriore della vita. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">De estilo pulcro y corte recto en su excelencia, incluye varios detalles del clásico vaquero; los Rexford lo tienen todo para encantar. Todo lo que te gusta en un buen vaquero: cinco bolsillos,  adornos metálicos, sutiles detalles de costura en los bolsillos traseros, bragueta de cremallera y parche de cuero con el logotipo en la parte trasera de la cintura. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>