<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ansada Fone Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appartement Ansada Fone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ansada Fone-Wohnung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Appartamento Ansada Fone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apartamento de Ansada Fone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Ansada Fone アパートメント</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Ansada Fone 아파트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ansada Fone Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「Ansada Fone」公寓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「Ansada Fone」公寓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ansada Fone Apartment</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This truly unique apartment isn't like anything you have ever seen before in PlayStation®Home.  A fantastic cartoon world where you can play a frantic 4 player mini game with your friends or chill out and redecorate.  Will you get there in time to Ansada Fone? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cet appartement réellement unique est différent de tout ce que vous avez pu voir jusqu'à présent dans PlayStation®Home. Un extraordinaire monde de dessins animés, où vous pourrez disputer un mini-jeu effréné avec 4 de vos amis, ou vous détendre et faire de la décoration. Arriverez-vous à temps pour répondre au téléphone ? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">So etwas wie diese wirklich einzigartige Wohnung hast du noch nie in PlayStation®Home gesehen. Eine fantastische Comic-Welt, in der du ein wildes 4-Spieler-Minispiel mit deinen Freunden spielen oder dich entspannen und neu dekorieren kannst.  Wirst du es rechtzeitig zu Ansada Fone schaffen? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo raro appartamento è un qualcosa di mai visto prima in PlayStation®Home. Un fantastico mondo in cui potrai divertirti con un frenetico mini gioco a 4 giocatori con i tuoi amici o rilassarti e ridecorare. Ce la farai ad arrivare ad Ansada Fone in tempo? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este apartamento verdaderamente único no se parece a nada que hayas visto antes en PlayStation®Home. Un fantástico mundo de dibujos animados en el que podrás jugar con tus amigos a un minijuego frenético para 4 jugadores o, simplemente, relajarte y cambiar la decoración. ¿Podrás llegar a tiempo para Ansada Fone? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">パーソナルスペースの概念を一新する個性的なアパートメント。4人プレイ対応の不思議なミニゲームも遊べる素敵なカートゥーンの世界へようこそ！もちろんこだわりのインテリアも用意されてます。さあ今すぐ Ansada Fone へ急ごう！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">당신이 한 번도 보지 못한 진정으로 독특한 아파트입니다. 친구들과 정신없는 4-플레이어 미니 게임을 플레이 하거나 편히 쉬면서 실내 장식을 새로 할수도 있는 환상적인 만화 세계입니다. 제 시간 안에 도착할 수 있겠습니까? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This truly unique apartment isn't like anything you have ever seen before in PlayStation®Home.  A fantastic cartoon world where you can play a frantic 4 player mini game with your friends or chill out and redecorate.  Will you get there in time to Ansada Fone? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這一真正獨特的公寓，是你在PlayStation®Home中從未見過的。在這個神奇的動漫世界中，您可以與朋友一起玩最多可以四位玩家共同遊玩的迷你遊戲，或者放鬆心情重新裝修。您跟得上Ansada Fone的潮流嗎？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這一真正獨特的公寓，是你在PlayStation®Home中從未見過的。在這個神奇的動漫世界中，您可以與朋友一起玩最多可以四位玩家共同遊玩的迷你遊戲，或者放鬆心情重新裝修。您跟得上Ansada Fone的潮流嗎？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This truly unique apartment isn't like anything you have ever seen before in PlayStation®Home.  A fantastic cartoon world where you can play a frantic 4 player mini game with your friends or chill out and redecorate.  Will you get there in time to Ansada Fone? [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>