<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blaster (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le blaster (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Blaster (Weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fulminatore (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El aniquilador (femenino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blaster (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The quintessential utility weapon, this is standard issue for any MiniBot in the field. Veteran MiniBots quickly replace this with a superior weapon. Awarded for scoring 10 kills with the Blaster in a multiplayer game of MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Arme à tout faire par excellence, elle équipe de base les MiniBots sur le champ de bataille. Les MiniBots vétérans la remplacent rapidement par une arme plus puissante. Attribué si vous tuez 10 ennemis avec le blaster lors d'une partie multijoueur de MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die unverzichtbare Dienstwaffe, dies ist das Standardobjekt eines jeden MiniBots im Einsatz. MiniBot-Veteranen tauschen sie schnell gegen eine bessere Waffe aus. Vergeben für 10 mit Der Blaster getötete Gegner in einem  MiniBots-Multiplayer-Spiel. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quintessenza delle armi strategiche, è la soluzione standard per ogni MiniBot sul campo. I MiniBot veterani lo sostituiscono presto con un'arma superiore. Premio per aver segnato 10 uccisioni con il Fulminatore in una partita in modalità multigiocatore di MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El arma de utilidad por antonomasia, es de uso común para cualquier MiniBot sobre el terreno. Los MiniBots veteranos la sustituyen rápidamente con un arma superior. Concedido por llegar a 10 víctimas con el aniquiladoren una partida para varios jugadores de MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The quintessential utility weapon, this is standard issue for any MiniBot in the field. Veteran MiniBots quickly replace this with a superior weapon. Awarded for scoring 10 kills with the Blaster in a multiplayer game of MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>