<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">C-3PO Protocol Droid Costume</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Costume Droïde de protocole C-3PO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">C-3PO Protokolldroidenkostüm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Costume Droide Protocollo C-3PO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de droide de protocolo C-3PO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">C-3PO プロトコル・ドロイドのコスチューム</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">C-3PO 프로토콜 드로이드 복장</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">C-3PO Protocol Droid Costume</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">C-3PO禮儀機器人的裝束</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">C-3PO禮儀機器人的裝束</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">C-3PO Protocol Droid Costume</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"I am C-3PO, human-cyborg relations."  C-3PO was fluent in over six million forms of communication. Generally seen with his counterpart, R2-D2, C-3PO's main function as a protocol droid was to assist with etiquette, customs and translations.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Je suis C-3PO, relations humains-cyborgs." C-3PO maîtrise plus de six millions de formes de communication. Généralement accompagné de son homologue R2-D2, la fonction principale du droïde de protocole C-3PO est d'aider en matière d'étiquette, de coutumes et de traductions.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Ich bin C-3PO, Roboter-Mensch-Kontakter." C-3PO beherrschte über sechs Millionen Formen der Kommunikation. Er wurde häufig mit seinem Partner R2-D2 gesehen und seine Hauptfunktion als Protokolldroide war, bei der Etikette, Gebräuchen und Übersetzungen zu helfen.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Sono C-3PO, relazioni umani-cyborg". C-3PO era fluente in oltre sei milioni di forme di comunicazione. Generalmente visto con il suo omologo, R2-D2, la funzione di C-3PO in quanto droide di protocollo era di assistere con l'etichetta, i costumi e le traduzioni.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“Soy C-3PO, relaciones cibernéticas y humanas”. C-3PO manejaba con fluidez seis millones de tipos de comunicación. Visto normalmente en compañía de su homólogo R2-D2, la principal misión de C-3PO como droide de protocolo era asistir en etiqueta, costumbres y traducciones.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「私はC-3PO、ヒューマン・サイボーグ・リレーションズです。」600万語を越す宇宙言語に精通し、相棒のR2-D2を供に、プロトコル・ドロイドとして宇宙各地のエチケットや習慣、通訳などに従事する。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"나는 C-3PO, 휴먼-사이보그 관계 담당". C-3PO는 6백만이 넘는 형태의 의사소통을 능숙하게 할 수 있습니다. 단짝 R2-D2와 주로 함께 다니는 C-3PO는 외교 로봇의 역할을 하면서 예의범절, 풍습, 번역을 지원합니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"I am C-3PO, human-cyborg relations."  C-3PO was fluent in over six million forms of communication. Generally seen with his counterpart, R2-D2, C-3PO's main function as a protocol droid was to assist with etiquette, customs and translations.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">〝我是C-3PO，負責人類與機器人的關係。〞C-3PO精通六百萬種以上的溝通方式。常與R2-D2形影不離的C-3PO，作為禮儀機器人的主要功能是在禮儀、習俗以及翻譯上提供協助。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">〝我是C-3PO，負責人類與機器人的關係。〞C-3PO精通六百萬種以上的溝通方式。常與R2-D2形影不離的C-3PO，作為禮儀機器人的主要功能是在禮儀、習俗以及翻譯上提供協助。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"I am C-3PO, human-cyborg relations."  C-3PO was fluent in over six million forms of communication. Generally seen with his counterpart, R2-D2, C-3PO's main function as a protocol droid was to assist with etiquette, customs and translations.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>