<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Moel, design Inga Sempé, Ligne Roset, 2007. Soft curves and unique appearance define this stylish and unusual piece of furniture. Bicolour interpretation recommended. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Moël, design Inga Sempé, Ligne Roset, 2007. Des lignes douces et un aspect unique pour un siège élégant et inédit. Modèle bicolore recommandé. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Moel, Design von Inga Sempé, Ligne Roset, 2007. Weiche Kurven und eine einzigartige Optik sind kennzeichnend für dieses stilvolle und ungewöhnliche Möbelstück. Zweifarbige Ausführung empfohlen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Moel, design di Inga Sempé, Ligne Roset, 2007. Le linee morbide e il look esclusivo caratterizzano questo mobile particolare ed elegante. Si consiglia la versione bicolore.\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Moel, diseño de Inga Sempé, Ligne Roset, 2007. Suaves curvas y una apariencia única definen este mueble lleno de estilo y originalidad. Se recomienda en una combinación bicolor.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Moel：2007年のリーン・ロゼ製品。インガ・サンペによるデザイン。柔らかな曲線と独特な外観が、このスタイリッシュで非凡な家具を特徴づける。2色使いの仕上げがお勧め。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">\nMoel, Inga Sempé, Ligne Roset의 디자인, 2007년. 부드러운 곡선 및\n독창적인 외양의 본 제품은 가구의 스타일 및 독창성이 무엇인지 보여줍니다. 두 가지 색상을\n사용하여 제작하는 것을 권장합니다.\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Moel, design Inga Sempé, Ligne Roset, 2007. Soft curves and unique\nappearance define this stylish and unusual piece of furniture. Bicolour\ninterpretation recommended. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Moel：Inga Sempé 設計，Ligne Roset，2007 年。 以柔和曲線與獨特\n外觀凸顯此傢俱的時尚非凡。 建議採用雙色\n設計。\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Moel：Inga Sempé 設計，Ligne Roset，2007 年。 以柔和曲線與獨特\n外觀凸顯此傢俱的時尚非凡。 建議採用雙色\n設計。\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Moel, design Inga Sempé, Ligne Roset, 2007. Soft curves and unique\nappearance define this stylish and unusual piece of furniture. Bicolour\ninterpretation recommended. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Moel Armchair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fauteuil Moël</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sessel "Moël"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Poltrona Moel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sillón Moel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">モエル・アームチェア</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">모엘 안락의자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Moel Armchair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Moel 扶手椅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Moel 扶手椅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Moel Armchair</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>