<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Terminus DX Air Brakes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aérofreins Terminus DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Terminus DX-Luftbremsen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aerofreni Terminus DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Frenos aéreos Terminus DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Terminus DX エアブレーキ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Terminus DX 에어 브레이크</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Terminus DX Air Brakes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Terminus DX 空氣制動系統</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Terminus DX 空氣制動系統</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Terminus DX Air Brakes</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Improved hydraulics for your Sodium2 vehicle will give you a greater braking force. You'll spend less time on the brakes round the tight bends and more time on the POWER! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un système hydraulique amélioré pour votre véhicule Sodium2 vous apportera une plus grande puissance de freinage, afin de passer moins de temps sur les freins dans les virages serrés et plus de temps sur la PUISSANCE ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verbesserte Hydraulik für deinen Sodium2-Gleiter verleiht dir eine höhere Bremskraft, so dass du in engen Kurven weniger auf der Bremse stehst und dafür länger auf dem GAS! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un'idraulica migliorata consentirà al tuo veicolo Sodium2 di disporre di maggiore forza frenante, riducendo i tempi di frenata nelle curve strette. In questo modo ci si potrà concentrare sulla POTENZA! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La hidráulica mejorada de tu vehículo de Sodium2 también te dará una mayor fuerza de frenado, así que necesitarás frenar menos en los giros cerrados y apretar más el ACELERADOR. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">液圧システムの改善により、高い制動力を実現。ブレーキ力が増し、急カーブ時にブレーキを踏む時間が短くなる。すなわち、加速に回す時間が長くなる！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium2 기체에 더욱 향상된 브레이크 시스템을 적용하여, 날카로운 코너 구간을 더욱 빨리 탈출할 수 있도록 합니다. 이제 직선 구간에서 가속을 붙이는 데 집중하십시오. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Improved hydraulics for your Sodium2 vehicle will give you a greater braking force. You'll spend less time on the brakes round the tight bends and more time on the POWER! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">經過改良的液壓裝置能給你的Sodium2飛船提供更大的煞車停止能量，減短急彎的煞車停止時間，將更多時間放在能量上！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">經過改良的液壓裝置能給你的Sodium2飛船提供更大的煞車停止能量，減短急彎的煞車停止時間，將更多時間放在能量上！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Improved hydraulics for your Sodium2 vehicle will give you a greater braking force. You'll spend less time on the brakes round the tight bends and more time on the POWER! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>