<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Baby Princess Room - drawers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chambre bébé Princesse - commode</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Prinzessin Babyraum - Kommode</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Camera Principessa bambino- cassettiera</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Habitación de bebé princesa - Cajonera</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Baby Princess Room - drawers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Baby Princess Room - drawers</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Royal blues or Pinks? The world is waiting to see whether the future British heir to the throne will be a boy or a girl? To celebrate we have everything you'll need to create your royal nursery in blue or pink. Everyone can join in the fun by grabbing a free prediction t-shirt, you decide whether you think the baby is a new prince or princess! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Royale bleu ou rose? Le monde attend avec impatience de savoir si le futur héritier de la couronne britannique sera une fille ou un garçon ! Pour fêter l’occasion, nous avons tout ce dont vous aurez besoin pour créer votre chambre royale en bleu ou en rose. Tout le monde peut participer à la fête en obtenant un t-shirt gratuit : à vous de voir si vous pensez que le bébé sera un prince ou une princesse [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Königliche blau oder rosa? Die Welt wartet darauf zu erfahren, ob der britische Thronfolger ein Junge oder ein Mädchen wird. Zur Feier haben wir alles, damit Sie Ihr königliches Kinderzimmer in blau oder rosa erschaffen können. Alle können sich dem Spaß anschließen, indem Sie sich ein kostenloses Vorhersage-T-Shirt schnappen. Sie entscheiden, ob Sie glauben, dass das Baby ein neuer Prinz oder eine Prinzessin wird! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Reale blu o rosa? Il mondo è in attesa di scoprire se il futuro erede al trono britannico sarà maschio o femmina... Nel frattempo, festeggia con noi e crea la tua nursery "reale" blu o rosa.  Tutti possono partecipare ordinando la t-shirt-pronostico gratuita! Secondo te, il bebè reale sarà un principe o una principessa? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Real azul o rosas? El mundo está impaciente por saber si el futuro heredero de la corona británica será niño o niña. Para celebrarlo, tenemos todo lo que necesitas para crear tu propia guardería real en azul o en rosa.  ¡Diviértete eligiendo tu camiseta de predicción gratuita si crees que el bebé será un príncipe o una princesa! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Royal blues or Pinks? The world is waiting to see whether the future British heir to the throne will be a boy or a girl? To celebrate we have everything you'll need to create your royal nursery in blue or pink.  Everyone can join in the fun by grabbing a free prediction t-shirt, you decide whether you think the baby is a new prince or princess! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Royal blues or Pinks? The world is waiting to see whether the future British heir to the throne will be a boy or a girl? To celebrate we have everything you'll need to create your royal nursery in blue or pink.  Everyone can join in the fun by grabbing a free prediction t-shirt, you decide whether you think the baby is a new prince or princess! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>