<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nathan's Jacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Veste de Nathan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nathans Jacke</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Giubbotto di Nathan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cazadora de Nathan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ネイトのジャケット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">네이던의 자켓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Nathan's Jacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">奈森的外套</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">奈森的外套</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Nathan's Jacket</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Leather Jacket with faux sheepskin interior. Using basic thermodynamic principals, this jacket will keep you warm and cosy even in the worst of the snowstorms. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Veste en cuir avec doublure en peau de mouton synthétique. Grâce à ses qualités thermodynamiques, cette veste vous tiendra chaud même en plein blizzard. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lederjacke mit Futter aus Schaffellimitat. Diese simple Thermojacke hält Sie selbst im schlimmsten Schneesturm kuschelig warm. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Giubbotto di pelle con interno in similpelle di montone. Grazie alle sue qualità questo giubbotto garantisce protezione contro il freddo anche nelle peggiori condizioni atmosferiche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cazadora de cuero con interior de borreguillo. De acuerdo a los principios de la termodinámica, esta chaqueta te mantendrá caliente aun en la peor de las ventiscas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">暖かいジャケット [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">인조 양모로 안을 덧댄 가죽 자켓.  기본적인 방열이 충분하기 때문에 최악의 눈보라 속에서도 버틸 수 있다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Leather Jacket with faux sheepskin interior. Using basic thermodynamic principals, this jacket will keep you warm and cozy even in the worst of the snowstorms. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">內裏混仿羊毛的羽毛外套。既使身陷嚴重暴風雪中亦能維持溫暖、舒適。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">內裏混仿羊毛的羽毛外套。既使身陷嚴重暴風雪中亦能維持溫暖、舒適。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Leather Jacket with faux sheepskin interior. Using basic thermodynamic principals, this jacket will keep you warm and cozy even in the worst of the snowstorms. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>