<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] Continuer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] Weiter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] Continua</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] Continuar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  [CROSS]Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  [CROSS]Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  [CROSS]Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  [CROSS]Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  [CROSS]Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[CROSS] Continue</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">select</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] Select answer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] Choisir une réponse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] Antwort auswählen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] Seleziona risposta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] Elegir respuesta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  [CROSS] Select answer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  [CROSS] Select answer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  [CROSS] Select answer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  [CROSS] Select answer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  [CROSS] Select answer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[CROSS] Select answer</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">move</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[UP][DOWN] Change answer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[UP][DOWN] Modifier la réponse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[UP][DOWN] Antwort ändern</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[UP][DOWN] Cambia risposta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[UP][DOWN] Cambiar respuesta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  [UP][DOWN]  Change answer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  [UP][DOWN]  Change answer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  [UP][DOWN]  Change answer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  [UP][DOWN]  Change answer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  [UP][DOWN]  Change answer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[UP][DOWN] Change answer</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A multiple choice quiz to determine your mana affinity. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un questionnaire à choix multiples pour déterminer votre affinité de mana. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Quiz, um deine Manaaffinität festzustellen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un quiz a risposta multipla per determinare la tua affinità di mana. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un cuestionario con opciones para determinar tu afinidad de maná. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  A multiple choice quiz to determine your mana affinity. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  A multiple choice quiz to determine your mana affinity. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  A multiple choice quiz to determine your mana affinity. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  A multiple choice quiz to determine your mana affinity. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  A multiple choice quiz to determine your mana affinity. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A multiple choice quiz to determine your mana affinity. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q1d</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Analyze the context of the situation until a suitable solution occurs to you.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Analysez le contexte de la situation jusqu'à ce que vous trouviez une solution appropriée à votre cas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du analysierst den Hintergrund der Situation, bis dir eine passende Lösung einfällt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Analizzi il contesto della situazione fino a che non trovi una soluzione accettabile.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Analizas el contexto de la situación hasta que se te ocurra una solución.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Analyze the context of the situation until a suitable solution occurs to you.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Analyze the context of the situation until a suitable solution occurs to you.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Analyze the context of the situation until a suitable solution occurs to you.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Analyze the context of the situation until a suitable solution occurs to you.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Analyze the context of the situation until a suitable solution occurs to you.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Analyze the context of the situation until a suitable solution occurs to you.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q5e</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Begin drawing mathematical diagrams in the sand, calculating the probability that you’ll be rescued before your resources run out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous commencez à dessiner des diagrammes mathématiques dans le sable pour calculer la probabilité que vous serez secouru avant d'être à court de ressources.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du fängst damit an, mathematische Diagramme in den Sand zu zeichnen, um die Wahrscheinlichkeit zu berechnen, dass du gerettet wirst, bevor deine Vorräte alle sind.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Inizi a disegnare diagrammi matematici nella sabbia, per calcolare le probabilità di essere salvato prima che le tue risorse si esauriscano.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Comienzas a dibujar diagramas matemáticos en la arena, calculando la probabilidad de que sean rescatados antes de que se les acaben los recursos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Begin drawing mathematical diagrams in the sand, calculating the probability that you’ll be rescued before your resources run out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Begin drawing mathematical diagrams in the sand, calculating the probability that you’ll be rescued before your resources run out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Begin drawing mathematical diagrams in the sand, calculating the probability that you’ll be rescued before your resources run out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Begin drawing mathematical diagrams in the sand, calculating the probability that you’ll be rescued before your resources run out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Begin drawing mathematical diagrams in the sand, calculating the probability that you’ll be rescued before your resources run out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Begin drawing mathematical diagrams in the sand, calculating the probability that you’ll be rescued before your resources run out.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q9a</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blackmail the arsonist, then turn them in anyway to get in good with the campus police.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous faites chanter l'incendiaire, puis vous le dénoncez quand même histoire d'être bien vu par le vigile du campus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du erpresst den Brandstifter und meldest ihn dann trotzdem, um dich gut mit der Univerwaltung zu stellen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ricatti il piromane, poi lo denunci comunque per ingraziarti la polizia del campus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Extorsionas al incendiario, luego lo entregas para estar en buenos términos con la policía.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Blackmail the arsonist, then turn him in anyway to get in good with the campus police.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Blackmail the arsonist, then turn him in anyway to get in good with the campus police.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Blackmail the arsonist, then turn him in anyway to get in good with the campus police.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Blackmail the arsonist, then turn him in anyway to get in good with the campus police.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Blackmail the arsonist, then turn him in anyway to get in good with the campus police.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blackmail the arsonist, then turn them in anyway to get in good with the campus police.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q3d</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Break out your trail guide, check the index for the “bear” entry, flip to the “bear” section, read up on this particular species and its feeding habits, and concoct a plan to outwit the bear using your superior intellect.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous ouvrez votre guide de survie dans la nature. Dans l'index, vous cherchez le chapitre sur les ours pour y trouver ses habitudes alimentaires et vous mettez au point un plan pour mettre l'ours en déroute grâce à votre intellect supérieur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du holst deinen Wanderführer heraus, suchst im Inhaltsverzeichnis nach dem Eintrag für „Bär“, blätterst hin,  lernst den Abschnitt über diese besondere Art auswendig und entwirfst einen Plan, wie du den Bär dank deines überlegenen Intellekts austricksen k</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tiri fuori la tua guida dei sentieri, cerchi nell'indice la voce “orso”, vai alla sezione “orso”, leggi tutto su questa specie particolare e sulle sue abitudini alimentari e architetti un piano per fregare l'orso sfruttando la tua intelligenza superiore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tomas tu guía de campo, buscas en el índice “oso”, vas a la sección “oso”, lees las particularidades de esta especie y sus hábitos alimenticios y elaboras un plan para vencer al oso usando tu intelecto superior.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Break out your trail guide, check the index for the “bear” entry, flip to the “bear” section, read up on this particular species and its feeding habits, and concoct a plan to outwit the bear using your superior intellect.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Break out your trail guide, check the index for the “bear” entry, flip to the “bear” section, read up on this particular species and its feeding habits, and concoct a plan to outwit the bear using your superior intellect.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Break out your trail guide, check the index for the “bear” entry, flip to the “bear” section, read up on this particular species and its feeding habits, and concoct a plan to outwit the bear using your superior intellect.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Break out your trail guide, check the index for the “bear” entry, flip to the “bear” section, read up on this particular species and its feeding habits, and concoct a plan to outwit the bear using your superior intellect.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Break out your trail guide, check the index for the “bear” entry, flip to the “bear” section, read up on this particular species and its feeding habits, and concoct a plan to outwit the bear using your superior intellect.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Break out your trail guide, check the index for the “bear” entry, flip to the “bear” section, read up on this particular species and its feeding habits, and concoct a plan to outwit the bear using your superior intellect.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q10c</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Build a mountaintop coliseum and rename yourself "Warlord of the Arena."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous construisez un colisée au sommet d'une montagne et vous vous déclarez « Seigneur de guerre de l'Arène ».</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du erbaust oben auf dem Berg einen Sportplatz und lässt dich ab jetzt „Kriegsherr der Arena“ nennen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Costruisci un colosseo in cima alla montagna e ti fai chiamare "Condottiero dell'Arena".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Construyes un coliseo en la cima de una montaña y cambias tu nombre a "Señor de la Arena".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Build a mountaintop coliseum and rename yourself Warlord of the Arena.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Build a mountaintop coliseum and rename yourself Warlord of the Arena.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Build a mountaintop coliseum and rename yourself Warlord of the Arena.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Build a mountaintop coliseum and rename yourself Warlord of the Arena.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Build a mountaintop coliseum and rename yourself Warlord of the Arena.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Build a mountaintop coliseum and rename yourself "Warlord of the Arena."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">calculating</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Calculating your mana colour.\nPlease wait . . .</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Calcul de votre couleur de mana en cours.\nVeuillez patienter. . .</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Deine Manafarbe wird berechnet.\nBitte warte kurz ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Valutazione del tuo colore di mana.\nIn attesa. . .</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Calculando tu color de maná.\nPor favor espera...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Calculating your mana colour.\nPlease wait...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Calculating your mana colour.\nPlease wait...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Calculating your mana colour.\nPlease wait...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Calculating your mana colour.\nPlease wait...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Calculating your mana colour.\nPlease wait...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Calculating your mana color.\nPlease wait . . .</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q7e</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Change the locks on your new storage container.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous changez les serrures de votre nouveau container de stockage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du tauschst die Schlösser an deinem neuen Container aus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cambi le serrature del tuo nuovo magazzino.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cambias la cerradura de tu nuevo contenedor.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Change the locks on my new storage container.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Change the locks on my new storage container.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Change the locks on my new storage container.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Change the locks on my new storage container.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Change the locks on my new storage container.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Change the locks on your new storage container.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q9c</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Chase down the suspect while dialling the authorities.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous pourchassez le suspect tout en appelant les autorités.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du verfolgst den Verdächtigen, während du die Behörden anrufst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Insegui il sospetto mentre telefoni alle autorità.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Persigues al sospechoso mientras llamas a las autoridades.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Chase down the suspect while dialing the authorities.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Chase down the suspect while dialing the authorities.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Chase down the suspect while dialing the authorities.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Chase down the suspect while dialing the authorities.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Chase down the suspect while dialing the authorities.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Chase down the suspect while dialing the authorities.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q9b</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Check to be sure the campus gardens aren’t in jeopardy, then empty your backpack of math textbooks onto the pyre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous vérifiez que les jardins du campus ne risquent rien, vous jetez au feu les manuels de mathématiques se trouvant dans votre sac à dos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Da die Campus-Grünflächen nicht in Gefahr sind, kippst du die Mathebücher aus deinem Rucksack noch auf den Scheiterhaufen drauf.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Controlli che le aiuole del campus non siano in pericolo, poi rovesci i libri di matematica del tuo zaino sul rogo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te aseguras de que los jardines no estén en peligro, luego sacas de tu mochila los libros de matemática y los arrojas a la pira.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Check to be sure the campus gardens aren’t in jeopardy, then empty my backpack of math textbooks onto the pyre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Check to be sure the campus gardens aren’t in jeopardy, then empty my backpack of math textbooks onto the pyre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Check to be sure the campus gardens aren’t in jeopardy, then empty my backpack of math textbooks onto the pyre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Check to be sure the campus gardens aren’t in jeopardy, then empty my backpack of math textbooks onto the pyre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Check to be sure the campus gardens aren’t in jeopardy, then empty my backpack of math textbooks onto the pyre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Check to be sure the campus gardens aren’t in jeopardy, then empty your backpack of math textbooks onto the pyre.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q6b</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Congratulate the developer on his or her forethought and celebrate the march of progress.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous félicitez le développeur de sa prévoyance et vous célébrez la marche du progrès.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du gratulierst dem Entwickler zu seiner Voraussicht und freust dich über den Vormarsch des Fortschritts.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ti congratuli con l'impresario per la sua previdenza e festeggi il cammino del progresso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Felicitas al constructor por su previsión y celebras la marcha del progreso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Congratulate the developer on his forethought and celebrate the march of progress.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Congratulate the developer on his forethought and celebrate the march of progress.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Congratulate the developer on his forethought and celebrate the march of progress.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Congratulate the developer on his forethought and celebrate the march of progress.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Congratulate the developer on his forethought and celebrate the march of progress.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Congratulate the developer on his or her forethought and celebrate the march of progress.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q10e</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Create a subterranean stronghold from which to build your power base, then confiscate all the footage of its construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous créez une forteresse souterraine pour renforcer votre pouvoir, puis vous confisquez tous les enregistrements sur sa construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du erschaffst eine unterirdische Festung, die dir als Stützpunkt dient, und vernichtest danach alle Konstruktionsunterlagen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Crei una roccaforte sotterranea su cui costruire la tua base del potere, poi sequestri tutte le riprese della sua costruzione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Creas una base subterránea donde construir tu fortaleza, luego confiscas todos los planos de su construcción.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Create a subterranean stronghold from which to build your power base, then confiscate all the footage of its construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Create a subterranean stronghold from which to build your power base, then confiscate all the footage of its construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Create a subterranean stronghold from which to build your power base, then confiscate all the footage of its construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Create a subterranean stronghold from which to build your power base, then confiscate all the footage of its construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Create a subterranean stronghold from which to build your power base, then confiscate all the footage of its construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Create a subterranean stronghold from which to build your power base, then confiscate all the footage of its construction.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q10d</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Demand that your house be grown organically from the native plants of your neighbourhood.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous exigez que votre maison soit totalement écolo, utilisant comme matériaux les plantes poussant dans les environs.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du verlangst, dass dein Haus organisch aus einheimischen Pflanzen gezüchtet werden soll.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chiedi che la tua casa sia fatta crescere in modo organico dalle piante autoctone del tuo quartiere.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Exiges que tu casa sea construida orgánicamente con plantas nativas de tu vecindad.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Demand that your house be grown organically from the native plants of your neighborhood.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Demand that your house be grown organically from the native plants of your neighborhood.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Demand that your house be grown organically from the native plants of your neighborhood.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Demand that your house be grown organically from the native plants of your neighborhood.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Demand that your house be grown organically from the native plants of your neighborhood.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Demand that your house be grown organically from the native plants of your neighborhood.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q4d</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Do the right thing:  Do the best I can with what I know, and tell that top student to cover up his or her answers so others don’t cheat, either.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous faites ce qui est juste : vous faites du mieux que vous pouvez avec vos connaissances et vous priez le premier de la classe de couvrir ses réponses pour ne pas tenter d'autres personnes à tricher.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du tust das einzig Richtige: Du vertraust nur deinem eigenen Wissen und sagst dem Streber, er möge seine Antworten zuhalten, damit auch andere nicht schummeln können.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fai la cosa giusta:  Faccio quello che posso con quello che so, e dico al migliore studente di nascondere le sue risposte così gli altri non copiano.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Haces lo correcto: Lo mejor que puedes con lo que sabes, y le dices a ese excelente estudiante que cubra sus respuestas para que otros tampoco se copien.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Do the right thing:  Do the best I can with what I know, and tell that top student to cover up her answers so others don’t cheat, either.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Do the right thing:  Do the best I can with what I know, and tell that top student to cover up her answers so others don’t cheat, either.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Do the right thing:  Do the best I can with what I know, and tell that top student to cover up her answers so others don’t cheat, either.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Do the right thing:  Do the best I can with what I know, and tell that top student to cover up her answers so others don’t cheat, either.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Do the right thing:  Do the best I can with what I know, and tell that top student to cover up her answers so others don’t cheat, either.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Do the right thing:  Do the best I can with what I know, and tell that top student to cover up his or her answers so others don’t cheat, either.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q4a</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Do what I always do: fill in the answers at random and hope for the best.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous faites comme toujours : vous remplissez les réponses au hasard et vous croisez les doigts.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du tust das, was du immer machst: die Antworten zufällig auswählen und auf dein Glück hoffen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Faccio come sempre: rispondo a caso e incrocio le dita.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Haces lo que siempre haces: completas las respuestas al azar y esperas lo mejor.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Do what I always do: fill in the answers at random and hope for the best.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Do what I always do: fill in the answers at random and hope for the best.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Do what I always do: fill in the answers at random and hope for the best.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Do what I always do: fill in the answers at random and hope for the best.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Do what I always do: fill in the answers at random and hope for the best.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Do what I always do: fill in the answers at random and hope for the best.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">doyou</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Do you:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Est-ce que :</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Was willst du tun:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tu:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tú:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Do you:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Do you:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Do you:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Do you:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Do you:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Do you:</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q2b</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Eat veggies until your stomach swells, and leave the technophile with the bill.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous vous empiffrez de légumes jusqu'à en avoir mal au ventre, et vous laissez le/la technophile payer la note.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du isst Gemüse, bis dein Magen voll ist, und überlässt dem Technikfreak die Rechnung.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mangi verdure fino a riempirti la pancia e fai pagare la tecnofila.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Comes vegetales hasta que tu estómago revienta y dejas al tecnófilo para que pague la cuenta.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Eat veggies until your stomach swells, and leave the technophile with the bill.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Eat veggies until your stomach swells, and leave the technophile with the bill.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Eat veggies until your stomach swells, and leave the technophile with the bill.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Eat veggies until your stomach swells, and leave the technophile with the bill.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Eat veggies until your stomach swells, and leave the technophile with the bill.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Eat veggies until your stomach swells, and leave the technophile with the bill.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q9d</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Enter the burning building to save as much of the classics collection as you possibly can.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous entrez dans le bâtiment en feu pour sauver tout ce que vous pouvez dans le rayon des classiques.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du betrittst das brennende Gebäude und versuchst, so viele der Klassiker zu retten, wie du kannst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Entri nell'edificio in fiamme per salvare il più possibile della raccolta di classici.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ingresas al edificio en llamas para salvar lo que puedas de la colección de clásicos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Enter the burning building to save as much of the classics collection as I possibly can.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Enter the burning building to save as much of the classics collection as I possibly can.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Enter the burning building to save as much of the classics collection as I possibly can.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Enter the burning building to save as much of the classics collection as I possibly can.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Enter the burning building to save as much of the classics collection as I possibly can.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Enter the burning building to save as much of the classics collection as you possibly can.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q4e</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Exam? What exam?  I’m listening to the birds singing outside the window.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'examen ? Quel examen ?  Vous écoutez les oiseaux qui chantent dehors.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Examen? Welches Examen?  Du hörst den Vögeln zu, die vor dem Fenster singen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esame? Quale esame?  Sto ascoltando gli uccellini che cantano fuori dalla finestra.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Examen? ¿Qué examen?  Estoy escuchando a las aves que cantan afuera.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Exam? What exam?  I’m listening to the birds singing outside the window.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Exam? What exam?  I’m listening to the birds singing outside the window.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Exam? What exam?  I’m listening to the birds singing outside the window.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Exam? What exam?  I’m listening to the birds singing outside the window.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Exam? What exam?  I’m listening to the birds singing outside the window.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Exam? What exam?  I’m listening to the birds singing outside the window.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q5a</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Feel right at home without all the trappings of modern civilization, and work to minimize your impact on the native ecosystem here in your new home.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous vous sentez à l'aise sans les privilèges de la civilisation moderne, et vous essayez de minimiser votre impact sur l'écosystème local dans votre nouvelle maison.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du fühlst dich ohne den Protz der modernen Gesellschaft viel wohler, und du gibst dir Mühe, möglichst wenig Einwirkung wie möglich auf das Ökosystem deiner neuen Heimat zu haben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ti rilassi nella tua casa senza tutti gli ammenicoli della civiltà moderna e lavori per minimizzare il tuo impatto sull'ecosistema locale nella tua nuova casa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te sientes como en casa sin todas las molestias de la civilización moderna, e intentas minimizar el impacto sobre el ecosistema nativo de tu nuevo hogar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Feel right at home without all the trappings of modern civilization, and work to minimize your impact on the native ecosystem here in your new home.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Feel right at home without all the trappings of modern civilization, and work to minimize your impact on the native ecosystem here in your new home.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Feel right at home without all the trappings of modern civilization, and work to minimize your impact on the native ecosystem here in your new home.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Feel right at home without all the trappings of modern civilization, and work to minimize your impact on the native ecosystem here in your new home.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Feel right at home without all the trappings of modern civilization, and work to minimize your impact on the native ecosystem here in your new home.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Feel right at home without all the trappings of modern civilization, and work to minimize your impact on the native ecosystem here in your new home.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q7c</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fill the container with soil and turn it into a rustic planter for fast-growing fungi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous remplissez le conteneur de terre pour le transformer en champignonnière rustique.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du kippst Muttererde in den Container und benutzt ihn als Pflanzschuppen für schnell wachsende Pilze.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Riempi il magazzino di terriccio e lo trasformi in una rustica serra per funghi a crescita rapida.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Llenas el contenedor con tierra fértil y lo conviertes en una maceta rústica para hongos de crecimiento rápido.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Fill the container with soil and turn it into a rustic planter for fast-growing fungi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Fill the container with soil and turn it into a rustic planter for fast-growing fungi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Fill the container with soil and turn it into a rustic planter for fast-growing fungi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Fill the container with soil and turn it into a rustic planter for fast-growing fungi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Fill the container with soil and turn it into a rustic planter for fast-growing fungi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fill the container with soil and turn it into a rustic planter for fast-growing fungi.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Find out your true colour by answering questions in this multiple choice quiz.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Découvrez votre véritable couleur en répondant à ce questionnaire à choix multiples.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Finde deine wahre Farbe heraus, indem du die Fragen in diesem Quiz beantwortest.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Trova il tuo colore rispondendo alle domande di questo semplice quiz a risposta multipla.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Encuentra tu verdadero color respondiendo las preguntas de este cuestionario.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Find out your true colour by answering questions in this multiple choice quiz.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Find out your true colour by answering questions in this multiple choice quiz.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Find out your true colour by answering questions in this multiple choice quiz.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Find out your true colour by answering questions in this multiple choice quiz.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Find out your true colour by answering questions in this multiple choice quiz.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Find out your true color by answering questions in this multiple choice quiz.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q1e</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Go camping.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous allez camper.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du gehst zelten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vai a campeggiare.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te vas de camping.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Go camping.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Go camping.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Go camping.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Go camping.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Go camping.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Go camping.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q5d</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Go swimming, then eat all the remaining food, then go to sleep; these things always work themselves out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous allez nager, vous mangez toutes les provisions qui restent et vous allez vous coucher. Ces problèmes se résolvent toujours tout seul.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du gehst schwimmen, isst dann das restliche Essen auf und gehst schlafen; solche Sachen klären sich meist von selbst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vai a nuotare, poi mangi tutto il cibo rimasto, poi vai a dormire; queste cose si risolvono sempre da sole.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Vas a nadar, luego comes lo que queda de comida, luego te vas a dormir; estas cosas siempre se solucionan solas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Go swimming, then eat all the remaining food, then go to sleep; these things always work themselves out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Go swimming, then eat all the remaining food, then go to sleep; these things always work themselves out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Go swimming, then eat all the remaining food, then go to sleep; these things always work themselves out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Go swimming, then eat all the remaining food, then go to sleep; these things always work themselves out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Go swimming, then eat all the remaining food, then go to sleep; these things always work themselves out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Go swimming, then eat all the remaining food, then go to sleep; these things always work themselves out.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q8e</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Grab the spouse and get to work on making the next kid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous attrapez votre moitiée et vous commencez un autre enfant.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du schnappst dir deine bessere Hälfte und arbeitest am nächsten Nachwuchs.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prendi tua moglie e ti dai da fare per il prossimo figlio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tomas a tu esposa y te pones a trabajar en hacer un nuevo niño.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Grab the spouse and get to work on making the next kid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Grab the spouse and get to work on making the next kid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Grab the spouse and get to work on making the next kid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Grab the spouse and get to work on making the next kid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Grab the spouse and get to work on making the next kid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Grab the spouse and get to work on making the next kid.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q8c</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Home-school him, giving him access to all the multimedia educational resources available.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous l'éduquez depuis la maison en lui donnant accès à toutes les ressources éducatives multimédia disponibles.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du unterrichtest ihn selbst mit Hilfe aller verfügbaren lehrreichen multimedialen Hilfsmittel.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lo istruisci a casa, dandogli accesso a tutte le risorse educative multimediali a disposizione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Le enseñas en casa, dándole acceso a todos los recursos educacionales multimediáticos disponibles.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Home-school him, giving him access to all the multimedia educational resources available.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Home-school him, giving him access to all the multimedia educational resources available.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Home-school him, giving him access to all the multimedia educational resources available.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Home-school him, giving him access to all the multimedia educational resources available.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Home-school him, giving him access to all the multimedia educational resources available.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Home-school him, giving him access to all the multimedia educational resources available.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q10b</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Honour your community by offering to help the show build an orphanage instead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous honorez votre communauté en proposant à la place d'aider le programme à construire un orphelinat.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du bietest an, stattdessen zur Unterstützung deiner Gemeinde ein Waisenhaus bauen zu lassen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Onori la tua comunità offrendo di aiutare lo show a costruire invece un orfanotrofio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Honras a tu comunidad ofreciéndote a ayudar al show a construir un orfanato en su lugar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Honor your community by offering to help the show build an orphanage instead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Honor your community by offering to help the show build an orphanage instead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Honor your community by offering to help the show build an orphanage instead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Honor your community by offering to help the show build an orphanage instead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Honor your community by offering to help the show build an orphanage instead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Honor your community by offering to help the show build an orphanage instead.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q5b</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, lest the infighting devolve into chaos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous organisez immédiatement un système de rationnement pour les survivants afin d'éviter que la situation ne dégénère.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du kümmerst dich sofort um eine Hackordnung unter den Überlebenden, damit aus dem Gerangel kein Chaos wird.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stabilisci subito una gerarchia tra i sopravvissuti, per evitare che le lotte interne creino il caos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Inmediatamente estableces un orden jerárquico entre los sobrevivientes, o de lo contrario las luchas internas se convertirán en un caos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, lest the infighting devolve into chaos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, lest the infighting devolve into chaos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, lest the infighting devolve into chaos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, lest the infighting devolve into chaos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, lest the infighting devolve into chaos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, lest the infighting devolve into chaos.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q5c</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, so that you can play them against one another and reap the benefits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous organisez immédiatement un système de rationnement injuste pour les survivants afin de les monter les uns contre les autres et d'en récolter les bénéfices.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du kümmerst dich sofort um eine Hackordnung unter den Überlebenden, damit du sie gegeneinander ausspielen und davon profitieren kannst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stabilisci subito una gerarchia tra i sopravvissuti, per poterli mettere uno contro l'altro e trarne beneficio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Inmediatamente estableces un orden jerárquico entre los sobrevivientes, para poder enfrentarlos entre ellos y beneficiarte de eso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, so that you can play them against one another and reap the benefits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, so that you can play them against one another and reap the benefits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, so that you can play them against one another and reap the benefits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, so that you can play them against one another and reap the benefits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, so that you can play them against one another and reap the benefits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Immediately establish a pecking order among the survivors, so that you can play them against one another and reap the benefits.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q8a</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Let the kid raise himself—a couple of hard knocks are good for character.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous laissez le gamin se débrouiller tout seul — les échecs, ça forme le caractère.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Kind kann alleine groß werden – ein paar Schläge auf den Hinterkopf sollen ganz gut wirken.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lasci che il bambino si alzi da solo... un paio di botte temprano il carattere.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dejas que el chico crezca solo, un par de golpes le ayudarán a formar su personalidad.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Let the kid raise himself—a couple of hard knocks are good for character.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Let the kid raise himself—a couple of hard knocks are good for character.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Let the kid raise himself—a couple of hard knocks are good for character.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Let the kid raise himself—a couple of hard knocks are good for character.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Let the kid raise himself—a couple of hard knocks are good for character.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Let the kid raise himself—a couple of hard knocks are good for character.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q6a</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Make sure the developer’s permits check out and that all his or her taxes are paid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous vous assurez que les permis du promoteur sont en règle et qu'il a payé toutes ses taxes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du überprüfst, ob die Genehmigungen des Bauherren alle gültig sind und ob er seine Steuern bezahlt hat.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Controlli che i permessi dell'impresario siano a posto e che abbia pagato tutte le tasse.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te aseguras que los permisos del constructor están en regla y que todos sus impuestos están pagados.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Make sure the developer’s permits check out and all his taxes are paid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Make sure the developer’s permits check out and all his taxes are paid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Make sure the developer’s permits check out and all his taxes are paid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Make sure the developer’s permits check out and all his taxes are paid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Make sure the developer’s permits check out and all his taxes are paid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Make sure the developer’s permits check out and that all his or her taxes are paid.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q9e</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Make sure to hide the accelerants before anyone catches you.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous cachez bien les combustibles avant d'être pris sur le fait.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du versteckst die Brandbeschleuniger, bevor dich jemand sehen kann.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ti assicuri di nascondere il combustibile prima che qualcuno ti scopra.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te aseguras de esconder el combustible antes de que alguien te atrape.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Make sure to hide the accelerants before anyone catches me.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Make sure to hide the accelerants before anyone catches me.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Make sure to hide the accelerants before anyone catches me.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Make sure to hide the accelerants before anyone catches me.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Make sure to hide the accelerants before anyone catches me.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Make sure to hide the accelerants before anyone catches you.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">flavour_black</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana’s specialty. Black mana comes from the swamps.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le mana est l'énergie qui alimente toute forme de magie. Le mana provient de la terre. Le mana noir corrompt et domine. Les créatures telles que les démons et les morts-vivants sont la spécialité du mana noir. Le mana noir vient des marais.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mana ist die Energie, die hinter aller Magie steckt. Mana kommt aus dem Land. Schwarzes Mana korrumpiert und beherrscht. Untote Kreaturen und Dämonen sind ohne schwarzes Mana kaum denkbar. Schwarzes Mana kommt aus den Sümpfen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mana è l'energia attraverso la quale è possibile compiere qualsiasi magia. Il mana proviene dalla terra. Il mana nero corrompe e comanda. La specialità delle magie nere è l'evocazione di creature come demoni e non morti. Il mana nero proviene dalle pal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El maná es la energía que potencia toda la magia. El maná proviene de la tierra. El maná negro corrompe y domina. Las criaturas como los demonios y los muertos vivientes son la especialidad del maná negro. El maná negro proviene de los pantanos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana’s speciality. Black mana comes from the swamps.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana’s speciality. Black mana comes from the swamps.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana’s speciality. Black mana comes from the swamps.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana’s speciality. Black mana comes from the swamps.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana’s speciality. Black mana comes from the swamps.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana’s specialty. Black mana comes from the swamps.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">flavour_blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le mana est l'énergie qui alimente toute forme de magie. Le mana provient de la terre. Le mana bleu contrôle et trompe. C'est la magie de l'esprit, du vent et des vagues. Le mana bleu coule des îles.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mana ist die Energie, die hinter aller Magie steckt. Mana kommt aus dem Land. Blaues Mana kontrolliert und betrügt. Dies ist die Magie des Verstandes, des Windes und der Wellen. Blaues Mana kommt aus den Inseln.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mana è l'energia attraverso la quale è possibile compiere qualsiasi magia. Il mana proviene dalla terra. Il mana blu manipola e inganna. Questa è la magia della mente, del vento e delle onde. Il mana blu proviene dalle isole.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El maná es la energía que potencia toda la magia. El maná proviene de la tierra. El maná azul controla y engaña. Ésta es magia de la mente, el viento y las olas. El maná azul proviende de las islas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">flavour_green</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le mana est l'énergie qui alimente toute forme de magie. Le mana provient de la terre. Le mana vert est la magie de la croissance et de la force. Elle est régie par la loi du plus fort, et les magiciens verts manipulent la force et la férocité de la vie.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mana ist die Energie, die hinter aller Magie steckt. Mana kommt aus dem Land. Grünes Mana bedeutet Wachstum und Stärke. Nur die Starken überleben, und in grünen Magiern fließt die Stärke von Leben und Wildheit. Grünes Mana kommt aus den Wäldern.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mana è l'energia attraverso la quale è possibile compiere qualsiasi magia. Il mana proviene dalla terra. Il mana verde si specializza nella crescita e nella forza bruta. Solo il più forte sopravvive e i maghi verdi impugnano la forza della vita e della</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El maná es la energía que potencia toda la magia. El maná proviene de la tierra. El maná verde se basa en el crecimiento y la fuerza. Sólo el más fuerte sobrevive, y los magos verde esgrimen la fuerza y ferocidad de la vida. El maná verde proviene de los</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">flavour_red</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this colour of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le mana est l'énergie qui alimente toute forme de magie. Le mana provient de la terre. Le mana rouge consume ses ennemis. Le feu et la destruction dominent cette couleur de magie. Les dragons en sont l'incarnation la plus pure. Le mana rouge provient des</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mana ist die Energie, die hinter aller Magie steckt. Mana kommt aus dem Land. Rotes Mana verbrennt seine Gegner. Feuer und Zerstörung sind die Kennzeichen dieser Farbe. Drachen sind die perfekte Verkörperung dessen. Rotes Mana kommt aus den Bergen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mana è l'energia attraverso la quale è possibile compiere qualsiasi magia. Il mana proviene dalla terra. Il mana rosso incenerisce qualsiasi avversario. Il fuoco e la distruzione dominano le magie di questo colore. I draghi rappresentano la sua incarna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El maná es la energía que potencia toda la magia. El maná proviene de la tierra. El maná rojo quema a sus oponentes. El fuego y la destrucción dominan este color de magia. Los dragones son su forma más pura. El maná rojo proviene de las montañas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this color of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this color of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this color of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this color of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this color of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this color of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">flavour_white</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. White mana lays down the law. It’s about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le mana est l'énergie qui alimente toute forme de magie. Le mana provient de la terre. Le mana blanc détermine les lois. Il se spécialise dans la protection, la lumière, les armées de soldats et les escadrilles d'anges. Le mana blanc provient des plaines.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mana ist die Energie, die hinter aller Magie steckt. Mana kommt aus dem Land. Weißes Mana kümmert sich um Recht und Ordnung. Du brauchst es für Schutz, Licht, Soldaten-Armeen und Engel-Geschwader. Weißes Mana kommt aus den Ebenen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mana è l'energia attraverso la quale è possibile compiere qualsiasi magia. Il mana proviene dalla terra. Il mana bianco amministra la legge. I suoi punti di forza sono luce e protezione, armate di soldati e schiere di angeli. Il mana bianco proviene da</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El maná es la energía que potencia toda la magia. El maná proviene de la tierra. El maná blanco dicta la ley. Trata de la protección, la luz, ejércitos de soldados y ángeles. El maná blanco proviene de las llanuras.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. White mana lays down the law. It’s about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. White mana lays down the law. It’s about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. White mana lays down the law. It’s about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. White mana lays down the law. It’s about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. White mana lays down the law. It’s about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mana is the energy that powers all magic. Mana comes from the land. White mana lays down the law. It’s about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q7b</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Open the container on a whim, hoping to find someone’s stash of illegal fireworks to shoot off.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous ouvrez le container sur un coup de tête, espérant y trouver une réserve illégale de feux d'artifice.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du öffnest den Behälter aus einer Laune heraus  und hoffst, darin Feuerwerk zu finden, das du verballern kannst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Apri il magazzino per capriccio, sperando di trovare la scorta di qualcuno di fuochi d'artificio illegali da sparare in aria.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Abres el contenedor deprisa, esperando encontrar un montón de pirotecnia ilegal que poder encender.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Open the container on a whim, hoping to find some guy’s stash of illegal fireworks to shoot off.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Open the container on a whim, hoping to find some guy’s stash of illegal fireworks to shoot off.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Open the container on a whim, hoping to find some guy’s stash of illegal fireworks to shoot off.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Open the container on a whim, hoping to find some guy’s stash of illegal fireworks to shoot off.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Open the container on a whim, hoping to find some guy’s stash of illegal fireworks to shoot off.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Open the container on a whim, hoping to find someone’s stash of illegal fireworks to shoot off.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q7a</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Open the container with great curiosity, hoping to learn the secrets of this mysterious cache.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La curiosité vous pousse à ouvrir le container, espérant découvrir les secrets de cette cache mystérieuse.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du öffnest den Behälter aus Neugier, um herauszufinden, welche Geheimnisse sich darin verbergen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Apri il magazzino per curiosità, sperando di scoprire i segreti di questo misterioso nascondiglio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Abres el contenedor con curiosidad, esperando aprender los secretos de su misterioso contenido.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Open the container with great curiosity, hoping to learn the secrets of this mysterious cache.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Open the container with great curiosity, hoping to learn the secrets of this mysterious cache.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Open the container with great curiosity, hoping to learn the secrets of this mysterious cache.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Open the container with great curiosity, hoping to learn the secrets of this mysterious cache.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Open the container with great curiosity, hoping to learn the secrets of this mysterious cache.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Open the container with great curiosity, hoping to learn the secrets of this mysterious cache.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q2e</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Politely pay for everything and make the best of it for the sake of a peaceful evening.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous payez poliment le repas. Vous ne voulez pas faire un scandale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du bezahlst höflicherweise die Rechnung und versuchst, das Beste draus zu machen, damit es ein friedlicher Abend bleibt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Paghi tutto educatamente e te la godi il più possibile per mantenere una serata pacifica.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cortesmente pagas por todo y haces lo posible para que sea una noche tranquila.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Politely pay for everything and make the best of it for the sake of a peaceful evening.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Politely pay for everything and make the best of it for the sake of a peaceful evening.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Politely pay for everything and make the best of it for the sake of a peaceful evening.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Politely pay for everything and make the best of it for the sake of a peaceful evening.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Politely pay for everything and make the best of it for the sake of a peaceful evening.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Politely pay for everything and make the best of it for the sake of a peaceful evening.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q1b</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Protest the injustice of the situation to a higher authority.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous protestez l'injustice de la situation devant une plus haute autorité.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du protestierst bei seinem Vorgesetzten gegen diese Ungerechtigkeit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Protesti per l'ingiustizia della situazione appellandoti a un'autorità superiore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Protestas por la injusticia de la situación con una autoridad superior.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Protest the injustice of the situation to a higher authority.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Protest the injustice of the situation to a higher authority.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Protest the injustice of the situation to a higher authority.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Protest the injustice of the situation to a higher authority.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Protest the injustice of the situation to a higher authority.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Protest the injustice of the situation to a higher authority.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q10a</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Provide the engineering blueprints for the hovering mastermind’s tower you’ve worked on for so long.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous fournissez les plans techniques du quartier général volant sur lequel vous travaillez depuis si longtemps.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du überreichst ihnen die Baupläne für den schwebenden Turm, an denen du schon so lange gearbeitet hast.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fornisci i progetti della torre sospesa del genio su cui hai lavorato così a lungo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Le das a los ingenieros los planos de la torre flotante en los cuales trabajaste tanto tiempo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Provide the engineering blueprints for the hovering mastermind’s tower you’ve worked on for so long.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Provide the engineering blueprints for the hovering mastermind’s tower you’ve worked on for so long.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Provide the engineering blueprints for the hovering mastermind’s tower you’ve worked on for so long.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Provide the engineering blueprints for the hovering mastermind’s tower you’ve worked on for so long.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Provide the engineering blueprints for the hovering mastermind’s tower you’ve worked on for so long.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Provide the engineering blueprints for the hovering mastermind’s tower you’ve worked on for so long.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q3e</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Puff yourself up as big as you can, unleash a primal roar from deep within your guts, and show that beast that you’re the bigger bear in this territory.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous tâchez de paraître le plus grand possible, vous lancez un cri primal avec la force de vos tripes, et vous montrez à cette bête qui est l'ours dominant du territoire.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du bläst dich so gut auf, wie du kannst, lässt einen Urschrei los und zeigst der Bestie, dass du der größere Bär von euch beiden bist.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ti gonfi il più possibile, lanci un ruggito primordiale a pieni polmoni e mostri a quella bestia che sei l'orso più grande di questo territorio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te inflas lo más que puedes, das un rugido primitivo desde lo profundo de tus entrañas y le muestras a esa bestia que tú eres el oso más grande en este territorio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Puff yourself up as huge as you can, unleash a primal roar from deep within your guts, and show that beast that you’re the bigger bear in this territory.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Puff yourself up as huge as you can, unleash a primal roar from deep within your guts, and show that beast that you’re the bigger bear in this territory.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Puff yourself up as huge as you can, unleash a primal roar from deep within your guts, and show that beast that you’re the bigger bear in this territory.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Puff yourself up as huge as you can, unleash a primal roar from deep within your guts, and show that beast that you’re the bigger bear in this territory.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Puff yourself up as huge as you can, unleash a primal roar from deep within your guts, and show that beast that you’re the bigger bear in this territory.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Puff yourself up as big as you can, unleash a primal roar from deep within your guts, and show that beast that you’re the bigger bear in this territory.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q6c</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Put on face paint, hide in the bushes until the bulldozers come, then defend nature’s lands to the death.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous appliquez vos peintures de guerre, vous vous cachez dans les buissons jusqu'à l'arrivée des bulldozers et  vous défendez Mère Nature jusqu'à la mort.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du bemalst dein Gesicht mit Tarnfarben, versteckst dich im Gebüsch, bis die Bulldozer kommen, und verteidigst dann die Natur bis zum Tod.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ti dipingi la faccia, ti nascondi nei cespugli finché non arrivano le scavatrici, poi difendi fino alla morte le terre della natura.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pintas tu cara, te escondes en los arbustos hasta que llegan las topadoras y defiendes las tierras de la naturaleza hasta la muerte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Put on facepaint, hide in the bushes till the bulldozers come, then defend Nature’s lands to the death.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Put on facepaint, hide in the bushes till the bulldozers come, then defend Nature’s lands to the death.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Put on facepaint, hide in the bushes till the bulldozers come, then defend Nature’s lands to the death.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Put on facepaint, hide in the bushes till the bulldozers come, then defend Nature’s lands to the death.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Put on facepaint, hide in the bushes till the bulldozers come, then defend Nature’s lands to the death.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Put on face paint, hide in the bushes until the bulldozers come, then defend nature’s lands to the death.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Question 1: Your teacher or boss yells at you for something you didn’t do and won’t listen to your excuses.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Question 1 : Votre professeur ou votre patron vous réprimande pour quelque chose que vous n'avez pas fait et il n'écoute pas vos excuses.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Situation 1: Dein Lehrer oder Chef brüllt dich wegen etwas an, an dem du nicht schuld bist, und will auch keine Entschuldigungen hören.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Domanda 1: Il tuo insegnante o capo ti urla dietro per qualcosa che non hai fatto e non vuole sentire da te alcuna scusa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pregunta 1: Tu profesor o jefe te grita por algo que no hiciste y no quiere escuchar tus excusas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Question 1: Your teacher or boss yells at you for something you didn’t do, and won’t hear your excuses.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Question 1: Your teacher or boss yells at you for something you didn’t do, and won’t hear your excuses.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Question 1: Your teacher or boss yells at you for something you didn’t do, and won’t hear your excuses.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Question 1: Your teacher or boss yells at you for something you didn’t do, and won’t hear your excuses.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Question 1: Your teacher or boss yells at you for something you didn’t do, and won’t hear your excuses.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Question 1: Your teacher or boss yells at you for something you didn’t do and won’t listen to your excuses.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q10</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Question 10: A reality show wants to fund the building of your dream house.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Question 10 : Une émission de téléréalité veut financer la construction de la maison de vos rêves.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Situation 10: Eine Fernsehshow will dir das Bauen deines Traumhauses bezahlen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Domanda 10: Un reality vuole finanziare la costruzione della tua casa dei sogni.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pregunta 10: Un reality show quiere financiar la construcción de la casa de tus sueños.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Question 10: A reality show wants to fund the building of your dream house.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Question 10: A reality show wants to fund the building of your dream house.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Question 10: A reality show wants to fund the building of your dream house.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Question 10: A reality show wants to fund the building of your dream house.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Question 10: A reality show wants to fund the building of your dream house.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Question 10: A reality show wants to fund the building of your dream house.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Question 2: You take a date to an expensive dinner, but your date jabbers into the cell phone all night.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Question 2 : Vous invitez quelqu'un à un dîner romantique dans un restaurant chic, mais cette personne passe la soirée pendue à son téléphone portable.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Situation 2: Ihr geht in ein teures Restaurant aus, doch deine neue Bekanntschaft ist den ganzen Abend nur mit dem Mobiltelefon beschäftigt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Domanda 2: Porti fuori a cena una ragazza in un ristorante costoso, ma lei parla al cellulare per tutta la sera.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pregunta 2: Sales a cenar con una cita en un lugar caro, pero tu cita habla por celular toda la noche.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Question 2: You take a date to an expensive dinner, but your date jabbers into the cell phone all night.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Question 2: You take a date to an expensive dinner, but your date jabbers into the cell phone all night.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Question 2: You take a date to an expensive dinner, but your date jabbers into the cell phone all night.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Question 2: You take a date to an expensive dinner, but your date jabbers into the cell phone all night.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Question 2: You take a date to an expensive dinner, but your date jabbers into the cell phone all night.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Question 2: You take a date to an expensive dinner, but your date jabbers into the cell phone all night.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Question 3: While hiking in the woods, your friend is trapped up a tree by an enormous bear.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Question 3 : Pendant une excursion dans les bois, votre ami se retrouve coincé en haut d'un arbre par un énorme ours.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Situation 3: Beim Wandern in den Wäldern wird dein Freund von einem Bär auf einen Baum gejagt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Domanda 3: Durante una gita nei boschi, il tuo amico viene intrappolato su un albero da un orso enorme.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pregunta 3: Mientras están paseando por el bosque, tu amigo es atrapado en un árbol por un oso enorme.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Question 3: While hiking in the woods, your friend is trapped up a tree by an enormous bear.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Question 3: While hiking in the woods, your friend is trapped up a tree by an enormous bear.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Question 3: While hiking in the woods, your friend is trapped up a tree by an enormous bear.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Question 3: While hiking in the woods, your friend is trapped up a tree by an enormous bear.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Question 3: While hiking in the woods, your friend is trapped up a tree by an enormous bear.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Question 3: While hiking in the woods, your friend is trapped up a tree by an enormous bear.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Question 4: You’re taking a final exam that you haven’t studied for. The paper of the top student in class is plainly visible.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Question 4 : Vous passez un examen final pour une matière que vous n'avez pas étudiée. La feuille d'examen du meilleur étudiant de la classe est clairement visible.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Situation 4: Du schreibst eine Abschlussprüfung, für die du nicht gelernt hast. Der Prüfungsbogen des Klassenbesten ist gut einsehbar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Domanda 4: Stai facendo un esame finale per cui non hai studiato. Il foglio del migliore studente della classe è in piena vista.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pregunta 4: Estás haciendo un examen final para el cual no estudiaste. La hoja del mejor estudiante de la clase se ve claramente.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Question 4: You’re taking a final exam that you haven’t studied for. The paper of the top student in class is plainly visible.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Question 4: You’re taking a final exam that you haven’t studied for. The paper of the top student in class is plainly visible.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Question 4: You’re taking a final exam that you haven’t studied for. The paper of the top student in class is plainly visible.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Question 4: You’re taking a final exam that you haven’t studied for. The paper of the top student in class is plainly visible.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Question 4: You’re taking a final exam that you haven’t studied for. The paper of the top student in class is plainly visible.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Question 4: You’re taking a final exam that you haven’t studied for. The paper of the top student in class is plainly visible.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Question 5: You shipwreck on an uninhabited island with a dozen of your fellow passengers.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Question 5 : Vous vous échouez sur une île déserte avec une douzaine d'autres passagers.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Situation 5: Du strandest mit einem Dutzend Mitreisender auf einer einsamen Insel.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Domanda 5: Naufraghi su un'isola disabitata con una dozzina di altri passeggeri.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pregunta 5: Naufragas en una isla desierta con una docena de compañeros de viaje.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Question 5: You shipwreck on a uninhabited island with a dozen of your fellow passengers.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Question 5: You shipwreck on a uninhabited island with a dozen of your fellow passengers.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Question 5: You shipwreck on a uninhabited island with a dozen of your fellow passengers.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Question 5: You shipwreck on a uninhabited island with a dozen of your fellow passengers.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Question 5: You shipwreck on a uninhabited island with a dozen of your fellow passengers.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Question 5: You shipwreck on an uninhabited island with a dozen of your fellow passengers.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Question 6: A real estate developer wants to demolish the local park to put up a strip mall.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Question 6 : Un promoteur immobilier veut détruire le parc du quartier pour construire un centre commercial.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Situation 6: Ein Baulöwe will den Stadtpark mit einer Einkaufsmeile zubetonieren.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Domanda 6: Un impresario edile vuole demolire il parco cittadino per costruire un centro commerciale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pregunta 6: Un constructor quiere demoler el parque local para poner unas tiendas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Question 6: A real estate developer wants to demolish the local park to put up a strip mall.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Question 6: A real estate developer wants to demolish the local park to put up a strip mall.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Question 6: A real estate developer wants to demolish the local park to put up a strip mall.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Question 6: A real estate developer wants to demolish the local park to put up a strip mall.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Question 6: A real estate developer wants to demolish the local park to put up a strip mall.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Question 6: A real estate developer wants to demolish the local park to put up a strip mall.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Question 7: One night at the shipping docks of a port town, you find the keys to a locked storage container.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Question 7 : Une nuit, sur les quais du port, vous trouvez les clés d'un container de stockage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Situation 7: Du findest nachts am Hafen die Schlüssel zu einem Container.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Domanda 7: Una notte sul molo del porto, trovi le chiavi di un magazzino chiuso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pregunta 7: Una noche en los puertos de una ciudad encuentras las llaves de un contenedor cerrado.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Question 7: One night at the shipping docks of a port town, you find the keys to a locked storage container.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Question 7: One night at the shipping docks of a port town, you find the keys to a locked storage container.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Question 7: One night at the shipping docks of a port town, you find the keys to a locked storage container.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Question 7: One night at the shipping docks of a port town, you find the keys to a locked storage container.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Question 7: One night at the shipping docks of a port town, you find the keys to a locked storage container.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Question 7: One night at the shipping docks of a port town, you find the keys to a locked storage container.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Question 8: You are raising your firstborn son.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Question 8 : Vous élevez votre fils aîné.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Situation 8: Du erziehst deinen Erstgeborenen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Domanda 8: Stai crescendo il tuo primo figlio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pregunta 8: Estás educando a tu primer hijo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Question 8: You are raising your firstborn son.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Question 8: You are raising your firstborn son.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Question 8: You are raising your firstborn son.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Question 8: You are raising your firstborn son.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Question 8: You are raising your firstborn son.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Question 8: You are raising your firstborn son.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q9</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Question 9: You’re an eyewitness to arson at the university library.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Question 9 : Vous êtes témoin d'un incendie criminel à la bibliothèque de l'université.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Situation 9: Du bist Augenzeuge, wie jemand die Uni-Bibliothek anzündet.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Domanda 9: Sei un testimone oculare dell'incendio alla biblioteca universitaria.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pregunta 9: Eres testigo de un incendio en la biblioteca de la universidad.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Question 9: You’re an eyewitness to arson at the university library.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Question 9: You’re an eyewitness to arson at the university library.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Question 9: You’re an eyewitness to arson at the university library.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Question 9: You’re an eyewitness to arson at the university library.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Question 9: You’re an eyewitness to arson at the university library.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Question 9: You’re an eyewitness to arson at the university library.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q3b</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Quietly gather any nearby valuables before tiptoeing away.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous rassemblez quelques objets de valeurs et vous vous esquivez en douce.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du sammelst leise alle Wertsachen in der Nähe ein, bevor du dich davonschleichst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Raccogli silenziosamente tutte le cose di valore lì vicino prima di allontanarti in punta di piedi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con cuidado recoges cualquier cosa de valor antes de marcharte silenciosamente.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Quietly gather any nearby valuables before tiptoeing away.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Quietly gather any nearby valuables before tiptoeing away.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Quietly gather any nearby valuables before tiptoeing away.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Quietly gather any nearby valuables before tiptoeing away.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Quietly gather any nearby valuables before tiptoeing away.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Quietly gather any nearby valuables before tiptoeing away.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q7d</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Return the missing keys to the lost and found and alert the local constabulary.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous donnez les clés au bureau des objets trouvés et vous prévenez les autorités.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du gibst die Schlüssel bei der Hafenmeisterei ab und sagst auch bei der Polizei Bescheid.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Riporti le chiavi all'ufficio degli oggetti smarriti e avverti la polizia locale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Devuelves las llaves perdidas al encargado y avisas a las autoridades locales.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Return the missing keys to the lost and found and alert the local constabulary.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Return the missing keys to the lost and found and alert the local constabulary.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Return the missing keys to the lost and found and alert the local constabulary.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Return the missing keys to the lost and found and alert the local constabulary.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Return the missing keys to the lost and found and alert the local constabulary.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Return the missing keys to the lost and found and alert the local constabulary.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q8b</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Send him off to the most prestigious military academy in the country to learn the discipline needed to become a productive member of society.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous l'envoyez dans l'académie militaire la plus prestigieuse du pays pour qu'il apprenne la discipline nécessaire afin de devenir un membre productif de la société.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du schickst ihn auf die ruhmreichste Militärakademie des Landes, damit er die Disziplin lernt, die er benötigt, um ein wertvolles Mitglied der Gesellschaft zu werden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lo spedisci all'accademia militare più prestigiosa della nazione per imparare la disciplina necessaria a diventare un produttivo membro della società.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lo envías a la más prestigiosa academia militar del país para que aprenda la disciplina que necesitará para convertirse en un miembro productivo de la sociedad.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Send him off to the most prestigious military academy in the country, to learn the discipline needed to become a productive member of society.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Send him off to the most prestigious military academy in the country, to learn the discipline needed to become a productive member of society.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Send him off to the most prestigious military academy in the country, to learn the discipline needed to become a productive member of society.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Send him off to the most prestigious military academy in the country, to learn the discipline needed to become a productive member of society.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Send him off to the most prestigious military academy in the country, to learn the discipline needed to become a productive member of society.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Send him off to the most prestigious military academy in the country to learn the discipline needed to become a productive member of society.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q6e</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Smack the developer across the face on principle, just ‘cause they're an uptight pencil pusher in a monkey suit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous giflez le promoteur pour le principe. Après tout, ce n'est qu'un petit gratte-papier sans importance.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du verprügelst den Baulöwen rein aus Prinzip, weil er ein Ausbeuterschwein im Nadelstreifenanzug ist.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prendi a schiaffi l'impresario per principio, solo perché è un impiegatuccio ingessato in giacca e cravatta.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Golpeas al constructor en la cara por principios, sólo porque son unos masca-lápices en traje de mono.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Smack the dude across the face on principle, just ‘cause he’s an uptight guy in a monkey suit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Smack the dude across the face on principle, just ‘cause he’s an uptight guy in a monkey suit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Smack the dude across the face on principle, just ‘cause he’s an uptight guy in a monkey suit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Smack the dude across the face on principle, just ‘cause he’s an uptight guy in a monkey suit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Smack the dude across the face on principle, just ‘cause he’s an uptight guy in a monkey suit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Smack the developer across the face on principle, just ‘cause they're an uptight pencil pusher in a monkey suit.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q2d</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Spontaneously hook up with the host of the restaurant, and spare not another thought to the “date.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous entamez la discussion avec la serveuse du restaurant et vous oubliez totalement votre « rendez-vous ».</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du amüsierst dich den ganzen Abend mit der Bedienung und lässt deine Bekanntschaft links liegen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fai subito un gancio alla cameriera e non rivolgi più neanche uno sguardo alla “ragazza”.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Espontáneamente te enganchas con una mesera y no vuelves a pensar en esa “cita”.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Spontaneously hook up with the host of the restaurant, and spare not another thought to the “date.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Spontaneously hook up with the host of the restaurant, and spare not another thought to the “date.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Spontaneously hook up with the host of the restaurant, and spare not another thought to the “date.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Spontaneously hook up with the host of the restaurant, and spare not another thought to the “date.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Spontaneously hook up with the host of the restaurant, and spare not another thought to the “date.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Spontaneously hook up with the host of the restaurant, and spare not another thought to the “date.”</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q6d</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Suggest to the developer that he or she could make even more money with a little deal on the side.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous suggérez au promoteur qu'il pourrait gagner encore plus d'argent en faisant un deal avec vous.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du gibst dem Baulöwen einen Tipp, wie er mit einem kleinen Nebengeschäft noch mehr verdienen könnte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Suggerisci all'impresario che può fare ancora più soldi con un piccolo affare sottobanco.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sugieres al constructor que podría hacer algo de dinero adicional con un pequeño "arreglito".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Suggest to the developer that he could make even more money with a little deal on the side.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Suggest to the developer that he could make even more money with a little deal on the side.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Suggest to the developer that he could make even more money with a little deal on the side.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Suggest to the developer that he could make even more money with a little deal on the side.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Suggest to the developer that he could make even more money with a little deal on the side.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Suggest to the developer that he or she could make even more money with a little deal on the side.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q4b</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take the short-cut to the top—copy down that sucker’s answers and cruise to an easy A.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous prenez le raccourci vers la victoire — vous copiez les réponses de cet imbécile pour vous assurer une note avec mention.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du nimmst den schnellen Weg zur Spitze: Du schreibst die Antworten des Strebers schnell ab und sicherst dir die Bestnote.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prendi una scorciatoia: copi le risposte di quel babbeo per guadagnarti un facile 10.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tomas el atajo hasta la cima: copias las respuestas de ese tonto y te aseguras una buena nota.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Take the short-cut to the top—copy down that sucker’s answers and cruise to an easy A.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Take the short-cut to the top—copy down that sucker’s answers and cruise to an easy A.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Take the short-cut to the top—copy down that sucker’s answers and cruise to an easy A.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Take the short-cut to the top—copy down that sucker’s answers and cruise to an easy A.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Take the short-cut to the top—copy down that sucker’s answers and cruise to an easy A.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Take the short-cut to the top—copy down that sucker’s answers and cruise to an easy A.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q1c</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Throw a raging tantrum, probably destroying something of value in the process.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous vous mettez en colère et vous en profitez pour détruire quelque objet de valeur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du bekommst einen Wutanfall, in dessen Verlauf wahrscheinlich etwas Wertvolles kaputt gehen wird.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fai una scenata pazzesca, magari distruggendo nel mentre qualcosa di valore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Entras en un ataque de ira, probablemente destruyendo algo valioso en el proceso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Throw a raging tantrum, probably destroying something of value in the process.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Throw a raging tantrum, probably destroying something of value in the process.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Throw a raging tantrum, probably destroying something of value in the process.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Throw a raging tantrum, probably destroying something of value in the process.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Throw a raging tantrum, probably destroying something of value in the process.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Throw a raging tantrum, probably destroying something of value in the process.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q3c</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Throw caution to the wind, roll up your sleeves, and wrestle that bear till it whines for its mummy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous perdez tout sens commun, vous retroussez vos manches et vous luttez avec cet ours jusqu'à ce qu'il appelle sa maman.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du kennst keine Vorsicht, krempelst die Ärmel hoch und ringst mit dem Bären, bis er nach seiner Mami schreit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dimentichi ogni prudenza, ti rimbocchi le maniche e picchi quell'orso finché non implora pietà.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pegas un grito, te arremangas y luchas con el oso hasta que llame llorando a su mami.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Throw caution to the wind, roll up your sleeves and wrassle that bear till he whines for his mommy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Throw caution to the wind, roll up your sleeves and wrassle that bear till he whines for his mommy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Throw caution to the wind, roll up your sleeves and wrassle that bear till he whines for his mommy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Throw caution to the wind, roll up your sleeves and wrassle that bear till he whines for his mommy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Throw caution to the wind, roll up your sleeves and wrassle that bear till he whines for his mommy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Throw caution to the wind, roll up your sleeves, and wrassle that bear till it whines for its mommy.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">To exit, press [CROSS]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour quitter, appuyez sur [CROSS]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücke [CROSS] zum Aufhören</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per uscire, premi [CROSS]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Para salir, presiona [CROSS]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  To exit, press [CROSS]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  To exit, press [CROSS]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG To exit, press [CROSS]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK To exit, press [CROSS]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  To exit, press [CROSS]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">To exit, press [CROSS]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q8d</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Train your tiny-brained minion well, so when the time is right, he’ll be ready to rule the empire at your side.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous éduquez bien votre stupide serviteur. Quand le temps sera venu, il sera prêt pour régner sur l'empire à vos côtés.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du trainierst deinen Winzling gut, damit er zu gegebener Zeit an deiner Seite über das Reich herrschen kann.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Addestri bene il tuo tirapiedi dal cervello minuscolo, così che al momento giusto, sarà pronto per comandare l'impero al tuo fianco.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Entrenas bien a tu pequeño sicario, para que cuando sea el momento correcto, esté listo para dirigir el imperio a tu lado.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Train your tiny-brained minion well, so when the time is right, he’ll be ready to rule the empire at your side.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Train your tiny-brained minion well, so when the time is right, he’ll be ready to rule the empire at your side.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Train your tiny-brained minion well, so when the time is right, he’ll be ready to rule the empire at your side.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Train your tiny-brained minion well, so when the time is right, he’ll be ready to rule the empire at your side.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Train your tiny-brained minion well, so when the time is right, he’ll be ready to rule the empire at your side.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Train your tiny-brained minion well, so when the time is right, he’ll be ready to rule the empire at your side.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q2c</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Trick your date into getting off the phone, then use your knowledge of cell phone towers to prevent further calls.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous vous débrouillez pour interrompre la conversation téléphonique, puis vous utilisez votre connaissance des téléphones portables pour prévenir d'autres appels.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du unterbrichst kurz das Telefonat und verhinderst dann mit deinem Wissen über Mobiltelefonsendemasten weitere Anrufe.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Interrompi la telefonata della ragazza con un trucco, poi usi le tue conoscenze di telefonia per prevenire altre chiamate.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Engañas a tu cita para que deje el teléfono, y luego usas tu conocimiento de tecnología celular para evitar más llamadas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Trick your date into getting off the phone, then use your knowledge of cell phone towers to prevent further calls.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Trick your date into getting off the phone, then use your knowledge of cell phone towers to prevent further calls.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Trick your date into getting off the phone, then use your knowledge of cell phone towers to prevent further calls.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Trick your date into getting off the phone, then use your knowledge of cell phone towers to prevent further calls.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Trick your date into getting off the phone, then use your knowledge of cell phone towers to prevent further calls.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Trick your date into getting off the phone, then use your knowledge of cell phone towers to prevent further calls.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q4c</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Um, hello, I’m the top student in class, and of course I studied.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Heu, c'est moi le meilleur de la classe, bien sûr que j'ai étudié.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wie bitte?  Ich bin der Klassenbeste, und natürlich habe ich gelernt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Beh, ecco, Io sono il migliore studente della classe e naturalmente ho studiato.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Perdón? Yo soy el mejor estudiante de la clase, y  por supuesto que estudié.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Um, hello, I’m the top student in class, and of course I studied.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Um, hello, I’m the top student in class, and of course I studied.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Um, hello, I’m the top student in class, and of course I studied.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Um, hello, I’m the top student in class, and of course I studied.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Um, hello, I’m the top student in class, and of course I studied.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Um, hello, I’m the top student in class, and of course I studied.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q3a</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Valiantly draw the bear’s attention to yourself so your friend can escape.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous attirez vaillamment l'attention de l'ours pour permettre à votre ami de déguerpir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du ziehst tapfer die Aufmerksamkeit des Bären auf dich, so dass dein Freund flüchten kann.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Con coraggio attiri l'attenzione dell'orso perché il tuo amico possa scappare.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Valientemente llamas la atención del oso para que tu amigo pueda escapar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Valiantly draw the bear’s attention to yourself so your friend can escape.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Valiantly draw the bear’s attention to yourself so your friend can escape.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Valiantly draw the bear’s attention to yourself so your friend can escape.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Valiantly draw the bear’s attention to yourself so your friend can escape.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Valiantly draw the bear’s attention to yourself so your friend can escape.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Valiantly draw the bear’s attention to yourself so your friend can escape.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q1a</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous jurez la perte et la souffrance éternelle de cet imbécile.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du gelobst, den Niedergang und das Leiden dieses Dummkopfs herbeizuführen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prometti rovina e atroci sofferenze a questo sempliciotto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Juras que el culpable sufrirá una caída memorable.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">q2a</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous jurez la perte et la souffrance éternelle de cet imbécile.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du gelobst, den Niedergang und das Leiden dieses Dummkopfs herbeizuführen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prometti rovina e atroci sofferenze a questa sempliciotta.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Juras que el culpable sufrirá una caída memorable.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Vow the downfall and suffering of this simpleton.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">What Mana Colour Are You? Game</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jeu Quelle est votre couleur de mana ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Was ist deine Manafarbe? Spiel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Qual è il Tuo Colore di Mana? Partita</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Qué color de maná eres? Juego</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  What Mana Colour Are You? Game</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  What Mana Colour Are You? Game</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  What Mana Colour Are You? Game</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  What Mana Colour Are You? Game</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  What Mana Colour Are You? Game</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">What Mana Color Are You? Game</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">complete</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">What Mana Colour Are You?\nGame Complete!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">\nJeu Quelle est votre couleur de mana ? terminé !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Was ist deine Manafarbe?\nSpiel geschafft!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Qual è il Tuo Colore di Mana?\nPartita Completata!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Qué color de maná eres?\n¡Juego terminado!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  What Mana Colour Are You?\nGame Complete!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  What Mana Colour Are You?\nGame Complete!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  What Mana Colour Are You?\nGame Complete!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  What Mana Colour Are You?\nGame Complete!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  What Mana Colour Are You?\nGame Complete!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">What Mana Color Are You?\nGame Complete!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">won_black</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You won a black mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez gagné un t-shirt mana noir !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast ein „schwarzes Mana“-T-Shirt gewonnen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai vinto una T-shirt di mana nero!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Te ganaste una camiseta de maná negro!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  You won a black mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  You won a black mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  You won a black mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  You won a black mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  You won a black mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You won a black mana T-shirt!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">won_blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You won a blue mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez gagné un t-shirt mana bleu !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast ein „blaues Mana“-T-Shirt gewonnen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai vinto una T-shirt di mana blu!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Te ganaste una camiseta de maná azul!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  You won a blue mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  You won a blue mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  You won a blue mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  You won a blue mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  You won a blue mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You won a blue mana T-shirt!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">won_green</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You won a green mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez gagné un t-shirt mana vert !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast ein „grünes Mana“-T-Shirt gewonnen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai vinto una T-shirt di mana verde!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Te ganaste una camiseta de maná verde!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  You won a green mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  You won a green mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  You won a green mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  You won a green mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  You won a green mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You won a green mana T-shirt!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">won_red</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You won a red mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez gagné un t-shirt mana rouge !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast ein „rotes Mana“-T-Shirt gewonnen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai vinto una T-shirt di mana rosso!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Te ganaste una camiseta de maná rojo!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  You won a red mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  You won a red mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  You won a red mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  You won a red mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  You won a red mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You won a red mana T-shirt!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">won_white</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You won a white mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez gagné un t-shirt mana blanc !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast ein „weißes Mana“-T-Shirt gewonnen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai vinto una T-shirt di mana bianco!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Te ganaste una camiseta de maná blanco!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  You won a white mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  You won a white mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  You won a white mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  You won a white mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  You won a white mana T-shirt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You won a white mana T-shirt!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">end_black</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Your mana colour is black.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Votre couleur de mana est le noir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Deine Manafarbe ist Schwarz.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il tuo colore di mana è il nero.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tu color de maná es negro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Your mana colour is Black</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Your mana colour is Black</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Your mana colour is Black</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Your mana colour is Black</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Your mana colour is Black</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Your mana color is black.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">end_blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Your mana colour is blue.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Votre couleur de mana est le bleu.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Deine Manafarbe ist Blau.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il tuo colore di mana è il blu.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tu color de maná es azul.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Your mana colour is Blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Your mana colour is Blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Your mana colour is Blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Your mana colour is Blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Your mana colour is Blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Your mana color is blue.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">end_green</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Your mana colour is green.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Votre couleur de mana est le vert.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Deine Manafarbe ist Grün.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il tuo colore di mana è il verde.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tu color de maná es verde.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Your mana colour is Green</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Your mana colour is Green</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Your mana colour is Green</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Your mana colour is Green</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Your mana colour is Green</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Your mana color is green.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">end_red</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Your mana colour is red.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Votre couleur de mana est le rouge.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Deine Manafarbe ist Rot.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il tuo colore di mana è il rosso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tu color de maná es rojo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Your mana colour is Red</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Your mana colour is Red</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Your mana colour is Red</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Your mana colour is Red</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Your mana colour is Red</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Your mana color is red.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">end_white</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Your mana colour is white.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Votre couleur de mana est le blanc.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Deine Manafarbe ist Weiß.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il tuo colore di mana è il bianco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tu color de maná es blanco.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Your mana colour is White</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Your mana colour is White</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Your mana colour is White</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Your mana colour is White</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Your mana colour is White</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Your mana color is white.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>