<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fancy Furniture Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Paquet de meubles de fantaisie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Paket der Phantasie Möbel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto di mobili fantasia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de muebles de lujo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ファンシー家具のパッケージ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이쁜 가구 패키지</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Fancy Furniture Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">包装花哨的家具</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">包装花哨的家具</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fancy Furniture Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Finely crafted furnishings. Includes Craftsman Bench, Shield Dining Chair, Craftsman Stool, Golden Chest, Craftsman Chair, Apothecary Chest, and Fancy Circular Table.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Finement ouvragé mobilier. Comprend Banc artisan, Salle à manger chaise bouclier, Selles artisan, Coffre d'or, Chaise artisan, Coffre apothicaire, et Fantaisie tableau circulaire.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fein gearbeitete Möbel. Beinhaltet Handwerker Bank, Esszimmerstuhl Schild, Hocker Handwerker, Gold-Truhe, Lehrstuhl für Handwerker, Apotheker Brust, und Phantasie runden Tisch.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mobili finemente lavorati. Include Artigiano panchina, Sedia da pranzo scudo, Sgabello artigiano, Oro al petto, Artigiano sedia, Petto speziale, e Fancy tavolo circolare.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Finamente diseñado muebles. Incluye Banco de artesano, Comedor escudo silla, Taburete artesano, Oro en el pecho, Silla artesano, El pecho Boticario, y Mesa redonda de lujo.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">細かく家具に細工された。職人ベンチ、シールドダイニングチェア、クラフツマンスツール、ゴールデンチェスト、職人の椅子、薬剤師胸、ファンシー円形のテーブルが含まれています。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">잘게 가구를 제작. 장인 교체 멤버, 쉴드 다이닝 의자, 장인 의자, 골든 가슴, 장인 위원장, 약종상 가슴, 그리고 팬시 원형 테이블을 포함합니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Finely crafted furnishings. Includes Craftsman Bench, Shield Dining Chair, Craftsman Stool, Golden Chest, Craftsman Chair, Apothecary Chest, and Fancy Circular Table.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">精雕细琢的家具。包括盾技工台，餐椅，技工凳，黄金胸部，技工主席，药剂师胸部，和花式圆桌。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">精雕细琢的家具。包括盾技工台，餐椅，技工凳，黄金胸部，技工主席，药剂师胸部，和花式圆桌。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Finely crafted furnishings. Includes Craftsman Bench, Shield Dining Chair, Craftsman Stool, Golden Chest, Craftsman Chair, Apothecary Chest, and Fancy Circular Table.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>