<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Raven Light Fixture</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Luminaire Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Raven-Lampe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lampada Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lámpara de Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">照明器具 レーヴン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Raven 램프</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Raven Light Fixture</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raven燈具</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raven燈具</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Raven Light Fixture</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This multi-directional, 750w halogen Raven lamp is portable, powerful and perfect for parties ... or for setting up defensive perimeters around your apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette lampe halogène multidirectionnelle de 750 W, portable et puissante est idéale pour vos soirées. Ou pour établir un périmètre défensif autour de votre appartement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese allseitig bewegliche 750-Watt-Halogenlampe von Raven ist tragbar, technisch ausgereift und toll für jede Party ... oder für die Abwehrstellungen um Ihr Apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa lampada alogena multidirezionale a 750 watt della Raven è portatile, potente e perfetta per l'intera squadra e anche per stabilire un perimetro difensivo intorno al proprio appartamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta lámpara halógena multidireccional de 750 W de Raven es potente, portátil y perfecta para las fiestas, o para establecer perímetros defensivos alrededor del apartamento.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この一方向ハロゲン750wランプは非常に明るく、携帯も可能。パーティーにも最適だが、防衛線を敷くにも最適だ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">750w 다방향 할로겐 램프입니다. Raven 답게 휴대성이 높고, 강력하며, 파티의 멋진 추가품입니다. 물론 아파트 주위에 방어선을 설치하는 데도 유용합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This multi-directional, 750w halogen Raven lamp is portable, powerful and perfect for parties. Or setting up defensive perimeters around your apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raven這款多向式750w鹵素燈，攜帶方便、效能強大，在派對時尤為實用。你也使用此燈設定住所的防衛周界。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raven這款多向式750w鹵素燈，攜帶方便、效能強大，在派對時尤為實用。你也使用此燈設定住所的防衛周界。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This multi-directional, 750w halogen Raven lamp is portable, powerful and perfect for parties. Or setting up defensive perimeters around your apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>