<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ghostbusters ™ Computer Console 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble informatique 1 S.O.S. Fantômes ™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ghostbusters ™ Computer-Konsole 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Console per Computer 1 Ghostbusters™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Consola ordenador 1 Cazafantasmas™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴーストバスターズ™ コンピューター機器1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ghostbusters ™ Computer Console 1</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Your very own Ghostbusters™ inspired Mad Scientist set decoration piece! We know. We shouldn’t have.  But now you can finally invent the perfectly weighted twenty-sided die! Mwahahaha! Check out the Mad Scientist Starter Kit for an exclusive item!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un élément de décoration de plateau Savant Fou inspiré de S.O.S. Fantômes™, rien que pour vous ! On sait. On n'aurait pas dû.  Vous pouvez enfin inventer un dé à vingt faces parfaitement lesté ! Muahahaha ! Allez voir le kit du débutant Savant Fou pour découvrir l'élément exclusif !  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dein eigenes, von Ghostbusters™ inspiriertes Dekorationsstück für den Verrückten Wissenschaftler! Wissen wir. Das wäre doch nicht nötig gewesen. Aber jetzt kannst du endlich die perfekt ausbalancierte zwanzigseitige Farbe entwickeln! Bruhahahah! Einen exklusiven Artikel findet ihr im Verrückter Wissenschaftler Anfängerset!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il tuo personale elemento decorativo da Scienziato Pazzo ispirato a Ghostbusters™! Lo sappiamo. Non avremmo dovuto. Ora puoi finalmente inventare un dado a 20 facce ben equilibrato! Ah, ah, ah! Trova un elemento esclusivo nel Kit Iniziale dello Scienziato Pazzo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Tu propio conjunto decorativo de Científico Loco inspirado en Cazafantasmas™! Lo sabemos. No deberíamos. ¡Pero por fin puedes inventar la muerte perfectamente equilibrada de veinte caras! ¡Anda que no! ¡Busca el juego de iniciación de Científico Loco para conseguir un producto exclusivo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴーストバスターズ™をイメージしたマッドサイエンティストセットのデコレーションピース！!ここまで豪華にする必要もなかったかなぁ。今なら完璧な20面サイコロを発明することができる！ムハハハハ！限定アイテムのマッドサイエンティスト スターターキットをチェック！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Your very own Ghostbusters™ inspired Mad Scientist set decoration piece! We know. We shouldn’t have.  But now you can finally invent the perfectly weighted twenty-sided die! Mwahahaha! Check out the Mad Scientist Starter Kit for an exclusive item!  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>