<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Animated black sneakers (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Baskets noires animées (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Animierte Turnschuhe (Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tennis	animate (per le donne)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Zapatillas animadas (para las mujeres)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Animated black sneakers (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Animated black sneakers (Women)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Those timeless casual sneakers will look good on any occasion. They also have a futuristic twist: a pulsating neon streak in the sole cycles through all colours. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ces baskets indémodables sont toujours du meilleur effet avec une tenue décontractée. Elles ont aussi une touche futuriste: la semelle contient une bande lumineuse qui varie en intensité et change de couleur.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese beiläufige Turnschuhe aussehen wird in jeder Gelegenheit gut. Eine sich ständig verändernde pulsierenden Neon-Licht ist in den Sohlen eingebettet unterschiedlicher Intensität, als auch sanft durch alle Farben des Regenbogens geht.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quelle scarpe da tennis casuali che starà bene in qualsiasi occasione. Cambiamenti di luce è incorporato nella suola, più o meno intenso, passa lentamente attraverso tutti i colori dell'arcobaleno.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esas zapatillas ocasionales va a quedar bien en cualquier ocasión. Una futurista luz cambiante en la planta del pie, que varían en intensidad, pasa lentamente a través de todos los colores del arco iris.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Those timeless casual sneakers will look good on any occasion. They also have a futuristic twist: a pulsating neon streak in the sole cycles through all colours. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Those timeless casual sneakers will look good on any occasion. They also have a futuristic twist: a pulsating neon streak in the sole cycles through all colours. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>