<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">20 pairs of sneakers bundle(Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bundle de 20 paires de baskets (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">20 Turnschuhe (Männer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">20 Tennis (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">20 Zapatillas (hombres)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">20 pairs of sneakers bundle(Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">20 pairs of sneakers bundle(Men)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This bundle for men contains exclusive animated sneakers, with a pulsating neon streak in the sole cycling through all colours. The other 19 sneakers are: pirate, khaki, bat, grey tartan, sand, grey, black leather, black, white, brown, US flag, union jack, black crocodile, camo, army, red, navy blue, studded grey and grey pattern sneakers. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce bundle pour homme contient des baskets animées exclusives, dont la semelle contient une bande lumineuse qui varie en intensité et change de couleur. Les 19 autres paires de baskets sont les suivantes: baskets de pirate, kaki, chauve-souris, à carreaux grises, sable, grises, cuir noir, noires, blanches, brunes, drapeau américain, drapeau britannique, croco noir, camouflage, militaires, rouges, bleu marines, cloutées grises et à motif gris. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diser bundle enthält 19 beiläufigen Turnschuhe, und die exklusiv animierte Turnschuhe mit pulsierenden Neon-Licht. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">19 scarpe da tennis casuali, e le tennis animate esclusive: cambiamenti di luce è incorporato nella suola, più o meno intenso, passa lentamente attraverso tutti i colori dell'arcobaleno. . [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">19 zapatillas ocasionales, van a quedar bien en cualquier ocasión, y las zapatillas animadas exclusivas: una futurista luz cambiante en la planta del pie, que varían en intensidad, pasa lentamente a través de todos los colores del arco iris[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This bundle for men contains exclusive animated sneakers, with a pulsating neon streak in the sole cycling through all colors. The other 19 sneakers are: pirate, khaki, bat, grey tartan, sand, grey, black leather, black, white, brown, US flag, union jack, black crocodile, camo, army, red, navy blue, studded grey and grey pattern sneakers. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This bundle for men contains exclusive animated sneakers, with a pulsating neon streak in the sole cycling through all colors. The other 19 sneakers are: pirate, khaki, bat, gray tartan, sand, gray, black leather, black, white, brown, US flag, union jack, black crocodile, camo, army, red, navy blue, studded gray and gray pattern sneakers. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>