<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dinner Set</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Service de table</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tafelgeschirr</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set per la cena</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de comedor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dinner Set</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A set of sturdy chairs and a table decked out with a meal.\n\nThe set includes the following items for customizing your personal space.\nDinner Table (Tables)\nSturdy Chairs (Chairs)\n\n*Each item will be added to their relevant wardrobe and furniture category. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Deux chaises robustes et une table avec repas.\n\nCe service comprend les éléments de personnalisation de l'espace personnel suivants :\nTable de cuisine (Tables)\nChaises robustes (Chaises)\n\n*Chaque objet sera ajouté à la catégorie garde-robe ou mobilier correspondante.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Robuste Stühle und gedeckter Tisch mit einer Mahlzeit.\n\nDas Set enthält folgende Objekte, mit denen du dich ausstatten kannst.\nEsstisch (Tische)\nRobuste Stühle (Stühle)\n\n*Jedes Objekt wird der entsprechenden Kleiderschrank- und Möbel-Kategorie hinzugefügt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un set composto da robuste sedie e un tavolo già apparecchiato, pietanze incluse.\n\nIl set include i seguenti articoli per la personalizzazione del tuo spazio.\nTavolo (Tavoli)\nSedie robuste (Sedie)\n\n*Ogni oggetto verrà aggiunto alla rispettiva categoria all'interno del guardaroba e dei mobili. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un conjunto de sillas robustas y mesa complementado con una cena.\n\nEl conjunto incluye los siguientes elementos para personalizar tu espacio personal.\nMesa de comedor (mesas)\nSillas robustas (sillas)\n\n*Cada objeto se añadirá a la categoría de vestuario o mobiliario correspondiente. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A set of sturdy chairs and a table decked out with a meal.\n\nThe set includes the following items for customizing your personal space.\nDinner Table (Tables)\nSturdy Chairs (Chairs)\n\n*Each item will be added to their relevant wardrobe and furniture category. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>