<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MuiMui King Swimwear Set (men's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Maillot de bain Roi MuiMui (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MuiMui-König-Badekleidungssatz (Männer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set costume Re MuiMui da uomo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de baño del Rey MuiMui (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ムイムイキング水着セット（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">무이무이 킹 수영복 세트(남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">MuiMui King Swimwear Set (men's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">姆依姆依國王泳裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">姆依姆依國王泳裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MuiMui King Swimwear Set (men's)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Be the king of the beach with the MuiMui King's memorable
striped shorts and a towel featuring His Majesty.\n
Includes MuiMui King body paint.\n
\n
This set includes the following items:\n
\n
-MuiMui King Swimwear Set (top/men's) (tops)\n
-MuiMui King Swimwear Set (bottom/men's) (bottom's)\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Deviens le roi de la plage avec ce short à rayures mémorable
du Roi MuiMui et une serviette représentant Sa Majesté.\n
Contient de la peinture pour le corps Roi MuiMui.\n
\n
Cet ensemble se compose des articles suivants :\n
\n
- Maillot de bain Roi MuiMui (haut/homme) (haut)\n
- Maillot de bain Roi MuiMui (bas/homme) (bas)\n\nAcheter cet objet ajoute 1 LocoRoco à ton espace personnel de l'île Loco.
Tu peux ajouter jusqu'à 20 LocoRoco à l'île Loco. Une fois le maximum atteint, tu ne peux plus ajouter d'unités.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sei der König des Strandes mit diesen unvergesslichen gestreiften Shorts
des MuiMui-Königs und einem Handtuch, auf dem Seine Majestät abgebildet ist. Enthält MuiMui-König-Körperfarbe.\n
\n
Dieser Satz enthält folgende Gegenstände:\n
\n
- MuiMui-König-Badekleidungssatz (Oberteil/Männer) (Oberteile)\n
- MuiMui-König-Badekleidungssatz (Unterteil/Männer) (Unterteile)\n\nDieser Gegenstand fügt deinem Loco-Insel-Apartment 1 LocoRoco hinzu.
Du kannst bis zu 20 LocoRoco hinzufügen. Ist das Maximum erreicht, können keine weiteren Einheiten hinzugefügt werden.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Diventa il re della spiaggia con questo memorabile costume di Re MuiMui
composto da pantaloncini a strisce e un asciugamano raffigurante Sua Maestà.\n
Include un body paint di Re MuiMui.\n
\n
Questo set include i seguenti oggetti:\n
\n
- Set costume Re MuiMui (busto) da uomo\n
- Set costume Re MuiMui (gambe) da uomo\n\nAcquistando questo oggetto, aggiungerai un LocoRoco al tuo spazio personale su Loco Island.
Puoi aggiungere fino a 20 LocoRoco su Loco Island. Una volta raggiunto il numero massimo, non potrai aggiungerne altri.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conviértete en el rey de la playa con el memorable bañador a rayas
del Rey MuiMui y una toalla con Su Majestad.\n
Incluye una pintura corporal del Rey MuiMui\n
\n
El conjunto incluye los siguientes elementos:\n
\n
- Conjunto de baño del Rey MuiMui (parte de arriba/hombre)\n
- Conjunto de baño del Rey MuiMui (parte de abajo/hombre)\n\nComprar este objeto añade 1 LocoRoco a tu espacio personal en la Loco Isla.
Puedes añadir un máximo de 20 LocoRoco a la Loco Isla. Cuando hayas alcanzado este número, no podrás añadir más unidades.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ムイムイキングの印象的なストライプパンツと、ムイムイキングが描かれたタオルのセット。\n
ムイムイキングのボディペイントもついてるよ！\n
これを着ていれば浜辺でも王様気分！？\n
\n
本セットには、以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n
\n
-ムイムイキング水着セット（上・男性用）（トップス)\n
-ムイムイキング水着セット（下・男性用）（ボトムス)\n
\n
このアイテムを購入するとパーソナルスペース”ロコアイランド”に\n”ロコロコ”が１匹追加されます。”ロコアイランド”には最大20匹まで”ロコロコ”を追加できます。最大数に達した場合は、それ以上の追加はされません。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">무이무이 킹의 인상적인 스트라이프 팬츠와 무이무이 킹이 그려진 타올 세트.\n
무이무이 킹의 바디 페인트도 포함되어 있어!\n
이것을 입고 있으면 해변에서도 왕이 된 기분!?\n
\n
본 세트에는 다음 아이템이 포함되어 있습니다.\n
\n
-무이무이 킹 수영복 세트(상/남성)(상의)\n
-무이무이 킹 수영복 세트(하/남성)(하의)\n\n이 아이템을 구입하면 퍼스널 스페이스 '로코 아일랜드'에 '로코로코'가 1마리 추가됩니다.
'로코 아일랜드'에는 최대 20마리까지 '로코로코'를 추가할 수 있습니다. 
최대치에 다다르면 더 이상은 추가할 수 없습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Be the king of the beach with the MuiMui King's memorable
striped shorts and a towel featuring His Majesty.\n
Includes MuiMui King body paint.\n
\n
This set includes the following items:\n
\n
-MuiMui King Swimwear Set (top/men's) (tops)\n
-MuiMui King Swimwear Set (bottom/men's) (bottom's)\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">姆依姆依國王那令人印象深刻的直條紋褲和畫有姆依姆依國王的毛巾套組。\n
還會附上姆依姆依國王圖案的人體彩繪喔！\n
穿上它，即使在海邊也能有王者風範？！\n
\n
本套裝包含以下內容。\n
\n
-姆依姆依國王泳裝組(上/男用）（上身)\n
-姆依姆依國王泳裝組(下/男用）（下身)\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">姆依姆依國王那令人印象深刻的直條紋褲和畫有姆依姆依國王的毛巾套組。\n
還會附上姆依姆依國王圖案的人體彩繪喔！\n
穿上它，即使在海邊也能有王者風範？！\n
\n
本套裝包含以下內容。\n
\n
-姆依姆依國王泳裝組(上/男用）（上身)\n
-姆依姆依國王泳裝組(下/男用）（下身)\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Be the king of the beach with the MuiMui King's memorable
striped shorts and a towel featuring His Majesty.\n
Includes MuiMui King body paint.\n
\n
This set includes the following items:\n
\n
-MuiMui King Swimwear Set (top/men's) (tops)\n
-MuiMui King Swimwear Set (bottom/men's) (bottom's)\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your LocoIsland personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to LocoIsland. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>