<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cronk Figure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Figurine de Cronk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Cronk-Figur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Modellino Cronk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Muñeco de Cronk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">クロックのフィギュア</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">크롱크 피규어</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Cronk Figure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">卡隆克角色模型</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">卡隆克角色模型</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cronk Figure</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The old 'stupid' caretaker to Talwyn. He has superior graphics and has fought in nineteen galactic wars, three interstellar battles, one planetary misunderstanding, and a lunar argument. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vieux et "stupide" serviteur de Talwyn. Ses compétences en graphisme sont supérieures à la normale et il a pris part à dix-neuf guerres galactiques, trois combats interstellaires, un conflit planétaire et une querelle lunaire. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der alte "dämliche" Diener von Talwyn. Er verfügt über eine überlegene Grafik und hat in neunzehn galaktischen Kriegen, drei interstellaren Schlachten, einem planetaren Missverständnis und einer lunaren Auseinandersetzung gekämpft. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il vecchio "stupido" custode di Talwyn. Ha un design eccezionale e ha combattuto in diciannove guerre galattiche, tre battaglie interstellari, un qui pro quo planetario e una lite lunare. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El viejo y "estúpido" cuidador de Talwyn. Dotado de gráficos superiores, ha luchado en diecinueve guerras galácticas, tres batallas interestelares, un conflicto planetario y un litigio lunar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">タルウィンの従者。ゼファーからは「まぬけ」と呼ばれる。グラフィックスの専門家であり、19の銀河大戦と3つの星間戦争、1つの惑星級けんか、1つの衛星級口げんかを戦った歴戦の勇者でもある。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">탈윈의 보호자 가운데 하나입니다. 보다 나은 그래픽 처리 능력을 가지고 있으며, 제피르와 함께 엄청나게 많은 전투에 참여하였습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The old 'stupid' caretaker to Talwyn. He has superior graphics and has fought in nineteen galactic wars, three interstellar battles, one planetary misunderstanding, and a lunar argument. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">塔文的老牌笨蛋守護者。他擅長繪圖功能，參加過19場銀河系戰爭和3場星際大戰，而且還曾捲入過一次行星的誤解及月球的爭端。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">塔文的老牌笨蛋守護者。他擅長繪圖功能，參加過19場銀河系戰爭和3場星際大戰，而且還曾捲入過一次行星的誤解及月球的爭端。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The old 'stupid' caretaker to Talwyn. He has superior graphics and has fought in nineteen galactic wars, three interstellar battles, one planetary misunderstanding, and a lunar argument. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>