<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LOOT™ Shuttle Antares</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Navette Antares LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LOOT™ Shuttle Antares</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Shuttle Antares LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LOOT™ Shuttle Antares</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LOOT™シャトル・アンタレス</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LOOT™ Shuttle Antares</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is a perfectly replicated scale model of the brand new Antares-class LSS Belem, currently in service between LOOT Space Stations Delta and Epsilon. Rapid advances in LOOT Heavy Industries space technology (possibly spurred by rumored discoveries at the LOOT Lunar Outpost) have expanded the shuttle's payload to 50,000 kg and decreased fuel consumption to practically zero, clearly outpacing the previous Ascella-class spacecraft technology. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette maquette est une reproduction parfaite du tout nouveau Antares-class LSS Belem, actuellement en service entre les stations spatiales Delat et Epsilon de LOOT. Des progrès rapides dans la technologie spatiale de Heavy Industries de LOOT (probablement stimulés par de supposées découvertes sur l'Avant-poste Lunaire de LOOT) ont développé la capacité de charge de la navette de 50000 kg et réduit la consommation de carburant à pratiquement zéro, devançant largement la technologie du précédent vaisseau spatial Ascella-class. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses perfekt maßstabsgetreu nachgebaute Modell der LSS Belem der brandneuen Antares-Klasse, wie sie derzeit zwischen den LOOT-Raumstationen Delta und Epsilon eingesetzt wird. Dank des schnellen Fortschritts von LOOT Heavy Industries in der Raumfahrttechnik (wahrscheinlich angefeuert durch die Gerüchte über Entdeckungen beim LOOT Lunar-Vorposten) hat die Nutzlast des Shuttles auf 50.000 kg erhöht und den Treibstoffbedarf auf nahezu Null heruntergefahren und damit die Leistungen der vorangegangenen Akella-Klasse weit übertroffen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Modello in scala che riproduce fedelmente il nuovissimo LSS Belem classe Antares, attualmente in servizio tra le Stazioni spaziali LOOT Delta ed Epsilon. I progressi senza precedenti nella tecnologia spaziale delle Industrie pesanti LOOT (sicuramente incentivati dalle scoperte sull'Avamposto lunare LOOT) hanno reso possibile l'aumento della capacità di carico della nave a 50.000 kg e portato il consumo di carburante praticamente a zero, superando di gran lunga la tecnologia della nave classe Ascella. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta es una perfecta réplica a escala del nuevo LSS Belem de clase Antares, activo entre las estaciones espaciales de LOOT Delta y Epsilon. Los rápidos avances en tecnología industrial pesada de LOOT (posiblemente impulsados por los descubrimientos que se rumorea se han desarrollado en el puesto lunar avanzado de LOOT) ham ampliado la carga útil de la lanzadera a 50.000 kg, reduciendo el consumo de combustible prácticamente a cero y superando con creces la tecnología espacial anterior de clase Ascella. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">現在LOOT™の宇宙ステーションデルタとエプシロンの間で利用されている最新アンタレス級LSSべレムの完璧なレプリカです。LOOT™の重工業宇宙技術における急速な進歩（LOOT™の月面基地における発見の噂も関係しているかも？）によってシャトルの有効荷重が５万キロに、燃料消費もほとんど０になったので、明らかにアスケラ級宇宙船の技術を上回っています。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This is a perfectly replicated scale model of the brand new Antares-class LSS Belem, currently in service between LOOT Space Stations Delta and Epsilon. Rapid advances in LOOT Heavy Industries space technology (possibly spurred by rumored discoveries at the LOOT Lunar Outpost) have expanded the shuttle's payload to 50,000 kg and decreased fuel consumption to practically zero, clearly outpacing the previous Ascella-class spacecraft technology. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>