<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Casual Cardigan Outfit Set (Black &amp; Beige, Men)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de tenue de cardigan décontractée (noir et beige, homme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Set: Lässiges Outfit mit Cardigan (schwarz &amp; beige, für Männer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set completo con cardigan casual (nero e beige, da uomo)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego del atuendo informal con cárdigan (negro y beis, hombre)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">カジュアルカーディガン着こなしセット（黒＆ベージュ・男性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Casual Cardigan Outfit Set (Black &amp; Beige, Men)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A set consisting of a hat, chino trousers, trainers, and an outfit consisting of a cardigan worn on top of a dress shirt.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nCoolness: ★~★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Felt Hat, Small (Black w/ Red Lines, Men) (Head Accessory)\n- Felt Hat, Large (Black w/ Red Lines, Men) (Head Accessory)\n- Cardigan &amp; Dress Shirt (Black &amp; White, Men) (Torso)\n- Zipper Pocket Chinos (Beige, Men) (Legs)\n- Fold-Down High Cut Trainers (Brown &amp; Red, Men) (Feet)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set incluant un chapeau, un pantalon chino, des baskets et une tenue comprenant un cardigan porté par dessus une chemise.\nDéfense : ★\nNiveau de cool : ★~★★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Chapeau de feutre, petit (noir avec lignes rouges, homme) (Accessoire de tête)\n- Chapeau de feutre, grand (noir avec lignes rouges, homme) (Accessoire de tête)\n- Cardigan et chemise (noir et blanche, homme) (Torse)\n- Chino à poches à fermeture Éclair (beige, homme) (Jambes)\n- Baskets hautes repliées (marron et rouges, homme) (Pieds)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Set, das einen Hut, eine Chinohose, Sneakers und ein Outfit mit Cardigan und Hemd enthält.\nVerteidigung: ★\nCoolness: ★~★★\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Filzhut, klein (schwarz mit roten Streifen, für Männer) (Kopfbedeckung)\n- Filzhut, groß (schwarz mit roten Streifen, für Männer) (Kopfbedeckung)\n- Cardigan &amp; Hemd (schwarz &amp; weiß, für Männer) (Rumpf)\n- Chinohose mit Reisverschlusstaschen (beige, für Männer) (Beine)\n- Umgeschlagene High-Cut Sneakers (braun &amp; rot, für Männer) (Füße)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set formato da un cappello, pantaloni chinos, scarpe da ginnastica e un completo che consiste in un cardigan indossato sopra una camicia elegante.\nDifesa: ★\nRicercatezza: ★~★★\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Cappello di feltro, piccolo (nero con strisce rosse, da uomo) (cappelli)\n- Cappello di feltro, grande (nero con strisce rosse, da uomo) (cappelli)\n- Cardigan e camicia elegante (nero e bianco, da uomo) (torso)\n- Chinos con tasche con cerniere (beige, da uomo) (gambe)\n- Scarpe da ginnastica con taglio alto ripiegato (marroni e rosse, da uomo) (piedi)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego que consiste en un sombrero, chinos, zapatillas, y un cárdigan sobre una camisa formal.\nDefensa: ★\nPorte: ★~★★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Sombrero de fieltro, pequeño (negro con rayas rojas, hombre) (accesorio de cabeza)\n- Sombrero de fieltro, grande (negro con rayas rojas, hombre) (accesorio de cabeza)\n- Cárdigan y camisa formal (negro y blanca, hombre) (torso)\n- Chinos con bolsillo de cremallera (beis, hombre) (piernas)\n- Zapatillas de corte alto con la parte superior doblada (marrones y rojas, hombre) (pies)\n\n* Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ワイシャツの上にカーディガンを着たコーディネートと、ハット、チノパン、スニーカーのセット。\n防御力：　★\nかっこよさ：　★～★★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・中折れハット・小（黒＆レッドライン・男性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n・中折れハット・大（黒＆レッドライン・男性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n・カーディガン＆ワイシャツ（黒＆白・男性）/トップス\n・ジッパーポケットチノパン（ベージュ・男性）/ボトムズ\n・履き口を折ったハイカットスニーカー（ブラウン＆レッド・男性）/靴\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A set consisting of a hat, chino pants, sneakers, and an outfit consisting of a cardigan worn on top of a dress shirt.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nCoolness: ★~★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Felt Hat, Small (Black w/ Red Lines, Men) (Head Accessory)\n- Felt Hat, Large (Black w/ Red Lines, Men) (Head Accessory)\n- Cardigan &amp; Dress Shirt (Black &amp; White, Men) (Torso)\n- Zipper Pocket Chinos (Beige, Men) (Legs)\n- Fold-Down High Cut Sneakers (Brown &amp; Red, Men) (Feet)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
