<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MAG - Valor Reinforced Fiber Armor Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">MAG - Pack gilet en fibres renforcées Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MAG-Paket: FKV-Panzerung (Valor)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">MAG - Pacchetto armatura in fibra rinforzata Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">MAG: paquete de blindaje de fibra reforzada de Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">MAG - Valor 방탄복 팩</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">MAG - Valor Reinforced Fiber Armor Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">MAG - Valor 強化纖維裝甲包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">MAG - Valor 強化纖維裝甲包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MAG - Valor Reinforced Fiber Armor Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Valor Reinforced Fibre Armour Pack relies heavily on proven battle technology, Valor believes that "if it ain't broke, don't fix it". Durable and functional, Valor's no-nonsense gear is comfortable and quiet for those long missions behind enemy lines. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le pack gilet en fibres renforcées Valor repose en grande partie sur une technologie éprouvée. Notre devise : "Si c'est pas cassé, le répare pas." Solide et fonctionnel, l'équipement épuré de Valor est confortable et silencieux, idéal pour ces longues missions en territoire ennemi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Für die FKV-Panzerung vertraut Valor in erster Linie auf bewährte Kriegstechnologien nach dem Motto: „Wenn es nicht kaputt ist, muss es auch nicht ersetzt werden.“ Die Ausrüstung von Valor verzichtet auf alles Überflüssige und ist ausdauernd, funktional und weist zugleich einen hohen Komfort und minimierte Lärmwerte auf, was sie für Missionen auf feindlichem Territorium prädestiniert. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il pacchetto armatura in fibra rinforzata Valor rispecchia la filosofia della Valor: la tecnologia collaudata in battaglia è sempre la migliore, se una cosa non si rompe, non va cambiata. Durevole e funzionale senza ghiribizzi, l'attrezzatura della Valor è comoda e silenziosa, adatta alle lunghe missioni dietro le linee nemiche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El paquete de blindaje de fibra reforzada de Valor es fruto de la tecnología probada en la batalla, según el principio de Valor "si no está roto, no lo arregles". Duradero y funcional, este práctico equipo de Valor es cómodo y silencioso para esas largas misiones tras las líneas enemigas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이미 전장에서 효능이 입증된 기술을 사용하여, '고장나지 않았다면 고치지 말라'는 격언을 실천하는 Valor의 장비입니다. 내구성과 기능에는 의심의 여지가 없습니다. 적진 뒤에서 오랜 시간 임무를 수행할 때에도 완벽한 착용감을 선사합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Valor Reinforced Fiber Armor Pack relies heavily on proven battle technology, Valor believes that "if it ain't broke, don't fix it". Durable and functional, Valor's no-nonsense gear is comfortable and quiet for those long missions behind enemy lines. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Valor的 強化纖維裝甲包非常倚重具備實績的戰鬥科技 ，相信「未壞掉就別修理」這個道理。耐用與功能齊全。Valor實事求是的裝備，使用上舒適而寧靜，適用於深入敵方戰線的長期任務。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Valor的 強化纖維裝甲包非常倚重具備實績的戰鬥科技 ，相信「未壞掉就別修理」這個道理。耐用與功能齊全。Valor實事求是的裝備，使用上舒適而寧靜，適用於深入敵方戰線的長期任務。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Valor Reinforced Fiber Armor Pack relies heavily on proven battle technology, Valor believes that "if it ain't broke, don't fix it". Durable and functional, Valor's no-nonsense gear is comfortable and quiet for those long missions behind enemy lines. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>