<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Jedi Banner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bannière Jedi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jedi-Banner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stendardo Jedi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estandarte Jedi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Jedi Banner</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The younglings have a habit of gathering around, excitedly, waiting for the Jedi Masters to enter the chamber. They will waste their time with smaller diversions; laughter, games, small talk, and more. These distractions do little to grow their strength. Instead their strength comes from the great symbols of our time, many of which adorn the walls of the Temple. One of these is the Jedi brand emblazoned across a banner, hanging over the younglings heads as they fritter their time away. Someday they will understand the meaning.  Someday. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les jeunes ont l'habitude de se rassembler, tout excités, en attendant que les maîtres Jedi entrent dans la salle. Ils perdent leur temps en distractions stériles : rires, jeux, bavardages. Ces distractions ne servent guère à accroître leur force. Celle-ci vient plutôt des grands symboles de notre temps, dont beaucoup ornent les murs du temple. L'un d'entre eux est l'emblème des Jedi, qui figure sur une bannière suspendue au-dessus des têtes de ces jeunes apprentis, tandis qu'ils gaspillent leur énergie. Un jour, ils en comprendront la signification. Un jour. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Jünglinge haben die Angewohnheit, sich zu versammeln und gespannt auf den Jedi-Meister zu warten. Sie vergeuden ihre Zeit mit kleinen Ablenkungen, Lachen, Spielen, Gerede und anderem. Diese Ablenkungen helfen nicht, um ihre Stärke aufzubauen. Stattdessen kommt ihre Stärke durch die großen Symbole unserer Zeit, von denen viele die Wände des Tempels verzieren. Eines davon ist das Zeichen der Jedi, das ein Banner schmückt und über den Köpfen der Jünglinge hängt, während sie ihre Zeit verplempern. Eines Tages werden sie die Bedeutung verstehen. Eines Tages. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I giovani hanno l'abitudine di radunarsi emozionati in attesa che i Maestri Jedi entrino nella sala. Essi perdono tempo con diversivi minori: il riso, i giochi, le chiacchiere e altro ancora. Queste distrazioni fanno ben poco per aumentare la loro forza, la quale deriva invece dai grandi simboli del nostro tempo, molti dei quali adornano i muri del Tempio. Uno di questi è il marchio dei Jedi che compare su uno stendardo posizionato sopra le teste dei giovani allievi. Un giorno anch'essi comprenderanno il significato di questo stemma. Un giorno. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los jóvenes suelen reunirse, emocionados, a la espera de que los Maestros Jedi entren en la sala. Malgastan su tiempo con diversiones menores: risas, juegos, charlas y demás. Estas distracciones no contribuyen a mejorar su fuerza. Su fuerza proviene de los grandes símbolos de nuestro tiempo, muchos de los cuales adornan los muros del Templo. Uno de ellos es el escudo Jedi plasmado en un estandarte, que cuelga sobre las cabezas de los jóvenes mientras ellos dejan pasar el tiempo. Algún día comprenderán su significado. Algún día. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The younglings have a habit of gathering around, excitedly, waiting for the Jedi Masters to enter the chamber. They will waste their time with smaller diversions; laughter, games, small talk, and more. These distractions do little to grow their strength. Instead their strength comes from the great symbols of our time, many of which adorn the walls of the Temple. One of these is the Jedi brand emblazoned across a banner, hanging over the younglings heads as they fritter their time away. Someday they will understand the meaning.  Someday. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>