<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Heavy LRM Drone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Drone LRM lourd</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schwere LRM-Drohne</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Drone pesante LRM</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Robot volador pesado LRM</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">重装備長距離ミサイル ドローン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">중무장 LRM 무인전투기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Heavy LRM Drone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">重型遠程飛彈攻擊機</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">重型遠程飛彈攻擊機</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Heavy LRM Drone</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Its heavy ordinance makes this an effective killer from long-range, so don’t be afraid to get in close where its low manoeuvrability will make it hard to fight back. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Son poids fait de lui un tueur de longue distance efficace. N'hésitez pas à vous en approcher car son manque de maniabilité l'empêche de se défendre facilement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Durch die schwere Bewaffnung tötet das Fahrzeug wirkungsvoll aus weiter Entfernung. Traue dich also, nahe heranzurücken, so dass es aufgrund seiner geringen Manövrierfähigkeit nur schwer zurückschlagen kann. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il suo armamento pesante è letale sul lungo raggio. Non esitare ad attaccarlo a distanza ravvicinata, dove la scarsa manovrabilità gli impedisce di rispondere. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Es un destructor muy efectivo a largo alcance gracias a su artillería pesado, así que no tengas miedo de acercarte, ya que su baja maniobrabilidad hará que le cueste defenderse. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">長距離からの攻撃に効果的な重装機。動きも鈍いく反撃を受けにくいので、至近距離まで近づくことを恐れるな。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">장거리에서 높은 효율을 자랑하는 중화기 플랫폼입니다. 기체의 낮은 운동 성능을 약점으로 이용할 수 있는 근거리 전투를 위해 가까이 접근해야 합니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Its heavy ordinance makes this an effective killer from long-range, so don’t be afraid to get in close where its low manoeuvrability will make it hard to fight back. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">雖然其重型武器使之成為高效的遠程殺手，但是切勿害怕接近它，因為其可憐的機動性令它難以大舉反擊。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">雖然其重型武器使之成為高效的遠程殺手，但是切勿害怕接近它，因為其可憐的機動性令它難以大舉反擊。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Its heavy ordinance makes this an effective killer from long-range, so don’t be afraid to get in close where its low maneuverability will make it hard to fight back. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>