<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Oriental Triptych</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Triptyque oriental</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Orientalisches Triptychon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Trittico orientale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tríptico oriental</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オリエンタル三連画</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">동양적인 패널아트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Oriental Triptych</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">東方風格三聯壁畫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">東方風格三聯壁畫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Oriental Triptych</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Express yourself with this great work of art! Three bamboo printed panels which are hinged together will make sure your apartment looks its best! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Exprimez-vous avec cette véritable oeuvre d'art ! Ces trois panneaux de bambou imprimés reliés entre eux par des charnières donneront un style unique à votre appartement ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bring deine Persönlichkeit mit diesem wunderbaren Kunstwerk zum Ausdruck. Drei miteinander verbundene, bedruckte Bambusplatten verleihen deiner Wohnung ein einzigartiges Flair! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premia la tua creatività con questo capolavoro! Questi tre pannelli di bambù dipinti, uniti a cerniera, daranno al tuo appartamento un tocco di delicata eleganza! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Exprésate con esta obra de arte! ¡Estos tres paneles de bambú estampados y unidos por bisagras darán a tu apartamento un look increíble! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この素晴らしい芸術品で自分を表現しましょう！ヒンジで連結され、竹の絵がプリントされたパネルによってあなたの部屋が素晴らしく見違えます！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 예술 작품으로 자신을 표현하세요! 3개의 대나무 패널에 그려진 그림이 연결된 이 작품은 여러분의 퍼스널 스페이스를 최상의 분위기로 만들어 줄 것입니다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Express yourself with this great work of art! Three bamboo printed panels which are hinged together will make sure your personal spaces looks its best! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用這件優質的藝術品來表達自我吧！將三張印刷竹畫連在一起，為個人空間錦上添花！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用這件優質的藝術品來表達自我吧！將三張印刷竹畫連在一起，為個人空間錦上添花！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Express yourself with this great work of art! Three bamboo printed panels which are hinged together will make sure your apartment looks its best! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>