<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ultimate Scribble Shooter PlayStation®Home Saviour Cape &amp; Sceptre (female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cape et sceptre Scribble Shooter de la sauveuse ultime de PlayStation®Home (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ultimativer "Scribble Shooter"-Retter-Umhang &amp; Zepter (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scribble Shooter - Scettro e mantello dell'impavida salvatrice di PlayStation®Home (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Capa y cetro de salvadora definitiva de PlayStation®Home de Scribble Shooter (Mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Scribble Shooter 王様の杖とマント（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">얼티밋 스크리블 슈터 "홈의 구원자" 망토와 지팡이 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ultimate Scribble Shooter PlayStation®Home Savior Cape &amp; Scepter (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Scribble Shooter終極PlayStation®Home拯救者斗篷與權杖（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Scribble Shooter終極PlayStation®Home拯救者斗篷與權杖（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ultimate Scribble Shooter PlayStation®Home Savior Cape &amp; Scepter (female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Let's face it, we can't all be heroes.  But don't let that stop you from fooling people into thinking you helped defend the PlayStation®Home Universe against the evil Scribble Shooter Aliens.  Remember kids, fake it 'til you make it. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Regardons les choses en face, n'est pas héros qui veut. Mais rien ne vous empêche de faire croire à tout le monde que vous avez aidé à défendre l'univers PlayStation®Home des aliens diaboliques de Scribble Shooter. Rappelez-vous les enfants : il suffit de faire semblant, le reste suivra. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ja, jeder kann ein Held sein. Aber das sollte niemanden daran hindern, andere glauben zu lassen, man hätte bei der Verteidigung des PlayStation®Home-Universums gegen fiese "Scribble Shooter"-Aliens geholfen. Ein bisschen Prahlerei hat noch keinem geschadet. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ammettiamolo: non siamo tutti eroi. Ma puoi sempre far credere di aver contribuito a difendere l'universo di PlayStation®Home dai malvagi alieni di Scribble Shooter. Ricorda: fingi finché non ti credono! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Afrontémoslo, no todas podemos ser heroínas. Pero eso no tiene por qué impedirte engañar a la gente para que piense que has ayudado a defender el universo PlayStation®Home de los malvados alienígenas de Scribble Shooter. Ya sabes, finge hasta que se lo crean. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">はっきり言って全員ヒーローにはなれないが、Scribble Shooterのエイリアン共からPlayStation®Homeの世界を救う手助けをしたことをみんなに思わせることぐらいはできるぞ！事実になるまでは嘘を吐き通すべし。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">우리 모두가 영웅이 될 수는 없습니다. 하지만 홈의 친구들에게 당신이 직접 스크리블 슈터 외계인들을 물리지고 우주를 구했다고 허풍을 칠 수 없는 것은 아닙니다. 언젠가는 사실이 될지도 모르니까요.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Let's face it, we can't all be heroes.  But don't let that stop you from fooling people into thinking you helped defend the PlayStation®Home Universe against the evil Scribble Shooter Aliens.  Remember kids, fake it 'till you make it.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">面對現實吧。不是所有人也能成為英雄。可是，不要因此而不再誤導人們，讓他們以為你有參與對抗Scribble Shooter外星人，保衛PlayStation®Home宇宙。年輕人，緊記：未能做到，也要一直假裝做到，直到真正做到為止。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">面對現實吧。不是所有人也能成為英雄。可是，不要因此而不再誤導人們，讓他們以為你有參與對抗Scribble Shooter外星人，保衛PlayStation®Home宇宙。年輕人，緊記：未能做到，也要一直假裝做到，直到真正做到為止。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Let's face it, we can't all be heroes.  But don't let that stop you from fooling people into thinking you helped defend the PlayStation®Home Universe against the evil Scribble Shooter Aliens.  Remember kids, fake it 'till you make it.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>