<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nebula Air Ship</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vaisseau nébuleux</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nebelflugschiff</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aeromobile Nebula</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aeronave Nebula</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">네뷸라 비행정</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Nebula Air Ship</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">星雲太空船</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">星雲太空船</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Nebula Air Ship</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take to the skies as a nautical air pilot as you maneuver your air ship through the soft billowy clouds. From atop your sky deck you will truly have a bird’s eye view of the land down below. You might even catch a glimpse of other air ships flying in the distance. Reward your guests with a Miniature Airship item, exclusive to Nebula Air Ship personal space. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Devenez pilote aéronautique en vous envolant à travers les nuages de coton à bord de ce vaisseau. Prenez-vous pour un oiseau en observant le monde du haut de votre pont. Avec un peu de chance, vous pourrez même apercevoir d'autres vaisseaux au loin dans le ciel. Récompensez vos clients avec un élément de Dirigeable miniature, une exclusivité de l'espace aérien du navire nébuleuse personnelle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erhebe dich als nautischer Luftpilot in die Lüfte und steuere dein Luftschiff durch die weichen, wogenden Wolken. Von deinem Himmelsdeck hast du einen tollen Ausblick auf das Land unter dir. Vielleicht entdeckst du in der Ferne sogar andere fliegende Luftschiffe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Decolla come un pilota dell'aviazione navale ai comandi del tuo aeromobile, e vola attraverso le soffici e gonfie nuvole. Dall'alto del tuo ponte di comando, avrai una reale prospettiva a volo d'uccello della terra sotto di te. Potresti perfino intravedere di sfuggita altri aeromobili in volo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Alcanza el cielo como piloto aéreo mientras maniobras tu aeronave a través de nubes suaves y ondulantes. Desde tu mirador tendrás una auténtica vista panorámica de pájaro de la tierra que sobrevuelas. Puede que incluso divises otros aviones volando a lo lejos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">하늘을 항해하는 비행정의 조종사가 되어 부드러운 구름 사이를 탐험하십시오. 하늘 위에 갑판에서는 지상을 향한 멋진 전망이 펼쳐지며, 저 멀리 비행하고 있는 다른 비행정들을 구경할 수 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Take to the skies as a nautical air pilot as you maneuver your air ship through the soft billowy clouds. From atop your sky deck you will truly have a bird’s eye view of the land down below. You might even catch a glimpse of other air ships flying in the distance. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">以機師的身分駕駛你的太空船，穿越棉軟的雲層，翱翔天空。從天空甲板你將可鳥瞰下面的大地。你亦可能瞥見在遠處飛過的太空船。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">以機師的身分駕駛你的太空船，穿越棉軟的雲層，翱翔天空。從天空甲板你將可鳥瞰下面的大地。你亦可能瞥見在遠處飛過的太空船。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Take to the skies as a nautical air pilot as you maneuver your air ship through the soft billowy clouds. From atop your sky deck you will truly have a bird’s eye view of the land down below. You might even catch a glimpse of other air ships flying in the distance. Reward your guests with a Miniature Airship item, exclusive to Nebula Air Ship personal space. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>