<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - New Force Tie Dye Jacket - Pro Blue (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Blouson New Force Tie Dye - Bleu pro (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - New Force Tie Dye Jacke - Blau (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Giacca New Force Tie Dye - Blu pro (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - New Force Tie Dye Chaqueta - Azul profesional (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The New Force brings a futuristic twist to classic windbreaker style with a tie-dye print, and a contrast reverse front zipper. Detailed with a woven logo patch at the chest, an inner yoke, side pockets, and mesh lining. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le New Force confère une touche futuriste au style coupe-vent classique avec un imprimé tie-dye et une fermeture frontale zippée inversée. Agrémenté d'un patch logo tissé sur la poitrine, d'une patte intérieure, de poches latérales et d'une doublure en filet. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Batikmotiv der New Force Jacke und der kontrastierende Zweiweg-Reißverschluss verleihen der klassischen Windjacke einen futuristischen Touch. Zu besonderen Details zählen das Stofflogo auf der Brust, eine interne Passe, Seitentaschen und Netzfutter. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il modello New Force dà un tocco futuristico alla giacca a vento di stile classico grazie al motivo tie-dye e alla cerniera anteriore a bobina inversa a contrasto. Sul petto ha un logo applicato in tessuto, carré interno, tasche laterali e fodera in rete. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La New Force aporta un toque futurista al estilo clásico de cortavientos, con un estampado en teñido anudado y cremallera delantera reversible y en color de contraste. Los detalles incluyen un parche cosido con el logotipo en el pecho, cuello interno y forro en malla. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>