<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Pirate Liar’s Dice Rules</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Poker Menteur Pirate Règles</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The complete rules of the game. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les règles complètes du jeu. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Pirate Liar’s Dice Rules</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Poker Menteur Pirate Règles</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Before you get to playing you need to know the rules. Not knowing the rules is the best way to lose.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avant d'arriver à jouer, vous devez connaître les règles. Ne connaissant pas les règles est le meilleur moyen de perdre.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Lowdown</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La Verité</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Each pirate starts with 5 dice and a cup. At the start of each round, all the dice are scooped up in each pirate’s cup, shaken, and the cup is flipped over onto the table. Pirates only get to look at their own dice. Peeking leads to losing body parts (see table leg).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaque pirate commence avec 5 dés et une tasse. Au début de chaque tour, tous les dés sont ramassés dans la tasse de chaque pirate, ébranlée, et la coupe est retournée sur la table. Pirates seulement obtenir de regarder leurs propres dés. Un coup d'oeil conduit à la perte de parties du corps (voir pied de table).</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The game begins with a pirate starting the bidding by picking a die number 2 through 6 and a number of them they think have been rolled in total on the table. Ones ("aces") are wild and count as the face of the current bid. In a five dice, four player game, the lowest bid is "one 2" and the highest bid "twenty 6s". After that bidding goes to the pirate on his left.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le jeu commence avec un pirate de départ l'appel d'offres en choisissant un numéro 2 die à 6 et un certain nombre d'entre eux qu'ils pensent avoir été roulé au total sur la table. Unes ("as") sont sauvages et compter comme le visage de l'offre actuelle. Dans une période de cinq dés, quatre joueurs, l'offre la plus basse est "un 2" et plus l'offre "vingt 6s". Après que l'enchère va à la pirate sur sa gauche.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The next pirate can make a higher bid, call “Spot On”, or call “Liar”. Making a higher bid means increasing the die or increase the count or both. If you increase the count, you can decrease the die. For instance, three 2s is greater than two 6s. Bidding continues until someone calls “Spot On” or “Liar”. Once a call is made, all dice are revealed.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le pirate peut prochaine faire de la surenchère, appelez "Dans Le Mille", ou appelez le "Menteur". Faire une offre plus élevée signifie qu'il faut augmenter la filière ou d'augmenter le nombre ou les deux. Enchère continue jusqu'à ce que quelqu'un appelle "Dans Le Mille" ou "Menteur". Une fois qu'un appel est effectué, tous les dés sont révélés.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Calling “Spot On” means you think the last bid is the exact right count for the die on the table including wild cards. If correct, everyone at the table but the caller loses a die. If incorrect, the caller loses a die.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Calling "Dans Le Mille" signifie que vous pensez de la dernière enchère est le nombre exact droit pour le dé sur la table y compris les cartes sauvages. Si elle est correcte, tout le monde à la table, mais l'appelant perd un dé. Si il est incorrecte, l'appelant perd un dé.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Calling “Liar” means you think there are less than the count of the die in the last bid including wild cards. If correct, the pirate who made the bid loses a die. If incorrect, the caller loses a die.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Calling "Menteur" signifie que vous pensez qu'il ya moins que le comte de la filière dans la dernière enchère y compris les cartes sauvages. Si elle est correcte, le pirate qui a fait l'offre perd un dé. Si il est incorrecte, l'appelant perd un dé.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The next round is started by whoever just lost a die or the pirate to their left if they go out.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le prochain cycle est lancé par celui qui vient de perdre une filière ou le pirate à leur gauche si elles sortent.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 9</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Once a pirate has no dice left, they are out. The winner is the last pirate left with at least one die. The winner collects the pot.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une fois un pirate n'a pas laissé dés, ils sont sortis. Le gagnant est le dernier pirate à gauche avec au moins une filière. Le gagnant recueille le pot.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 10</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Controls</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Contrôles</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[UP][DOWN] Change the count</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[UP][DOWN] Changer le nombre</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 12</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[LEFT][RIGHT] Change the die</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFT][RIGHT] Changer le dé</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Make bid</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Faire offre</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 14</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[CIRCLE] Call “Liar”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CIRCLE] Appelez "Menteur"</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 15</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[SQUARE] Call “Spot On”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[SQUARE] Appelez "Dans Le Mille"</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">help paragraph 16</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[TRIANGLE] Help</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[TRIANGLE] Aider</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">controller</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[UP][DOWN] Scroll [DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[UP][DOWN] Défiler [DECLINE] Quitter</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>