<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Strut - Leggings - Bundle Volume 3 (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Devotion - Legging - Lot volume 3 (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Strut - Leggings - Paket 3 (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Strut - Leggings - Set Volume 3 (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Strut - Mallas - Pack Volumen 3 (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A selection of leggings with a variety of patterns, boots, hotpants and skirts.  A devotion to Fashion.\n
\n
This bundle contains:\n
(1) Strut - Leggings with Hotpants - White Stars (Women)\n
(2) Strut - Leggings with Hotpants - Black Stars (Women)\n
(3) Strut - Leggings - Black Skulls (Women)\n
(4) Strut - Leggings - White Skulls (Women)\n
(5) Strut - Leggings with Skirt - White (Women)\n
(6) Strut - Leggings with Skirt - Black (Women)\n
(7) Strut - Leggings with Leather Boots - BlackJolly Roger (Women)\n
(8) Strut - Leggings with Leather Boots - White Jolly Roger (Women)\n
(9) Strut - Leggings with Biker Boots - White (Women)\n
(10) Strut - Leggings with Biker Boots - Black (Women)\n
(11) Strut - Leggings with Platform Shoes - White Stars (Women)\n
(12) Strut - Leggings with Platform Shoes - Black Stars (Women) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une sélection de leggings avec une variété de motifs, de bottes, de shorty et de jupes. Une Dévotion à la mode.\n
\n
Ce lot contient :\n
(1) Strut - Legging avec shorty - Étoiles  blancs (femme)\n
(2) Strut - Legging avec shorty - Étoiles noires (femme)\n
(3) Strut - Legging - Crânes noirs (femme)\n
(4) Strut - Legging - Crânes blancs (femme)\n
(5) Strut - Legging avec jupe - Blanc (femme)\n
(6) Strut - Legging avec jupe - Noir (femme)\n
(7) Strut - Legging avec bottes en cuir - Pavillon de pirate noir (femme)\n
(8) Strut - Legging avec bottes en cuir - Pavillon de pirate blanc (femme)\n
(9) Strut - Legging avec bottes de motard - Blanc (femme)\n
(10) Strut - Legging avec bottes de motard - Noir (femme)\n
(11) Strut - Legging avec chaussures à semelle compensée - Étoiles  blancs (femme)\n
(12) Strut - Legging avec chaussures à semelle compensée - Étoiles noires (femme) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sortiment an Leggings in verschiedenen Mustern, dazu Stiefel, Hotpants und Röcke. Aus Liebe zur Mode.\n
\n
Dieses Bündel enthält:\n
(1) Strut - Leggings und Hotpants - Weiße Sterne (Damen)\n
(2) Strut - Leggings und Hotpants - Schwarze Sterne (Damen)\n
(3) Strut - Leggings - Schwarze Totenschädel (Damen)\n
(4) Strut - Leggings - Weiße Totenschädel (Damen)\n
(5) Strut - Leggings und Rock - Weiß (Damen)\n
(6) Strut - Leggings und Rock - Schwarz (Damen)\n
(7) Strut - Leggings mit Lederstiefeln - Schwarze Seeräuberflagge (Damen)\n
(8) Strut - Leggings mit Lederstiefeln - Weiße Seeräuberflagge (Damen)\n
(9) Strut - Leggings und Motorradstiefel - Weiß (Damen)\n
(10) Strut - Leggings und Motorradstiefel - Schwarz (Damen)\n
(11) Strut - Leggings und Plateauschuhe - Weiße Sterne (Damen)\n
(12) Strut - Leggings und Plateauschuhe - Schwarze Sterne (Damen) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una selezione di leggings con vari motivi, stivali, pantaloncini e gonne. Devotion: devozione alla moda.\n
\n
Il set comprende:\n
(1) Strut - Leggings con pantaloncini - Stelle Bianchi (Donna)\n
(2) Strut - Leggings con pantaloncini - Stelle Nere (Donna)\n
(3) Strut - Leggings - Teschi Neri (Donna)\n
(4) Strut - Leggings - Teschi Bianchi (Donna)\n
(5) Strut - Leggings e gonna - Bianco (Donna)\n
(6) Strut - Leggings e gonna - Nero (Donna)\n
(7) Strut - Leggings con Stivali di Pelle - Nero Jolly Roger (Donna)\n
(8) Strut - Leggings con Stivali di Pelle - Bianco Jolly Roger (Donna)\n
(9) Strut - Leggings con Stivali da Motociclista - Bianco (Donna)\n
(10) Strut - Leggings con Stivali da Motociclista - Nero (Donna)\n
(11) Strut - Leggings e scarpe con zeppa - Stelle Bianchi (Donna)\n
(12) Strut - Leggings e scarpe con zeppa - Stelle Nere (Donna) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una selección de mallas con una amplia variedad de estampados, botas, culotes y faldas. Una auténtica devoción por la moda.\n
\n
Este pack contiene:\n
(1) Strut - Mallas con culote - Estrellas blancas (Mujer)\n
(2) Strut - Mallas con culote - Estrellas negras (Mujer)\n
(3) Strut - Mallas - Calaveras negras (Mujer)\n
(4) Strut - Mallas - Calaveras blancas (Mujer)\n
(5) Strut - Mallas con falda - Blanco (Mujer)\n
(6) Strut - Mallas con falda - Negro (Mujer)\n
(7) Strut - Mallas con botas de cuero - Bandera pirata negra (Mujer)\n
(8) Strut - Mallas con botas de cuero - Bandera pirata blanca (Mujer)\n
(9) Strut - Mallas con botas de motera - Blanco (Mujer)\n
(10) Strut - Mallas con botas de motera - Negro (Mujer)\n
(11) Strut - Mallas con zapatos de plataforma - Estrellas blancas (Mujer)\n
(12) Strut - Mallas con zapatos de plataforma - Estrellas negras (Mujer) [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>