<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Audi Shop</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Audi Shop</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Audi Shop</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Audi Shop</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Audi Shop</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Products bearing the Audi brand logo can be depended upon to stand out from their relevant environment. What we call “Vorsprung durch Technik” in relation to cars has been interpreted in entirely different ways in our other product areas – an aesthetic best defined by a focus on functionality and simple, understated design. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les produits portant le logo de la marque Audi peut compter sur eux pour se démarquer de leur environnement pertinent. Ce que nous appelons "Vorsprung durch Technik" par rapport aux voitures a été interprété de façon tout à fait différent dans nos autres produits - une esthétique mieux défini par un accent sur la fonctionnalité et simple, design discret. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Produkte mit der Marke Audi Logo kann angewiesen werden, um sich von ihrer jeweiligen Umwelt. Was wir als "Vorsprung durch Technik" in Bezug auf Autos wurde in ganz verschiedener Weise in unseren anderen Produktbereichen - interpretiert eine ästhetische besten definiert durch einen Fokus auf Funktionalität und einfache, schlichte Design. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prodotti recanti il logo del marchio Audi può essere dipeso a stare fuori dal loro ambiente rilevante. Ciò che noi chiamiamo "Vorsprung durch Technik" in relazione alle automobili è stato interpretato in modi completamente diversi nel nostro altri settori di prodotti - un valore estetico meglio definita da un focus sulla funzionalità e semplice, sobrio design. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los productos que llevan el logotipo de la marca Audi se puede depender de destacar de su entorno relevante. Lo que llamamos "Vorsprung durch Technik" en relación con los coches ha sido interpretada de modos muy diferentes en nuestras otras áreas de producto - una estética más definida por un enfoque en la funcionalidad y sencillo, discreto diseño. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>