<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Cherry Blossom Ikebana 2-piece Set</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de 2 pièces d'Ikebana de fleurs de cerisier</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">2-teiliges Set von Kirschblüten-Ikebana</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set 2 ikebana con fiori di ciliegio</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos artículos de ikebana de flores de cerezo</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">桜の生け花２点セット</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Cherry Blossom Ikebana 2-piece Set</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 2-piece set of cherry blossoms arranged in bamboo and ceramic vases.\nThis set includes the following items for customizing your private lounge:\n\n- Cherry Blossoms Arranged in Bamboo (Wall Hangings)\n- Cherry Blossoms Arranged in Ceramics (Ornaments)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category in "Private Lounge Customization".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 2 pièces de fleurs de cerisiers arrangées dans des vases de bambou et de céramique.\nCe set inclut les objets suivants pour personnaliser votre espace privé :\n\n- Fleurs de cerisier arrangées en bambou (Décorations murales)\n- Fleurs de cerisier arrangées en céramique (Décoration)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective dans "Personnalisation de l'espace privé".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 2-teiliges Set, das Kirschblütenarrangements in einer Bambusvase und einer Keramikvase enthält.\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände für deine private Lounge.\n\n- Bambusvase mit Kirschblütenarrangement (Wandbehang)\n- Keramikvase mit Kirschblütenarrangement (Verzierungen)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie unter "Private Lounge bearbeiten" hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set composto da 2 elementi comprendente dei fiori di ciliegio in un vaso di bambù e in un vaso di ceramica.\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti per la personalizzazione della stanza privata.\n\n- Fiori di ciliegio sistemati in un vaso di bambù (decorazioni per pareti)\n- Fiori di ciliegio sistemati in un vaso di ceramica (decorazioni)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettiva categoria in "Personalizzazione stanza privata".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos artículos que incluye arreglos de flores de cerezo en jarrones de bambú y cerámica.\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos para la personalizar la sala.\n\n- Arreglo de flores de cerezo en recipiente de bambú (ornamentos de pared)\n- Arreglo de flores de cerezo en recipiente de cerámica (adorno)\n\n* Al adquirir este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su categoría correspondiente en "Personalización de la sala privada".[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">桜を竹の器に生けたものと陶器に生けたものの２点セット。\n本セットには、プライベートラウンジのカスタマイズ用の下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・竹の器に生けた桜/額・壁掛け装飾\n・陶器に生けた桜/装飾品\n\n※購入すると、「プライベートラウンジのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 2-piece set of cherry blossoms arranged in bamboo and ceramic vases.\nThis set includes the following items for customizing your private lounge:\n\n- Cherry Blossoms Arranged in Bamboo (Wall Hangings)\n- Cherry Blossoms Arranged in Ceramics (Ornaments)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category in "Private Lounge Customization".[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
