<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Valor Footlocker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Malle Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Valor-Truhe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scarpiera Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Baúl de Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ベッドトランクケース ベイラー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Valor 락커</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Valor Footlocker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Valor裝備箱</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Valor裝備箱</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Valor Footlocker</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Favouring straight forward construction and appearance, Valor furniture always works in any situation, from frozen battlefields to a tropical bunkhouse. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">De facture et d'apparence épurées, le mobilier Valor résistera à toutes les situations, des champs de bataille gelés aux bunkers tropicaux. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Valor-Möbel sind für einfache Bauweise und Design bekannt und eignen sich sowohl für gefrorene Schlachtfelder als auch für Schlafbaracken in den Tropen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'arredamento Valor, dalla linea e dall'aspetto semplice, è ideale per qualsiasi ambiente, dai campi di battaglia gelidi alle baracche tropicali. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con una estructura y apariencia sencillas, los muebles de Valor siempre van bien en cualquier situación, desde campos de batalla helados a barracones en la selva tropical. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">実務性を何より重視するベイラーらしいトランクだ。凍った戦場から南国のキャンプサイトまで、想定されるすべての戦場で最大の効果が得られる作りだ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">직관적인 디자인과 기능을 선호하는 Valor 답게, 눈보라가 휘날리는 설원이나, 땀이 비오듯하는 열대지방에서나 동일한 성능을 보장합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Favoring straight forward construction and appearance, Valor furniture always works in any situation, from frozen battlefields to a tropical bunkhouse. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">喜愛構造與外觀直截了當的Valor，其傢具總能在所有情況下使用，從凍僵的戰場到熱帶宿舍，無所不能。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">喜愛構造與外觀直截了當的Valor，其傢具總能在所有情況下使用，從凍僵的戰場到熱帶宿舍，無所不能。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Favoring straight forward construction and appearance, Valor furniture always works in any situation, from frozen battlefields to a tropical bunkhouse. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>