<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Jungle Riot Tank Top - True Blue (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Débardeur Jungle Riot - Bleu profond (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Jungle Riot Tanktop - Blau (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Jungle Riot Canottiera - Blu (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Jungle Riot Camiseta sin mangas - Azul auténtico (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Jungle Riot's soft, flowing knit with a tribal print makes it so easy to throw on, you won't want to take it off. Details like a handkerchief hem and a skinny tie across the back add a perfect amount of street edge to its beach chic. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La maille douce et légèrement flottante du débardeur Jungle Riot avec son imprimé tribal le rend si facile à porter que vous ne voudrez plus le quitter. Les détails tels que son ourlet à pointes et le mince nœud dans le dos ajoutent une touche citadine parfaite à son style plage très chic. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Jungle Riot Strickoberteil mit Dschungelmuster ist so weich und bequem, dass Sie es sicher nie wieder ausziehen wollen. Augenfällige Details wie der Zipfelsaum und der dünne Tie-Back verleihen dem modischen Strandtop einen Hauch von urbanem Chic. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La canottiera Jungle Riot in morbida maglia e con stampa tribale è così facile da indossare che non vorrai più togliertela. L'orlo a fazzoletto e il cordoncino sulla schiena aggiungono il giusto tocco di stile urbano a questo capo da spiaggia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El tejido flojo y suave de la Jungle Riot, junto a su estampado tribal, la hacen tan agradable de vestir que no querrás quitártela.  Detalles como los bajos con puntas y un delicado lazo cruzando la espalda añaden la dosis perfecta de modernidad urbana a su carácter chic y playero. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>