<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Female01_Torso_Nis_Tops_Disgaea3_001</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">T-shirt Raspberyl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">魔界戦記ディスガイア３　ラズベリル先生Ｔシャツ（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">마계전기 디스가이아3 라즈베릴 선생 T셔츠(여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Disgaea 3: Dean Raspberyl" T-shirt (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">魔界戰記 Disgaea 3 RASPBERYL老師T恤(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">魔界戰記 Disgaea 3 RASPBERYL老師T恤(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Raspberyl T-Shirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nis_Tops_Disgaea3_001_f</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Untitled</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un T-shirt d'après le personnage Raspberyl, un démon délinquant du Netherworld.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ラ・ラ・ララ・ラズベリル～♪ボランティア・マナー厳守・無遅刻無欠席☆魔界においては“不良”と称されるラズベリルが魔界邪悪学園の危機に立ち上がって、なんと凶師になっちゃった！学園に広がるボランティア精神と清く正しい正義の心。これは、逆に邪悪学園の危機？果たして学園からは今後、立派な魔王や魔神は輩出できるのか！？そんな『魔界戦記ディスガイア３　ラズベリル編』の配信を記念し、超ド級の“不良”色で、凶師ラズベリルのラブリーＴシャツが登場！魔界邪悪学園を変革したい皆はこれを着てラズベリルに続け！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">라,라,라라,라즈베릴~. 봉사활동, 매너 엄수, 무지각 무결석☆마계에 있어서는 "불량"으로 통하는 라즈베릴이 마계 사악학원의 위기에 일어나 무려 교사가 되었다! 학원에 널리 퍼지는 봉사활동 정신과 깨끗하고 올바른 정의의 마음. 이것은 반대로 사악학원의 위기? 학원에서는 앞으로 과연 휼륭한 마왕이나 마신을 배출할 수 있을 것인가!? 그런『마계전기 디스가이아3 라즈베릴 편』의 공개를 기념해 엄청난 "불량"색의 교사 라즈베릴의 러블리 T셔츠가 등장! 마계 사악학원을 변혁하려는 분은 이것을 입고 라즈베릴로 계속해서 진행! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Raspberyl was a model student, never tardy or absent, and always volunteering her time for good deeds--making her the No.1 Delinquent at Evil Academy. She spread her cheer and spirit for volunteering around campus, which triggered a crisis at the Academy, and somehow ended up as the Dean. How can they expect to churn out exceptional Overlords and Demon Lords at this rate!? Commemorate the Raspberyl Chapters of Disgaea 3 with this lovely T-shirt in a color only the worst of the worst delinquents would wear! Recommended for those who want to bring forth a revolution at the Nether Institute, Evil Academy! Goody two-shoes unite! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raspberyl有禮貌、不遲到、不缺席，有魔界頭號“不良少女”之稱的Raspberyl，成為了不良教師。且引起了魔界邪惡學園的危機，讓學園裡瀰漫著犠牲奉獻的精神及聖潔正直的正義感！換句話說，這就是邪惡學園的危機嗎？到底學園以後還會有出色的魔王或魔神崛起嗎？為了紀念『魔界戰記  Disgaea 3 RASPBERYL篇』推出，有著超“不良”色彩的不良教師Raspberyl的可愛T恤登場！想要改變 魔界邪惡學園的您，可以穿著這件T恤跟隨Raspberyl哦！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raspberyl有禮貌、不遲到、不缺席，有魔界頭號“不良少女”之稱的Raspberyl，成為了不良教師。且引起了魔界邪惡學園的危機，讓學園裡瀰漫著犠牲奉獻的精神及聖潔正直的正義感！換句話說，這就是邪惡學園的危機嗎？到底學園以後還會有出色的魔王或魔神崛起嗎？為了紀念『魔界戰記  Disgaea 3 RASPBERYL篇』推出，有著超“不良”色彩的不良教師Raspberyl的可愛T恤登場！想要改變 魔界邪惡學園的您，可以穿著這件T恤跟隨Raspberyl哦！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A T-shirt themed after Raspberyl, a demon delinquent from the Netherworld.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>