<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Disruption Shot Pistols (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pistolets à tir disruptif (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Disruptorpistole (weibliche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pistole distruttrici (per donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pistolas de disparos de interrupción (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ジャマーピストル（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Disruption Shot Pistols (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Disruption Shot Pistols (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">These highly-portable pistols are built from the disruption emitters harvested from a Bot Scout.  A notable improvement in the cooling systems allows for fifteen shots to be fired from each gun in rapid succession before cool-down time is needed. This item passively absorbs Nebulon, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base Nebulon gains by about 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ces pistolets faciles à porter sont construits d'émetteurs disruptifs récoltés sur un éclaireur Bot. Une amélioration notable du système de refroidissement permet à quinze coups d'être tirés de chaque pistolet en succession rapide avant qu'un temps de refroidissement soit nécessaire. Cet objet absorbe passivement le Nébulon, augmentant efficacement vos gains en Nébulon de base Novus Prime d'approximativement 5%.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese leicht zu tragende Pistole wurde aus Disruptoremittern gebaut, die aus einem Bot-Schiff geborgen wurden. Eine bemerkenswerte Weiterentwicklung im Kühlsystem erlaubt es, bis zu fünfzehn Schuss in extrem schneller Abfolge aus jeder Waffe abzufeuern, bevor eine Abkühlung nötig wird. Dieser Ausrüstungsgegenstand absorbiert zusätzlich Nebulon und erhöht die Zufuhr von Nebulon deiner Novus Prime Basis effektiv um ca. 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Queste scattanti pistole sono state costruite sfruttando gli emettitori di distruzione coltivati da un Bot Scout. Un notevole miglioramento del sistema di raffreddamento permette di sparare quindici colpi da entrambe le pistole in rapida successione, al quale segue un periodo di raffreddamento. Questo oggetto assorbe passivamente l'energia nebulon, incrementando l'assorbimento della stessa da parte della base Novus Prime di circa il 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estas pistolas altamente portátiles están construidas con emisores de interrupción recogidos de un robot explorador.  Una mejora notable en los sistemas de enfriamiento permite que quince disparos sean hechos de cada arma en sucesión rápida antes que tiempo de enfriamiento sea necesario. Este objeto absorbe Nebulón pasivamente, incrementado efectivamente tu base Novus Prime cerca de un 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">携帯性が極めて高いこれらのピストルはロボットスパイから回収した妨害放射装置から作られている。冷却装置における特筆すべき向上点は、冷却時間が必要になる前に各砲座から１５発の絶え間ない発射が可能になった事である。\n※購入すると、ミニゲーム「ノーバス・プライム」内でネブロンの増加量が5%上がります。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">These highly-portable pistols are built from the disruption emitters harvested from a Bot Scout.  A notable improvement in the cooling systems allows for fifteen shots to be fired from each gun in rapid succession before cool-down time is needed. This item passively absorbs Nebulon, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base Nebulon gains by about 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">These highly-portable pistols are built from the disruption emitters harvested from a Bot Scout.  A notable improvement in the cooling systems allows for fifteen shots to be fired from each gun in rapid succession before cool-down time is needed. This item passively absorbs Nebulon, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base Nebulon gains by about 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>