<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Talk to the man</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Parler à l'homme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sprechen Sie mit dem Mann.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Parla con l'uomo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Habla con el hombre</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Resistance 3™ Re-locator. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Station de téléportation Resistance 3™ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Resistance 3™"-Teleporter [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Teletrasporto di Resistance 3™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Relocalizador de Resistance 3™. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">npc_message</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Can you help us? We ain't having any luck finding any decent supplies here, so me and my boy are going to head over to the next town through this tunnel. Hopefully the Chimera would have moved on, leaving us free to gather what ever resources we can find. Come back soon and we can travel together, strength in numbers and all that!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous pourriez nous aider ? Il n'y a rien pour se ravitailler ici, alors je vais traverser ce tunnel avec mon fils pour rejoindre la ville la plus proche. J'espère que les Chimères seront parties, et qu'on pourra rassembler autant de ressources que possible. Revenez vite, comme ça on pourra voyager ensemble. L'union fait la force, pas vrai ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Können Sie uns helfen? Wir können hier keine brauchbaren Vorräte finden. Deshalb wollen mein Junge und ich jetzt durch diesen Tunnel in die nächste Stadt. Hoffentlich sind die Bestien schon weitergezogen, und wir können alles, was an Vorräten da ist, in Ruhe einsammeln. Kommen Sie bald zurück, dann können wir gemeinsam reisen – von wegen "zahlenmäßiger Überlegenheit" und so.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Puoi aiutarci? Purtroppo qui non siamo riusciti a trovare vettovaglie decenti, perciò io e il mio ragazzo ci dirigeremo verso la prossima città attraverso questa galleria. Speriamo che i Chimera se ne siano andati, almeno potremo recuperare tutte le risorse che ci servono. Torna presto, così potremo viaggiare insieme... L'unione fa la forza!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Puedes ayudarnos? Aquí no hemos logrado encontrar suministros decentes, así que mi chico y yo iremos al siguiente pueblo por este túnel. Espero que las quimeras hayan pasado ya y nos dejen recoger los recursos que encontremos. Vuelve pronto y podremos viajar juntos, la unión hace la fuerza y todo eso.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">npc_legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Sortir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE] Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE] Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] Salir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>