<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Soul Hunter Bundle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack chasseur d'âmes (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Seelenjäger - Paket (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completo Animanera (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de cazador de almas (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Omitted from SCEJ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">소울 헌터 세트 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Soul Hunter Bundle (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">靈魂獵人服裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">靈魂獵人服裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Soul Hunter Bundle (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Spawning a suit with blackened armour and jagged spikes isn't as easy as it looks. Bundle includes mask, top, bottom, shoes, and gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tout le monde ne peut pas porter cette armure noire à épines acérées. Le pack contient un masque, un haut et un bas de vêtement, des chaussures et des gants. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Einen Anzug mit geschwärzter Panzerung und Stacheln hervorzubringen, ist nicht so einfach, wie es erscheint. Zum Paket gehören Maske, Oberteil, Unterteil, Schuhe und Handschuhe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un vestito con corazza annerita con spuntoni acuminati. Il completo include maschera, parte superiore e inferiore, scarpe e guanti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Llevar un traje con armadura negra y púas no es tan sencillo como parece. El conjunto comprende una máscara, torso, pantalones, guantes y zapatos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Omitted from SCEJ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">검게 제련된 갑옷과 날카로운 스파이크를 착용하는 것은 생각 만큼 쉽지 않습니다. 이 세트는 소울 헌터 마스크, 소울 헌터 상의, 소울 헌터 하의, 소울 헌터 신발, 그리고 소울 헌터 장갑을 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Spawning a suit with blackened armor and jagged spikes isn't as easy as it looks. Bundle includes the Soul Hunter Mask, Soul Hunter Top, Soul Hunter Bottom, Soul Hunter Shoes, and Soul Hunter Gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">穿著一套燻黑的盔甲和長釘沒有看上去那麼容易。組合包包括靈魂獵人面具、靈魂獵人服裝-上身、靈魂獵人服裝-下身、靈魂獵人鞋及靈魂獵人手套。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">穿著一套燻黑的盔甲和長釘沒有看上去那麼容易。組合包包括靈魂獵人面具、靈魂獵人服裝-上半身、靈魂獵人服裝-下半身、靈魂獵人鞋及靈魂獵人手套。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Spawning a suit with blackened armor and jagged spikes isn't as easy as it looks. Bundle includes mask, top, bottom, shoes, and gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>