<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mysterious Emblem /Red Circle (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Emblème mystérieux/Cercle rouge (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mysteriöses Emblem/Roter Kreis (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Emblema misterioso/Cerchio rosso (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Emblema misterioso círculo rojo (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ミステリーエンブレム・レッドサークル・男性用</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Male01_Hands_mark</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Male01_Hands_mark</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Male01_Hands_mark</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Male01_Hands_mark</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mysterious Emblem /Red Circle (Men)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Emblem to get mysterious power from space. For male.\n
Equipping this item raises the amount of experience points gained while playing the Abduction Simulator.\n
The amount of experience gained increases with other same-valued items.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Emblème permettant d'obtenir un pouvoir mystérieux de l'espace. Pour homme.\n Utilisez-le pour augmenter la quantité de points d'expérience gagnés avec le simulateur d'enlèvement.\n Vous pouvez gagner un bonus supplémentaire, en plus de l'augmentation des points d'expérience.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Emblem, das einem mysteriöse Kraft aus dem All verleiht. Für Herren.\n
Erhöht die Anzahl der Erfahrungspunkte im Entführungssimulator.\n
Ein weiterer Bonus kann hinzugefügt werden, die Erhöhung der Erfahrungspunkte ausgenommen.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Emblema per ricevere un misterioso potere dallo spazio. Per uomo.\n
Utilizzandolo, la quantità di punti esperienza in Rapimento simulato verrà incrementata. \n
Possono essere aggiunti altri bonus tranne quelli relativi all'incremento di punti esperienza.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Emblema para obtener poder misterioso del espacio. Para hombre.\n
Al equipártelo, se dobla la cantidad de puntos de experiencia en Abduction Simulator.\n
Se pueden añadir otras bonificaciones, excepto las de aumentar la cantidad de puntos de experiencia.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">宇宙から強大な力を受け取れる紋章・男性用。\n装着しているとアブダクトシミュレーターに「獲得経験値UP」のボーナスが付きます。\nこのアイテムは他の「獲得経験値UP」ボーナスと組み合わせても追加ボーナス効果は得られませんが、他のボーナスとの加算効果はあります。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Male01_Hands_mark [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Male01_Hands_mark [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Male01_Hands_mark [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Male01_Hands_mark [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Emblem to get mysterious power from space. For male. \nEquipping this item raises the amount of experience points gained while playing the Abduction Simulator.\n The amount of experience gained increases with other same-valued items.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>