<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to the Music Unlimited Club</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue au Club Music Unlimited</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen beim Music Unlimited-Club</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuto nel Club di Music Unlimited</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te damos la bienvenida al club de Music Unlimited</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sign up for the free 30 day trial of Music Unlimited on the PlayStation®Store to listen to all of your favourite artists, albums and songs now. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Inscrivez-vous à l'essai gratuit de 30 jours de Music Unlimited sur le PlayStation®Store pour écouter dès maintenant tous vos artistes, vos albums et vos titres préférés. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Melde dich jetzt für eine 30-tägige Testversion von Music Unlimited im PlayStation®Store an, um dir die besten Künstler, Alben und Lieder anzuhören. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Richiedi la prova gratuita di 30 giorni di Music Unlimited sul PlayStation®Store per ascoltare subito tutti i tuoi interpreti, album e brani preferiti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Suscríbete a la prueba gratuita de 30 días de Music Unlimited en PlayStation®Store para escuchar tus artistas, álbumes y canciones favoritos. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kNotice</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Remember if you're a previous Music Unlimited subscriber, you will not be eligible for the free trial. Sign up now for the premium service from just £4.99 per month!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour rappel, si vous avez déjà été abonné à Music Unlimited, vous ne pouvez pas bénéficier de l'essai gratuit. Abonnez-vous maintenant au service Premium pour seulement 4,99 € par mois !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beachte bitte, dass ehemalige Music Unlimited-Abonnenten keinen Anspruch auf eine Gratis-Testversion haben. Melde dich jetzt für den Premium-Service an - ab 4,99 € im Monat!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ricorda che se in passato sei già stato iscritto a Music Unlimited, non potrai richiedere la prova gratuita. Richiedi il servizio premium a soli €4,99 al mese!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Recuerda que, si has estado suscrito alguna vez a Music Unlimited, no podrás disfrutar de la prueba gratuita. ¡Suscríbete al servicio Premium por solo 4,99 € al mes!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kEnterHere</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Enter here to receive your free 30 day voucher code.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Entrez ici pour recevoir votre code de bon d'achat et bénéficier de 30 jours gratuits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hol dir hier deinen kostenlosen Gutschein-Code für 30 Tage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Accedi qui per richiedere il tuo codice voucher valido per ottenere 30 giorni gratuiti.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Solicita aquí el vale de descarga para probar el servicio gratis durante 30 días.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kSuccess</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Congratulations! Download the Music Unlimited app from the XMB and enjoy limitless music at the touch of a button</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bravo ! Téléchargez l'application Music Unlimited depuis le menu XMB et profitez de toute la musique que vous aimez en toute simplicité</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Herzlichen Glückwunsch! Lade dir die Music Unlimited-App im XMB-Menü herunter und genieß unbegrenzte Musik auf Tastendruck.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Congratulazioni! Scarica l'app di Music Unlimited dal menu XMB e ascolta musica senza limiti con il solo tocco di un pulsante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Enhorabuena! Descarga la aplicación Music Unlimited desde el menú XMB y disfruta de música sin límites con solo tocar un botón</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kFailure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Unfortunately Music Unlimited is not available in your region.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Malheureusement, Music Unlimited n'est pas disponible dans votre zone géographique.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Leider ist Music Unlimited in deiner Region nicht verfügbar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Purtroppo Music Unlimited non è disponibile nel tuo Paese.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Por desgracia, Music Unlimited no está disponible en tu región.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kAccept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] Continuer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] Weiter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] Continua</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] Continuar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kQuit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CIRCLE] Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CIRCLE] Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CIRCLE] Beenden</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CIRCLE] Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CIRCLE] Salir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>