<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Stick Up Kid Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack voyou</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gauner-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Dici a me?!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de atracador</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">반항아 번들 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Stick Up Kid Bundle (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">潮童服裝組(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">潮童服裝組(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Stick Up Kid Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Walk around the mean streets of PlayStation®Home in style with the Stick Up Kid bundle! From a diamond eye patch, to gold brass knuckles, to skinny jeans, to Gold Guns and a tie. This bundle has it all! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Traînez dans les rues hostiles de PlayStation®Home avec style grâce au pack voyou. Avec le bandeau diamant, le poing américain doré, le slim, les revolvers dorés et la cravate, il y a tout ce qu'il faut ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beweg dich mit Stil durch die harten Straßen von PlayStation®Home – mit dem Gauner-Paket! Von der Diamant-Augenklappe über den goldenen Schlagring und enge Jeans bis zur goldenen Pistole und einer Krawatte – in diesem Paket fehlt einfach nichts! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fatti rispettare con stile lungo le strade di PlayStation®Home con il pacchetto Dici a me?! Non manca niente: benda per occhio con diamante, tirapugni in ottone dorato, jeans attillati, pistole d'oro e cravatta. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Camina por las calles de PlayStation®Home con estilo con el conjunto de atracador! Un parche para el ojo de diamante, un puño americano dorado, vaqueros ajustados, pistolas doradas y corbata. ¡Este conjunto lo tiene todo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">PlayStation®Home의 비열한 거리를 걷는 도중에는 스타일을 챙겨야 합니다. 이 번들은 헤어 스타일, 신발, 다이아몬드 안대, 황금 너클스, 스키니 진, 권총, 그리고 넥타이를 포함합니다. 모든 것을 갖춘 번들입니다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Walk around the mean streets of PlayStation®Home in style with the Stick Up Kid bundle! From a hairdo, to shoes, to diamond eye patch, to gold brass knuckles, to skinny jeans, to Gold Guns and a tie. This bundle has it all! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">以潮童服裝組在趨炎附勢的PlayStation®Home街道上展現你的個人風格！有潮童髮型、潮童鞋、鑽石眼罩、潮童閃耀指節銅環、緊身牛仔褲、黃金手槍和領帶。這服裝組應有盡有！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">以潮童服裝組在趨炎附勢的PlayStation®Home街道上展現你的個人風格！有潮童髮型、潮童鞋、鑽石眼罩、潮童閃耀指節銅環、緊身牛仔褲、黃金手槍和領帶。這服裝組應有盡有！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Walk around the mean streets of PlayStation®Home in style with the Stick Up Kid bundle! From a diamond eye patch, to gold brass knuckles, to skinny jeans, to Gold Guns and a tie. This bundle has it all! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>