<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Lovely Stool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Charmant Tabouret</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schöne Hocker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bello Sgabello</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Taburete Encantador</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Valentines day, the quality and attention to detail of Altamar blend with romance to create this exclusive line. This limited edition is a unique design, accompanied by a line of warm and captivating accessories. Fall in love with class, fall in love with Altamar.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En ce jour de Saint-Valentin, la qualité et l'attention portée au détail d'Altamar s'allient au romantisme pour créer cette ligne exclusive. Cette édition limitée est une création unique, accompagnée d'une gamme d'accessoires chaleureux et captivants. Tombez amoureux avec classe, tombez amoureux avec Altamar.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">An diesem Valentinstag vermischen sich die Qualität und Liebe zum Detail von Altamar mit der Romantik, um diese exklusive Linie zu erschaffen. Diese limitierte Edition hat ein einzigartiges Design und wird von einer Reihe warmen und fesselnden Zubehörs begleitet. Verlieben Sie sich in Klasse, verlieben Sie sich in Altamar.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il giorno di San Valentino, la qualità e l’attenzione ai dettagli di Altamar si fondono con il sentimento romantico, dando vita a questa linea esclusiva. Questa edizione limitata è caratterizzata da un design speciale, accompagnato da una linea di accessori accattivanti e sensuali. Innamorati con classe, innamorati con Altamar.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este San Valentin, la calidad de Altamar se funde con el gusto por el detalle y el romanticismo creando esta línea exclusiva. Una edición limitada que da paso a un diseño único acompañado de una línea de accesorios cálida y cautivadora. Enamórate con clase, enamórate con Altamar[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>