<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Eliminator</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Home Square Mini game</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Beat the Eliminator by reaching the final nodes on the top level.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Battez l'Eliminator en atteignant les nœuds finaux du niveau supérieur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Besiegen Sie den Eliminator, indem Sie die letzten Knoten auf der oberen Ebene erreichen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sconfiggi l'Eliminatore raggiungendo i nodi finali sul livello più alto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Llega a los últimos nodos del nivel superior para vencer al Eliminador.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Confirm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [CROSS] to dismiss</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyez sur [CROSS] pour fermer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit [CROSS] schließen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi [CROSS] per annullare</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa [CROSS] para descartar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">turn_player</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Player Turn:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tour du joueur :</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zug Spieler:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Turno del giocatore:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Turno del jugador:</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">turn_eliminator</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Eliminator Move</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mouvement de l'Eliminator</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zug Eliminator</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mossa dell'Eliminatore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Movimiento del Eliminador</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">SCORE:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">SCORE:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">PUNKTE:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">PUNTEGGIO:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">PUNTUACIÓN:</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">bonus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">BONUS:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">BONUS:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">BONUS:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">BONUS:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">BONIFICACIÓN:</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">joining</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">waiting to start…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Attente du départ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wartet auf Spielstart ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">in attesa dell'inizio...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">esperando para empezar...</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">eliminated</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Elimination!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Élimination !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eliminiert!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Eliminazione!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Eliminación!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">congrats</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Congratulations! You beat the Eliminator!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Félicitations, vous avez battu l'Eliminator !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gratulation! Sie haben den Eliminator besiegt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Congratulazioni! Hai sconfitto l'Eliminatore!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Enhorabuena! ¡Has vencido al Eliminador!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">refresh</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Refreshing…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rafraîchissement…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aktualisieren …</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aggiornamento…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Actualizando…</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">multiplier</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">BONUS MULTIPLIER:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">MULTIPLICATEUR DE BONUS:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">BONUSMULTIPLIKATOR:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">MOLTIPLICATORE BONUS:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">MULTIPLICADOR:</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Each turn you have 4 seconds to move one node in any direction. Then the Eliminator moves.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">À chaque tour vous avez 4 secondes pour déplacer un noeud vers n'importe quelle direction. Ensuite, c'est à l'Eliminator de se déplacer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bei jedem Zug hast du 4 Sekunden, um dich in einer beliebigen Richtung einen Knotenpunkt weiterzubewegen. Dann bewegt sich der Eliminator.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ad ogni turno hai 4 secondi per spostarti di un nodo in qualsiasi direzione.  Dopodiché toccherà all'Eliminatore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">En cada turno tienes 4 segundos para mover un nodo en cualquier dirección. Después, moverá el Eliminador.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If it moves onto your node you will be sent back to the starting nodes at the bottom.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">S'il arrive sur le même nœud que vous, vous serez renvoyé au nœud de départ, en bas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Falls er sich auf Ihren Knoten bewegt, werden Sie zu den Startknoten unten zurückgeschickt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se lui muove sul tuo nodo, tu verrai rispedito in basso, ai nodi iniziali.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si se mueve a tu nodo, deberás volver a los nodos iniciales de la parte inferior.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Reaching the teleport nodes on one level will move you up to the starting nodes of the next level.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si vous atteignez un nœud de téléportation, vous serez envoyé au nœud de départ du niveau suivant.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erreichen Sie die Teleporterknoten eines Levels, werden Sie zum Startknoten des nächsten Levels hinaufgesetzt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una volta raggiunti i nodi di teletrasporto di un livello passerai ai nodi iniziali del livello successivo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si llegas a los nodos de teletransporte de un nivel, accederás a los nodos iniciales del siguiente.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You score bonus points for every move you make, but only bank these points when you reach the next level.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous marquez des points bonus à chacun de vos mouvements, mais ils ne sont comptabilisés que si vous atteignez le niveau suivant.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Für jeden Zug erhalten Sie Bonuspunkte, die erst dann angerechnet werden, wenn Sie das nächste Level erreichen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ottieni punti bonus per ogni mossa, ma vengono conteggiati solo se raggiungi il livello successivo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Obtienes puntos de bonificación por cada movimiento que realices, pero solo se acumulan si superas el nivel.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Look out for Powerups which will show you the current position of the eliminator or grant you a Bonus Multiplier.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Guettez les améliorations qui vous indiqueront la position actuelle de l'Eliminator ou vous donneront un multiplicateur de bonus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Halten Sie Ausschau nach Powerups, die Ihnen die derzeitige Position des Eliminators verraten oder Ihnen einen Bonusmultiplikator verschaffen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cerca i potenziamenti che ti potranno mostrare l'attuale posizione dell'Eliminatore o fornire un moltiplicatore bonus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Busca los potenciadores para conocer la posición actual del Eliminador y obtener multiplicadores de bonificación.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Good luck!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bonne chance !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Viel Glück!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Buona fortuna!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Buena suerte!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>