<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Raven Gun Display Case</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Présentoir armes Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Raven-Waffenregal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bacheca armi Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estante para armas de Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">銃展示ケース レーヴン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Raven 총기 진열대</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Raven Gun Display Case</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raven槍械展示架</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raven槍械展示架</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Raven Gun Display Case</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">When storing their high tech firearms, Raven like show off how good their equipment looks.  Visitors prefer to see them in the rack, as opposed to looking down the barrel. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lorsque les soldats de Raven rangent leurs armes high-tech, ils aiment les mettre en valeur. Les invités préfèrent les voir sur les râteliers, plutôt que pointées vers eux. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bei der Aufbewahrung ihrer Waffen prahlen Raven-Soldaten gerne damit, wie gut ihre Ausrüstung eigentlich aussieht. Besucher bevorzugen es, sie ausgestellt zu sehen – eher unbeliebt hingegen ist die Frontalansicht in den Lauf. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I Raven ci tengono a mettere in mostra il loro equipaggiamento sofisticato quando conservano le loro armi. Gli ospiti preferiscono ammirare le armi in questa bacheca piuttosto che trovarsi la canna puntata i mezzo agli occhi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuando guardan sus armas de última tecnología, a los soldados de Raven les gusta fardar del buen aspecto que tienen. La verdad es que los visitantes prefieren ver las armas expuestas antes que apuntándoles directamente a la cara. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">レーヴンは最新鋭の武器を見せびらかすのが好きだ。それを意識した収納デザインも納得がいく。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">고성능 총기를 보관할 때, Raven은 자신들의 장비가 얼마나 멋진 모습을 가졌는지 자랑하고 싶어합니다. 방문객들 역시 진열된 총기를 보는 것이, 자신들을 겨눈 총기를 보는 것보다는 낫다고 생각합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">When storing their high tech firearms, Raven likes to show off how good their equipment looks. Visitors prefer to see them in the rack, as opposed to looking down the barrel. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raven在存放其高科技武器時，喜歡炫耀這些器材有多亮眼。參觀者只喜歡看到武器放在展示架上，而絕不願意望著對準自己的槍口。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raven在存放其高科技武器時，喜歡炫耀這些器材有多亮眼。參觀者只喜歡看到武器放在展示架上，而絕不願意望著對準自己的槍口。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">When storing their high tech firearms, Raven likes to show off how good their equipment looks. Visitors prefer to see them in the rack, as opposed to looking down the barrel. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>