<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Pulse Field Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Siège à champ pulsé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Impulsfeld-Stuhl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sedia con campo a impulsi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Silla de campo pulsante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Pulse Field Chair</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Protected by the force field generated by this chair, your avatar can completely negate the special powers of other avatars. BONUS: unlocks the Pulse Field gadget for use in MiniBots: Battlebox and in MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Protégé par le champ de force généré par ce siège, votre avatar pourra totalement annihiler les pouvoirs spéciaux des autres avatars. BONUS : déverrouille le gadget Champ pulsé utilisable dans MiniBots : Battlebox et dans MiniBots multijoueur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Von dem Kraftfeld, das dieser Stuhl erzeugt, geschützt, kann Ihr Avatar die speziellen Kräfte der anderen Avatare vollständig abwehren. BONUS: Schaltet das Impulsfeld-Gadget für die Anwendung in MiniBots: Battlebox und MiniBots-Multiplayer-Modus frei. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Protetto dalla forza del campo generato da questa sedia, il tuo avatar può contrastare completamente i poteri speciali degli altri avatar. BONUS: sblocca il gadget Campo a impulsi per usarlo in MiniBots: Battlebox e modalità multigiocatore di MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tu avatar puede anular totalmente los poderes especiales de otros avatares cuando esté protegido por el campo de fuerzas generado por esta silla. BONUS:  libera el dispositivo Campo pulsante para utilizarlo en MiniBots: Battlebox y el modo varios jugadores de MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Protected by the force field generated by this chair, your avatar can completely negate the special powers of other avatars. BONUS: unlocks the Pulse Field gadget for use in MiniBots: Battlebox and in MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>