<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">EG-X Table</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">EG-X Table</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Table EG-X</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">EG-X-Tisch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tavolo EG-X</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mesa de EG-X</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">EG-X Table</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">EGX 탁자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">EGX Table</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">EGX 桌子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">EGX 桌子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">EG-X Table</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Today you can solve the problem of where you’re going to place those new WipEout® trophies. What better than this lavish, glass-topped EG-X coffee table?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Today you can solve the problem of where you’re going to place those new WipEout® trophies. What better than this lavish, glass-topped EG-X coffee table? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aujourd'hui, vous pouvez résoudre le problème du rangement de vos nouveaux trophées WipEout®. Où seront-ils mieux mis en valeur que dans cette superbe table à café EG-X, dotée d'un plateau en verre ? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Heute weiß endlich jeder, wohin er seine neuen WipEout®-Trophäen stellen kann. Welcher Ort eignet sich auch besser als dieser edle EG-X-Couchtisch mit Glasplatte?  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ora saprete dove riporre i nuovi trofei WipEout®. Cosa c’è di meglio di questo lussuoso tavolo da caffé in vetro EG-X? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ya tienes respuesta a la pregunta de dónde colocar esos nuevos trofeos de WipEout®. ¿Qué mejor que esta espléndida mesita de café de cristal de EG-X? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Today you can solve the problem of where you’re going to place those new WipEout® trophies. What better than this lavish, glass-topped EG-X coffee table? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이제 당신의 WipEout 트로피 보관 문제가 해결되었습니다. 유리로 마감된 EGX 탁자보다 잘 어울리는 가구는 없을 겁니다. 중국과 스웨덴을 뿌리로 삼는 팀답게, 이 탁자는 튼튼한 품질에도 불구하고 저렴한 가격대를 가지고 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Today you can solve the problem of where you’re going to place those new Wipeout trophies. What better than this lavish, glass-topped EG-X coffee table? Befitting the Chinese and Swedish heritage of the team itself, this piece is both affordable and flat packed for home construction. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">有了這個設計奢華、以玻璃蓋面的EG-X咖啡桌，您便可以有一個最適合的地方來放置您的WipEout獎盃了。製作人員來自中國和瑞典，正好反映在這件價錢合理、需要自行組裝的家具上。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">有了這個設計奢華、以玻璃蓋面的EG-X咖啡桌，您便可以有一個最適合的地方來放置您的WipEout獎盃了。製作人員來自中國和瑞典，正好反映在這件價錢合理、需要自行組裝的家具上。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Today you can solve the problem of where you’re going to place those new WipEout® trophies. What better way than this lavish, glass-topped EG-X coffee table? [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>