<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Nis_Dots_No018</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Personnage 2D: Raspberyl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドットオブジェ　魔界の不良　ラズベリル</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">도트 오브제 마계의 불량 라즈베릴</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Raspberyl: Netherworld Delinquent" Sprite Statue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">像素雕像 魔界的不良少女RASPBERYL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">像素雕像 魔界的不良少女RASPBERYL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">2D Character Objects: Raspberyl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nis_dot_No018</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Untitled</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La statuette d'un personnage que tu peux mettre dans ta chambre pour décorer.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ピンク！それは窮極の不良の証！（『魔界戦記ディスガイア３』に限ります）掲げるは、正義と愛とボランティア精神が押し詰まったラブリーバイブル！注目を浴びたいという強い意思によって、悪魔であるにも関わらず自ら清く正しい道を進んだアウトロー。マオの幼馴染だが、彼とは正反対のロードを極めるラズベリル。二人は宿敵！「学園の立て直しだって任せとけ！魔界の明日はどっちだ！？さぁ皆、あたいについてきな！」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">핑크! 그것은 궁극의 불량의 증거! (『마계전기 디스가이아3』에 한해서입니다）그녀의 슬로건, 정의와 사랑과 봉사활동 정신에 사로잡힌 라즈베릴! 주목을 끌고 싶다는 강한 의지에 따라, 악마임에도 불구하고 스스로 깨끗하고 올바른 길을 걸어가는 무법자. 마오의 소꿉친구지만, 그와는 정반대의 길을 추구하는 라즈베릴. 두 사람은 숙적!「학원의 재건도 맡겨달라구! 마계의 내일은 어느 쪽!? 자, 모두, 나를 따라와!」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Pink is the ultimate color of badness! (only in Disgaea 3). Somehow it symbolizes the depths of justice, love, a volunteering spirit, and other delinquent activities. She's a demon, but it doesn't matter. Raspberyl has chosen to be a rebel by walking the path of righteousness. She was childhood friends with Mao, but they both went their separate ways. Now they are archenemies! "I'll make this Academy shine! Where is the Netherworld headed tomorrow? Follow me everyone!" [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">粉紅色，就是最凶惡不良的證明 ！（只限『魔界戰記 Disgaea 3』）背負著正義、愛及犠牲奉獻的精神於一身，強烈想成為眾人的焦點，不管是否為離經叛道，不顧一切朝著聖潔的路走。雖是Mao的青梅竹馬，但Raspberyl和他走的是完全不同的人生道路。二人是宿敵！「學園的重整就交給我！魔界的明天會在誰手上！？大家跟著我就對了！」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">粉紅色，就是最凶惡不良的證明 ！（只限『魔界戰記 Disgaea 3』）背負著正義、愛及犠牲奉獻的精神於一身，強烈想成為眾人的焦點，不管是否為離經叛道，不顧一切朝著聖潔的路走。雖是Mao的青梅竹馬，但Raspberyl和他走的是完全不同的人生道路。二人是宿敵！「學園的重整就交給我！魔界的明天會在誰手上！？大家跟著我就對了！」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A small character statue that you can place to decorate your own room.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>