<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">22 pairs of sneakers bundle(Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bundle de 22 paires de baskets (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">22 Turnschuhe (Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">22 Tennis (per le donne)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">22 Zapatillas (para las mujeres)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">22 pairs of sneakers bundle(Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">22 pairs of sneakers bundle(Women)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This bundle for women contains exclusive animated sneakers, with a pulsating neon streak in the sole cycling through all colours. The other 21 sneakers are: yellow, US flag, union jack, black studded, white, pink studded, bat, rose pattern, black, chocolate, leopard, blue, red, red glitter, pink, pink glitter, purple glitter, green, grey pattern, orange and red crocodile skin. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce bundle pour femme contient des baskets animées exclusives, dont la semelle contient une bande lumineuse qui varie en intensité et change de couleur. Les 21 autres paires de baskets sont les suivantes: jaunes, USA, drapeau britannique, cloutées noires, blanches, cloutées roses, chauve-souris, motifs floraux de roses, noires, chocolat, léopard, bleues, rouges, rouges à paillettes, roses, roses à paillettes, violettes à paillettes, vertes, motif gris, orange, et croco rouge.    [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diser bundle enthält 21 beiläufigen Turnschuhe, und die exklusiv animierte Turnschuhe mit pulsierenden Neon-Licht. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">21 scarpe da tennis casuali, e le tennis animate esclusive: cambiamenti di luce è incorporato nella suola, più o meno intenso, passa lentamente attraverso tutti i colori dell'arcobaleno. . [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">21 zapatillas ocasionales, van a quedar bien en cualquier ocasión, y las zapatillas animadas exclusivas: una futurista luz cambiante en la planta del pie, que varían en intensidad, pasa lentamente a través de todos los colores del arco iris[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This bundle for women contains exclusive animated sneakers, with a pulsating neon streak in the sole cycling through all colours. The other 21 sneakers are: yellow, US flag, union jack, black studded, white, pink studded, bat, rose pattern, black, chocolate, leopard, blue, red, red glitter, pink, pink glitter, purple glitter, green, grey pattern, orange and red crocodile skin. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This bundle for women contains exclusive animated sneakers, with a pulsating neon streak in the sole cycling through all colors. The other 21 sneakers are: yellow, US flag, union jack, black studded, white, pink studded, bat, rose pattern, black, chocolate, leopard, blue, red, red glitter, pink, pink glitter, purple glitter, green, grey pattern, orange and red crocodile skin. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>