<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - All Day Puff Jacket - Camo (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Blouson bouffant All Day- Camouflage (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - All Day Puff Jacke - Tarnfarbe (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - All Day Puff Giacca - Mimetica (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - All Day Puff Chaqueta - Camuflaje (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Lightweight puff jacket is indispensable for its classic design, top quality, and rugged durability. Distinct details include a multi colored zip closure, side pockets, and a logo patch at the chest. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Blouson léger bouffant, indispensable pour sa conception classique, sa qualité élevée et sa grande solidité. Parmi les détails caractéristiques figurent une fermeture zippée multicolore, des poches latérales et un patch logo sur la poitrine. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese hochwertige, leichte, aber dennoch robuste Steppjacke im klassischen Stil darf in keinem Kleiderschrank fehlen. Zu besonderen Details zählen der mehrfarbige Reißverschluss, die Seitentaschen und das Logoetikett auf der Brust. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo leggero piumino è indispensabile con il suo design classico, l'alta qualità e la robustezza. I dettagli esclusivi comprendono zip multicolore, tasche laterali e toppa con logo sul petto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta chaqueta ligera y acolchada es indispensable por su diseño clásico, su calidad superior, su resistencia y durabilidad. Entre los detalles distintivos destacan un cierre de cremallera multicolor, bolsillos laterales y un parche con el logotipo en el pecho. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>