<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Commander's Dress Uniform Shoes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaussures pour Uniforme de Cérémonie de Commandant</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kommandanten Uniform - Handschuhe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scarpe dell'uniforme del Comandante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Zapatos del uniforme de comandante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コマンダーのドレスユニフォーム・シューズ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사령관의 유니폼 신발</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Commander's Dress Uniform Shoes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">指挥官套装鞋</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">指挥官套装鞋</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Commander's Dress Uniform Shoes</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is a piece of the Novus Prime Commander's Dress Uniform Set. Suit up and command respect from your subordinates at any event or occasion. Earn all five pieces by achieving higher levels in Novus Prime! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Voici une pièce de l'Uniforme de Cérémonie de Commandant de Novus Prime. Distingué et inspirant le respect à vos subordonnés lors n'importe quel évènement ou occasion. 
Rassemblez les 5 parties en terminant les niveaux supérieurs de Novus Prime! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Teil der Uniform des Kommandanten von Novus Prime. 
Uniformiere dich und ernte bei jedem Ereignis oder Anlass Respekt von deinen Untergebenen. 
Erwerbe alle 5 Teile in dem du höhere Level auf Novus Prime erreichst! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa è una parte dell'uniforme del Comandante della Novus Prime. Equipaggiala e pretendi rispetto dai tuoi subordinati in ogni occasione o evento. Ottieni tutte e 5 le parti raggiungendo livelli più elevati nella Novus Prime! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta es una pieza del conjunto del uniforme de comandante de Novus Prime. Póntelo y comanda con respecto de tus subordinados en cualquier evento u ocasión. ¡Gana todas las cinco piezas alcanzando los altos niveles en Novus Prime! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">これはノーバス・プライムにおけるコマンダーのドレスユニフォームセットのひとつ。盛装して、イベントなどことある機会に部下からの尊敬を得よう。ノーバス・プライムで高いレベルを達成して５つすべてを手に入れよう！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이것은 노버스 프라임 사령관의 유니폼 세트이다. 복장을 갖추고 어떤 사태나 사항에 맞게 당신의 부하에게 존경을 명하라. 노버스 프라임에서 가장 높은 단계를 달성하여 다섯개 모두를 적립하라. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This is a piece of the Novus Prime Commander's Dress Uniform Set. Suit up and command respect from your subordinates at any event or occasion. Earn all five pieces by achieving higher levels in Novus Prime! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">这是若瓦斯总司令的指挥官套装。
穿上它并让你的部下无论任何的事件以及场合下都听从您所下达的指令。
提升等级来获得所有指挥官套件吧！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">这是若瓦斯总司令的指挥官套装。
穿上它并让你的部下无论任何的事件以及场合下都听从您所下达的指令。
提升等级来获得所有指挥官套件吧！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This is a piece of the Novus Prime Commander's Dress Uniform Set. Suit up and command respect from your subordinates at any event or occasion. Earn all five pieces by achieving higher levels in Novus Prime! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>