<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wrangler - On The Edge Robyn Blazer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Wrangler — Blazer On The Edge Robyn</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wrangler -  Top-Blazer Robyn</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Wrangler - Blazer modello Robyn</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Wrangler - Blazer On The Edge Robyn</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Wrangler - On The Edge Robyn Blazer (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Wrangler - On The Edge Robyn Blazer (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Wrangler - On The Edge Robyn Blazer (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Wrangler - On The Edge Robyn Blazer (Women)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Chic and easy, a stylish denim blazer on a rich blue shade comes with a shawl collar lapel, double button fastening at the front and mock tab pockets at the sides. With a high waisted design, this blazer features double button cuffs. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chic et simple, un blazer stylé en denim avec une teinte bleu profond, col châle à revers, fermeture à double bouton sur le devant et poches à rabat sur les côtés. Avec sa coupe à taille haute, ce blazer a des poignets à doubles boutons. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Chick und leicht, ein stylischer Jeansblazer in sattem Blau mit einem Schalkragen-Revers, Doppelknopfverschluss vorn und angedeuteten Seitentaschen. Dieser Blazer hat eine hohe Taille und Doppelknopf-Manschetten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chic e pratico da indossare, questo elegante blazer in jeans di colore blu intenso presenta un bavero a scialle, allacciatura frontale a due bottoni e tasche finte laterali. Inoltre è arricchito da un design a vita alta e da polsini a doppio bottone. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Simple y chic, un blazer en un fuerte tono azul vaquero, presenta solapas chal, dobles botones frontales y falsas lengüetas de bolsillo a uno y otro lado.  Con un diseño de cintura alta, este blazer tiene también puños de doble botón. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>