<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">DUST 514™: Minmatar Logistics Dropsuit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">DUST 514™ : Combinaison de soutien Minmatar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">DUST 514™: Minmatar-Logistikkampfanzug</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">DUST 514™: Armatura logistica Minmatar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">DUST 514™: traje de salto de logística Minmatar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not localised</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not localised</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not localised</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not localised</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not localised</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">DUST 514™: Minmatar Logistics Dropsuit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Native Minmatar tech favors straightforward solutions, a consequence of the fledgling nation’s indigent past. Used to working with limited resources, Minmatar scientists and engineers have made good use of the cutting-edge equipment allocated to them, creating a high-tech armor system that is at once an homage to the traditions of the past, and a bold statement that speaks to the future of the Minmatar people. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La technologie issue de Minmatar privilégie les solutions simples, une conséquence du passé nécessiteux de cette nouvelle nation. Habitués à travailler avec des ressources limitées, les scientifiques et les ingénieurs de Minmatar ont optimisé l'équipement de pointe à leur disposition pour créer un système d'armures innovant, qui rend à la fois hommage au passé de Minmatar et appréhende audacieusement l'avenir de ce jeune peuple. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Technologie der Minmatar bevorzugt einfache Lösungen ausgelegt, was aus der mittellosen Vergangenheit dieser Nation rührt. Die Wissenschaftler und Ingenieure der Minmatar mussten schon oft mit begrenzten Ressourcen arbeiten. Sie setzten die ihnen zugewiesene, hochmoderne Ausrüstung effizient ein, um ein Hightech-Panzerungssystem zu schaffen, das eine Hommage an die Traditionen der Vergangenheit und gleichzeitig ein Zeichen für die Zukunft der Minmatar ist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La tecnologia Minmatar offre soluzioni semplici, influenzate dal passato indigente della nuova nazione. Abituati a lavorare con risorse limitate, gli scienziati e gli ingegneri di Minmatar hanno fatto buon uso delle attrezzature all'avanguardia assegnategli, riuscendo a creare un'armatura altamente tecnologica che rappresenta al contempo un omaggio alle tradizioni del passato e una decisa apertura al futuro del popolo di Minmatar  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La tecnología Minmatar de este traje favorece las soluciones simples, como consecuencia del pasado sin fondos de una nación en ciernes. Apto para entornos con recursos limitados, los científicos e ingenieros de Minmatar supieron dar buen uso a este equipo y dotarlo de un sistema de blindaje de alta tecnología que rinde culto a las tradiciones del pasado y, al mismo tiempo, refleja el futuro de sus habitantes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not localised [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not localised [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not localised [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not localised [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not localised [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Native Minmatar tech favors straightforward solutions, a consequence of the fledgling nation’s indigent past. Used to working with limited resources, Minmatar scientists and engineers have made good use of the cutting-edge equipment allocated to them, creating a high-tech armor system that is at once an homage to the traditions of the past, and a bold statement that speaks to the future of the Minmatar people. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>