<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Studio Stage Set from LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plateau de tournage modulable de LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Studio Stage Set von LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Studio Stage Set di  LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Studio Stage Set de LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LOOT™スタジオ・ステージ・セット・バンドル</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Studio Stage Set from LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Modular Studio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Studio Stage Set from LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Studio Stage Set from LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Modular Stage Set from LOOT™</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Plateau de Tournage Modulable fournit une expérience machimina encore plus évoluée. Le Plateau de Tournage Modulable permet à l'utilisateur de contrôler de manière exceptionnelle le sol, les murs, les toiles de fond et les sytèmes d'éclairage et de caméras. La Caméra Active de LOOT™ et les articles d'éclairage Active de LOOT™ font aussi partie du Plateau de Tournage Modulable de LOOT™, ils vous permettent d'utiliser les outils machimina de LOOT™ dans tout espace privé vous appartenant pour le transformer en parfait studio de tournage pour réaliser vos films et émissions de télé. Le Plateau de Tournage Modulable est un outil merveilleux pour donner vie à vos projets.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Modular Stage Set hebt Machinima auf die nächste Stufe. Mit dem Modular Stage Set hat der Benutzer nie gekannte Kontrollmöglichkeiten über Boden, Wände, Kulissen, Beleuchtung und Kamerasysteme. Im Modular Stage Set enthalten sind auch das LOOT™ Active Camera-System und die LOOT™ Active Light-Artikel, die es dir erlauben, mit den LOOT™ Machinima- Werkzeugen aus deinen Privatbereichen einen perfekten Drehort für deine Filme und Fernsehserien zu machen. Das Modular Stage Set ist ein wunderbares Werkzeug, um deine Geschichten zum Leben zu erwecken. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il sistema Modular Stage Set porta il machinima al livello successivo. Il Modular Stage Set offre all'utente nuove possibilità di controllare pavimento, pareti, fondali, luci e sistemi di ripresa.Nel  Modular Stage Set sono comprese la LOOT™ Active Camera e la LOOT™ Active Light, che permettono di portare i mezzi del machinima LOOT™ in qualunque tuo spazio privato e trasformarlo in un set perfetto per girare i tuoi film e show TV. Il Modular Stage Set è un mezzo meraviglioso per dare vita alle tue storie. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Modular Stage Set lleva la machinima un paso más allá. El Modular Stage Set proporciona al usuario niveles de control inauditos sobre el suelo, las paredes, los fondos, las luces y los sistemas de cámara. El Modular Stage Set incluye la Active Camera LOOT™ y los elementos Active Light de LOOT™, que permiten llevar las herramientas de machinima LOOT™ a cualquier espacio privado que tengas, transformándolo en un espacio perfecto para filmar tus películas y programas de televisión. El Modular Stage Set es una herramienta ideal para dar vida a tus historias. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スターになる準備はいいですか！LOOT™ がお送りするLOOT™スタジオ・ステージは映画やテレビが製作されているソニーピクチャーズのプロフェッショナルなサウンドステージにインスパイアされました。友だちを集め、監督であれ、美術監督であれ、俳優、或いは撮影であれ、あなたの役目を選択して製作を開始しよう！LOOT™スタジオ・ステージは照明、壁、フロア、背景、そしてカメラシステムを前代未聞のレベルでコントロール可能です。また、収縮可能なグリーン、及びブルースクリーン、PlayStation®Homeの高度にカスタマイズ可能なアバター、服、そして家具のアイテムを使って、あなたが創造するストーリーを描きましょう。\n\nLOOT™スタジオ・ステージ・セット・バンドルを購入すると、LOOT™アクティブ・ライトであらゆるパーソナルスペースで撮影でき、LOOT™アクティブ・カメラでPlayStation®3のハードディスクドライブに映像を保存してYouTube™にアップロードできます！\n本コンテンツには、以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n「LOOT™スタジオ・ステージ」/パーソナルスペース\n「LOOT™アクティブ・ライト」/アドバンスド家具\n「LOOT™アクティブ・カメラ」/アドバンスド家具\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Modular Stage Set takes professional machinima to the next level. It provides the user with unprecedented levels of control over the floor, walls, backdrops, lights and camera systems.  Also included are the Portable Camera and Portable Light active items, which let you take the LOOT™ machinima tools to any private space you own, transforming it into a perfect location for shooting your movies and TV shows. It is the ultimate tool for having fun with your friends while bringing new stories to life.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>