<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blazing Twin-tails IdolStyle (special colour)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">IdolStyle Couettes Ardentes (couleur spéciale)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Flammender IdolStyle mit doppeltem Pferdeschwanz (Spezialfarbe)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">IdolStyle Code Fiammanti (colore speciale)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Colas gemelas ardientes IdolStyle (color especial)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブレージングツインテール・アイドルスタイル (スペシャルカラーウィッグ)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Blazing Twin-tails IdolStyle (Special color, Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Blazing Twin-tails IdolStyle (Special color, Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Blazing Twin-tails IdolStyle (Special color, Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Blazing Twin-tails IdolStyle (Special color, Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blazing Twin-tails IdolStyle (special color)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Steal the spotlight and go wild with IdolStyles!  Don't let little things like gravity keep you from showing off an amazing hairstyle.  Idols need to live on the edge, and so do you! This hairstyle is a special colour variant that cannot be changed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Attirez l'attention de tout le monde et faites des choses dingues avec IdolStyle ! Ne laissez pas les petites choses comme la gravité vous empêcher d'avoir une coiffure extraordinaire. Les idoles doivent êtres originales et marginales, et vous aussi ! Cette coiffure a une variation de couleur spéciale qui ne peut pas être changée. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schnapp dir das Rampenlicht und tob dich richtig aus mit einem IdolStyle. Lass dich nicht von Kleinigkeiten wie der Gravitation davon abhalten, mit verblüffenden Frisuren zu prahlen. Stars leben in einer anderen Welt, so wie du auch! Diese Frisur gibt es in einer speziellen Farbvariante, die nicht geändert werden kann. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guadagnati le luci dei riflettori e scatenati con gli IdolStyle! Non lasciare che cose insulse come la gravità ti impediscano di sfoggiare un'acconciatura sfavillante. Le star sono persone stravaganti, vivi come loro! Il colore di questa acconciatura è speciale e non può essere modificato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Róbate el centro de atención y enloquece con IdolStyles!  No dejes que las pequeñeces como la gravedad te impidan mostrar peinado espectacular. ¡Las ídolos necesitan vivir al límite, y tú también! Este peinado es una variante de color especial que no puede ser cambiado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アイドルスタイルで注目を浴びてワイルドでいこう！重力なんてちっぽけなものに素敵なウィッグの自慢を邪魔させるな。刺激的に生きよう！ このウィッグの色を変更することはできません。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Steal the spotlight and go wild with IdolStyles!  Don't let little things like gravity keep you from showing off an amazing hairstyle.  Idols need to live on the edge, and so do you! This hairstyle is a special color variant that cannot be changed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Steal the spotlight and go wild with IdolStyles!  Don't let little things like gravity keep you from showing off an amazing hairstyle.  Idols need to live on the edge, and so do you! This hairstyle is a special color variant that cannot be changed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Steal the spotlight and go wild with IdolStyles!  Don't let little things like gravity keep you from showing off an amazing hairstyle.  Idols need to live on the edge, and so do you! This hairstyle is a special color variant that cannot be changed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Steal the spotlight and go wild with IdolStyles!  Don't let little things like gravity keep you from showing off an amazing hairstyle.  Idols need to live on the edge, and so do you! This hairstyle is a special color variant that cannot be changed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Steal the spotlight and go wild with IdolStyles!  Don't let little things like gravity keep you from showing off an amazing hairstyle.  Idols need to live on the edge, and so do you! This hairstyle is a special color variant that cannot be changed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>