<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Bolting Blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Fleche Bleue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Aufjagendes Blau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Blu Fulmineo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Azul Fulminante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_25</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - 전격 블루</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Bolting Blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - 極速藍</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - 極速藍</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Bolting Blue</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Super Powered Peep is fueled by Heavy Water for all of his mad skills! Bring him with you into your apartment and let the fun begin.  You can control your Peep with custom animations and special Peep moves![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Super Powered Peep est alimente par Heavy Water pour tous ses talents de fou! Ramène le avec toi dans ton appartement et que la fête commence. Tu peux contrôler ton Peep avec des animations personnalisées et des manœuvres spéciales Peep![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Angetrieben von Heavy Water ist Super Powered Peep bereit für alle seine verrückten Fähigkeiten! Bring ihn mit in deine Wohnung und der Spaß beginnt. Du kannst dein Peep mit benutzerdefinierten Animationen und speziellen Peep-Bewegungen steuern![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Super Powered Peep é alimentato da Heavy Water dovuto alle sue straordinarie abilitá! Portalo nel tuo appartamento e che il divertimento abbia inizio. Puoi controllare il tuo Peep con animazioni fatte a posta e movimenti speciali Peep![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Super Powered Peep es impulsado por Heavy Water debido a sus tremendas habilidades!   Llévalo a tu departamento y que empieze la fiesta!  Puedes controlar a tu Peep con animaciones personalizadas y movimientos Peep especiales. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_25 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Super Powered Peep을 Heavy Water로 충전하여 환상의 스킬을 경험해 보세요!  아파트에 데려와 신나게 놀아 보세요.  사용자 지정 애니메이션과 특수 Peep 모션으로 컨트롤할 수 있습니다![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Super Powered Peep is fueled by Heavy Water for all of his mad skills! Bring him with you into your apartment and let the fun begin.  You can control your Peep with custom animations and special Peep moves![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Super Powered Peep由Heavy Water提供動力，使出瘋狂的技巧！帶他進入您家，開始玩樂。您可以用自訂動態和專屬Peep動作來控制Peep！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Super Powered Peep由Heavy Water提供動力，使出瘋狂的技巧！帶他進入您家，開始玩樂。您可以用自訂動態和專屬Peep動作來控制Peep！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Super Powered Peep is fueled by Heavy Water for all of his mad skills! Bring him with you into your apartment and let the fun begin.  You can control your Peep with custom animations and special Peep moves![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>