<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Mini-skirt &amp; Socks 6-piece Set (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set 6 pièces Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes (grise à carreaux &amp; blanches, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Minirock &amp; Socken 6-teiliges Set (graukariert &amp; weiß, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set 6 minigonne (a scacchi grigi con calzini bianchi, da donna) </LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de seis artículos de minifalda y calcetines (gris a cuadros y blancos, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ミニスカート＆ソックス６点セット（グレーチェック＆白・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Mini-skirt &amp; Socks 6-piece Set (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">6-piece set of checked grey mini skirts with different socks. 5 types of white socks (ankle, crew, knee, over-the-knee, thigh) and white tights. \nDefensive Strength: ★\nYouth Level: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Ankle Socks (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Crew Socks (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Knee Socks (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Over-the-Knee Socks (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Thigh High Socks (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Tights (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set 6 pièces de mini-jupes à carreaux grise avec différentes chaussettes. 5 types de chaussettes blanches (socquettes, chaussettes de sport, sous le genou, au-dessus du genou, aux cuisses) et des collants blancs. \nDéfense : ★\nNiveau de Jeunesse : ★★★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Socquettes (grise à carreaux &amp; blanches, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes de Sport (grise à carreaux &amp; blanches, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes sous le Genou (grise à carreaux &amp; blanches, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes au-dessus du Genou (grise à carreaux &amp; blanches, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes aux Cuisses (grise à carreaux &amp; blanches, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Collants (grise à carreaux &amp; blancs, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">6-teiliges Set eines graukarierten Minirocks mit 5 verschiedenen Typen weißer Socken (Söckchen, Waden, Knie, Overknee, Schenkel) und weißen Strumpfhosen. \nVerteidigung: ★\nJugendlichkeitslevel: ★★★\nDas Set beinhaltet die folgenden Kleidungsstücke:\n\n- Minirock &amp; Söckchen (graukariert &amp; weiß, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe) \n- Minirock &amp; Wadensocken (graukariert &amp; weiß, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Minirock &amp; Kniestrümpfe (graukariert &amp; weiß, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Minirock &amp; Overknees (graukariert &amp; weiß, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Minirock &amp; Schenkelstrümpfe (graukariert &amp; weiß, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Minirock &amp; Strumpfhosen (graukariert &amp; weiß, für Frauen) Unterteil, Schuhe)\n \n- Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set composto da 6 minigonne decorate con una trama a scacchi grigia accoppiate con diversi tipi di calzini bianchi (alla caviglia, calzettoni, sotto le ginocchia, sopra le ginocchia, collant) e calze bianche.\nDifesa: ★\nLivello giovinezza: ★★★\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Minigonna (a scacchi grigi con calzini alla caviglia bianchi, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi grigi con calzettoni bianchi, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi grigi con calzini sotto le ginocchia bianchi, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi grigi con calzini sopra le ginocchia bianchi, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi grigi con collant bianchi, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi grigi con calze bianche, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de seis artículos con minifalda a cuadros grises con diferentes calcetines. Cinco tipos de calcetines blancos (cortos, de deporte, a la altura de la rodilla, por encima de la rodilla y a la altura del muslo) y leotardos blancos. \nDefensa: ★\nNivel de juventud: ★★★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Minifalda y calcetines cortos (gris a cuadros y blancos, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines de deporte (gris a cuadros y blancos, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines hasta la rodilla (gris a cuadros y blancos, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines por encima de la rodilla (gris a cuadros y blancos, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines hasta el muslo (gris a cuadros y blancos, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y leotardos (gris a cuadros y blancos, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n\n*Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">グレーチェック柄のミニスカートの、足元違い６点セット。白ソックス５種（足首丈、スネ丈、膝下丈、膝上丈、太もも丈）、白タイツ。\n防御力：　★\n青春度：　★★★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・ミニスカートとアンクルソックス（グレーチェック＆白・女性）/ボトムズ・靴\n・ミニスカートとクルーソックス（グレーチェック＆白・女性）/ボトムズ・靴\n・ミニスカートとハイソックス（グレーチェック＆白・女性）/ボトムズ・靴\n・ミニスカートとオーバーニーソックス（グレーチェック＆白・女性）/ボトムズ・靴\n・ミニスカートとサイハイソックス（グレーチェック＆白・女性）/ボトムズ・靴\n・ミニスカートとタイツ（グレーチェック＆白・女性）/ボトムズ・靴\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">6-piece set of checked gray mini skirts with different socks. 5 types of white socks (ankle, crew, knee, over-the-knee, thigh) and white tights. \nDefensive Strength: ★\nYouth Level: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Ankle Socks (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Crew Socks (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Knee Socks (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Over-the-Knee Socks (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Thigh High Socks (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Tights (Gray Checked &amp; White, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category. [#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
