<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Piranha Stool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Piranha Stool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tabouret Piranha</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Piranha-Hocker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sgabello Piranha</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Taburete de Piranha</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Piranha Stool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Piranha 의자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Piranha Stool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Piranha 腳凳</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Piranha 腳凳</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Piranha Stool</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Do you want your interior design to have more bite? Then you simply NEED this shockingly comfortable stool brought to you by the boffins at Piranha. Perfectly engineered angles support your body so ergonomically that it doesn’t even feel like you’re sitting down. </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Do you want your interior design to have more bite? Then you simply NEED this shockingly comfortable stool brought to you by the boffins at Piranha. Perfectly engineered angles support your body so ergonomically that it doesn’t even feel like you’re sitting down. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous rêvez d'une décoration intérieure plus féroce ? Alors, il vous FAUT ce tabouret monstrueusement confortable, conçu par les experts de Piranha. Ses angles parfaitement étudiés soutiendront votre corps de manière tellement ergonomique que vous n'aurez même pas l'impression d'être assis. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Inneneinrichtung mit Biss gefällig? Dann ist dieser unfassbar bequeme, von Piranha-Experten entwickelte Hocker unbedingt zu empfehlen. Perfekt angepasste Formen stützen den Körper so ergonomisch, dass man nicht einmal merkt, dass man sitzt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Volete un arredamento che abbia carattere? Allora questo sgabello incredibilmente comodo creato dagli esperti della Piranha fa al caso vostro. Perfettamente bilanciato, è in grado di sostenere ergonomicamente il corpo tanto da non dare la sensazione di essere seduti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Quieres que tu diseño de interiores tenga un aspecto más feroz? En ese caso, NECESITAS este sorprendentemente cómodo taburete, nacido en el departamento de investigación militar de Piranha. Sus formas ergonómicas se adaptan a tu cuerpo de tal forma que no parecerá que estés sentado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Do you want your interior design to have more bite? Then you simply NEED this shockingly comfortable stool brought to you by the boffins at Piranha. Perfectly engineered angles support your body so ergonomically that it doesn’t even feel like you’re sitting down. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">인테리어 디자인에 날카로움이 좀 더 필요하신가요? 그렇다면 놀라울 정도로 편안한 Piranha 의자를 체험해 보십시오. 신체를 받쳐주는 특수 기술을 접목하여, 본인이 앉아 있다는 사실 마저도 잊어버리게 만듭니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Do you want your interior design to have more bite? Then you simply NEED this shockingly comfortable stool brought to you by the boffins at Piranha. Perfectly engineered angles support your body so ergonomically that it doesn’t even feel like you’re sitting down. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">想不想為房間的設計加添一抹新意？那您一定要購買這個Piranha研究人員專誠為您設計、意想不到地舒適的腳凳了。這個腳凳的每一個設計均經過精心計算，完全乎合人工力學，讓您的坐姿達到最舒適自然的境界。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">想不想為房間的設計加添一抹新意？那您一定要購買這個Piranha研究人員專誠為您設計、意想不到地舒適的腳凳了。這個腳凳的每一個設計均經過精心計算，完全乎合人工力學，讓您的坐姿達到最舒適自然的境界。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Do you want your interior design to have more bite? Then you simply NEED this shockingly comfortable stool brought to you by the boffins at Piranha. Perfectly engineered angles support your body so ergonomically that it doesn’t even feel like you’re sitting down. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>