<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sodium2 Legendary Pilot Trousers - Grey (for Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bas de combinaison de protection Sodium2 Pilote Légendaire - Gris (pour Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sodium2 Legendäre Pilotenhose – Grau (für Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pantaloni Sodium 2 Pilota leggendario - Grigi (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pantalones Piloto legendario Sodium2 - Grises (para hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Sodium2レジェンダリーパイロットズボン （男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium2 전설적인 파일럿 바지 - 회색 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sodium2 Legendary Pilot Trousers - Grey (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sodium2傳奇飛行員長褲：灰色（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sodium2傳奇飛行員長褲：灰色（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sodium2 Legendary Pilot Trousers - Gray  (for Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ultra lightweight and super tough, the Sodium2 Legendary Pilot Range offers ultimate protection combined with anti-drag technology. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ultralégère et extrêmement résistante, la gamme Sodium2 Pilote Légendaire offre une protection au top combinée à une technologie antifriction. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Sodium2 Legendäre Pilotenkollektion ist ultraleicht und superwiderstandsfähig und bietet den ultimativen Schutz gepaart mit extrem geringem Strömungswiderstand. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I prodotti della gamma Sodium2 Pilota leggendario sono ultraleggeri e resistenti e offrono la migliore protezione attualmente disponibile combinata alla tecnologia anti-drag. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ultraligeros y superresistentes, los productos de la gama Piloto legendario Sodium2 ofrecen la máxima protección combinada con tecnología antiarrastre. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">超軽量で頑丈。Sodium2レジェンダリーパイロットレンジは、反抗力技術を併用して究極の防御を提供します。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">초경량이면서 극도로 질긴 Sodium2 전설적인 파일럿 제품은 미끄럼 방지 기술까지 적용된 최상의 보호장비입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ultra lightweight and super tough, the Sodium2 Legendary Pilot Range offers ultimate protection combined with anti-drag technology. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sodium2傳奇飛行員系列產品採用超輕強韌材質，不但提供最高等級防護，更有抗阻力技術。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sodium2傳奇飛行員系列產品採用超輕強韌材質，不但提供最高等級防護，更有抗阻力技術。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ultra lightweight and super tough, the Sodium2 Legendary Pilot Range offers ultimate protection combined with anti-drag technology. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>