<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tembo the Baby Elephant</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tembo l'Éléphanteau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tembo das Elefantenbaby</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tembo, il cucciolo di elefante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tembo, el bebé elefante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">赤ちゃん象テンボー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">아기 코끼리 템보</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Tembo the Baby Elephant</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">天寶小象</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">天寶小象</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Tembo the Baby Elephant</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Lockwood's intensive breeding program means that the once rare virtual elephant is now flourishing. Adopt Tembo today and help this shy and special species continue to thrive! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le programme d'élevage intensive de Lockwood veut dire que l'éléphant virtuel jadis rare est désormais florissant. Adoptez Tembo aujourd'hui et aidez cette espèce timide et spéciale à continuer de prospérer! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lockwoods intensives Zuchtprogramm hat dazu geführt, dass die Zahlen der vormals seltenen virtuellen Elefanten rasch steigen. Adoptiere Tembo noch heute, damit diese besondere und scheue Tierart weiter floriert! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il programma di allevamento intensivo di Lockwood ha fatto sì che l'elefante virtuale una volta raro ora possa prosperare. Adotta Tembo oggi e aiutare questa specie timida e speciale a continuare a prosperare! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El programa de cría de Lockwood ha logrado crear a este elefante virtual en edad de crecimiento. Adopta a Tembo hoy y ayuda a que esta tímida y reducida especie siga con nosotros. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Lockwoodが真剣に取り組み始めた動物育成プログラム。その結果としてあの珍しかったゾウという生き物がこの世界であふれるかも！？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Lockwood 의 집중적인 번식 프로그램을 통해, 한 때 희귀했던 이 가상 코끼리가 이제는 번성하고 있습니다. 오늘 템보를 입양해서 이 내성적이고 특별한 종이 계속 잘 자랄 수 있도록 해주세요![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Lockwood's intensive breeding program means that the once rare virtual elephant is now flourishing. Adopt Tembo today and help this shy and special species continue to thrive! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Lockwood的復育計畫非常積極，所以這種罕見的虛擬大象已經不再稀有。現在領養天寶，就能讓這種害羞的特殊動物繼續繁衍下去！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Lockwood的復育計畫非常積極，所以這種罕見的虛擬大象已經不再稀有。現在領養天寶，就能讓這種害羞的特殊動物繼續繁衍下去！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Lockwood's intensive breeding program means that the once rare virtual elephant is now flourishing. Adopt Tembo today and help this shy and special species continue to thrive! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>