<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Fossil Collection Plates Set (for fish)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de plateaux de collection de fossiles (pour poissons)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Fossiliensammlung Tafelset (für Fische)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set di teche per la collezione di fossili (per pesci)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de placas de colección de fósiles (para peces)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">化石収集プレートセット（魚用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Fossil Collection Plates Set (for fish)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 2-piece set of collection plates for displaying fish fossils.\nThis set includes the following items.\n\n- Old Fossil Collection Plate (for fish)(Decoration)\n- Brand New Fossil Collection Plate (for fish)(Decoration)\n\n*Upon purchase, each item in the applicable category will be added.  [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 2 plateaux de collection pour exposer des fossiles de poissons.\nCe set contient les objets suivants :\n\n- Vieux plateau de collection de fossiles (pour poissons)(Décoration)\n- Plateau de collection de fossiles tout neuf (pour poissons)(Décoration)\n\n*Après achat, chaque objet sera ajouté dans la catégorie adéquate. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein zweiteiliger Satz aus Sammeltafeln, mit dem Fisch-Fossilien zur Schau gestellt werden können.\nDieser Satz enthält die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Alte Tafel zur Fossiliensammlung (für Fische)(Dekoration)\n- Brandneue Tafel zur Fossiliensammlung (für Fische)(Dekoration)\n\n * Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand in entsprechender Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set comprendente 2 teche per esporre fossili di pesci.\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Vecchia teca per la collezione di fossili (per pesci)(decorazione)\n- Ultimo modello di teca per la collezione di fossili (per pesci)(decorazione)\n*Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Un juego de 2 piezas de placas para exponer fósiles de peces.\nEste juego contiene los siguientes objetos:\n\n- Placa antigua de colección de fósiles (para peces) (adorno)\n- Placa nueva de colección de fósiles (para peces) (adorno)\n\n * Después de la compra, cada objeto será agregado a la categoría correpondiente. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">魚の化石をピッタリ収めて飾ることが出来る収集プレートの2枚セット。\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・古めかしい化石収集プレート（魚用）（装飾品）\n・真新しい化石収集プレート（魚用）（装飾品）\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 2-piece set of collection plates for displaying fish fossils.\nThis set includes the following items.\n\n- Old Fossil Collection Plate (for fish)(Decoration)\n- Brand New Fossil Collection Plate (for fish)(Decoration)\n\n*Upon purchase, each item in the applicable category will be added.  [#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
