<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Juno Eclipse Gloves</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Gants Juno Eclipse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Juno Eclipse-Handschuhe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guanti Juno Eclipse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guantes de Juno Eclipse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Juno Eclipse Gloves</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">(Gloves) A dedicated Imperial officer nearly all of her life; Captain Juno Eclipse was hand-picked by Darth Vader to pilot his secret apprentice -- the agent Starkiller -- across the galaxy. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">(Gants) Cet officier a été dévoué à l'Empire pratiquement toute sa vie ; le capitaine Juno Eclipse a été  recrutée par Dark Vador pour piloter son apprenti secret - l'agent Starkiller - à travers toute la galaxie. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">(Handschuhe) Fast ihr ganzes Leben lang war sie eine hingebungsvolle Pilotin des Imperiums; Captain Juno Eclipse wurde von Darth Vader persönlich ausgewählt, um seinen geheimen Schüler -- den Agenten Starkiller -- durch die Galaxie zu fliegen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">(Guanti) Fedele ufficiale dell'Impero per quasi tutta la sua vita, il capitano Juno Eclipse è stata scelta personalmente da Dart Fener per pilotare il suo apprendista segreto -- l'agente Starkiller -- in giro per la galassia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">(Guantes) Dedicada oficial imperial durante casi toda su vida; la capitana Juno Eclipse fue elegida personalmente por Darth Vader para transportar a su aprendiz secreto, el agente Starkiller, por toda la galaxia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">(Gloves) A dedicated Imperial officer nearly all of her life; Captain Juno Eclipse was hand-picked by Darth Vader to pilot his secret apprentice -- the agent Starkiller -- across the galaxy. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>