<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - You're Smitten Dress - True Blue (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Robe You're Smitten - Bleu profond (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - You're Smitten Kleid - Dunkelblau (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - You're Smitten Vestito - Blu (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - You're Smitten Vestido - Azul verdadero (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The hi-low hem trend takes on edgier form with the dramatic look of the You're Smitten dress. As part of our Designer's Closet collection, special details include a button front closure, along with criss cross straps and cut outs at back. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'ourlet irrégulier tendance prend ici une forme plus dynamique avec le look spectaculaire de cette robe You're Smitten.  Figurant dans notre collection Designer's Closet, ses caractéristiques sont notamment une fermeture frontale à boutons ainsi que des bretelles et découpes en treillis dans le dos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der High-Low-Trend nimmt neue Formen an mit dem dramatischen Look dieses You're Smitten Kleids aus der Designer's Closet Kollektion. Zu besonderen Details zählen der Knopfverschluss vorne, die Kreuzträger und die Ausschnitte auf dem Rücken. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'orlo asimmetrico diventa ancora più intrigante grazie al look eccezionale del vestito You're Smitten. Il capo fa parte della nostra collezione Designer's Closet e comprende chiusura frontale con bottoni, laccetti incrociati e ritagli sulla schiena. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La tendencia de los bajos asimétricos da un nuevo giro con el espectacular "look" del vestido You're Smitten. Forma parte de nuestra colección Designer's Closet, y los detalles especiales incluyen cierre delantero de botones, así como tirantes y espalda recortada y cruzada. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>