<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Easter Tree</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Arbre de Pâques</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Osterbaum</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Albero di Pasqua</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Árbol de Pascua</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Easter Tree [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TreeTalk1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You need to be more generous with your gifting to be given a special reward from the tree...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour recevoir une récompense spéciale de l'arbre... vous devez être plus généreux pour vos cadeaux</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie sollten mit Ihren Geschenken etwas großzügiger sein, wenn Sie eine Belohnung vom Baum erhalten wollen….</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Devi essere più generoso e fare più regali se vuoi ricevere il premio speciale dall'albero...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tendrás que ser más generoso con tus regalos para que el árbol te conceda un premio especial…</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TreeTalk2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Maybe you should try being more generous with your gifts?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Peut-être devriez-vous être plus généreux pour vos cadeaux ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vielleicht sollten Sie etwas großzügiger sein, wenn Sie Geschenke machen?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Magari dovresti provare a essere più generoso e fare più regali?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Quizás debieras intentar ser más generoso con tus regalos.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TreeTalk3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Congratulations! You've shared gifts with the community and here's a special reward.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Félicitations ! Vous avez partagé des cadeaux avec la communauté et voici une récompense spéciale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Herzlichen Glückwunsch! Sie haben der Gemeinschaft großzügige Geschenke gemacht und erhalten dafür eine besondere Belohnung!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Congratulazioni! Hai scambiato regali con la comunità e ti meriti un premio speciale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Enhorabuena!  Has compartido regalos con la comunidad y aquí tienes un premio especial.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TreeTalk4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You've already had a gift from the tree!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez déjà reçu un cadeau de l'arbre !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben bereits ein Geschenk vom Baum erhalten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai già ricevuto un regalo dall'albero!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡El árbol ya te ha concedido un regalo!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sortie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beenden</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salida</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>