<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Raven Watercolour Painting</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aquarelle Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Raven-Aquarell</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Acquerello Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acuarela de Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">水彩画 レーヴン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Raven 수채화</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Raven Watercolor Painting</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raven水彩畫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raven水彩畫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Raven Watercolor Painting</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Using a beautiful palette of greens and blues, this Raven commissioned painting juxtaposes nature and technology as well as the ancient and modern worlds. This timeless masterpiece will elevate the culture of any apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Dans un délicieux mélange de verts et de bleus, ce tableau commandé par Raven juxtapose nature et technologie, temps anciens et monde moderne. Ce chef-d'œuvre intemporel donnera une nouvelle dimension à votre appartement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses im Auftrag von Raven gemalte Bild verbindet mit einer wunderschönen Palette an Grün- und Blautönen sowohl Natur und Technologie als auch das Altertum und die Neuzeit. Dieses zeitlose Meisterwerk bringt ein bisschen Kultur in jedes Apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usando tonalità verdi e azzurre, questo dipinto commissionato dalla Raven accosta natura e tecnologia, mondo antico e mondo moderno. Questo capolavoro senza tempo arricchirà la vostra abitazione con un elemento di cultura. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con una hermosa gama de verdes y azules, este cuadro que encargó Raven reúne la naturaleza y la tecnología, además de los mundos antiguo y moderno. Esta eterna obra de arte le dará un toque cultural a cualquier apartamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">美しい緑と青を基調に自然と技術、古代と現代を見事に融合した逸品だ。 レーヴンが依頼して描かれた水彩画。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">녹색과 청색의 아름다운 조합으로, Raven의 의뢰에 의해 만들어진 이 작품은 자연과 기술, 그리고 과거와 미래가 하나되는 순간을 포착하였습니다. 보는 이의 수준을 높여주는 그림입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Using a beautiful palette of greens and blues, this Raven commissioned painting juxtaposes nature and technology as well as the ancient and modern worlds. This timeless masterpiece will elevate the culture of any apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">使用藍色與綠色系顏料，這幅Raven水彩畫將自然與科技融合，同時也結合了歷史與現代。這幅永遠不褪時的插畫能提升任何個人空間的文化氣息。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">使用藍色與綠色系顏料，這幅Raven水彩畫將自然與科技融合，同時也結合了歷史與現代。這幅永遠不褪時的插畫能提升任何個人空間的文化氣息。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Using a beautiful palette of greens and blues, this Raven commissioned painting juxtaposes nature and technology as well as the ancient and modern worlds. This timeless masterpiece will elevate the culture of any apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>