<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Yukata, Bottom (Flowing Water on Black, Men)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Yukata, Bas (Noir - motif de rivière - Homme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Yukata, Unterteil (fließendes Wasser auf Schwarz, Männer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Yukata - parte inferiore (sfondo nero con corso d'acqua raffigurato, da uomo)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Kimono de verano, parte inferior (tela con fondo negro y estampado de agua corriente, hombre)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">浴衣＜下＞（黒地流水・男性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">유카타, 하의 (검은 바탕에 물결 무늬, 남성)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Yukata, Bottom (Flowing Water on Black, Men)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">浴衣下身（黑色襯流水/男用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">浴衣下半身（黑色襯流水/男用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Yukata, Bottom (Flowing Water on Black, Men)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Men's yukata bottom showing gold-coloured flowing water on a black background.\nDefensive Strength:★\nStylishness:★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Bas de yukata pour homme en tissu noir brodé d'un motif de rivière doré.\nDéfense:★\nStyle:★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Das Unterteil eines Yukata für Männer, der mit dem Muster von goldenem, fließenden Wasser auf schwarzem Hintergrund verziert ist.\nVerteidigung:★\nEleganz:★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">La parte inferiore di uno yukata da uomo che reca la raffigurazione color oro di un corso d'acqua su tessuto nero.\nDifesa:★\nRaffinatezza:★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Parte inferior del kimono de verano para hombre, de tela fondo negro y estampado color dorado de agua corriente. \nDefensa:★\nBuen gusto:★★[#Legal] [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">黒地に金色の流水柄が描かれた男物浴衣の下半身。\n防御力：　★\n粋：　★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">검은 바탕에 금색의 물결 무늬가 그려진 남성용 유카타 하의. \n방어력：　★\n세련됨：　★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Men's yukata bottom showing gold-colored flowing water on a black background.\nDefensive Strength:★\nStylishness:★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">男性浴衣的下身，黑色底映襯出金色的流水花紋。\n防禦力：★\n時尚指數：★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">男性浴衣的下半身，黑色底映襯出金色的流水花紋。\n防禦力：★\n時尚指數：★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Men's yukata bottom showing gold-colored flowing water on a black background.\nDefensive Strength:★\nStylishness:★★[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
