<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Auroralite Contraption (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appareil Auroralite (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Auroralite-Vorrichtung (Mann)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Apparecchiatura Auroralite (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Artilugio de Auroralite (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロライトウィジェット (男性用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">오로라 시민 장치 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Auroralite Contraption (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">極光奇妙裝置（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">極光奇妙裝置（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Auroralite Contraption (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This inspired item will boost the amount of XP you earn in Aurora by 150% from level 1 to 100. If you also own the Auroralite Hoodie, then from level 55 onwards you will earn triple XP. How amazing is that? Note - You do not have to wear this item to get the XP benefits, you just have to own it. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cet objet pratique augmentera de 150 % la quantité de XP que vous gagnerez dans Aurora, du niveau 1 à 100. Si vous possédez aussi le sweat à capuche Auroralite, vous gagnerez le triple de XP à partir du niveau 55. Génial non ? Veuillez noter - vous n'êtes pas tenu de porter cet objet pour obtenir ces avantages de XP, il suffit de le posséder.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser fantastische Gegenstand wird den Betrag der EP, die du in Aurora erhältst, von Level 1 bis 100 auf 150 % steigern. Wenn du auch den Auroralite-Kapuzenpullover hast, wirst du ab Level 55 dreifache EP erhalten. Wie toll ist das?  Anmerkung: Du musst diesen Gegenstand nicht anhaben, um die EP-Steigerung zu erhalten, du musst ihn nur besitzen.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo brillante oggetto farà aumentare del 150% la quantità di XP che guadagnerai in Aurora, dal livello 1 a 100. Se possiedi anche la felpa con cappuccio Auroralite, dal livello 55 in poi guadagnerai tripli XP. Fantastico, vero? Nota bene: non devi indossare questo oggetto per ottenere il bonus XP, ma solo possederlo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este artículo inspirado incrementará la cantidad de EXP que consigas en Aurora en un 150 % del nivel 1 al 100. Si, además, tienes la sudadera con capucha de Auroralite, a partir del nivel 55 conseguirás el triple de EXP. ¿A que es increíble? Nota: no hace falta que lleves puesto el artículo para conseguir los beneficios de la EXP; basta con que lo hayas comprado.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラ島防衛やOrbRunnerのゲームに参加したときに得られる経験値がレベル 1 から 100 までの間、150% に増幅してくれる不思議なアイテム。Auroraliteパーカーも所有している場合、レベル 55 以降に獲得できる経験値が 3 倍になります。すごいでしょう!?  ※オーロライトウィジェットは着用していなくても効果が現れます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이것은 레벨 1에서 100까지 Aurora에서 얻은 경험치의 양을 150% 높여줄 것입니다. 또한 Aurora 후디를 가지고 있다면, 레벨 55부터 세 배의 경험치를 얻게 됩니다. 정말 놀랍지 않나요? 주의 - 경험치 혜택을 얻기 위해 이 아이템을 착용할 필요가 없으며 가지고 있기만 하면 됩니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This inspired item will boost the amount of XP you earn in Aurora by 150% from level 1 to 100. If you also own the Auroralite Hoodie, then from level 55 onwards you will earn triple XP. How amazing is that? Note - You do not have to wear this item to get the XP benefits, you just have to own it. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這個受啟發的產品將促進您在極光群島中於等級1到等級100獲得150%的XP。如果您還擁有極光連帽外套，從55級起您可以贏得三倍的XP。真的太棒了！※註 - 您不必佩戴此物品即可獲得XP的增加效果，只需擁有即可。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這個受啟發的產品將促進您在極光群島中於等級1到等級100獲得150%的XP。如果您還擁有極光連帽外套，從55級起您可以贏得三倍的XP。真的太棒了！※註 - 您不必佩戴此物品即可獲得XP的增加效果，只需擁有即可。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This inspired item will boost the amount of XP you earn in Aurora by 150% from level 1 to 100. If you also own the Auroralite Hoodie, then from level 55 onwards you will earn triple XP. How amazing is that? Note - You do not have to wear this item to get the XP benefits, you just have to own it. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>