<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Gateway_legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] Use</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] Utiliser</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] Verwenden</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] Usa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] Usar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  [CROSS] Use</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  [CROSS] Use</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  [CROSS] Use</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  [CROSS] Use</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  [CROSS] Use</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[CROSS] Use</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Daemon_2_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A cry of pain as it enters the world. A chorus of screams as it leaves.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un cri de douleur quand il arrive dans ce monde. Une cacophonie de hurlements quand il le quitte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Schrei der Schmerzen, als er auf diese Welt kommt. Ein Chor der Schreie, als er sie verlässt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un grido di dolore quando viene al mondo. Un coro di urla quando se ne va.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un grito de dolor cuando entra en este mundo. Un coro de gritos cuando se va.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  A cry of pain as it enters the world. A chorus of screams as it leaves.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  A cry of pain as it enters the world. A chorus of screams as it leaves.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  A cry of pain as it enters the world. A chorus of screams as it leaves.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  A cry of pain as it enters the world. A chorus of screams as it leaves.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  A cry of pain as it enters the world. A chorus of screams as it leaves.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A cry of pain as it enters the world. A chorus of screams as it leaves.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Sphinx_2_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">About the Sphinx, I have mixed feelings. Their wisdom I crave, but their secrecy I can’t tolerate.\n—Szadek</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">« Je suis toujours partagé en ce qui concerne les sphinx. J'ai besoin de leur sagesse, mais je ne peux tolérer leur passion du secret. »\n—Szadek</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ich bin mir meiner Meinung über die Sphinx nicht sicher. Ich neide ihr ihre Weisheit, aber ich kann ihre Geheimnistuerei nicht dulden.\n—Szadek</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Riguardo alla Sfinge, ho sentimenti contrastanti. Bramo la loro saggezza, ma non posso tollerare la loro segretezza.\n—Szadek</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tengo sentimientos encontrados sobre la esfinge. Ansío su sabiduría, pero no puedo tolerar su secretismo.\n—Szadek</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  About the Sphinx, I have mixed feelings. Their wisdom I crave, but their secrecy I can't tolerate. Szadek</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  About the Sphinx, I have mixed feelings. Their wisdom I crave, but their secrecy I can't tolerate. Szadek</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  About the Sphinx, I have mixed feelings. Their wisdom I crave, but their secrecy I can't tolerate. Szadek</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  About the Sphinx, I have mixed feelings. Their wisdom I crave, but their secrecy I can't tolerate. Szadek</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  About the Sphinx, I have mixed feelings. Their wisdom I crave, but their secrecy I can't tolerate. Szadek</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">About the Sphinx, I have mixed feelings. Their wisdom I crave, but their secrecy I can’t tolerate.\n—Szadek</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gather all the keys to the Knowledge Font by completing the mini-games throughout the Great Halls, and then return here to claim your Final Reward. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rassemblez toutes les clés permettant d'accéder à la Fontaine du Savoir en jouant les mini-jeux des Grandes salles, puis revenez ici pour recevoir votre récompense finale [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sammle alle Schlüssel zur Quelle des Wissens, indem du die Minispiele in den Großen Hallen löst, und kehre dann hierher zurück, um deine Abschlussbelohnung zu erhalten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Raccogli tutte le chiavi per la Fonte della Conoscenza completando le mini-partite nelle Grandi Sale e poi torna qui per reclamare la tua Ricompensa Finale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Reúne todas las llaves de la Fuente del Conocimiento completando los mini-juegos de los Grandes Salones, y luego regresa aquí para reclamar tu Recompensa Final. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Access the key portal upon completion of all games. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Access the key portal upon completion of all games. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Access the key portal upon completion of all games. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Access the key portal upon completion of all games. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Access the key portal upon completion of all games. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gather all the keys to the Knowledge Font by completing the mini-games throughout the Great Halls, and then return here to claim your Final Reward. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Black_Portal_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Black mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mana noir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schwarzes Mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mana nero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Maná negro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Black mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Black mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Black mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Black mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Black mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Black mana</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Black_Portal_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana’s specialty. Black mana comes from the swamps.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le mana noir corrompt et domine. Les créatures telles que les démons et les morts-vivants sont la spécialité du mana noir. Le mana noir vient des marais.\nCette exposition est en cours de construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schwarzes Mana korrumpiert und beherrscht. Untote Kreaturen und Dämonen sind ohne schwarzes Mana kaum denkbar. Schwarzes Mana kommt aus den Sümpfen.\nAn dieser Ausstellung wird derzeit noch gearbeitet.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mana nero corrompe e comanda. La specialità delle magie nere è l'evocazione di creature come demoni e non morti. Il mana nero proviene dalle paludi.\nQuesta mostra al momento è in costruzione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El maná negro corrompe y domina. Las criaturas como los demonios y los muertos vivientes son la especialidad del maná negro. El maná negro proviene de los pantanos.\nEsta muestra está actualmente en construcción.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana's speciality. Black mana comes from the swamps.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana's speciality. Black mana comes from the swamps.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana's speciality. Black mana comes from the swamps.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana's speciality. Black mana comes from the swamps.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana's speciality. Black mana comes from the swamps.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Black mana corrupts and dominates. Creatures such as demons and the undead are black mana’s specialty. Black mana comes from the swamps.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Blue_Portal_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blue mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mana bleu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blaues Mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mana blu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Maná azul</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Blue mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Blue mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Blue mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Blue mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Blue mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blue mana</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Blue_Portal_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le mana bleu contrôle et trompe. C'est la magie de l'esprit, du vent et des vagues. Le mana bleu coule des îles.\nCette exposition est en cours de construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blaues Mana kontrolliert und betrügt. Dies ist die Magie des Verstandes, des Windes und der Wellen. Blaues Mana kommt aus den Inseln.\nAn dieser Ausstellung wird derzeit noch gearbeitet.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mana blu manipola e inganna. Questa è la magia della mente, del vento e delle onde. Il mana blu proviene dalle isole.\nQuesta mostra al momento è in costruzione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El maná azul controla y engaña. Ésta es magia de la mente, el viento y las olas. El maná azul proviende de las islas.\nEsta muestra está actualmente en construcción.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blue mana controls and deceives. This is magic of the mind, the wind, and the waves. Blue mana comes from the islands.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Chandra_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Chandra Nalaar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chandra Nalaàr</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Chandra Nalaar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chandra Nalaar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chandra Nalaar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Chandra Nalaar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Chandra Nalaar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Chandra Nalaar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Chandra Nalaar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Chandra Nalaar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Chandra Nalaar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Chandra_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Chandra Nalaar is a red-magic-wielding Planeswalker. Her specialty is pyromancy: spells of fire, fire, and more fire.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chandra Nalaàr est une planeswalker qui utilise la magie rouge. Elle est spécialisée en pyromancie : les sorts de feu, le feu, sans oublier le feu.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Chandra Nalaar ist eine Planeswalkerin, die rotes Mana verwendet. Ihr Spezialgebiet ist die Pyromagie: Zauber mit Feuer, Feuer und noch mehr Feuer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chandra Nalaar è una planeswalker che brandisce la magia rossa. La sua specialità è la piromanzia: magie che bruciano, ardono e ustionano.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chandra Nalaar es una Planeswalker que usa magia roja. Su especialidad es la piromancia: hechizos de fuego, fuego y más fuego.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Chandra Nalaar is a red-magic-wielding planeswalker. Her specialty is pyromancy: spells of fire, fire, and more fire.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Chandra Nalaar is a red-magic-wielding planeswalker. Her specialty is pyromancy: spells of fire, fire, and more fire.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Chandra Nalaar is a red-magic-wielding planeswalker. Her specialty is pyromancy: spells of fire, fire, and more fire.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Chandra Nalaar is a red-magic-wielding planeswalker. Her specialty is pyromancy: spells of fire, fire, and more fire.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Chandra Nalaar is a red-magic-wielding planeswalker. Her specialty is pyromancy: spells of fire, fire, and more fire.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Chandra Nalaar is a red-magic-wielding Planeswalker. Her specialty is pyromancy: spells of fire, fire, and more fire.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Gateway_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gather all the keys to the Knowledge Font by completing the mini-games throughout the Great Halls, and then return here to claim your Final Reward.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rassemblez toutes les clés permettant d'accéder à la Fontaine du Savoir en jouant les mini-jeux des Grandes salles, puis revenez ici pour recevoir votre récompense finale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sammle alle Schlüssel zur Quelle des Wissens, indem du die Minispiele in den Großen Hallen löst, und kehre dann hierher zurück, um deine Abschlussbelohnung zu erhalten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Raccogli tutte le chiavi per la Fonte della Conoscenza completando le mini-partite nelle Grandi Sale e poi torna qui per reclamare la tua Ricompensa Finale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Reúne todas las llaves de la Fuente del Conocimiento completando los mini-juegos de los Grandes Salones, y luego regresa aquí para reclamar tu Recompensa Final.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Come back when you have collected all the key fragments</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Come back when you have collected all the key fragments</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Come back when you have collected all the key fragments</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Come back when you have collected all the key fragments</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Come back when you have collected all the key fragments</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gather all the keys to the Knowledge Font by completing the mini-games throughout the Great Halls, and then return here to claim your Final Reward.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Gateway_details2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Congratulations! You have unlocked the Font of all Magic: The Gathering knowledge and can claim your reward.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Félicitations ! Vous avez déverrouillé la Fontaine de tout le savoir de Magic: The Gathering et vous pouvez recevoir votre récompense.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gratulation! Du hast die Quelle alles Wissens über Magic: The Gathering erreicht und kannst dir deine Belohnung abholen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Congratulazioni! Hai sbloccato la Fonte di tutte le conoscenze di Magic: The Gathering e puoi reclamare la tua ricompensa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Felicitaciones! Haz desbloqueado la Fuente de todo el conocimiento de Magic: The Gathering y puedes reclamar tu recompensa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Congratulations! You Unlocked the Key Portal.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Congratulations! You Unlocked the Key Portal.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Congratulations! You Unlocked the Key Portal.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Congratulations! You Unlocked the Key Portal.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Congratulations! You Unlocked the Key Portal.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Congratulations! You have unlocked the Font of all Magic: The Gathering knowledge and can claim your reward.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Daemon_1_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Demon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">démon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dämon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Demone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Demonio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Demon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Demon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Demon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Demon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Demon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Demon</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Daemon_2_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Demon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">démon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dämon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Demone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Demonio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Demon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Demon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Demon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Demon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Demon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Demon</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Dragon_1_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drache</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Drago</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dragón</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dragon</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Dragon_2_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drache</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Drago</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dragón</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Dragon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dragon</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Dragon_2_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dragons erupt from peaks of chaos and flow from rivers of molten rage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les dragons surgissent des pics du chaos et naissent des rivières de rage en fusion.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drachen tauchen aus Gipfeln des Chaos aus und schwimmen auf Flüssen aus geschmolzenem Zorn.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I draghi spuntano da picchi di caos e sgorgano da fiumi di rabbia fusa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los dragones brotan de cimas de caos y fluyen de ríos de ira fundida.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Dragons erupt from peaks of chaos and flow from rivers of molten rage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Dragons erupt from peaks of chaos and flow from rivers of molten rage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Dragons erupt from peaks of chaos and flow from rivers of molten rage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Dragons erupt from peaks of chaos and flow from rivers of molten rage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Dragons erupt from peaks of chaos and flow from rivers of molten rage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dragons erupt from peaks of chaos and flow from rivers of molten rage.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Green_Portal_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Green mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mana vert</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Grünes Mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mana verde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Maná verde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Green mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Green mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Green mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Green mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Green mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Green mana</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Green_Portal_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le mana vert est la magie de la croissance et de la force. Elle est régie par la loi du plus fort, et les magiciens verts manipulent la force et la férocité de la vie. Le mana vert émane des forêts.\nCette exposition est en cours de construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Grünes Mana bedeutet Wachstum und Stärke. Nur die Starken überleben, und in grünen Magiern fließt die Stärke von Leben und Wildheit. Grünes Mana kommt aus den Wäldern.\nAn dieser Ausstellung wird derzeit noch gearbeitet.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mana verde si specializza nella crescita e nella forza bruta. Solo il più forte sopravvive, e i maghi verdi impugnano la forza della vita e della ferocia. Il mana verde proviene dalle foreste.\nQuesta mostra al momento è in costruzione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El maná verde se basa en el crecimiento y la fuerza. Sólo el más fuerte sobrevive, y los magos verde esgrimen la fuerza y ferocidad de la vida. El maná verde proviene de los bosques.\nEsta muestra está actualmente en construcción.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Green mana is about growth and strength. Only the strong survive, and green mages wield the strength of life and ferocity. Green mana comes from the forests.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Serra_Angel_1_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Her sword sings more beautifully than any choir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le chant de son épée est plus exaltant que celui du plus beau des chœurs.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ihr Schwert singt schöner als jeder Chor.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La sua spada canta meglio di qualsiasi coro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Su espada canta más bellamente que cualquier coro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Her sword sings more beautifully than any choir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Her sword sings more beautifully than any choir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Her sword sings more beautifully than any choir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Her sword sings more beautifully than any choir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Her sword sings more beautifully than any choir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Her sword sings more beautifully than any choir.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Hydra_1_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">hydre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Idra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hidra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hydra</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Hydra_2_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">hydre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Idra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hidra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Hydra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hydra</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Hydra_1_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It shreds its prey as each head fights for the choicest bits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Elle déchiquette sa proie car chaque tête désire les morceaux de choix.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie zerfetzt ihre Beute, da die Köpfe miteinander um die leckersten Bissen streiten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fa a pezzi la sua preda mentre ogni testa lotta per i bocconi più saporiti.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Destroza a su presa mientras cada cabeza elige el mejor pedazo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  It shreds its prey as each head fights for the choicest bits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  It shreds its prey as each head fights for the choicest bits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  It shreds its prey as each head fights for the choicest bits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  It shreds its prey as each head fights for the choicest bits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  It shreds its prey as each head fights for the choicest bits.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">It shreds its prey as each head fights for the choicest bits.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Daemon_1_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It’s drawn to the scent of screaming.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il est attiré par l'odeur des hurlements.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Er scheint deine Schreie riechen zu können.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Viene attirato dal profumo delle urla.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lo atrae el aroma de los gritos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  It's drawn to the scent of screaming.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  It's drawn to the scent of screaming.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  It's drawn to the scent of screaming.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  It's drawn to the scent of screaming.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  It's drawn to the scent of screaming.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">It’s drawn to the scent of screaming.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Jace_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Jace Beleren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jace Beleren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jace Beleren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Jace Beleren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Jace Beleren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Jace Beleren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Jace Beleren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Jace Beleren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Jace Beleren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Jace Beleren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Jace Beleren</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Jace_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Jace Beleren is a Planeswalker who wields blue magic. His specialty is mental magic: spells of mind-reading, illusion, knowledge, and deception.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jace Beleren est un planeswalker qui utilise la magie bleue. Il est spécialisé dans la magie mentale : les sorts de télépathie, d'illusion, de connaissance et de tromperie.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jace Beleren ist ein Planeswalker, der blaue Magie verwendet. Sein Spezialgebiet ist Mentalmagie: Zaubersprüche des Gedankenlesens, der Illusion, des Wissens und der Täuschung.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Jace Beleren è un planeswalker che brandisce la magia blu. La sua specialità è la magia mentale: incantesimi di inganno e illusione, capaci di leggere le menti e scoprire qualsiasi segreto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Jace Beleren es un Planeswalker que usa magia azul. Su especialidad es la magia mental: hechizos para leer la mente, ilusión, conocimiento y engaño.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Jace Beleren is a planeswalker who wields blue magic. His specialty is mental magic: spells of mind-reading, illusion, knowledge, and deception.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Jace Beleren is a planeswalker who wields blue magic. His specialty is mental magic: spells of mind-reading, illusion, knowledge, and deception.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Jace Beleren is a planeswalker who wields blue magic. His specialty is mental magic: spells of mind-reading, illusion, knowledge, and deception.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Jace Beleren is a planeswalker who wields blue magic. His specialty is mental magic: spells of mind-reading, illusion, knowledge, and deception.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Jace Beleren is a planeswalker who wields blue magic. His specialty is mental magic: spells of mind-reading, illusion, knowledge, and deception.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Jace Beleren is a Planeswalker who wields blue magic. His specialty is mental magic: spells of mind-reading, illusion, knowledge, and deception.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Gateway_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Knowledge Font</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La Fontaine du Savoir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Quelle des Wissens</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Fonte della Conoscenza</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La Fuente del Conocimiento</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Key Portal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Key Portal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Key Portal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Key Portal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Key Portal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Knowledge Font</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Hydra_2_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Look at this creature, so like the conclave it serves. Cut one head and it grows two. Damage it and it flourishes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Regardez cette créature. Elle ressemble tant au Conclave qu'elle sert. Coupez-lui une tête ; il en repousse deux. Blessez-la et elle fleurit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schau dir diese Kreatur an, wie sie dem Konklave dient. Haue einen Kopf ab, und es wachsen zwei neue nach. Verletze sie, und sie wird stärker.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Osserva questa creatura, così simile al conclave che serve. Taglia una testa e ne ricrescono due. Danneggiala e prospera.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Miren esta criatura, tan parecida al Cónclave que sirve. Le cortas una cabeza y le crecen dos. La dañas y crece.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Look at this creature, so like the conclave it serves. Cut one head and it grows two. Damage it and it flourishes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Look at this creature, so like the conclave it serves. Cut one head and it grows two. Damage it and it flourishes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Look at this creature, so like the conclave it serves. Cut one head and it grows two. Damage it and it flourishes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Look at this creature, so like the conclave it serves. Cut one head and it grows two. Damage it and it flourishes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Look at this creature, so like the conclave it serves. Cut one head and it grows two. Damage it and it flourishes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Look at this creature, so like the conclave it serves. Cut one head and it grows two. Damage it and it flourishes.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Get Final T-Shirt Reward</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Recevez le T-shirt récompense final</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erhalte die abschließende T-Shirt-Belohnung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vinci la T-shirt del Premio Finale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Obtén el premio de la última camiset</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Get Final T-Shirt Reward</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Get Final T-Shirt Reward</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Get Final T-Shirt Reward</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Get Final T-Shirt Reward</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Get Final T-Shirt Reward</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Get Final T-Shirt Reward</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Red_Portal_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Red mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mana rouge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rotes Mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mana rosso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Maná rojo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Red mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Red mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Red mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Red mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Red mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Red mana</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Red_Portal_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this colour of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le mana rouge consume ses ennemis. Le feu et la destruction dominent cette couleur de magie. Les dragons en sont l'incarnation la plus pure. Le mana rouge provient des montagnes.\nCette exposition est en cours de construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rotes Mana verbrennt seine Gegner. Feuer und Zerstörung sind die Kennzeichen dieser Farbe. Drachen sind die perfekte Verkörperung dessen. Rotes Mana kommt aus den Bergen.\nAn dieser Ausstellung wird derzeit noch gearbeitet.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mana rosso incenerisce qualsiasi avversario. Il fuoco e la distruzione dominano le magie di questo colore. I draghi rappresentano la sua incarnazione più pura. Il mana rosso proviene dalle montagne.\nQuesta mostra al momento è in costruzione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El maná rojo quema a sus oponentes. El fuego y la destrucción dominan este color de magia. Los dragones son su forma más pura. El maná rojo proviene de las montañas.\nEsta muestra está actualmente en construcción.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this color of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this color of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this color of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this color of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this color of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Red mana burns away its foes. Fire and destruction rule this color of magic. Dragons are its purest embodiment. Red mana comes from the mountains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Serra_Angel_1_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Serra Angel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ange de Serra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Serra Engel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Angelo di Serra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ángel de Serra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Serra Angel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Serra Angel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Serra Angel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Serra Angel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Serra Angel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Serra Angel</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Serra_Angel_2_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Serra Angel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ange de Serra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Serra Engel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Angelo di Serra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ángel de Serra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Serra Angel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Serra Angel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Serra Angel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Serra Angel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Serra Angel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Serra Angel</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Sphinx_1_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sfinge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esfinge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sphinx</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Sphinx_2_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sfinge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esfinge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Sphinx</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sphinx</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Sphinx_1_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sphinxes drink from the mystic meres of Serra’s realm, where their keen eyes watch reflections of what is and what is yet to come.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les sphinx s'abreuvent dans les étangs mystiques du royaume de Serra, où leur regard vif surprend les reflets de ce qui est et de ce qui va venir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sphingen trinken aus den mystischen Weihern in Serras Reich, in denen sie mit ihren wachen Augen die Spiegelungen dessen, was war und was noch kommen wird, lesen können.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le sfingi bevono dai mistici laghi del reame di Serra, dove il loro sguardo acuto osserva il riflesso di ciò che è e di ciò che sarà.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las esfinges beben de las lagunas místicas del reino de Serra, en donde sus agudos ojos ven reflejos de lo que es y lo que será.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  Sphinxes drink from the mystic meres of Serra's realm, where their keen eyes watch reflections of what is and what is yet to come.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  Sphinxes drink from the mystic meres of Serra's realm, where their keen eyes watch reflections of what is and what is yet to come.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  Sphinxes drink from the mystic meres of Serra's realm, where their keen eyes watch reflections of what is and what is yet to come.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  Sphinxes drink from the mystic meres of Serra's realm, where their keen eyes watch reflections of what is and what is yet to come.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  Sphinxes drink from the mystic meres of Serra's realm, where their keen eyes watch reflections of what is and what is yet to come.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sphinxes drink from the mystic meres of Serra’s realm, where their keen eyes watch reflections of what is and what is yet to come.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Dragon_1_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">They say a single drop of dragon’s blood turns skin to scale and fist to claw.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une seule goutte suffit à faire pousser des écailles sur la peau, des griffes sur les mains.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schon ein kleiner Tropfen verwandelt Haut in Schuppen und Faust in Klaue.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dicono che una sola goccia di sangue di drago trasforma la pelle in scaglie e i pugni in artigli.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una sola gota cambia la piel por escamas y los puños por garras.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  They say a single drop of dragon's blood turns skin to scale and fist to claw.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  They say a single drop of dragon's blood turns skin to scale and fist to claw.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  They say a single drop of dragon's blood turns skin to scale and fist to claw.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  They say a single drop of dragon's blood turns skin to scale and fist to claw.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  They say a single drop of dragon's blood turns skin to scale and fist to claw.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">They say a single drop of dragon’s blood turns skin to scale and fist to claw.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Serra_Angel_2_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">When she flies above the good, they consider themselves blessed. When she flies above the wicked, they consider themselves dead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">« Les anges sont peut-être irréels, mais leurs épées sont bien forgées. » —Un barbare profane</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn sie über den Guten fliegt, bedeutet das Segen. Wenn sie über den Bösen fliegt, bedeutet das Tod.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quando vola sopra i retti, si considerano benedetti. Quando vola sopra i malvagi, si considerano morti.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuando vuela sobre los buenos, se consideran bendecidos. Cuando vuela sobre los perversos, se consideran muertos.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  When she flies above the good, they consider themselves blessed. When she flies above the wicked, they consider themselves dead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  When she flies above the good, they consider themselves blessed. When she flies above the wicked, they consider themselves dead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  When she flies above the good, they consider themselves blessed. When she flies above the wicked, they consider themselves dead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  When she flies above the good, they consider themselves blessed. When she flies above the wicked, they consider themselves dead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  When she flies above the good, they consider themselves blessed. When she flies above the wicked, they consider themselves dead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">When she flies above the good, they consider themselves blessed. When she flies above the wicked, they consider themselves dead.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">White_Portal_title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">White mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mana blanc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weißes Mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mana bianco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Maná blanco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  White mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  White mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  White mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  White mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  White mana</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">White mana</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">White_Portal_details</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">White mana lays down the law. It’s about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le mana blanc détermine les lois. Il se spécialise dans la protection, la lumière, les armées de soldats et les escadrilles d'anges. Le mana blanc provient des plaines.\nCette exposition est en cours de construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weißes Mana kümmert sich um Recht und Ordnung. Du brauchst es für Schutz, Licht, Soldaten-Armeen und Engel-Geschwader. Weißes Mana kommt aus den Ebenen.\nAn dieser Ausstellung wird derzeit noch gearbeitet.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mana bianco amministra la legge. I suoi punti di forza sono luce e protezione, armate di soldati e schiere di angeli. Il mana bianco proviene dalle pianure.\nQuesta mostra al momento è in costruzione.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El maná blanco dicta la ley. Trata de la protección, la luz, ejércitos de soldados y ángeles. El maná blanco proviene de las llanuras.\nEsta muestra está actualmente en construcción.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">JP  White mana lays down the law. It's about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">KR  White mana lays down the law. It's about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SG  White mana lays down the law. It's about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HK  White mana lays down the law. It's about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">TW  White mana lays down the law. It's about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">White mana lays down the law. It’s about protection, light, armies of soldiers, and flights of angels. White mana comes from the plains.\nThis exhibit is currently under construction.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>