<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Water Bug Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack Insecte D'Eau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wasserkäfer-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pack Insetti D'Acqua</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack Bicho De Agua </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The water bug is one of your weirdest creations, becoming stronger in death, multiplying to overwhelm the enemy. This pack gives you  access to all 3 types of water bug for use in Killer Plants from Outer Space. Also included in this pack is a water bug T-shirt (both male and female versions included) and a large mortar pot plant to decorate your apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'insecte d'eau est l'une de vos créations les plus étranges. Il devient plus fort une fois mort et se multiplie pour assaillir vos ennemis. Ce pack vous donne accès aux trois types d'insectes d'eau à utiliser dans Killer Plants From Outer Space, à un t-shirt insecte d'eau (versions homme et femme incluses) et à une grande plante mortier en pot pour décorer votre appartement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Wasserkäfer ist eine der seltsamsten Kreationen, da er im Todeskampf stärker wird und sich vermehrt, um den Feind zu überwältigen. Dieses Paket verleiht Zugriff auf alle 3 Wasserkäfer-Arten in "Killer Plants from Outer Space". Es enthält ebenfalls ein Wasserkäfer-Shirt (Damen und Herren) und eine große Mörser-Topfpflanze zur Verschönerung Ihres Apartments. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'Insetto d'Acqua è una creatura stranissima, perché da morta diventa ancora più forte, moltiplicandosi e sopraffacendo così il nemico. Questo pack ti consente di accedere a tutti i 3 tipi di Insetti d'Acqua utilizzabili in Killer Plants from Outer Space. Il pack include anche una t-shirt Insetto d'Acqua (in doppia versione per uomo e donna) e una grande pianta mortaio in vaso per decorare il tuo appartamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El bicho de agua es una de tus creaciones más extrañas, se hace más fuerte con la muerte multiplicándose hasta asfixiar al enemigo. Este pack garantiza el acceso a los tres tipos de bicho de agua para usarlos en Killer Plants from Outer Space. También se incluye en este pack una camiseta de bicho de agua y una gorra de béisbol (versiones para hombre y mujer) y una planta mortero en maceta grande para decorar tu apartamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>