<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">AT-ST Statue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Statue AT-ST</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">AT-ST Statue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Statua AT-SC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estatua del AT-ST</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">AT-ST Statue</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is a statue of the Imperial All Terrain Scout Transport.  These vehicles don’t fair too well on terrain that consists of rolling logs… or swinging logs.  Maybe you should just stay away from forests for a while and keep it in your living room. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C'est une statue de la force tout-terrain de l'Empire.  Ces véhicules n'aiment pas trop les terrains boisés. Vous devriez vous éloigner des forêts pendant quelque temps et garder cette statue dans votre salon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dies ist eine Statue des imperialen All Terrain-Scout Transport. Diese Fahrzeuge kommen nicht sehr gut mit Gebieten zurecht, die aus rollenden oder schwankenden Baumstämmen bestehen. Vielleicht solltest du dich einfach für eine Weile von den Wäldern fernhalten und sie in deinem Wohnzimmer lassen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa è la statua del Camminatore AT-ST Imperiale. Questi veicoli non se la cavano troppo bene su superfici fatte di tronchi che rotolano… o che ondeggiano. Forse faresti meglio a stare lontano dalle foreste per un po' e tenerla nel tuo salotto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta es una estatua del All Terrain Scout Transport. Estos vehículos no funcionan muy bien en terrenos con troncos rodantes… o troncos oscilantes.  Quizá deberías alejarte de los bosques durante un tiempo y ponerla en tu sala de estar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This is a statue of the Imperial All Terrain Scout Transport.  These vehicles don’t fair too well on terrain that consists of rolling logs… or swinging logs.  Maybe you should just stay away from forests for a while and keep it in your living room. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>