<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Genie in a Bottle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Génie dans une bouteille</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Flaschengeist</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Genio in una bottiglia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Genio en una botella</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ビンの中の精霊</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">병 속의 지니</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Genie in a Bottle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">瓶中精靈</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">瓶中精靈</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Genie in a Bottle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There is no better way to catch the elusive Treasure in the Aurora Sky Fishing game than with this fantastical lure. This will increase your chances of catching Treasure items dramatically.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il n'y a pas de meilleur appât afin d'attraper le trésor insaisissable du jeu de pêche d'Aurora Sky. Vous augmenterez radicalement vos chances d'attraper de précieux objets. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es gibt keinen besseren Weg, die Schätze beim Aurora Sky Fishing zu fangen, als mit diesem fantastischen Köder. Er wird deine Chancen darauf, Schätze zu fangen, erheblich steigern. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non c'è un'esca migliore di questa per trovare l'inafferrabile Tesoro nel gioco Pesca del cielo di Aurora. Aumenterà in maniera considerevole le tue possibilità di trovare gli oggetti Tesori.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sin duda, este cebo es la mejor forma de atrapar el escurridizo tesoro en el juego de pesca espacial de Aurora. Aumentará con creces las probabilidades de atrapar tesoros.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラのスカイフィッシングゲームでこのルアを使うと、すばしっこい宝物を釣ることができます。このルアを使えば宝物を釣る確率がグンと上がります！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">오로라 스카이 피싱 게임에서 찾아내기 힘든 보물을 잡으려면 이 환상적인 미끼가 최고입니다. 이 미끼는 보물 아이템 포획 확률을 크게 높여줍니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">There is no better way to catch the elusive Treasure in the Aurora Sky Fishing game than with this fantastical lure. This will increase your chances of catching Treasure items dramatically.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這個神奇魚餌是極光空中釣魚遊戲中釣到絕世珍寶的最佳方式。這將大大增加您釣到各種珍寶的機會。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這個神奇魚餌是極光空中釣魚遊戲中釣到絕世珍寶的最佳方式。這將大大增加您釣到各種珍寶的機會。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">There is no better way to catch the elusive Treasure in the Aurora Sky Fishing game than with this fantastical lure. This will increase your chances of catching Treasure items dramatically.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>