<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Novus Prime Concept: The Blackwing</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Concept de Novus Prime : Le Blackwing</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Novus Prime Konzept: The Blackwing</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Design Novus Prime: Blackwing</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Concepto de Novus Prime: Blackwing</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムのコンセプト：ブラックウィング</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임 컨셉: 블랙윙</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Novus Prime Concept: The Blackwing</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Novus Prime概念畫：Blackwing</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Novus Prime概念畫：Blackwing</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Novus Prime Concept: The Blackwing</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. Collapsing into a nearly-undetectable shape, the Blackwing can be carried and deployed by Bot capital ships, providing an assault force of incredible numbers. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ornez vos murs de peintures conceptuelles de Novus Prime. Changeant de forme jusqu'à être quasi-indétectable, le Blackwing peut être transporté et déployé par les droïdes amiraux, fournissant une force de combat incroyablement nombreuse. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schmücke deine Wände mit den Konzeptzeichnungen von Novus Prime. Indem er auf eine kaum wahrnehmbare Form zusammenschrumpft, kann der Blackwind von Bot-Schiffen transportiert und eingesetzt werden. Dadurch wird ein Überraschungsgriff von unglaublicher Größe möglich. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Decora le tue pareti con il design della Novus Prime. Collassando in una forma quasi non identificabile, la Blackwing può essere trasportata e dispiegata dalle navi ammiraglie, assicurando un'incredibile forza di assalto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Adorna tus paredes con las pinturas conceptuales de Novus Prime. Adorna tus paredes con las pinturas conceptuales de Novus Prime. Creando formas casi indetectables, Blackwing puede ser cargado y lanzado por buques capitales robot, creando una fuerza de ataque de números increíbles. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムのコンセプト絵画を壁に飾ろう。検出不可能なほどの変形できるブラッグウィングはボット主力艦に収納され、そこから出撃させることができるため、その圧倒的な数で敵の脅威となる。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임의 컨셉화로 벽을 장식합니다. 거의 탐지가 불가능한 함선인 블랙윙은 봇 주력함에 수송되어 출격하며, 엄청난 수로 강력한 기습력을 제공합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. Collapsing into a nearly-undetectable shape, the Blackwing can be carried and deployed by Bot capital ships, providing an assault force of incredible numbers. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用Novus Prime的概念繪畫裝飾你的牆壁。Blackwing能變形成幾乎不能探測到的形狀，由機械主力艦運送及調派，組成驚人的攻擊力量。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用Novus Prime的概念繪畫裝飾你的牆壁。Blackwing能變形成幾乎不能探測到的形狀，由機械主力艦運送及調派，組成驚人的攻擊力量。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. Collapsing into a nearly-undetectable shape, the Blackwing can be carried and deployed by Bot capital ships, providing an assault force of incredible numbers. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>