<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Abuser (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le ravageur (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Neutralisator (Weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Neutralizzatore (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Despiadado (femenino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Abuser (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Highly effective at close range, but lacking in long range accuracy, the Abuser is a common sight on the battlefield. Hopefully not a sight you'll be on the wrong end of. BONUS: Unlocks the Abuser for use in MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Extrêmement efficace à bout portant, mais manquant de précision à longue portée, le ravageur est une arme fréquente sur le champ de bataille. Vous n'avez plus qu'à espérer ne pas vous retrouver du mauvais côté du canon. BONUS : Déverrouille le ravageur utilisable dans MiniBots multijoueur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Äußerst wirksam im Nahkampf ist er im Fernkampf weniger genau. Der Neutralisator ist auf dem Schlachtfeld häufig anzutreffen. Hoffentlich kommt Sie sein Anblick nicht teuer zu stehen!  BONUS: Gibt den Neutralisator für den Einsatz im MiniBots-Multiplayer-Modus frei. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Altamente efficace a distanza ravvicinata, ma privo di precisione a lunga portata, il Neutralizzatore è molto comune sul campo di battaglia. Augurati di non trovarti mai dalla parte sbagliata di quest'arma. BONUS: sblocca il Neutralizzatore per l'uso in modalità multigiocatore in MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Abusador, muy efectivo a poca distancia pero menos preciso a mayor distancia, es una vista común en el campo de batalla. Esperemos que no estés en la vista equivocada. BONUS: Desbloquea el Despiadado para usarlo en modo de varios jugadores de los MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Highly effective at close range, but lacking in long range accuracy, the Abuser is a common sight on the battlefield. Hopefully not a sight you'll be on the wrong end of. BONUS: Unlocks the Abuser for use in MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>