<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Head on a plate (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La tête sur un plateau, pour femme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kopf auf einer Servierplatte, für die Frauen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Testa su un vassoio, per le donne</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cabeza en una bandeja, para las muejeres</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Head on a plate (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Head on a plate (Women)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This striking costume will make you look like your head is detached from your neck, held up on a tray! As hilarious as it is gruesome, it will be certain to turn a few heads, and be the center of attention at any Party! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avec ce costume étonnant, votre tête aura l'air détachée de votre cou, et brandie sur un plateau d'argent! Aussi irrésistible que choquant, ce déguisement ne laissera personne indifférent, et attirera l'attention de tous, où que vous soyez! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE"> Diese markante Kostüm werden Sie sich wie Sie Ihren Kopf schauen ist vom Hals abgetrennt, auf einem Tablett gehalten! So komisch wie grausam ist, wird es sicher sein, ein paar Köpfe drehen, und wird das Zentrum der Aufmerksamkeit zu jeder Party![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Con questo incredibile costume, la tua testa sarà staccata dal tuo collo, e brandito sul piatto d'argento! Irresistibile come scioccante, questo costume non lascia nessuno indifferente, e di attirare l'attenzione di tutti, ovunque tu sia![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con este traje increíble, tu cabeza se verá separada de su cuello y la blandió en bandeja de plata! Como irresistible como impactante, este traje no deja indiferente a nadie, y atraer la atención de todo el mundo, dondequiera que estés! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This striking costume will make you look like your head is detached from your neck, held up on a tray! As hilarious as it is gruesome, it will be certain to turn a few heads, and be the center of attention at any Party! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This striking costume will make you look like your head is detached from your neck, held up on a tray! As hilarious as it is gruesome, it will be certain to turn a few heads, and be the center of attention at any Party! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>