<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">nDreams Ultimate Fantasy Fashion Bundle (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot tendance ultime de style "Fantaise" nDreams (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">nDreams Ultimatives Fantasie-Mode-Bundle (Frau)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Super pacchetto moda Fantasia di nDreams (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete superior Moda Fantasía de nDreams (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">nDreams 究極のファンタジーファッションセット （女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">nDreams 얼티메이트 판타지 패션 번들 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">nDreams Ultimate Fantasy Fashion Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">nDreams 終極幻想風格服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">nDreams 終極幻想風格服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">nDreams Ultimate Fantasy Fashion Bundle (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Ultimate Fantasy Fashion Bundle contains all of the currently released Fantasy Fashion clothing items, exclusively from nDreams. This incredible value for money bundle contains the following items: \n\n

* Fantasy Fashion - Angel Wings (Female) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Demon Wings (Female) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Barbarian Torso (Female) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Barbarian Legs and Boots (Female) (Legs and Feet) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Savage Blade (Female) (Hands) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Savage Torso (Female) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Savage Legs and Feet (Female) (Legs and Feet) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Amazonian Tribal Torso (Female) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Amazonian Tribal Legs and Feet (Female) (Legs and Feet) \n\n

※ All of the above items will become available in their relevant categories on purchasing this bundle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le lot tendance ultime de style "Fantaise" contient tous les vêtements actuellement proposés dans le style “Fantaisie”, proposés en exclusivité par nDreams. Ce lot à l’excellent rapport qualité-prix comporte les éléments suivants : \n\n

* Style "Fantaise" – Ailes d’ange (Femme) (Torse) \n
* Style "Fantaise" – Ailes de démon (Femme) (Torse) \n
* Style "Fantaise" – Torse de barbare (Femme) (Torse) \n
* Style "Fantaise" – Jambes et bottes de barbare (Femme) (Jambes et pieds) \n
* Style "Fantaise" – Lame sauvage (Femme) (Mains) \n
* Style "Fantaise" – Torse sauvage (Femme) (Torse) \n
* Style "Fantaise" – Jambes et pieds sauvages (Femme) (Jambes et pieds) \n
* Style "Fantaise" – Torse tribal amazonien (Femme) (Torse) \n
* Style "Fantaise" – Jambes et pieds tribaux amazoniens (Femme) (Jambes et pieds) \n\n

※ Les éléments ci-dessus seront disponibles dans leurs catégories respectives lors de l’achat de ce lot. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Ultimative Fantasie-Mode-Bundle enthält alle derzeit erhältlichen Fantasie-Mode-Teile, exklusiv von nDreams. Dieses unglaublich preisgünstige Bundle enthält die folgenden Gegenstände: \n\n

* Fantasie-Mode - Engelsflügel (Frau) (Torso)\n
* Fantasie-Mode - Dämonenflügel (Frau) (Torso)\n
* Fantasie-Mode - Barbar: Torso (Frau) (Torso)\n
* Fantasie-Mode - Barbar: Beine und Stiefel (Frau) (Beine und Füße)\n
* Fantasie-Mode - Wilde Klinge (Frau) (Hände)\n
* Fantasie-Mode - Wilder Torso (Frau) (Torso)\n
* Fantasie-Mode - Wilde Beine und Füße (Frau) (Beine und Füße)\n
* Fantasie-Mode - Amazonenstamm-Rumpf (Frau) (Torso)\n
* Fantasie-Mode - Amazonenstamm-Hosen und -Füße (Frau) (Beine und Füße)\n\n

※ Nach dem Kauf dieses Bundles werden alle Gegenstände in ihrer entsprechenden Kategorie abgelegt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il super pacchetto moda Fantasia contiene tutti i capi d'abbigliamento già disponibili di moda Fantasia, in esclusiva da nDreams. Questo pacchetto vale tutti i soldi che costa e contiene i seguenti oggetti: \n\n

* Moda Fantasia - Ali d'angelo (donna) (torso) \n
* Moda Fantasia - Ali di demone (donna) (torso) \n
* Moda Fantasia - Torso da barbaro (donna) (torso) \n
* Moda Fantasia - Gambe e stivali da barbaro (donna) (gambe e piedi) \n
* Moda Fantasia - Spada da barbaro (donna) (mani) \n
* Moda Fantasia - Torso da barbaro (donna) (torso) \n
* Moda Fantasia - Gambe e piedi da barbaro (donna) (gambe e piedi) \n
* Moda Fantasia - Torso tribale da amazzone (donna) (torso) \n
* Moda Fantasia - Gambe e piedi tribali da amazzone (donna) (gambe e piedi) \n\n

※ Dopo aver acquistato il pacchetto, tutti questi capi saranno disponibili nelle relative categorie.
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El paquete superior Moda Fantasía contiene, de forma exclusiva para nDreams, todos los artículos de la Moda Fantasía que hemos sacado al mercado. Este increíble paquete con una buena relación calidad-precio contiene: \n\n

* Moda Fantasía: alas de ángel (mujer) (torso) \n
* Moda Fantasía: alas de demonio (mujer) (torso) \n
* Moda Fantasía: torso de bárbaro (mujer) (torso) \n
* Moda Fantasía: piernas y botas de bárbaro (mujer) (piernas y pies) \n
* Moda Fantasía: espada salvaje (mujer) (manos) \n
* Moda Fantasía: torso salvaje (mujer) (torso) \n
* Moda Fantasía: piernas y pies salvajes (mujer) (piernas y pies) \n
* Moda Fantasía: torso de tribu amazónica (mujer) (torso) \n
* Moda Fantasía: piernas y pies de tribu amazónica (hombre) (piernas y pies) \n\n

※ Estos objetos estarán disponibles en sus categorías correspondientes una vez que hayas comprado este paquete. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">究極のファンタジーファッションセットにはnDreamsだけで手に入る、最近リリースされたファンタジーファッションの衣装アイテム全てが入っています。このお買い得セットには、以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n\n

* ファンタジーファッション - 天使の羽（女性用）（胴体） \n
* ファンタジーファッション - 悪魔の羽（女性用）（胴体） \n
* ファンタジーファッション - 野獣の胴体（女性用）（胴体） \n
* ファンタジーファッション - 野獣の脚とブーツ（女性用）（脚と足）\n
* ファンタジーファッション - 勇猛な戦士の剣（女性用）（手） \n
* ファンタジーファッション - 勇猛な戦士の胴体（女性用）（胴体）\n
* ファンタジーファッション - 勇猛な戦士の脚と足（女性用）（脚と足）\n
* ファンタジーファッション – アマゾン トライバル胴体（女性用）（胴体）\n
* ファンタジーファッション – アマゾン トライバル脚と足（女性用）（脚と足）\n\n

※ このセットを買うと、上記全アイテムが関連カテゴリー内で使用できるようになります。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">얼티메이트 판타지 패션 번들은 nDreams에서 독점으로 현재 출시된 모든 판타지 패션 의상 아이템을 포함하고 있습니다. 이 놀라울 정도로 저렴한 번들은 다음 아이템을 포함합니다: \n\n

* 판타지 패션 – 천사 날개 (여성) (몸통) \n
* 판타지 패션 – 악마 날개 (여성) (몸통) \n
* 판타지 패션 – 미개인 몸통 (여성) (몸통) \n
* 판타지 패션 – 미개인 다리 및 부츠 (여성) (다리 및 발) \n
* 판타지 패션 – 야만인 검 (여성) (손) \n
* 판타지 패션 – 야만인 몸통 (여성) (몸통) \n
* 판타지 패션 – 야만인 다리 및 발 (여성) (다리 및 발) \n
* 판타지 패션 – 아마존 여전사 몸통 (여성) (몸통) \n
* 판타지 패션 – 아마존 여전사 다리 및 발 (여성) (다리 및 발) \n\n

※ 상기 모든 아이템들은 이 번들 구입과 동시에 적절한 카테고리에서 이용할 수 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Ultimate Fantasy Fashion Bundle contains all of the currently released Fantasy Fashion clothing items, exclusively from nDreams. This incredible value for money bundle contains the following items: \n\n

* Fantasy Fashion - Angel Wings (Women) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Demon Wings (Women) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Barbarian Torso (Women) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Barbarian Legs and Boots (Women) (Legs and Feet) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Savage Blade (Women) (Hands) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Savage Torso (Women) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Savage Legs and Feet (Women) (Legs and Feet) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Amazonian Tribal Torso (Women) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Amazonian Tribal Legs and Feet (Women) (Legs and Feet) \n\n

※ All of the above items will become available in their relevant categories on purchasing this bundle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">終極幻想風格服裝套裝包括 nDreams 當前獨家推出的所有幻想風格服裝，本套超值裝包含以下物品：\n\n


* 幻想風格服裝 — 天使翅膀（上身/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 惡魔翅膀（上身/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 野蠻人（上身/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 野蠻人（下身和靴子/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 野蠻之刃（手部/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 野人（上身/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 野人（下身和靴子/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 亞馬遜族人（上身/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 亞馬遜族人（下身和靴子/女用）\n\n

※購買套裝後，以上所有物品都會加入相關的類別中。 [#legal] [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">終極幻想風格服裝套裝包括 nDreams 當前獨家推出的所有幻想風格服裝，本套超值裝包含以下物品：\n\n


* 幻想風格服裝 — 天使翅膀（上身/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 惡魔翅膀（上身/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 野蠻人（上身/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 野蠻人（下身和靴子/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 野蠻之刃（手部/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 野人（上身/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 野人（下身和靴子/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 亞馬遜族人（上身/女用）\n
* 幻想風格服裝 — 亞馬遜族人（下身和靴子/女用）\n\n

※購買套裝後，以上所有物品都會加入相關的類別中。 [#legal] [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Ultimate Fantasy Fashion Bundle contains all of the currently released Fantasy Fashion clothing items, exclusively from nDreams. This incredible value for money bundle contains the following items: \n\n

* Fantasy Fashion - Angel Wings (Female) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Demon Wings (Female) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Barbarian Torso (Female) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Barbarian Legs and Boots (Female) (Legs and Feet) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Savage Blade (Female) (Hands) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Savage Torso (Female) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Savage Legs and Feet (Female) (Legs and Feet) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Amazonian Tribal Torso (Female) (Torso) \n
* Fantasy Fashion - Amazonian Tribal Legs and Feet (Female) (Legs and Feet) \n\n

※ All of the above items will become available in their relevant categories on purchasing this bundle. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>