<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MotorStorm® Busted TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MotorStorm® Busted TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">TV HS MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MotorStorm®: Kaputter Fernseher</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">TV esplosa MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tele rota de MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">MotorStorm® 映らないテレビ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">MotorStorm® 부서진 TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">MotorStorm™ Busted TV</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">MotorStorm™ 壞掉的電視機</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">MotorStorm™ 壞掉的電視機</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MotorStorm® Busted TV</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">0 channels of nothing for you to stare at during those long desert evenings. Some may say it's more entertaining than watching most TV shows, but why don't you just switch it off and we'll see you down the bar.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">0 channels of nothing for you to stare at during those long desert evenings. Some may say it's more entertaining than watching most TV shows, but why don't you just switch it off and we'll see you down the bar.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">0 chaînes à regarder pendant les longues soirées du désert. Certains diront que c'est toujours mieux que la plupart des émissions de télé, mais pourquoi ne pas l'éteindre et venir nous rejoindre au bar?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Null Programme mit Nichts, die du dir an diesen langen Abenden in der Wüste ansehen können. Manche würden sagen, dass es interessanter ist, als die meisten Fernsehsendungen, aber warum schaltest du den Kasten nicht einfach aus und wir sehen uns an der Bar ...[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Zero canali di nulla da fissare durante le lunghe sere nel deserto. Alcuni direbbero che è più divertente di molti programmi televisivi, ma perchè non la spegni e non ci raggiungi giù al bar?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cero canales para que no veas nada durante esas largas noches en el desierto. Algunos te dirían que es más interesante que la gran mayoría de los programas de la tele, pero mejor, ¿por qué no la apagas y nos vemos en el bar?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">合計０チャンネル楽しめる壊れたテレビ。だが砂漠の上に広がる星空はどのテレビ番組よりも迫力がある。このテレビの持ち主もそれに気付き自らテレビを叩き壊したらしい。大自然を愛するモタストフリークには壊れたテレビこそなにか意味があるのかも。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">기나긴 사막의 밤을 즐겁게 해 줄 고장난 TV입니다. 나오지 않는 화면을 쳐다보는 게 최근의 TV 프로그램들을 시청하는 것 보다는 재미있다는 사람도 있지만요. 차라리 TV를 끄고, 바깥에서 만나는 게 어떨까요.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">0 channels of nothing for you to stare at during those long desert evenings. Some may say it's more entertaining than watching most TV shows, but why don't you just switch it off and we'll see you down the bar.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在沙漠的漫長夜晚，甚麼電視節目也沒有。有些人也許認為看這個比其他電視節目更具娛樂性，但你何不索性關掉它，到酒吧喝一杯呢。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在沙漠的漫長夜晚，甚麼電視節目也沒有。有些人也許認為看這個比其他電視節目更具娛樂性，但你何不索性關掉它，到酒吧喝一杯呢。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">0 channels of nothing for you to stare at during those long desert evenings. Some may say it's more entertaining than watching most TV shows, but why don't you just switch it off and we'll see you down the bar.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>