<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dead to Rights®: Retribution GAC Scout Gloves</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Gants d'éclaireur du GAC Dead to Rights®: Retribution</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dead to Rights®: Retribution - guanti esploratore GAC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guantes de observador del GAC de Dead to Rights®: Retribution</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">『DEAD TO RIGHTS®：RETRIBUTION』GACスカウトグローブ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">「Dead to Rights®: Retribution」 정찰용 장갑(남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Dead to Rights®: Retribution GAC Scout Gloves (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「Dead to Rights®: Retribution」 GAC軍用手套(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「Dead to Rights®: Retribution」 GAC軍用手套(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dead to Rights®: Retribution GAC Scout Gloves</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">These synthetic leather gloves are part of the Grant City Anti-Crime standard model 12 armour loadout. They feature silicone finger tips for increased versatility, a gel palm patch for ulnar nerve protection, and are reinforced with carbon fibre/para-aramid knuckle panels.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ces gants en cuir synthétique font partie de l'armure anti-crime de Grant City de modèle standard 12. Les extrémités en silicone facilitent la souplesse du geste, une poche de gel sur la paume garantit la protection du nerf cubital, et les jointures sont renforcées par des plaques de fibres de carbone et d'aramide.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questi guanti sintetici in pelle fanno parte dell'equipaggiamento standard modello 12 della divisione anti-crimine di Grant City. Sono dotati di punte in silicone per una maggiore versatilità, di una toppa palmare in gelatina per meglio proteggere il nervo ulnare, e di paranocche rinforzati in fibra di carbonio e kevlar. </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estos guantes de cuero sintético son parte de las protecciones estándar modelo 12 del Grupo de Asalto contra el Crimen. Las yemas de los dedos de silicona proporcionan una mayor versatilidad y el refuerzo de gel de la palma protege el nervio ulnar. Los nudillos están reforzados con paneles de fibra de carbono y para-aramida.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この合成繊維のグローブは、グラントシティ防犯機動隊のスタンダード装備である"モデル12アーマー"の一部である。指先部分はシリコン製で伸縮性があり、手のひら部分にはゲル状のパッチを使用して尺骨神経を守っている。また、ナックルパネルには強化カーボン/パラアラミド繊維を採用している。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">합성 가죽으로 제작한 장갑은 GAC 표준 모델 12 방어구의 하나입니다. 실리콘으로 만들어진 손가락 끝 부분은 뛰어난 착용감과 접지력을 자랑합니다. 손바닥을 보호하는 젤은 민감한 손의 신경을 지켜주며, 카본 섬유와 파라-아라미드로 덧대었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">These synthetic leather gloves are part of the Grant City Anti-Crime standard model 12 armour loadout. They feature silicone finger tips for increased versatility, a gel palm patch for ulnar nerve protection, and are reinforced with carbon fibre/para-aramid knuckle panels.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這對合成纖維手套是Grant City反罪惡機動隊的標準裝備「12號防護裝備」的一部份。指尖部份以矽膠製成，可自由伸縮；手掌部份使用了凝膠狀的軟墊，保護尺骨神經。此外，手指關節的部份採用了碳纖維／對位芳香聚醯胺進一步強化。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這對合成纖維手套是Grant City反罪惡機動隊的標準裝備「12號防護裝備」的一部份。指尖部份以矽膠製成，可自由伸縮；手掌部份使用了凝膠狀的軟墊，保護尺骨神經。此外，手指關節的部份採用了碳纖維／對位芳香聚醯胺進一步強化。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">These synthetic leather gloves are part of the Grant City Anti-Crime standard model 12 armor loadout. They feature silicone finger tips for increased versatility, a gel palm patch for ulnar nerve protection, and are reinforced with carbon fiber/para-aramid knuckle panels.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>