<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tree House Personal Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appartement personnel Cabane dans les arbres</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Persönliches Apartment "Baumhaus"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Appartamento personale Casa sull'albero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apartamento personal Casa del árbol</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A stunning circular treehouse built around the trunk of an ancient tree high up in the mountains. Made of wood and circular in design, there are two levels each offering spectacular views of the waterfalls and mountains outside. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une étonnante cabane construite autour du tronc d'un vieil arbre au cœur des montagnes. En bois et circulaire, cette cabane dispose de deux étages offrant des vues incroyables sur les chutes d'eau et les montagnes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein atemberaubendes rundes Baumhaus, das hoch oben in den Bergen um den Stamm eines alten Baums gebaut wurde. Das Baumhaus ist aus Holz und hat zwei Stockwerke, von denen  man eine fantastische Aussicht auf die Wasserfälle und die Berge hat. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una splendida casa circolare sull'albero costruita attorno al tronco di un antico albero in cima alle montagne. Fatta di legno e di forma circolare, è costruita su due livelli dai quali si possono ammirare panorami spettacolari sulle cascate e le montagne circostanti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una alucinante casa circular construida en el tronco de un antiguo árbol en lo alto de las montañas. Fabricada en madera y de diseño circular. Tiene dos pisos, ambos con vistas espectaculares a las cascadas y las montañas del exterior. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>