<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">skunk works tutorial</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Firing Range Tutorial</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Firing Range Tutorial</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Firing Range Tutorial</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Didacticiel Ateliers Moufette</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schießplatz-Anleitung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esercitazione Poligono di Tiro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tutorial del Proyecto Arsenalia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사격장 튜토리얼</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">射程挑戰的說明</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">射程挑戰的說明</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スカンクワークスについて</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">tutorial text 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to the Firing Range where we test out all the fantastic weapons in the Grummelnet library! In here you’ll find lots to discover, so let’s get started.\n\nTo my left are the computer terminals that operate the turrets on our amazing Firing Range. You and up to three other players will use a variety of classic weapons to try and stop a simulated army of the galaxy’s most infamous villains.\n\nTo my right is a Time Machine. Using it will transport you between Past, Present and Future versions of this very room! Each time period will allow you to test Grummelnet's weapons on the villains of that era.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Welcome to the Firing Range where we test out all the fantastic weapons in the Grummelnet library! In here you’ll find lots to discover, so let’s get started.\n\nTo my left are the computer terminals that operate the turrets on our amazing Firing Range. You and up to three other players will use a variety of classic weapons to try and stop a simulated army of the galaxy’s most infamous villains.\n\nTo my right is a Time Machine. Using it will transport you between Past, Present and Future versions of this very room! Each time period will allow you to test Grummelnet’s weapons on the villains of that era.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome to the Firing Range where we test out all the fantastic weapons in the Grummelnet library! In here you’ll find lots to discover, so let’s get started.\n\nTo my left are the computer terminals that operate the turrets on our amazing Firing Range. You and up to three other players will use a variety of classic weapons to try and stop a simulated army of the galaxy’s most infamous villains.\n\nTo my right is a Time Machine. Using it will transport you between Past, Present and Future versions of this very room! Each time period will allow you to test Grummelnet’s weapons on the villains of that era.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue aux Firing Range où nous testons toutes les armes fantastiques du catalogue Gruminnet ! Ici, il y a beaucoup à découvrir, alors commençons. \n\nÀ ma gauche, les terminaux informatiques qui gèrent les tourelles sur notre incroyable stand de tir. Toi, et jusqu'à trois autres joueurs, essaierez toute une série d'armes classiques pour tenter d'arrêter une armée factice des plus infâmes méchants de la galaxie. \n\nÀ ma droite, une machine à remonter le temps. Grâce à elle, tu pourras voyager dans la version passée, présente et future de cette pièce ! Tu auras l'opportunité de tester les armes Gruminnet sur les méchants appartenant à chacune des époques. \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen bei Schießplatz, wo wir all die fantastischen Waffen der Grummelnet-Sammlung testen! Hier gibt es eine Menge zu entdecken, also nichts wie los!\n\nLinks von mir befinden sich die Computer-Terminals, über die die Geschütze auf unserem unglaublichen Schießplatz gesteuert werden. Benutze zusammen mit bis zu drei weiteren Spielern eine Vielzahl von altbewährten Waffen, um eine simulierte Armee, bestehend aus den berüchtigtsten Schurken der Galaxie, aufzuhalten.\n\nRechts von mir befindet sich eine Zeitmaschine. Wenn du sie benutzt, kannst du zwischen Vergangenheit, Gegenwart und Zukunft dieses Raums hin- und herreisen! In jeder Zeitspanne kannst du die GrummelNet-Waffen an den Schurken der jeweiligen Ära erproben.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuti al Poligono di Tiro dove proveremo tutte le fantastiche armi dell'arsenale Grummelnet! Qui dentro ci sono un sacco di cose da scoprire, perciò iniziamo subito.\n\nAlla mia sinistra ci sono i computer che controllano le torrette della nostra strepitosa Bocca di fuoco. Tu e altri tre giocatori al massimo utilizzerete una serie di armi classiche con cui proverete a fermare un esercito simulato dei più infami malfattori della galassia.\n\nAlla mia destra c'è una Macchina del tempo, che vi permetterà di viaggiare tra le versioni del passato, presente e futuro della stanza in cui ci troviamo! In ogni periodo temporale potrete provare delle armi Grummelnet sui nemici di quell'era.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Bienvenido al Campo de Tiro, donde probamos todas las fantásticas armas del repertorio de Grummelnet! Aquí tienes mucho que descubrir, así que vamos a empezar.\n\nA mi izquierda están los terminales informáticos que operan las torretas de nuestro increíble campo de tiro. Tú y un máximo de otros tres jugadores podréis usar una gran variedad de armas clásicas para intentar detener un ejército simulado de los villanos más infames de la galaxia. \n\nA mi derecha está la máquina del tiempo. ¡Usándola viajarás a versiones pasadas, presentes y futuras de esta misma sala! En cada periodo de tiempo podrás probar armas de GrummelNet con los villanos de esa época.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사격장에 오신 것을 환영합니다! 그러멜넷의 모든 최신 무기들을 시험하는 장소이지요. 구경할 것이 많으니 천천히 둘러 보세요. \n\n제 왼쪽에는 우리의 환상적인 사격장에 있는 포탑들을 조종하는 단말기가 있습니다. 최대 3명의 다른 플레이어들과 여러 가지 무기들을 사용해서 우주에서 가장 흉악한 악당들의 시뮬레이션과 대결을 벌이세요. \n\n제 오른쪽에는 타임머신이 있습니다. 이걸 사용하면 과거, 현재, 그리고 미래에 존재하는 이 장소로 옮겨갈 수 있지요. 각기 다른 시간들은 그 시대의 악당과 싸울 수 있는 기회를 줄 거에요. \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">歡迎來到射程挑戰，我們要在這裡徹底檢驗格魯莫網路武器庫裡的各種珍奇武器！在這裡，有太多的東西等待你去探索，所以我們趕緊開始吧。\n\n我左手邊的是電腦終端機，用來操控射程裡的炮塔。你可和最多三名玩者將使用各種各樣的經典武器來阻擋由銀河系裡最惡名昭彰的惡棍組成的模擬軍團。\n\n我的右手邊是時光機。它可以讓你在這個房間內的過去、現在與未來時間來回穿梭。你可在每個時段利用那些惡棍來測試格魯莫網路的武器。\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">歡迎來到射程挑戰，我們要在這裡徹底檢驗格魯莫網路武器庫裡的各種珍奇武器！在這裡，有太多的東西等待你去探索，所以我們趕緊開始吧。\n\n我左手邊的是電腦終端機，用來操控射程裡的炮塔。你可和最多三名玩者將使用各種各樣的經典武器來阻擋由銀河系裡最惡名昭彰的惡棍組成的模擬軍團。\n\n我的右手邊是時光機。它可以讓你在這個房間內的過去、現在與未來時間來回穿梭。你可在每個時段利用那些惡棍來測試格魯莫網路的武器。\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">射撃練習場へようこそ！　ここは、グラメルネット社の自慢の武器ガラメカの数々をテストしています！　どうぞお楽しみください！\n\n右に見えるのは、当社自慢のキャノン操作用コンピュータです。最大で4人のプレイヤーが一緒にプレイできます。いろんな兵器を使って、銀河最悪の悪者たちのコピーを撃退するゲームです。\n左に見えるのはタイムマシンです。これを使えばあなたは過去・現在・未来のこの部屋へ自由に行き来できるのです！　どの時代でも、グラメルネット社の武器を使って敵をやっつけられます。\n\n</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">tutorial text 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Each Time Period has its own Firing Range challenges to offer. Present is for beginners, Past is for experienced players, and the Future is for expert players. Complete the challenge of the Future firing range and earn a Prize to be added to your Inventory for placement in your apartment spaces! \n\nDid we mention the Apogee Space Station is now available for sale out in the Central Hub of Grummelnet's factory?\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Each Time Period has its own Firing Range challenges to offer. Present is for beginners, Past is for experienced players, and the Future is for expert players. Complete the challenge of the Future firing range and earn a Prize to be added to your Inventory for placement in your apartment spaces! \n\nDid we mention the Apogee Space Station is now available for sale out in the Central Hub of Grummelnet’s factory?\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Each Time Period has its own Firing Range challenges to offer. Present is for beginners, Past is for experienced players, and the Future is for expert players. Complete the challenge of the Future firing range and earn a Prize to be added to your Inventory for placement in your apartment spaces! \n\nDid we mention the Apogee Space Station is now available for sale out in the Central Hub of Grummelnet’s factory?\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaque époque offre ses propres défis au Firing Range. Le Présent est destiné aux débutants, le Passé aux joueurs expérimentés et le Futur aux experts. Réussis le défi du stand de tir du Futur et remporte un Prix à ajouter dans ton inventaire avant de le placer dans ton appartement personnel ! \n\nAvons-nous mentionné que la Station Spatiale Apogée est maintenant disponible à la vente sur la plateforme centrale de l'usine GruminNet ? \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In jeder Zeitspanne gibt es spezielle Schießplatz-Herausforderungen. Die Gegenwart ist für Anfänger, die Vergangenheit für fortgeschrittene Spieler und die Zukunft für Experten. Absolviere die Herausforderung auf dem Schießplatz in der Zukunft und gewinne einen Preis, der deinem Inventar zur Ausstattung deines Apartments hinzugefügt wird! \n\nHatten wir schon erwähnt, dass die Apogee-Raumstation jetzt im Zentrum der Grummelnet-Fabrik erworben werden kann?\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ogni periodo temporale contiene delle sfide Poligono di Tiro. Il Presente è per i principianti, il Passato per i giocatori che hanno già qualche esperienza e il Futuro per giocatori molto esperti. Completa la sfida Firing Range del Futuro e vincerai un premio da aggiungere al tuo inventario e che potrai mettere nei tuoi appartamenti! \n\nTi abbiamo detto che la Stazione spaziale Apogee è ora in vendita presso l'Hub centrale dello stabilimento Grummelnet?\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cada periodo de tiempo tiene sus propios desafíos de campo de tiro que ofrecer. El presente es para los principiantes; el pasado, para los jugadores experimentados; y el futuro, para los expertos. ¡Supera el desafío del campo de tiro del futuro y gana un premio que se añadirá a tu inventario para que lo coloques en tus aposentos! \n\n¿Hemos dicho ya que la estación espacial Apogee está ahora a la venta en el centro de conexiones de la fábrica de Grummelnet?\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">각기 다른 시대에는 저마다의 도전 과제가 있습니다. 현재는 초보자를 위한 장소이고, 과거는 경험을 쌓은 플레이어, 그리고 미래는 숙련된 전문가를 위한 곳입니다. 미래의 사격장에서 도전 과제를 완료하면, 집을 꾸밀 수 있는 리워드를 받을 수 있다는 말도 있지요! \n\n참, 아포지 우주정거장을 이제 그러멜넷 공장 한 가운데서 살 수 있다는 말을 했나요?\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">每個時段都有不同的射程挑戰。「現在」適合初級玩者，「過去」適合熟練玩家，「未來」適合職業玩家。完成未來階段的挑戰將可贏得獎品，可以追加至你的道具一覽來裝飾個人空間內！\n\n還有，別忘了在格魯莫網路工廠的中央集線器區域可以購買各種商品！\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">每個時段都有不同的射程挑戰。「現在」適合初級玩者，「過去」適合熟練玩家，「未來」適合職業玩家。完成未來階段的挑戰將可贏得獎品，可以追加至你的道具一覽來裝飾個人空間內！\n\n還有，別忘了在格魯莫網路工廠的中央集線器區域可以購買各種商品！\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">時代ごとにむずかしさが違います。「現在」はかんたーんな初心者向け、「過去」はそこそこの中級者向け、「未来」はキビシー上級者向けです。未来でゲームをクリアすると、パーソナルスペースに置ける賞品がアイテムに追加されます！\n\nそれから、グラメル社の工場では、アポジー宇宙ステーションを購入することができますよ？\n\n</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">tutorial text 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">How to Play:\n\nThe battle is broken up into rounds, with the players making a move and then the villains. If the enemies get too close, and enter the Danger Zone, the Game is Over!\n\nUse the Gauge icons on your HUD to help you judge where to aim your shots.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">How to Play:\n\nThe battle is broken up into rounds, with the players making a move and then the villains. If the enemies get too close, and enter the Danger Zone, the Game is Over!\n\nUse the Gauge icons on your HUD to help you judge where to aim your shots.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">How to Play:\n\nThe battle is broken up into rounds, with the players making a move and then the villains. If the enemies get too close, and enter the Danger Zone, the Game is Over!\n\nUse the Gauge icons on your HUD to help you judge where to aim your shots.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Comment jouer : \n\n La bataille est divisée en tours : les joueurs font un mouvement, puis c'est aux vilains. Si les ennemis se rapprochent trop et entrent dans la Zone Danger, la partie est terminée ! \n\n Utilise les icônes des jauges sur ton HUD pour t'aider à bien viser tes cibles. \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">So wird gespielt:\n\nDer Kampf ist in Runden unterteilt, in denen jeweils die Spieler einen Zug machen, und dann die Schurken. Wenn die Gegner zu nah kommen und die Gefahrenzone betreten, ist das Spiel vorbei!\n\nDie Symbole auf der Anzeige helfen dir beim Zielen.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ecco come si gioca:\n\nLa battaglia è divisa in round. La prima mossa spetta ai giocatori, poi segue quella dei nemici. Se i nemici si avvicinano troppo ed entrano nella Zona pericolo, il gioco finisce!\n\nUsa le icone della Barra sul display e valuta dove indirizzare i tuoi colpi.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cómo jugar:\n\nEl combate se compone de rondas: los jugadores hacen un movimiento y luego les corresponde a los villanos. Si los enemigos se acercan demasiado y entran en la Zona Peligrosa, se acaba el juego.\n\nFíjate en los medidores que aparecen en pantalla para ayudarte a decidir dónde dirigir tus disparos.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">플레이 방법: \n\n전투는 턴제로 이루어집니다. 플레이어들이 움직인 다음, 악당들이 행동을 취합니다. 악당이 너무 가까이 다가와서 위험지역에 입장하면 게임이 종료됩니다! \n\n HUD의 게이지 아이콘을 사용해서 어디로 발사해야 하는지 가늠해 보세요. \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">遊戲說明：\n\n戰鬥分成數個回合，玩家和敵人輪流選擇行動。如果敵人靠得太近並進入「危險地帶」，便會Game Over！\n\n你可使用畫面上的「準心」圖示來協助判斷瞄準何處。\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">遊戲說明：\n\n戰鬥分成數個回合，玩家和敵人輪流選擇行動。如果敵人靠得太近並進入「危險地帶」，便會Game Over！\n\n你可使用畫面上的「準心」圖示來協助判斷瞄準何處。\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">遊び方：\n\nバトルはターン制で、プレイヤーと敵とが交互にアクションを起こします。敵が接近し、デンジャーゾーンに入ってしまうとゲームオーバー！\n\n画面上のゲージを使って、どこを攻撃するのか、よく考えてから慎重に決めましょう。\n\n</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">tutorial text 4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Pick your ammo type using the L1 and R1 buttons. Use the Left or Right stick to control the vertical and horizontal angle of your shot. When the timer expires the turrets will fire in succession, and your shots will rain down on the enemy.\n\nWatch for the Starting Puck which appears over the turret of the player that’s set to fire first. The Starting Puck changes players between rounds, so pay attention and get the best bonuses for yourself!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Pick your ammo type using the L1 and R1 buttons. Use the Left or Right stick to control the vertical and horizontal angle of your shot. When the timer expires the turrets will fire in succession, and your shots will rain down on the enemy.\n\nWatch for the Starting Puck which appears over the turret of the player that’s set to fire first. The Starting Puck changes players between rounds, so pay attention and get the best bonuses for yourself!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Pick your ammo type using the L1 and R1 buttons. Use the Left or Right stick to control the vertical and horizontal angle of your shot. When the timer expires the turrets will fire in succession, and your shots will rain down on the enemy.\n\nWatch for the Starting Puck which appears over the turret of the player that’s set to fire first. The Starting Puck changes players between rounds, so pay attention and get the best bonuses for yourself!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Choisis ton type de munition en utilisant les touches L1 et R1. Utilise le joystick gauche ou droit pour contrôler l'angle de ton tir verticalement et horizontalement. Lorsque le temps est écoulé, les tourelles ouvriront le feu successivement, et tes tirs s'abattront sur l'ennemi. \n\nRegarde l'icône de départ qui apparaît au dessus de la tourelle du joueur qui doit tirer en premier. L'icône de départ change de joueur entre les tours, alors prêtes-y attention et récolte les meilleurs bonus ! \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wähle mithilfe der L1- und R1-Taste die Munitionsart. Mit dem linken und rechten Stick kannst du den vertikalen und horizontalen Winkel deines Schusses bestimmen. Wenn der Timer abläuft, feuern die Geschütze in Folge und deine Schüsse hageln auf den Gegner herab.\n\nHalte nach dem Startsymbol Ausschau, das über dem Geschütz desjenigen Spielers erscheint, der zuerst mit dem Abfeuern dran ist. Das Startsymbol ändert von Runde zu Runde seine Position, also pass auf und schnapp dir die besten Boni!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scegli un tipo di munizioni usando i tasti L1 e R1. Usa la levetta sinistra o la levetta destra per controllare l'angolo verticale e orizzontale del colpo. Quando il timer scade, le torrette spareranno in successione e una pioggia di proiettili cadrà sul nemico.\n\nOsserva l'indicatore che compare sulla torretta del giocatore che deve sparare per primo. L'indicatore cambia giocatori in ogni round, perciò presta attenzione e cerca di accaparrarti i bonus migliori!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Elige el tipo de munición usando los botones L1 y R1. Usa el joystick izquierdo o el derecho para controlar los ángulos vertical y horizontal de los disparos. Cuando el tiempo se agote, las torretas dispararán en sucesión, y tus disparos caerán sobre el enemigo.\n\nFíjate en el disco de inicio que aparece sobre la torreta del jugador que va a disparar primero. El disco de inicio cambia de jugador en cada ronda, así que presta atención y consigue las mejores bonificaciones.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">L1과 R1을 눌러서 탄약을 선택하세요. 오른쪽과 왼쪽 스틱을 사용해서 상하좌우로 조준할 수 있습니다. 타이머가 종료되면 포탑들이 연달아 발사되어 악당에게 공격을 퍼붓습니다. \n\n가장 먼저 발사하게 되는 플레이어의 포탑 위에는 시작 표시가 나타납니다. 턴이 돌아가면서 시작 표시 역시 플레이어들 사이에서 돌아갑니다. 참고하세요! \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用L1和R1按鈕選擇彈藥類型。用左或右操作桿控制射擊的垂直和水平角度。當定時器停止，炮塔會連續開火，讓彈藥大量落在敵方。\n\n請仔細觀察起始球的位置。起始球出現在哪個玩者的炮塔上方，該玩者即可首先開火。起始球每個回合的出現位置都不同，所以請小心留意，為自己爭取最高分數！\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用L1和R1按鈕選擇彈藥類型。用左或右操作桿控制射擊的垂直和水平角度。當定時器停止，炮塔會連續開火，讓彈藥大量落在敵方。\n\n請仔細觀察起始球的位置。起始球出現在哪個玩者的炮塔上方，該玩者即可首先開火。起始球每個回合的出現位置都不同，所以請小心留意，為自己爭取最高分數！\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">L1ボタンとR1ボタンで武器タイプを選択し、左右のスティックでショットの上下左右の角度を調整できます。タイマーが０になるとキャノンは自動で発射し、プレイヤーが決めた攻撃を敵にあびせます。\n\n最初に発射するプレイヤーのキャノンの上にスタートマークが表示されます。ターンごとにスタートマークが表示されるプレイヤーは変わります。よく確かめてボーナスをねらいましょう！\n\n</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">tutorial text 5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ammo Types: A new ammo type is granted at the end of each round. There are many different ammo types, each with a unique way of damaging the enemy. Experiment to find out each one’s unique blast pattern and properties!\n\nGrunts: These are the smaller, weaker enemies you face on the battlefield. They take one hit to destroy.\n\nBosses: Bosses are large and in charge. They each take five hits to destroy.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ammo Types: A new ammo type is granted at the end of each round. There are many different ammo types, each with a unique way of damaging the enemy. Experiment to find out each one’s unique blast pattern and properties!\n\nGrunts: These are the smaller, weaker enemies you face on the battlefield. They take one hit to destroy.\n\nBosses: Bosses are large and in charge. They each take five hits to destroy.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ammo Types: A new ammo type is granted at the end of each round. There are many different ammo types, each with a unique way of damaging the enemy. Experiment to find out each one’s unique blast pattern and properties!\n\nGrunts: These are the smaller, weaker enemies you face on the battlefield. They take one hit to destroy.\n\nBosses: Bosses are large and in charge. They each take five hits to destroy.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Types de munition : Un nouveau type de munition est accordé à la fin de chaque tour. Il y a de nombreux types différents de munition, chacun avec un moyen unique de blesser l'ennemi. Fais des essais pour découvrir la ligne de tir et les propriétés uniques de chacun ! \n\n Grungs : Ce sont tes ennemis les plus petits et les plus faibles sur le champ de bataille. Il suffit d'un tir pour les détruire. \n\n Boss : Les Boss sont grands et responsables. Il faut trois tirs pour en détruire un. \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Munitionsarten: Am Ende jeder Runde wird dein Arsenal mit einer neuen Munitionsart aufgestockt. Es gibt eine Vielzahl verschiedener Munitionsarten, von denen jede dem Gegner auf einzigartige Weise Schaden zufügt. Experimentiere ein bisschen herum, um die Zerstörungsweise und die Eigenschaften jeder Art herauszufinden!\n\nGrunts: Dabei handelt es sich um die kleineren, schwächeren Gegner, denen du auf dem Schlachtfeld begegnest. Nach einem Treffer sind sie erledigt.\n\nEndgegner: Endgegner sind groß und mächtig. Um sie zu erledigen, sind drei Treffer nötig.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tipi di munizioni: un nuovo tipo di munizione viene rilasciato al termine di ogni round. Esistono molti tipi diversi di munizioni, ognuno con un potere distruttivo specifico. Provali per scoprire traiettorie e caratteristiche di ognuno!\n\nGrunt: sono i nemici più piccoli e meno pericolosi che affronti sul campo di battaglia. Basta un solo colpo a distruggerli.\n\nBoss: i boss sono grossi e pericolosi. Per distruggerli occorrono tre colpi.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tipos de munición: al final de cada ronda se consigue un nuevo tipo de munición. Hay muchos tipos distintos de munición, cada uno con un modo único de dañar al enemigo. Experimenta para averiguar los patrones de explosión y las propiedades de cada uno.\n\nGrunts: son enemigos pequeños y débiles a los que te enfrentas en el campo de batalla. Puedes eliminarlos con solo un impacto.\n\nJefes: los jefes son grandes y potentes. Necesitas tres impactos para acabar con ellos.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">탄약: 매 턴이 끝난 후에는 새로운 탄약이 제공됩니다. 여러 가지 종류의 탄약이 있으니 발사 방향과 특수 능력 등을 시험해 보세요. \n\n병사: 병사들은 작고 약하지만 수로 밀어붙입니다. 한 번 명중시키면 파괴할 수 있습니다. \n\n보스: 보스들은 크고 병사들의 공격을 지휘합니다. 세 번 명중되어야 사라집니다.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">彈藥類型：每一回合結束時會提供新類型的彈藥。彈藥類型繁多，每一種皆有獨特的效果。請多加嘗試，找出各種彈藥的爆炸模式和特點！\n\n步兵：小型和較弱的敵人，一擊即可消滅。\n\n頭目：體型較大，負責指揮大局。每隻要擊中3次才可消滅。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">彈藥類型：每一回合結束時會提供新類型的彈藥。彈藥類型繁多，每一種皆有獨特的效果。請多加嘗試，找出各種彈藥的爆炸模式和特點！\n\n步兵：小型和較弱的敵人，一擊即可消滅。\n\n頭目：體型較大，負責指揮大局。每隻要擊中3次才可消滅。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">武器タイプ： ターン終了ごとに、新しい武器タイプが追加されます。いろいろな武器タイプがあり、それぞれ違った威力をもっています。一つ一つの武器に特有の攻撃パターンや効果を試してみましょう！\n\n敵：戦場にいる小さめで弱い敵。一撃でたおすことができる。\n\nボス：ボスは体が大きく、敵のリーダーである。３回の攻撃をあてるとたおせる。\n\n</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">tutorial text 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Crates: Shoot these to earn valuable RARE ammo types to add to your arsenal!\n\nDanger Zone: This is the yellow-striped area just in front of the turrets. Don’t let them get this far!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Crates: Shoot these to earn valuable RARE ammo types to add to your arsenal!\n\nDanger Zone: This is the yellow-striped area just in front of the turrets. Don’t let them get this far!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Crates: Shoot these to earn valuable RARE ammo types to add to your arsenal!\n\nDanger Zone: This is the yellow-striped area just in front of the turrets. Don’t let them get this far!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Caisses : Fais-les exploser pour ajouter des types de munitions RARES et précieux à ton arsenal ! \n\n Zone Danger : Il s'agit de la zone à rayures jaunes juste devant les tourelles. Ne les laisse pas approcher jusqu'ici ! \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kisten: Schieße sie kaputt, um dein Arsenal mit wertvollen SELTENEN Munitionsarten aufzustocken!\n\nGefahrenzone: Das ist der gelb gestreifte Bereich vor den Geschützen. Lass sie nicht so weit vorrücken!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Casse: spara alle casse per ottenere tipi di munizioni RARE con cui arricchire il tuo arsenale!\n\nZona pericolo: è l'area delimitata da una striscia gialla davanti le torrette. Non permettere ai nemici di arrivare fin qui!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cajas: dispáralas para añadir a tu arsenal valiosos tipos de munición POCO COMUNES.\n\nZona Peligrosa: es la zona de franjas amarillas que hay justo enfrente de las torretas. ¡No dejes que lleguen hasta ella!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">상자: 상자들을 쏘면 희귀한 탄약을 얻을 수 있습니다! \n\n위험지역: 노란 선으로 표시된 위험지역은 포탑 바로 앞에 위치합니다. 이곳에 적을 허용하면 안됩니다! \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">箱子：射擊箱子贏得珍貴稀有的彈藥類型，追加到你的軍械庫！\n\n危險地帶：炮塔前方的黃線區域。不要讓敵人攻到這裡來喔！\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">箱子：射擊箱子贏得珍貴稀有的彈藥類型，追加到你的軍械庫！\n\n危險地帶：炮塔前方的黃線區域。不要讓敵人攻到這裡來喔！\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">弾薬箱： 弾薬箱に攻撃をあてれば、貴重なレア武器をゲットできます！\n\nデンジャーゾーン： キャノンの手前にある、黄色いしま模様のエリア。敵をここに入らせないように！\n\n</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">present desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Right now you’re in the Present, which means you’ll be facing off against Captain Romulus Slag and his Space Pirates!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Right now you’re in the Present, which means you’ll be facing off against Captain Romulus Slag and his Space Pirates!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Right now you’re in the Present, which means you’ll be facing off against Captain Romulus Slag and his Space Pirates!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En ce moment, tu es dans le Présent, ce qui veut dire que tu vas affronter le capitaine Romulus Slag et ses pirates de l'espace ! \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du befindest dich gerade in der Gegenwart, was bedeutet, dass du es mit Captain Romulus Slag und seinen Weltraumpiraten aufnehmen musst!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ora sei nel Presente, ciò significa che affronterai il capitano Romulus Slag e i suoi pirati spaziali!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ahora mismo estás en el presente, lo que significa que estarás enfrentándote al capitán Romulus Slag y a sus piratas espaciales.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">지금은 "현재"입니다. 캡틴 로물러스 슬래그와 우주 해적들을 상대로 싸우게 됩니다!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">你正身處「現在」，將迎戰羅繆勒斯‧史拉各艦長和他的宇宙海盜！\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">你正身處「現在」，將迎戰羅繆勒斯‧史拉各艦長和他的宇宙海盜！\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ここは「現代」です。攻めてくるのは、スラッグ船長と手下のパイレーツです！\n\n</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">the future</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Future</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Future</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Future</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Futur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Zukunft</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Futuro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El futuro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">미래</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">未來</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">未來</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">未来</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">the past</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Past</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Past</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Past</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Passé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Vergangenheit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Passato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El pasado</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">과거</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">過去</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">過去</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">過去</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">the present</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Present</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Present</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Present</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Présent</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Gegenwart</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Presente</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El presente</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">현재</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">現在</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">現在</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">現在</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">future desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Right now you’re in the Future, which means you’ll be facing off against Dr. Nefarious and a clone army of his semi-faithful servant Lawrence!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Right now you’re in the Future, which means you’ll be facing off against Dr. Nefarious and a clone army of his semi-faithful servant Lawrence!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Right now you’re in the Future, which means you’ll be facing off against Dr. Nefarious and a clone army of his semi-faithful servant Lawrence!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En ce moment, tu es dans le Futur, ce qui veut dire que tu vas affronter le Dr Nefarious et une armée de clones de son servant semi-fidèle, Lawrence ! \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du befindest dich gerade in der Zukunft, was bedeutet, dass du es mit Dr. Nefarious und einer Klon-Armee seines fast loyalen Butlers Lawrence aufnehmen musst!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ora sei nel Futuro, ciò significa che affronterai il Dr. Nefarious e un esercito di cloni del suo quasi fedele servo Lawrence!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ahora mismo estás en el futuro, lo que significa que estarás enfrentándote al Dr. Nefarius y a un ejército de clones de su semi-fiel sirviente Lawrence.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">지금은 "미래"입니다. 네파리우스 박사와 약간 충직스러운 그의 종 로렌스의 클론 군대에 맞서십시오! \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">你正身處「未來」，將迎戰尼發利斯博士和他半忠誠的僕人羅倫斯帶領的複製人軍團！\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">你正身處「未來」，將迎戰尼發利斯博士和他半忠誠的僕人羅倫斯帶領的複製人軍團！\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ここは「未来」です。攻めてくるのは、ドクター・ネファリウスと、無礼な執事ローレンスのクローンです！\n\n</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">past desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Right now you’re in the Past, which means you’ll be facing off against Chairman Drek and his Blarg forces!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Right now you’re in the Past, which means you’ll be facing off against Chairman Drek and his Blarg forces!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Right now you’re in the Past, which means you’ll be facing off against Chairman Drek and his Blarg forces!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En ce moment, tu es dans le Passé, ce qui veut dire que tu vas affronter le Président Drek et ses forces Blargs !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du befindest dich gerade in der Vergangenheit, was bedeutet, dass du es mit dem Vorsitzenden Drek und seiner Blarg-Armee aufnehmen musst!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ora sei nel Passato, ciò significa che affronterai Chairman Drek e le sue forze Blarg!\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ahora mismo estás en el pasado, lo que significa que estarás enfrentándote al presidente Drek y a sus fuerzas blargianas.\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">지금은 "과거"입니다. 드렉 회장과 그의 블라그 군에 맞서 싸워야 합니다! \n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">你正身處「過去」，將迎戰德雷克主席和他的卜拉格軍隊！\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">你正身處「過去」，將迎戰德雷克主席和他的卜拉格軍隊！\n\n</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ここは「過去」です。攻めてくるのは、BBB（ビッグ・バッド・ボス）と配下のブラーグ軍団です！\n\n</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Continuer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fortfahren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Continua</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Continuar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">계속</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">繼續</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">繼續</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コンティニュー</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">cancel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cancel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Cancel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cancel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Annuler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Abbrechen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Annulla</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cancelar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">취소</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">取消</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">取消</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">キャンセル</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>