<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ion Beam (bundle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rayon à ion (lot)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ionen-Strahl (Paket)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Raggio a ioni (pacchetto)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Haz de iones (paquete)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">イオンビームセット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이온광선 세트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ion Beam (bundle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">離子光束組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">離子光束組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ion Beam (bundle)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Capable of dealing out massive damage, the Ion Beam is a turret-mounted cannon that fires upon the turret’s target for as long as the fire button is held. Once the beam connects, it takes a few seconds to reach the maximum damage potential. The Ion Blaster Cannons are included, which can be worn as a hand item.  This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Capable d'infliger d'énormes dégâts, le Rayon à ion est un canon monté sur tourelle ouvrant le feu sur sa cible tant que la touche est maintenue. Une fois que le rayon atteint la cible, il lui faut quelques secondes avant d'infliger le maximum de dégâts potentiels. Les Canons à ions sont inclus et peuvent être tenus en main. Ce lot comprend les versions homme et femme. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Ionen-Strahl, der schweren Schaden verursachen kann, ist eine Geschützturm-Kanone, die so lange auf das Ziel des Geschützturmes feuert, wie der Feuerknopf gedrückt gehalten wird. Sobald der Strahl verbunden ist, dauert es einige Sekunden, bis der maximale Schaden verursacht wird. Die Ionen-Blasterkanone, die als Hand-Gegenstand getragen werden kann, ist inbegriffen. Dieses Paket beinhaltet sowohl die Herren- als auch die Damenversion. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">In grado di arrecare gravi danni, il raggio a ioni è un cannone a torretta che spara sull'obiettivo per tutto il tempo in cui il pulsante di fuoco è premuto. Una volta che il raggio è collegato, impiega alcuni secondi per raggiungere il massimo potenziale di danni. Include i cannoni blaster a ioni come armi da mano. Il pacchetto comprende sia la versione femminile sia quella maschile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Capaz de inflingir un daño masivo, el haz de iones es un cañón montado en torre que dispara al objetivo mientras esté pulsado el botón de disparo. Una vez que se conecte el haz, tardará unos segundos en alcanzar el potencial máximo de daños. Se incluyen los cañones explosivos de iones, que se pueden llevar como artículo de mano.  Este paquete incluye las versiones masculina y femenina. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">すさまじいダメージを敵に与えるこのイオンビームは、ボタンを押す間ずっとターゲットに銃弾を浴びせるタレットウェポンである。\n※購入すると、ミニゲーム「ノーバス・プライム」内の戦闘機にこの武器が装備されます。\n\n本セットには、アバターのカスタマイズ用の以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n・「イオンブラスターキャノン（男性用）」（手）\n・「イオンブラスターキャノン（女性用）」（手）\n※購入すると、「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">상대에게 큰 피해를 입힐 수 있는 이온 광선을 발사하는 포탑으로, 발사 버튼이 눌러진 동안 계속해서 대상을 공격합니다. 광선이 상대에게 닿으면 최대 피해치에 도달할 때까지 약간의 시간이 걸립니다. 손 부위에 장착 가능한 이온 블래스터포가 포함되어 있습니다. 이 번들에는 남성용과 여성용이 모두 포함되어 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Capable of dealing out massive damage, the Ion Beam is a turret-mounted cannon that fires upon the turret’s target for as long as the fire button is held. Once the beam connects, it takes a few seconds to reach the maximum damage potential. The Ion Blaster Cannons are included, which can be worn as a hand item.  This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">離子光束是一種配備迴轉砲塔的大炮，只要按住射擊按鈕，便能一直對目標開火。光束連接上後數秒才能達到最大的破壞力。組合包包括男用及女用離子衝擊波炮，能戴在手上。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">離子光束是一種配備迴轉砲塔的大炮，只要按住射擊按鈕，便能一直對目標開火。光束連接上後數秒才能達到最大的破壞力。組合包包括男用及女用離子衝擊波炮，能戴在手上。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Capable of dealing out massive damage, the Ion Beam is a turret-mounted cannon that fires upon the turret’s target for as long as the fire button is held. Once the beam connects, it takes a few seconds to reach the maximum damage potential. The Ion Blaster Cannons are included, which can be worn as a hand item.  This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>