<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Storm of the North - Mercenary Veteran - Bundle (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tempête du nord - Vétéran mercenaire - Lot (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Storm of the North - Söldnerveteran - Paket (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tempesta del Nord - Mercenario - Set (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tormenta del Norte - Veterano Mercenario - Pack (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Suit up for battle with this Mercenary Veteran Bundle.\n
\n
This bundle contains:\n
(1) Storm of the North - Mercenary Veteran - The Musketeer (Men)\n
(2) Storm of the North - Mercenary Veteran - Full Plate - Gold (Men)\n
(3) Storm of the North - Mercenary Veteran - Gauntlets - Gold (Men)\n
(4) Storm of the North - Mercenary Veteran - Mask - Red (Men) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Habillez-vous pour la bataille avec ce lot Vétéran mercenaire.\n
\n
Ce lot contient :\n
(1) Tempête du nord - Vétéran mercenaire - Les mousquetaires (Homme)\n
(2) Tempête du nord - Vétéran mercenaire - Bouclier intégral - Or (Homme)\n
(3) Tempête du nord - Vétéran mercenaire - Gantelets - Or (Homme)\n
(4) Tempête du nord - Vétéran mercenaire - Masque - Rouge (Homme) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Auf geht's in den Kampf - mit diesem Paket für Söldnerveteranen.\n
\n
Dieses Bündel enthält:\n
(1) Storm of the North - Söldnerveteran - Der Musketier  (Herren)\n
(2) Storm of the North - Söldnerveteran - Rüstung - Gold  (Herren)\n
(3) Storm of the North - Söldnerveteran - Panzerhandschuhe - Gold (Herren)\n
(4) Storm of the North - Söldnerveteran - Gesichtsmaske - Rot (Herren) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Preparati alla battaglia con questo Set Mercenario.\n
\n
Il set comprende:\n
() Tempesta del Nord - Mercenario - Il Moschettiere (Uomo)\n
() Tempesta del Nord - Mercenario - Armatura Completa - Oro (Uomo)\n
() Tempesta del Nord - Mercenario - Guanti di metallo - Oro (Uomo)\n
() Tempesta del Nord - Mercenario - Maschera - Rossa (Uomo)\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Vístete para la batalla con este Pack de Veterano Mercenario.\n
\n
Este pack contiene:\n
(1) Tormenta del Norte - Veterano Mercenario - El Mosquetero (Hombre)\n
(2) Tormenta del Norte - Veterano Mercenario - Armadura completa - Oro (Hombre)\n
(3) Tormenta del Norte - Veterano Mercenario - Guanteletes - Oro
(4) Tormenta del Norte - Veterano Mercenario - Visera - Rojo (Hombre) [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>