<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sodium Scorpio's Green and Gray Checkered Bartender Shirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chemise à carreaux verts et gris de barman du Scorpio's de Sodium</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Grün und grau kariertes Sodium-Scorpio's Barkeeper-Hemd</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Camicia da barista dello Scorpio's di Sodium a scacchi verdi e grigi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camisa de camarero con cuadros verdes y grises de Scorpio’s en Sodium</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Scorpio'sチェックアクセント・バーテンダーシャツ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium Scorpio's 녹/회색 체크무늬 바텐더 셔츠(남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sodium Scorpio's Green and Gray Checkered Bartender Shirt (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sodium Scorpio's 灰綠色調酒師格仔襯衫（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sodium Scorpio's 灰綠色調酒師格仔襯衫（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sodium Scorpio's Green and Gray Checkered Bartender Shirt</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wear  this item with  the Green and Gray Checkered Bartender Trousers whilst working in Scorpio’s Bar to earn Sodium credits. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Portez cette chemise avec le pantalon à carreaux verts et gris de barman pour servir au bar Scorpio’s afin de gagner des crédits Sodium. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Trage diesen Artikel mit den grün und grau karierten Barkeeper-Hosen, wenn du in Scorpio's Bar arbeitest, um Sodium-Credits zu verdienen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Indossa questo articolo insieme ai pantaloni da barista a scacchi verdi e grigi mentre lavori al Bar Scorpio's per guadagnare Crediti Sodium. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Combínala con los pantalones de camarero con cuadros verdes y grises mientras trabajas en Scorpio's para conseguir créditos Sodium. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Scorpio's のバーで働いて Sodiumクレジットを稼ぐ際、このアイテムを着用しよう。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 셔츠를 녹/회색 체크무늬 바텐더 긴바지와 함께 입고 Scorpio's 바에서 일하면 Sodium 포인트를 적립할 수 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Wear  this item with  the Green and Gray Checkered Bartender Trousers whilst working in Scorpio’s Bar to earn Sodium credits. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在 Scorpio's 酒吧工作時穿著本制服及灰綠色調酒師格仔長褲，可賺取Sodium積分。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在 Scorpio's 酒吧工作時穿著本制服及灰綠色調酒師格仔長褲，可賺取Sodium積分。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Wear  this item with  the Green and Gray Checkered Bartender Trousers whilst working in Scorpio’s Bar to earn Sodium credits. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>