<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Petrified Pete</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pete le Pétrifié</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Petrified Pete</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pete pietrificato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pete Petrificado</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">굳어버린 피트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Petrified Pete</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">石化彼得</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">石化彼得</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Petrified Pete</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Legend has it Pete was the familiar of a great and powerful white witch, who met his match against an uppity Cockatrice. Sadly the witch could not save Pete from being petrified and her heart too turned to cold, dark stone. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La légende raconte que Pete était le compagnon d'une grande et puissante sorcière blanche, qui a rencontré son égal contre une prétentieuse Cockatrice. Malheureusement la sorcière n'a pas pu empêcher que Pete ne soit pétrifié et son cœur s'est transformé en pierre sombre et froide. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Legende zufolge war Pete der Vertraute eines mächtigen weißen Hexe, die von einem Cockatrice besiegt wurde. Leider konnte die Hexe Pete nicht vor der Versteinerung retten, so dass sich beide zu kaltem, dunklem Stein erstarrten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La leggenda narra che Pete fosse il famiglio di una grande e potente strega bianca che incontrò il suo destino contro un basilisco arrogante. Purtroppo la strega non riuscì a impedire che Pete fosse trasformato in pietra e anche il suo cuore si trasformò in una pietra fredda e scura. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La leyenda cuenta que Pete era familiar de una poderosa bruja blanca que tenía a su mayor rival en la engreída Cockatrice. Por desgracia, la bruja no pudo evitar que Pete quedara petrificado y que su corazón se convirtiera en una piedra fría y oscura. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">전설에 따르면, 피트는 강력한 백마녀의 반려동물로, 건방진 독사에 맞서다가 패하였다고 합니다. 안타깝게도 그 마녀는 피트가 굳어버리는 것을 막지 못했고, 그녀의 심장 역시 차고 어두운 돌로 변해 버렸다고 하는군요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Legend has it Pete was the familiar of a great and powerful white witch, who met his match against an uppity Cockatrice. Sadly the witch could not save Pete from being petrified and her heart too turned to cold, dark stone. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">相傳某個法力高強的好巫婆養了彼得，某一天卻棋逢對手，遇上高傲的雞龍魔獸。故事的結局很悲慘 - 彼得最後變成石頭，巫婆無以回天，心臟也跟著變成冰冷的黑色石頭。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">相傳某個法力高強的好巫婆養了彼得，某一天卻棋逢對手，遇上高傲的雞龍魔獸。故事的結局很悲慘 - 彼得最後變成石頭，巫婆無以回天，心臟也跟著變成冰冷的黑色石頭。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Legend has it Pete was the familiar of a great and powerful white witch, who met his match against an uppity Cockatrice. Sadly the witch could not save Pete from being petrified and her heart too turned to cold, dark stone. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>