<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Over It All Denim Overalls - Plain Grey Top Ref (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Salopette Over It All Denim - Gris uni (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Over It All Jeans-Overall - Grau (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Over It All Salopette di jeans - Top grigio semplice (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Over It All Peto vaquero - Gris liso clásico (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our Over It All overalls set a blistering new trend for denim. Fun, attention-grabbing details include low cut sides and a skinny racer back. Designed with a slouchy fit, plus worn-in abrasions and a distressed wash. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Notre salopette Our Over It All remet le denim à la mode. Des détails très sympas avec une coupe basse sur les côtés et un dos cintré. Conçu avec une coupe large, et un look délavé et déjà porté. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unser Over It All Overall bestimmt den heißen neuen Trend für Jeansmode. Zu augenfälligen neuen Details zählen tiefgeschnittene Seitenpartien, ein Skinny-Racerback und ein extrem salopper Schnitt sowie ein abgewetzter Look und ausgewaschene Farben. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le nostre salopette Over It All definiscono un trend completamente nuovo per i jeans. Gli attraenti dettagli comprendono taglio profondo sui lati e taglio sportivo sulla schiena. Presentano taglio morbido, abrasioni per un tocco vissuto e lavaggio con effetto consumato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nuestro peto Over It All marca una nueva e intrépida tendencia en el vaquero. Entre los divertidos y llamativos detalles están los laterales abiertos y la espalda nadadora. Diseñado con un corte flojo y abrasiones de efecto desgastado y efecto lavado. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>