<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Quiet Down Jacket - Grass Roots (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Blouson Quiet Down - Herbe (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Quiet Down Jacke - Hellbraun (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Quiet Down Giacca - Radici d'Erba (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Quiet Down Chaqueta - Color verde raíz (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">We've blended street-chic styling with the classic look of a moto jacket to create the Quiet Down's subtly sophisticated appeal. Special details include colour blocking, quilting details at the shoulders, and angled zip front, and a hood. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nous avons réuni le chic de la ville et le look classique d'un blouson de moto pour créer l'attrait subtilement sophistiqué du Quiet Down. Parmi les détails caractéristiques figurent les blocs de couleur, les détails de courtepointe aux épaules et la fermeture zippée frontale en biais, ainsi qu'une capuche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Quiet Down Jacke verbindet Straßenchic mit dem klassischen Stil der Motorradjacke zu einen modisch eleganten Look. Zu besonderen Details zählen das attraktive Colorblocking,  die Steppdetails oben an den Ärmeln, der schräg verlaufende Reißverschluss und die Kapuze. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lo stile "street-chic" si unisce al look classico di una giacca da motociclista per dare un fascino sofisticato alla giacca Quiet Down. Tra i dettagli speciali vi sono: blocchi di colore, dettagli trapuntati sulle spalle, zip frontale obliqua e cappuccio. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hemos mezclado un estilo callejero-chic con la clásica chaqueta motera para crear el sutil y sofisticado atractivo de la Quiet Down. Entre los detalles especiales se cuentan los colores uniformes, bordado en los hombros, cremallera delantera oblicua y capucha. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">We've blended street-chic styling with the classic look of a moto jacket to create the Quiet Down's subtly sophisticated appeal. Special details include color blocking, quilting details at the shoulders, and angled zip front, and a hood. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>