<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Spunland Cottage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Domaine Spunland</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Spunland-Hütte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Cottage Spunland</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Casa Rural De Spunland</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Spunland Cottage</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take up residence in the Spunland Cottage, with scenic views of the purple skies and hills of Spunland. Includes a garden area with a grazing Flusho Spunner, suitable for relaxing in the afternoon. Explore the maze in the darker depths of the cottage when the house Lumino Spunner permits access. Trigger Sonic Spunners for your own combination of soundtrack, or invite your friends over for a Score Challenge and start the Spun Clock: who can catch the most Rabbits, collect the most Fruit and find the most Eggs in the spun time limit? Become a spun home owner today! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Installez-vous dans le Domaine Spunland et admirez la vue panoramique des collines de Spunland se détachant sur le ciel pourpre. Passez un après-midi relaxant dans le jardin où broute paisiblement un Spunner Flusho. Explorez le labyrinthe dans les profondeurs du Domaine lorsque le Spunner Lumino vous en ouvre l'accès. Allumez les Spunners soniques pour créer votre propre sélection musicale, ou invitez vos amis pour un défi Score et démarrez le chrono Spun : qui attrapera le plus de lapins, ramassera le plus de fruits et trouvera le plus d'œufs dans le temps Spun imparti ? Devenez un propriétaire Spun dès aujourd'hui ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beziehe deinen Wohnsitz in der Spunland-Hütte, die einen malerischen Ausblick auf den violetten Horizont und die Hügel von Spunland bietet. Enthält einen Gartenbereich mit einem grasenden Flusho-Spunner, wo man am Nachmittag wunderbar entspannen kann. Erkunde das Labyrinth in den finsteren Tiefen der Hütte, wenn der Lumino-Spunner des Hauses Zutritt gewährt. Erzeuge Sonic-Spunner für deinen eigenen Soundtrack oder lade deine Freunde zu einer Punkteherausforderung ein und starte die Spun-Uhr. Wer fängt die meisten Hasen, sammelt die meisten Früchte und findet die meisten Eier innerhalb des Spun-Zeitlimits? Werde noch heute ein Spun-Eigenheimbesitzer! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fai del Cottage Spunland la tua residenza, con panorami dei cieli violacei e colline di Spunland. Include un giardino con un pascolo di Flusho Spunner, perfetto per rilassarsi nel pomeriggio. Esplora il labirinto nelle oscure profondità del cottage quando il Lumino Spunner della casa ne permette l'accesso. Scatena Sonic Spunners per la tua personale combinazione della colonna sonora, o invita i tuoi amici per una Sfida a punti e inizia l'Orologio Spun: chi riuscirà a catturare più Conigli, collezionare più Frutta e troverà più Uova nel tempo limite spun? Diventa subito un possessore d casa spun! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Instálate en la casa rural de Spunland, con vistas fabulosas de los cielos y colinas morados de Spunland. Incluye una zona ajardinada con un Spunner Flusho pastando, apropiado para relajarse por la tarde. Explora el laberinto en el extremo más oscuro cuando el Spunner Lumino de la casa te permita el acceso. Activa los Spunner sónicos para obtener una combinación de banda sonora personalizada, o invita a tus amigos para un desafío de puntos e inicia el reloj Spun: ¿quién atrapará más conejos, recogerá más fruta o encontrará más huevos antes de que se acabe el tiempo Spun? ¡Conviértete en el dueño de una casa Spun hoy mismo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Take up residence in the Spunland Cottage, with scenic views of the purple skies and hills of Spunland. Includes a garden area with a grazing Flusho Spunner, suitable for relaxing in the afternoon. Explore the maze in the darker depths of the cottage when the house Lumino Spunner permits access. Trigger Sonic Spunners for your own combination of soundtrack, or invite your friends over for a Score Challenge and start the Spun Clock: who can catch the most Rabbits, collect the most Fruit and find the most Eggs in the spun time limit? Become a spun home owner today! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>