<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Element - Move It Denim Overall with Noir Bralette - Black And Natural (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Element - Salopette denim Move It avec Noir Bralette - Noir et naturel (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Element - Move It Jeansoverall mit Noir Bralette - Schwarzweiß (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Element - Move It Salopette di jeans e Top Noir Bralette - Nero e Naturale (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Element - Move It Peto vaquero con Noir Bralette - Negro y natural (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Denim overall pant with pocket details, floral voile trim, cuffed hem, and metal logo trim over a knit bralette with contrast fabric bodice detail, center front zip closure and smocked back panel piecing. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Salopette en denim avec poches fantaisie, garniture voile floral, ourlets à revers et plaque logo métallique sur un bustier tricoté avec ornements en tissus sur le corsage, fermeture frontale à zip et pièces smockées dans le dos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jeansoverall mit Taschen, Verzierungen aus blumigem Schleierstoff, umgeschlagenen Hosenbeinen und metallenen Logoverzierungen über einer Strickbralette mit Oberteil aus Kontraststoff, Reißverschluss vorne in der Mitte und gesmokter Rückenpartie [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Salopette di jeans con tasche, ricamo floreale in voile, orlo elasticizzato e targhetta in metallo con logo, con sotto un top in maglia con corpetto in tessuto di colore contrastante, chiusura con zip al centro e arricciatura sulla schiena. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Peto vaquero con detalles de bolsillo, adorno floral de gasa, dobladillo en los bajos, adorno metálico con el logotipo sobre top de punto y detalle en tejido contrastado del corpiño, cremallera frontal central y rectángulo en nido de abeja en la espalda. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>