<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cartel de Red Bull illume™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Red Bull illume™ Storyboard [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">categories</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">CATEGORIES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">CATÉGORIES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">KATEGORIEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">CATEGORIES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">CATEGORÍAS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">応募カテゴリー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">제출 분야</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">CATEGORIES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">作品類別</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">作品類別</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">CATEGORIES</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">playground</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">PLAYGROUND</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">TERRAIN DE JEU</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">SPIELPLATZ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">PLAYGROUND</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LUGAR DE JUEGO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「場」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">플레이그라운드</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">PLAYGROUND</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">運動場</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">運動場</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">PLAYGROUND</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">newcreativity</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">NEW CREATIVITY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">CRÉATIVITÉ NOUVELLE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">NEUE KREATIVITÄT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">NEW CREATIVITY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">CREATIVIDAD INNOVADORA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「創」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">뉴 크리에이티브</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">NEW CREATIVITY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">新創意</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">新創意</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">NEW CREATIVITY</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">spirit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">SPIRIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">ESPRIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">GEIST</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">SPIRIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">ESPÍRITU</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「魂」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">스피릿</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SPIRIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">精神</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">精神</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">SPIRIT</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">energy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">ENERGY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">ÉNERGIE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">ENERGIE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">ENERGY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">ENERGÍA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「力」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">에너지</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">ENERGY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">活力</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">活力</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">ENERGY</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">closeup</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">CLOSE-UP</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">GROS PLAN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">NAHAUFNAHME</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">CLOSE-UP</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">DE CERCA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「近」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">클로즈업</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">CLOSE-UP</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">近照</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">近照</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">CLOSE-UP</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">wings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">WINGS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">AILES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">FLÜGEL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">WINGS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">ALAS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「翼」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">비상</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">WINGS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">展翅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">展翅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">WINGS</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">sequence</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">SanDisk® SEQUENCE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">SanDisk® SÉQUENCE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">SanDisk® FOLGE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">SanDisk® SEQUENCE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">SanDisk® SECUENCIA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">SanDisk®「続」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">SanDisk® 연사</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SanDisk® SEQUENCE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">SanDisk® 順序</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">SanDisk® 順序</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">SanDisk® SEQUENCE</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">experimental</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">EXPERIMENTAL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">EXPÉRIMENTATION</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">EXPERIMENTELL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">EXPERIMENTAL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">EXPERIMENTAL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「験」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">실험정신</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">EXPERIMENTAL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">實驗</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">實驗</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">EXPERIMENTAL</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">illumination</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">ILLUMINATION</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">ILLUMINATION</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">ILLUMINATION</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">ILLUMINATION</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">iluminación</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「明」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">일루미네이션</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">ILLUMINATION</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">光輝</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">光輝</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">ILLUMINATION</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">culture</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">CULTURE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">CULTURE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">KULTUR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">CULTURA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">CULTURA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">CULTURE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">CULTURE</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">cultureDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Images that visually capture the creativity of the culture, music and lifestyle that surrounds action and freesports, or represents what happens before, between, and after the action."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Des photographies qui capturent visuellement la créativité de la culture, de la musique et du style de vie qui entoure l'action et les sports libres, ou qui représentent ce qui se passe avant, pendant et après l'action."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Bilder, die die Kreativität von Kultur, Musik, Mode und Lifestyle im Kontext von actionbetontem Extrem- und Freesport festhalten und anschaulich wiedergeben, was vor, während und nach der Action geschieht."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Immagini che catturano visivamente la cultura, la musica e lo stile di vita tipici dell'azione e degli sport liberi o che rappresentano quello che accade prima, durante e dopo l'azione."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Imágenes que capturen de forma visual la creatividad de la cultura, la música y el estilo de vida que rodea a los deportes de acción y al aire libre, o que representen lo que ocurre antes, durante y después de la acción."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Images that visually capture the creativity of the culture, music and lifestyle that surrounds action and freesports, or represents what happens before, between, and after the action."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Images that visually capture the creativity of the culture, music and lifestyle that surrounds action and freesports, or represents what happens before, between, and after the action."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">playgroundDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Images that showcase the landscape, locations, platforms, and environments in which athletes play."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Des photographies qui présentent des paysages, des endroits, des plateformes et des environnements où les athlètes s'amusent."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Fotos, die die Landschaft, Orte, Plattformen und die Umgebung, in der die Athleten sich bewegen, abbilden."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Immagini di panorami, scenari, strutture e ambienti in cui agiscono atleti."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Imágenes que muestren paisajes, lugares, plataformas y ambientes en los que compiten los atletas."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アスリートが活躍する風景、場所、競技場、環境などの写真。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"선수들이 플레이를 펼치는 경관, 장소, 무대, 환경 등을 표현하는 이미지."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Images that showcase the landscape, locations, platforms, and environments in which athletes play."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">展示運動員大展身手之風景、地點、平臺和環境的影像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">展示運動員大展身手之風景、地點、平臺和環境的影像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Images that showcase the landscape, locations, platforms, and environments in which athletes play."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">energyDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Images that demonstrate the force that powers an action and show the energy, speed and strength required for an athlete to perform."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Des photographies qui témoignent de la force qui pousse une action ainsi que l'énergie, la vitesse, la force requises par l'athlète qui effectue la performance."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Fotos, die die Kraft zeigen, die eine Leistung antreibt, und die Energie, Geschwindigkeit und Stärke, mit der ein Athlet seine Leistungen vollbringt."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Immagini che catturano la forza dell'azione mettendo in luce l'energia, la velocità e la vitalità dell'atleta."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Imágenes en las que se manifieste  la fuerza necesaria para llevar a cabo una acción, que muestren la energía, la velocidad y la potencia necesarias para que un atleta ejecute su labor."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">競技に必要なエネルギー、スピード、パワーをとらえ、アクションの力を感じさせる写真。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"운동 능력을 발휘하는 데 꼭 필요한 에너지, 속도감, 힘을 보여주며 파워있는 액션을 그려낸 이미지."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Images that demonstrate the force that powers an action and show the energy, speed and strength required for an athlete to perform."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">展現完成某個動作所需之力量，以及表現運動員競技所需之活力、 速度和力量的影像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">展現完成某個動作所需之力量，以及表現運動員競技所需之活力、 速度和力量的影像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Images that demonstrate the force that powers an action and show the energy, speed and strength required for an athlete to perform."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">spiritDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Images that portray the spirit or personality that athletic performances produce, as well as the pain, emotion and struggles that go along with trying to achieve one‘s goals, whether due to injury, failure or simply being in the wrong place at the wrong time."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Des photographies qui portraient l'esprit ou la personnalité des performances athlétiques, sans oublier la douleur, l'émotion et les difficultés qui vont de pair avec la tentative d'atteindre les buts que l'on s'est fixé, qu'elles soient causées par une blessure, un échec ou seulement par le fait d’être au mauvais endroit au mauvais moment."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Bilder, die den Geist oder Charakter sportlicher Höchstleistungen sowie den Einsatz, die Emotionen und die Schmerzen auf dem Weg ans Ziel wiedergeben, ganz gleich, ob sie durch Verletzungen oder Misserfolg entstehen, oder weil man schlicht zur falschen Zeit am falschen Ort war."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Immagini che ritraggono lo spirito o la personalità, frutto dalla prestazione atletica così come il dolore, l'emozione e la lotta, elementi imprescindibili della vita di chi prova a raggiungere i propri obiettivi e affronta infortuni, fallimenti o semplicemente si trova nel posto sbagliato al momento sbagliato."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Imágenes que plasmen el espíritu o la personalidad que se desprenden del desempeño atlético, así como el dolor, la emoción y el esfuerzo que conlleva  intentar alcanzar metas personales, ya sea debido a una lesión, error o simplemente por estar en el lugar equivocado en el momento equivocado."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Images that portray the spirit or personality that athletic performances produce, as well as the pain, emotion and struggles that go along with trying to achieve one‘s goals, whether due to injury, failure or simply being in the wrong place at the wrong time."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Images that portray the spirit or personality that athletic performances produce, as well as the pain, emotion and struggles that go along with trying to achieve one‘s goals, whether due to injury, failure or simply being in the wrong place at the wrong time."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">closeupDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Images that show extreme detail of one or more aspects of an athletic feat: a tight shot of the action, the equipment, the body, the face."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Des photographies qui montrent des détails poussés d'un ou plusieurs des aspects d'une prouesse athlétique : un gros plan de l'action, de l'équipement, du corps, du visage."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Bilder, die einen oder mehrere Aspekte einer sportlichen Leistung im Detail zeigen: eine Nahaufnahme der Action, der Sportausrüstung, des Körpers, des Gesichts."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Immagini che mostrano dettagli estremi di uno o più aspetti del gesto atletico: uno primo piano sull'azione, sull'equipaggiamento, sul corpo, sul volto."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Imágenes que muestren en gran detalle  uno o más aspectos de una proeza deportiva: un plano detalle de la acción, el equipo, el cuerpo, la cara."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Images that show extreme detail of one or more aspects of an athletic feat: a tight shot of the action, the equipment, the body, the face."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Images that show extreme detail of one or more aspects of an athletic feat: a tight shot of the action, the equipment, the body, the face."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">wingsDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Images that capture the point in a performance in which the athlete jumps, catches air, free falls, soars."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Des photographies qui capturent le point culminant d'une performance au cours de laquelle l'athlète saute, plane, tombe en chute libre."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Fotos, die den Moment einfangen, in dem der Sportler springt, in der Luft ist, fällt, in die Höhe steigt."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Immagini che fissano l'istante in cui l'atleta si libra, salta, è in volo, cade."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Imágenes que capturen el momento justo de saltos por los aires, caídas libres, vuelos."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ジャンプ、フリーフォールなど、アスリートが空中高く舞い上がった瞬間をとらえた写真。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"운동 선수가 점프하거나, 하늘을 날거나, 떨어지거나, 높이 치솟는 모습을 포착한 이미지."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Images that capture the point in a performance in which the athlete jumps, catches air, free falls, soars."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">捕捉運動員跳躍、騰空、自由墜落、翱翔等動作瞬間的影像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">捕捉運動員跳躍、騰空、自由墜落、翱翔等動作瞬間的影像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Images that capture the point in a performance in which the athlete jumps, catches air, free falls, soars."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">sequenceDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Images that tell the whole story in a single frame and capture the progression of an action at every stage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Des photographies qui racontent toute une histoire en une seule image et capturent la progression d'une action à chaque étape.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Bilder, die die ganze Geschichte in einer einzigen Aufnahme erzählen und den Fortschritt einer Aktivität zu jedem Zeitpunkt erfassen."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Immagini che raccontano una storia in un unico fotogramma e catturano la continuità di un'azione in ogni suo attimo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Imágenes que narren una historia entera en un solo fotograma y que capturen cada fase del progreso de una acción.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ひとつひとつのアクションを、流れとして一枚のフレームにおさめた物語性のある写真。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">한 프레임에서 여러 장의 사진을 순서대로 연사 촬영하여 전체 스토리를 보여주는 이미지.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Images that tell the whole story in a single frame and capture the progression of an action at every stage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用單幅相片講述整個故事，或者捕捉某個動作各階段進展的影像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用單幅相片講述整個故事，或者捕捉某個動作各階段進展的影像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Images that tell the whole story in a single frame and capture the progression of an action at every stage.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">newcreativityDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Images that reveal a unique angle, a visual idea, a different format, light and flash effects... something never seen before! It's the purely creative image without digital alterations."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Des photographies qui révèlent un angle unique, une idée visuelle, un format différent, des effets de lumière et de flash : quelque chose d'inédit. Ce sont des photographies de pure création sans modifications numériques."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Bilder aus einem ausgefallenen Blickwinkel, mit einer visuellen Idee, in einem anderen Format, mit Licht- und Blitzeffekten: etwas noch nie Dagewesenes. Es geht um das rein kreative Bild ohne digitale Bearbeitungen."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Immagini che rivelano angolazioni uniche, idee visive, formati particolari, effetti di luce: qualcosa di mai visto prima. Immagini creative allo stato puro, senza alterazioni digitali."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Imágenes que revelen un ángulo único, una idea visual, un formato distinto, efectos de luz y flash: algo que no se haya visto antes. Imágenes  puramente creativas sin alteraciones digitales."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">独自のアングル、視覚的アイディア、変わったフォーマット、ライトとフラッシュによる効果など、創造プロセスに挑戦する、デジタル修正をまったく使わない独創的な写真。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"지금껏 보지 못한 독특한 각도, 시각적 아이디어, 새로운 형식, 조명 및 플래시 효과를 발견해낸 이미지. 디지털 보정을 거치치 않은 순수 창작 이미지입니다."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Images that reveal a unique angle, a visual idea, a different format, light and flash effects... something never seen before! It's the purely creative image without digital alterations."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">展現獨特角度、視覺觀點、獨到格式、光線和閃爍效果（前所未見）的影像。 應該是未經數碼修改的絕對創作影像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">展現獨特角度、視覺觀點、獨到格式、光線和閃爍效果（前所未見）的影像。 應該是未經數碼修改的絕對創作影像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Images that reveal a unique angle, a visual idea, a different format, light and flash effects... something never seen before! It's the purely creative image without digital alterations."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">experimentalDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Images that have been enhanced digitally or in the darkroom through alterations made in the production or the digital editing process.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Des photographies améliorées lors de la production ou du processus d'édition numérique grâce à la technologie numérique, ou modifiées dans la chambre noire."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Fotos, die digital oder in der Dunkelkammer durch Veränderungen in der Herstellung oder den digitalen Bearbeitungsvorgang verbessert wurden."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Immagini ritoccate digitalmente o in camera oscura durante il processo di produzione o di editing digitale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Imágenes que hayan sido mejoradas digitalmente o en el cuarto oscuro a través de alteraciones en el proceso de producción o en el de edición digital.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">制作過程において、デジタル処理、フォトレタッチを駆使した写真。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"디지털로 보정했거나, 암실에서 개조했거나, 디지털 편집으로 손을 본 이미지."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Images that have been enhanced digitally or in the darkroom through alterations made in the production or the digital editing process.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在製作或數碼編輯過程中以暗室或數碼方式進行優質化的影像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在製作或數碼編輯過程中以暗室或數碼方式進行優質化的影像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Images that have been enhanced digitally or in the darkroom through alterations made in the production or the digital editing process.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">illuminationDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Images that illuminate your artistic skill, your personal best, your unique style; this is an open category so anything goes."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Des photographies qui illuminent vos talents artistiques, le meilleur de vous-même, votre style unique. Cette catégorie est ouverte : tout est permis."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Bilder, die deine künstlerischen Fähigkeiten, deine persönliche Bestleistung, deinen einzigartigen Lifestyle zur Schau stellen. Dies ist eine offene Kategorie: Erlaubt ist, was gefällt."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Immagini che esaltano la tua capacità artistica, ciò che sai fare meglio, il tuo stile unico; questa è una categoria aperta, perciò qualunque cosa va bene."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Imágenes que ilustren tu talento artístico, tu mejor habilidad personal, tu estilo único. Se trata de una categoría abierta en la que todo vale."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Images that illuminate your artistic skill, your personal best, your unique style; this is an open category so anything goes."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Images that illuminate your artistic skill, your personal best, your unique style; this is an open category so anything goes."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">webpage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">www.redbullillume.com</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">www.redbullillume.com</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">www.redbullillume.com</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">www.redbullillume.com</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">www.redbullillume.com</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">www.redbullillume.com</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">www.redbullillume.com</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">www.redbullillume.com</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">www.redbullillume.com</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">www.redbullillume.com</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">www.redbullillume.com</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">exhibitedPhotographers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">EXHIBITED\nPHOTOGRAPHERS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">PHOTOGRAPHIES\nEXPOSÉES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">AUSGESTELLTE\nFOTOGRAFEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">FOTOGRAFI\nPRESENTI</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">FOTÓGRAFOS\nDE LA EXHIBICIÓN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">展示作品</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">전시 사진작가</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">EXHIBITED\nPHOTOGRAPHERS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">展出攝影師</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">展出攝影師</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">EXHIBITED\nPHOTOGRAPHERS</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">christoph</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Christoph Schöch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Christoph Schöch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Christoph Schöch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Christoph Schöch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Christoph Schöch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Christoph Schöch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Christoph Schöch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Christoph Schöch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Christoph Schöch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Christoph Schöch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Christoph Schöch</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">steph</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stéphane Candé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Stéphane Candé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stéphane Candé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stéphane Candé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Stéphane Candé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Stéphane Candé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Stéphane Candé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Stéphane Candé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Stéphane Candé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Stéphane Candé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Stéphane Candé</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">eric</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Éric Antoine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Éric Antoine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Éric Antoine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Éric Antoine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Éric Antoine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Éric Antoine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Éric Antoine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Éric Antoine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Éric Antoine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Éric Antoine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Éric Antoine</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">marcel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Marcel Lämmerhirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Marcel Lämmerhirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Marcel Lämmerhirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Marcel Lämmerhirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Marcel Lämmerhirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Marcel Lämmerhirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Marcel Lämmerhirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Marcel Lämmerhirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Marcel Lämmerhirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Marcel Lämmerhirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Marcel Lämmerhirt</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">miguel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Miguel Angel López Virgen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Miguel Angel López Virgen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Miguel Angel López Virgen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Miguel Angel López Virgen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Miguel Angel López Virgen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Miguel Angel López Virgen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Miguel Angel López Virgen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Miguel Angel López Virgen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Miguel Angel López Virgen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Miguel Angel López Virgen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Miguel Angel López Virgen</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">roberto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Roberto Alegría</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Roberto Alegría</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Roberto Alegría</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Roberto Alegría</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Roberto Alegría</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Roberto Alegría</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Roberto Alegría</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Roberto Alegría</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Roberto Alegría</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Roberto Alegría</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Roberto Alegría</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">sebastien</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sébastien Anex</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sébastien Anex</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sébastien Anex</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sébastien Anex</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sébastien Anex</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Sébastien Anex</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sébastien Anex</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sébastien Anex</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sébastien Anex</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sébastien Anex</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sébastien Anex</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">thomas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Thomas Stöckli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Thomas Stöckli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Thomas Stöckli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Thomas Stöckli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Thomas Stöckli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Thomas Stöckli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Thomas Stöckli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Thomas Stöckli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Thomas Stöckli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Thomas Stöckli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Thomas Stöckli</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">storyTitle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">THE STORY OF RED BULL iLLUME™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'HISTOIRE DE RED BULL iLLUME™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">DIE GESCHICHTE VON RED BULL iLLUME™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">LA STORIA DI RED BULL iLLUME™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LA HISTORIA DE RED BULL iLLUME™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">THE STORY OF RED BULL iLLUME™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">THE STORY OF RED BULL iLLUME™</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">storyMain</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Red Bull Illume is the biggest international photography competition that celebrates the world of action and adventure sports. Building on its inaugural success in 2006, the Image Quest 2010 set out once again to find the cream of free sports photography.\n\nThis exhibition is the result of that search and presents the 50 best images from the 22,764 photos that were submitted by 4773 photographers from 112 countries. Fifty-three judges, expert photo editors from around the world, assessed these finalists, the ten category winners and the one overall winner.\n\nThese 50 exhibited images have a story behind each one of them. That’s 50 reasons to celebrate the world of action and adventure sports, the photographers and the athletes who inspire them."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Red Bull Illume est le plus grand concours international de photographie qui célèbre le monde des sports d'action et d'aventure." Surfant sur le succès connu lors de son inauguration en 2006, l'Image Quest 2010 a une fois de plus tenté de trouver la crème de la photographie de sports libres.\n\nCette exposition est le résultat de cette fastidieuse recherche et présente les 50 meilleures images parmi 22 764 photographies soumises par 4773 photographes venus de 112 pays différents. Cinquante trois juges, des éditeurs de photographies professionnels des quatre coins du globe, ont évalué ces finalistes pour choisir le vainqueur de chacune des dix catégories et le vainqueur absolu.\n\nChacune de ces 50 photographies possède sa propre histoire. Elles ne sont pas moins de 50 raisons de célébrer le monde des sports d'action et d'aventure sans oublier les photographes et les athlètes qui les inspirent."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Red Bull Illume ist der größte internationale Fotowettbewerb, der die Welt des Extrem- und Freesports zelebriert. Die Image Quest 2010 baute auf ihrem ersten Erfolg im Jahr 2006 auf und versuchte erneut, die Crème de la Crème der Freesport-Fotografie ausfindig zu machen.\n\nDiese Ausstellung ist das Ergebnis dieser Suche und präsentiert die 50 besten Bilder aus 22.764 Fotos von 4773 Fotografen aus 112 Ländern. 53 Juroren, allesamt Fotografie-Experten aus der ganzen Welt bewerteten die Finalisten und wählten die zehn Gewinner in den einzelnen Kategorien sowie den Gesamtsieger.\n\nHinter jedem der 50 ausgestellten Bilder steckt eine Geschichte. Das sind 50 gute Gründe, die Welt des Extrem- und Freesports, die Fotografen und die Sportler, die sie inspirierten, zu feiern."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Red Bull illume™ è il più grande concorso fotografico internazionale che celebra il mondo dell'azione, dell'avventura e dello sport. Dopo l'iniziale successo nel 2006, l'Image Quest 2010 è di nuovo alla ricerca dell'eccellenza nella fotografia sportiva.\n\nQuesta mostra è il risultato di quella ricerca e presenta le 50 migliori immagini tra le 22.764 fotografie inviate da 4773 fotografi di 112 paesi. Cinquantatre giudici, esperti editor fotografici da tutto il mondo, hanno scelto questi finalisti, le dieci categorie vincitrici e un vincitore assoluto.\n\nQueste 50 immagini esposte hanno ognuna una storia da raccontare. Sono 50 ragioni per celebrare il mondo dell'azione e degli sport avventurosi, i fotografi e gli atleti che li hanno ispirati."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Red Bull Illume es el mayor concurso de fotografía internacional que exalta el mundo de los deportes de acción y de aventura. Sobre la base de su éxito inaugural en 2006, se emprendió una vez más la Búsqueda de la imagen de 2010 para encontrar la mejor fotografía de deportes al aire libre.\n\n Esta exposición es el resultado de esa búsqueda y presenta las 50 mejores imágenes de las 22.764 fotos que presentaron 4.773 fotógrafos de 112 países. Cincuenta y tres jueces, editores de fotos expertos de todo el mundo, evaluaron estos finalistas, los diez ganadores de cada categoría y el ganador absoluto.\n\n Cada una de las 50 imágenes expuestas tiene una historia detrás: 50 motivos para homenajear el mundo de los deportes de acción y aventura, los fotógrafos y los atletas que los inspiran."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Red Bull Illume is the biggest international photography competition that celebrates the world of action and adventure sports. Building on its inaugural success in 2006, the Image Quest 2010 set out once again to find the cream of free sports photography.\n\nThis exhibition is the result of that search and presents the 50 best images from the 22,764 photos that were submitted by 4773 photographers from 112 countries. Fifty-three judges, expert photo editors from around the world, assessed these finalists, the ten category winners and the one overall winner.\n\nThese 50 exhibited images have a story behind each one of them. That’s 50 reasons to celebrate the world of action and adventure sports, the photographers and the athletes who inspire them."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Red Bull Illume is the biggest international photography competition that celebrates the world of action and adventure sports. Building on its inaugural success in 2006, the Image Quest 2010 set out once again to find the cream of free sports photography.\n\nThis exhibition is the result of that search and presents the 50 best images from the 22,764 photos that were submitted by 4773 photographers from 112 countries. Fifty-three judges, expert photo editors from around the world, assessed these finalists, the ten category winners and the one overall winner.\n\nThese 50 exhibited images have a story behind each one of them. That’s 50 reasons to celebrate the world of action and adventure sports, the photographers and the athletes who inspire them."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">prepare</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">PREPARE TO BE ENLIGHTENED.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">PRÉPAREZ-VOUS À ÊTRE ILLUMINÉ.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">SEI BEREIT FÜR DIE ERLEUCHTUNG.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">PREPARATI A RAGGIUNGERE L'ILLUMINAZIONE.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">PREPÁRATE PARA ILUSTRARTE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">PREPARE TO BE ENLIGHTENED.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">PREPARE TO BE ENLIGHTENED.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">pictureThis</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Picture\nthis:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Imaginez:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stell dir\ndas vor:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Immagina:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Imagina:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">想像してみよう</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">상상해 보세요.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Picture\nthis:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">抓拍此時此刻</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">抓拍此時此刻</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Picture\nthis:</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">pictureThisMain</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"The best action and adventure sports photography, as never seen before.\n\nCelebrated, honoured, and exhibited in breathtaking outdoor venues around the world."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"La meilleure photographie d'action et de sports extrêmes.\n\nFêtée, honorée et exposée en extérieur, dans des endroits exceptionnels du monde entier."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Die besten Action- und Abenteuersportfotos aller Zeiten.\n\nGefeiert, geehrt und ausgestellt an überwältigenden Orten im Freien auf der ganzen Welt."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Le migliori fotografie d'azione e d'avventura, in tutto il loro splendore.\n\nCelebrate, ammirate ed esibite nelle installazioni all'aperto di tutto il mondo."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La mejor fotografía de deportes de acción y aventura como nunca antes la has visto.\n\nHomenajeada y exhibida en impresionantes lugares abiertos de todo el mundo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アクションスポーツとアドベンチャースポーツの、今までに見たことのない最高の写真。息を呑むほど美しい野外会場にて記念展示会を開催します。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">지금껏 보지 못한 최고의 액션 및\n 어드벤처 스포츠 사진들이 세계\n각국의 멋진 야외 전시장에서\n찬사와 감탄을 받으며\n전시되었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"The best action and adventure sports photography, as never seen before.\n\nCelebrated, honored, and exhibited in breathtaking outdoor venues around the world."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">從未見過的最佳動作和探險運動相片。\n在世界各地令人摒息的戶外地點歡慶、\n讚譽和展示。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">從未見過的最佳動作和探險運動相片。\n在世界各地令人摒息的戶外地點歡慶、\n讚譽和展示。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"The best action and adventure sports photography, as never seen before.\n\nCelebrated, honored, and exhibited in breathtaking outdoor venues around the world."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>