<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MAG - Raven Spyder Armor Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">MAG - Pack armure Spyder Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MAG-Paket: Panzerung „Spyder" (Raven)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">MAG - Pacchetto armatura Spyder Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">MAG: paquete de blindaje Spyder de Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">MAG - Raven "스파이더" 방어복 팩</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">MAG - Raven Spyder Armor Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">MAG - Raven「Spyder」裝甲包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">MAG - Raven「Spyder」裝甲包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MAG - Raven Spyder Armor Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Raven Spyder Armour Pack comes with a unique Spyder Camo Pattern, Spyder Reinforced 2nd Gen Composite Armour and Spyder Reinforced 2nd Gen Helmet.
Quoting a recent Raven press release, "Spyder defence materials are designed by Raven Industries' top field weapons researchers. Stealthy yet defensive, the Spyder materials increase Raven operatives ability to take control of the battle with superior technology." [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le pack armure Spyder Raven comprend le camouflage Spyder, une protection en composite renforcé et un casque renforcé Spyder de 2ème génération.
Pour citer un récent communiqué de presse Raven, "Le matériel de défense Spyder est conçu par les meilleurs chercheurs militaires de Raven Industries. Furtif et défensif, il vient améliorer l'efficacité des agents Raven sur le champ de bataille, par sa supériorité technologique." [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Raven-Panzerung „Spyder“ umfasst das einzigartige „Spyder“-Tarnmuster, die verstärkte „Spyder“-Kompositpanzerung der 2. Generation und den verstärkten „Spyder“-Komposithelm der 2. Generation.
Einer aktuellen Raven-Pressemitteilung zufolge wird die „Militärmarke „Spyder“ von den besten Waffenentwicklern von Raven Industries entwickelt. Da sie für Tarnung und Schutz bürgt, verbessert die Militärmarke „Spyder“ die Fähigkeit der Raven-Soldaten, mit ihrer überlegenen Technologie die Kontrolle über den Schlachtverlauf zu übernehmen.“ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il pacchetto armatura Spyder Raven presenta un motivo mimetico originale Spyder, l'armatura composita rinforzata Spyder di seconda generazione e l'elmetto rinforzato Spyder di seconda generazione.
Citando una conferenza stampa recente della Raven: "I materiali di difesa Spyder sono progettati dai migliori ricercatori di armamenti delle Raven Industries. Mimetici ed efficaci per la difesa, i materiali Spyder aumentano la capacità dei soldati Raven di assumere il controllo in battaglia avvalendosi di una tecnologia superiore". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El paquete de blindaje Spyder de Raven incluye el exclusivo diseño de camuflaje Spyder, el blindaje de material compuesto reforzado Spyder de 2.ª generación y el casco reforzado Spyder también de 2.ª generación.
Según una reciente nota de prensa de Raven, "el material defensivo Spyder es un diseño de los mejores investigadores de Raven Industries. Sigiloso sin renunciar a la protección, el material del uniforme Spyder aumenta la capacidad de los agentes de Raven para hacerse con el control de la batalla gracias a su tecnología superior". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Raven의 "스파이더" 방어복 팩은 "스파이더" 시리즈의 방어복 아이템을 모두 포함합니다. 최근 발표된 보도자료에 따르면, ""스파이더" 방어복은 최신 전투 기술을 집약하는 Raven 디자인의 결정체입니다. 극상의 방어 성능을 자랑하면서도 가벼우며 사용자의 소음을 최소화하기 때문에 전장의 주도권을 장악하는데 최적입니다."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Raven Spyder Armor Pack comes with a unique Spyder Camo Pattern, Spyder Reinforced 2nd Gen Composite Armor and Spyder Reinforced 2nd Gen Helmet.
Quoting a recent Raven press release, "Spyder defence materials are designed by Raven Industries' top field weapons researchers. Stealthy yet defensive, the Spyder materials increase Raven operatives ability to take control of the battle with superior technology." [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raven的「Spyder」裝甲包內含獨一無二的「Spyder」迷彩圖案、「Spyder」強化第二代複合材料裝甲及「Spyder」強化第二代頭盔。以下摘錄自Raven近期的新聞稿：「Spyder防禦物料由Raven最精銳的武器開發人員設計，隱密性與防禦力兼備。Spyder物料提高了Raven人員透過頂尖科技控制戰局的能力。」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raven的「Spyder」裝甲包內含獨一無二的「Spyder」迷彩圖案、「Spyder」強化第二代複合材料裝甲及「Spyder」強化第二代頭盔。以下摘錄自Raven近期的新聞稿：「Spyder防禦物料由Raven最精銳的武器開發人員設計，隱密性與防禦力兼備。Spyder物料提高了Raven人員透過頂尖科技控制戰局的能力。」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Raven Spyder Armor Pack comes with a unique Spyder Camo Pattern, Spyder Reinforced 2nd Gen Composite Armor and Spyder Reinforced 2nd Gen Helmet.
Quoting a recent Raven press release, "Spyder defence materials are designed by Raven Industries' top field weapons researchers. Stealthy yet defensive, the Spyder materials increase Raven operatives ability to take control of the battle with superior technology." [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>