<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Motorized Rotating Bed</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-US">Motorized Rotating Bed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lit Rotatif Motorisé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drehbares Bett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Letto Rotante Motorizzato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cama Rotativa Motorizada</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce lit est le dernier cri de la technologie du sommeil ! Placez simplement ce lit high-tech dans votre espace privé et activez ses systèmes rotatifs. Mais attendez, ce n'est pas tout ! Vous pouvez également vous allonger et faire un tour à tout moment avec un de vos amis. Profitez du neuf et du meilleur dès aujourd'hui ! Il s'agit d'un élément animé actif. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Esta cama es la última tecnología aplicada al sueño! Simplemente coloca esta cama de alta tecnología en tu espacio privado y activa el sistema de rotación. Pero espérate - ¡hay más! También puedes acostarte e ir a dar una vuelta en cualquier momento con cualquiera de tus amigos. ¡Disfruta hoy de lo mejor y lo más avanzado! Este es un elemento activo animado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Bett ist das Ultimative, was die Schlaftechnologie zu bieten hat! Stellen Sie dieses Spitzentechnologiebett einfach in Ihrem Privatraum auf und schalten Sie sein Rotationssystem ein. Aber warten Sie - denn es gibt noch mehr! Sie können Sich auch hinlegen und jeder Zeit eine Spritztour mit einem Ihrer Freunde machen. Genießen Sie diese neueste Erfindung noch heute! Dies ist eine animierte aktive Element. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo letto è l'ultimo ritrovato della tecnologia del sonno! Non dovete fare altro che installare questo letto ad alta tecnologia nella  vostra stanza privata e accendere il sistema di rotazione. Ma, aspettate, non è tutto! Potrete anche sdraiarvi in qualunque momento, e farvi un bel giretto con uno dei vostri amici. Godetevi oggi questa fantastica novità!  Questo è un elemento animato attiva. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The bed is the ultimate in sleep technology! Simply place this high tech bed in your private space and activate its rotation systems. But wait - there's more! You can also lie down and go for a spin any time with any of your friends. Enjoy the latest and greatest today! This is an animated active item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The bed is the ultimate in sleep technology! Simply place this high tech bed in your private space and activate its rotation systems. But wait - there's more! You can also lie down and go for a spin any time with any of your friends. Enjoy the latest and greatest today! This is an animated active item. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>

</LOCALISATION>