<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Golden VIP Top Hat (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chapeau haut-de-forme doré VIP (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Goldener VIP-Zylinderhut (Männlich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cilindro dorato da VIP (Maschio)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sombrero de copa Dorado VIP (Hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_Hat_VIPTophat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_Hat_VIPTophat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Male01_Hat_VIPTophat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_Hat_VIPTophat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_Hat_VIPTophat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Golden VIP Top Hat (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our VIP section is where serious gamers come to play. This Golden VIP Top Hat will give you unlimited access to the higher stakes tables in our VIP area. You'll be able to earn some serious rewards, fast! It's time to prove you're one of the best! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Notre section VIP est celle où les joueurs sérieux viennent jouer. Le chapeau haut-de-forme doré VIP vous donnera un accès illimité aux tables avec les mises les plus hautes dans notre espace VIP. Vous pourrez aussi remporter de sérieuses récompenses, rapidement ! Il est temps de prouver que vous êtes l'un des meilleurs ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Profispieler treffen sich in unserem VIP-Bereich. Dieser goldene VIP-Zylinderhut ermöglicht Dir unbegrenzten Zugang zu den Tischen mit den höchsten Einsätzen. Hier bekommst Du die Chance, wertvolle Preise zu gewinnen. Es ist Zeit zu beweisen, dass Du einer der Besten bist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La nostra sezione VIP è dove i giocatori seri vengono a giocare. Il Cappello Dorato da VIP ti darà accesso illimitato ai tavoli con la posta più alta nella nostra area VIP. Sarai in grado di ottenere dei premi importanti, velocemente! E' ora di provare che sei uno dei migliori! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nuestra sección VIP es donde los jugadores importantes van a jugar. Este sombrero de copa dorado VIP te dará acceso ilimitado a las más altas mesas de apuesta en el juego de nuestra área VIP. ¡Serás capaz de ganar algunos premios importantes rápido! ¡Es hora de probar que tú eres uno de los mejores!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_Hat_VIPTophat [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_Hat_VIPTophat [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Male01_Hat_VIPTophat [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_Hat_VIPTophat [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_Hat_VIPTophat [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Our VIP section is where serious gamers come to play. This Golden VIP Top Hat will give you unlimited access to the higher stakes tables in our VIP area. You'll be able to earn some serious rewards, fast! It's time to prove you're one of the best! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>