<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fire Bug Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack Insecte De Feu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Feuerkäfer-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pack Insetti Di Fuoco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack Bicho De Fuego</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The fire bug is one of the your most fierce creatures, able to destroy Ginger's plant life with its flame attack. This pack gives you immediate access to all 3 types of fire bug for use in Killer Plants from Outer Space. Also included in this pack is a fire bug T-shirt and baseball cap (both male and female versions included), and access to the stylish firefly liveries for all of your ships. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'insecte de feu est l'une des créatures les plus féroces, capable de détruire les plantes de Ginger avec son attaque enflammée. Ce pack vous donne accès aux trois types d'insectes de feu à utiliser dans Killer Plants From Outer Space, à un t-shirt insecte de feu, une casquette de base-ball (versions homme et femme incluses) et aux superbes livrées Fire Fly pour tous vos vaisseaux. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Feuerkäfer ist eine der erschreckendsten Kreaturen, denn er kann Gingers Pflanzen mit einem Feuerstoß vernichten. Dieses Paket verleiht sofortigen Zugriff auf alle 3 Feuerkäfer-Arten in "Killer Plants from Outer Space". Es enthält ebenfalls ein Feuerkäfer-Shirt und eine Baseballkappe (jeweils für Damen und Herren). Des Weiteren gewährt es Zugriff auf die schicken Glühwürmchen-Lackierungen für alle Schiffe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'Insetto di Fuoco è particolarmente aggressivo e capace di distruggere le piante di Ginger con il suo attacco fiammeggiante. Questo pack fornisce accesso immediato a tutti i 3 tipi di Insetti di Fuoco utilizzabili in Killer Plants from Outer Space. Il pack include anche una t-shirt Insetto di Fuoco, un cappellino da baseball (in doppia versione per uomo e donna) e l'accesso alle scenografiche livree Firefly per le tue navicelle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El bicho de fuego es unas de tus criaturas más feroces. Puede destruir una planta de Ginger con sus llamas. Este pack garantiza el acceso a los tres tipos de bicho de fuego para usarlos en Killer Plants from Outer Space. También se incluye en este pack una camiseta de bicho de fuego y una gorra de béisbol (versiones para hombre y mujer) y acceso a estilos Fire Fly para todas las naves. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>