<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Floral Strappy Top Bundle (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack hauts fleuris à bretelles (pour Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blumen-Trägertop-Paket (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Top a fiori con spalline (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de camisetas florales de tirantes (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">꽃무늬 탱크탑 번들 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Floral Tank Top Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">花圖案緊身短背心組合包（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">花圖案緊身短背心組合包（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Floral Tank Top Bundle (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">These three strappy tops will be a great addition to your wardrobe. Bundle includes the Black Floral Strappy top, Blue Floral Strappy Top, and Pink Floral Strappy Top. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ces trois hauts à bretelles trouveront naturellement leur place dans votre garde-robe. Le pack comprend le haut fleuri noir, le haut fleuri bleu et le haut fleuri rose. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese drei Trägertops machen sich in deinem Kleiderschrank wunderbar. Im Paket enthalten sind das schwarze Blumen-Trägertop, das blaue Blumen-Trägertop und das rosafarbene Blumen-Trägertop. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questi tre top con spalline arricchiranno con stile il tuo guardaroba. Il pacchetto include un top a fiori nero, uno blu e uno rosa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estas tres camisetas de tirantes serán una magnífica incorporación para tu fondo de armario. El conjunto incluye la camiseta de tirantes floreada negra, la camiseta de tirantes floreada azul y la camiseta de tirantes floreada rosa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">당신의 옷장을 멋지게 채워 주는 세 종류의 탱크탑입니다. 이 번들은 검은 꽃무늬 탱크탑, 푸른 꽃무늬 탱크탑, 그리고 분홍 꽃무늬 탱크탑을 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">These three tank tops will be a great addition to your wardrobe. Bundle includes the Black Floral Tank top, Blue Floral Tank Top, and Pink Floral Tank Top. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這三款緊身短背心能為你的衣帽間錦上添花。組合包包括黑色花圖案緊身短背心、藍色花圖案緊身短背心及粉紅色花圖案緊身短背心。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這三款緊身短背心能為你的更衣室錦上添花。組合包包括黑色花圖案緊身短背心、藍色花圖案緊身短背心及粉紅色花圖案緊身短背心。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">These three tank tops will be a great addition to your wardrobe. Bundle includes the Black Floral Tank top, Blue Floral Tank Top, and Pink Floral Tank Top. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>