<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Alu Ra's Shield (Legendary Weapon)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le bouclier d'Alu Ra (arme légendaire)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Alu Ras Schild (Legendäre Waffe)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scudo di Alu Ra (Arma leggendaria)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Escudo de Alu Ra (Arma legendaria)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Alu Ra's Shield (Legendary Weapon)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Legendary Shield is said to have protected Alu Ra, the Priestess of the desert lands who renounced her old Gods in favour of the Guardians of Mercia to create peace between her people.\n\nHolding off Death's touch, this shield allowed one of the first Guardians of Mercia to survive a thousand battles.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">On dit que ce légendaire bouclier protégeait Alu Ra, prêtresse des territoires du désert qui renonça à ses anciennes divinités en faveur des gardiens de Mercia, pour amener la paix entre leurs peuples.\n\nCapable d'écarter les assauts de la mort, ce bouclier a permis à l'un des premiers gardiens de Mercia de survivre à d'innombrables batailles.\n\nDÉBLOQUE DES ARTICLES DU JEU MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS – N'OFFRE PAS DE COMPOSANTS D'AVATAR POUR UN USAGE GÉNÉRAL SUR PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBLE POUR LES UTILISATEURS DU JAPON ET DE L'ASIE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser legendäre Schild hat der Sage nach Alu Ra beschützt, die Priesterin des Wüstenlands, die ihren alten Göttern entsagte und mit Hilfe der Wächter Mercias Frieden zwischen ihren Völkern stiftete.\n\nDieser Schild kann die Berührung des Todes abwehren und ermöglichte den ersten Wächtern Mercias, tausend Schlachten zu überleben.\n\nZUM FREISCHALTEN VON GEGENSTÄNDEN IN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS - NICHT ZUM ERHALT VON AVATAR-KOMPONENTEN ZUR ALLGEMEINEN NUTZUNG AUF PLAYSTATION®HOME. NICHT VERFÜGBAR FÜR BENUTZER IN JAPAN UND ASIEN [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Si dice che questo scudo leggendario abbia protetto Alu Ra, la sacerdotessa dei deserti che rinunciò ai suoi antichi dei a favore dei guardiani di Mercia affinché regnasse la pace tra la sua gente.\n\nAllontanando il tocco della morte, questo scudo permise a uno dei primi guardiani di Mercia di sopravvivere a migliaia di battaglie.\n\nSBLOCCA OGGETTI ALL'INTERNO DEL GIOCO MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS. NON REGALA COMPONENTI PER AVATAR PER USO GENERICO CON PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBILE PER GLI UTENTI IN ASIA E GIAPPONE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Se dice que este legendario escudo protegió a Alu Ra, la sacerdotisa de las tierras desérticas que renunció a sus viejos dioses en favor de los guardianes de Mercia para establecer la paz entre su pueblo.\n\nDesviando el toque de la muerte, este escudo permitió que uno de los primeros guardianes de Mercia sobreviviera a mil batallas.\n\nDESBLOQUEARÁ ELEMENTOS EN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS GAME. NO REGALARÁ COMPONENTES DE AVATAR PARA EL USO GENERAL EN CASA DE PLAYSTATION. NO DISPONIBLE PARA LOS USUARIOS DE JAPÓN Y ASIA. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This Legendary Shield is said to have protected Alu Ra, the Priestess of the desert lands who renounced her old Gods in favor of the Guardians of Mercia to create peace between her people.\n\nHolding off Death's touch, this shield allowed one of the first Guardians of Mercia to survive a thousand battles.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>