<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LMO - Spundeer</LANG>
	<LANG ID="de-DE">LMO - Spundeer</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-US">LMO - Spundeer</LANG>
	<LANG ID="es-ES">LMO - Spundeer</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">LMO - Spundeer</LANG>
	<LANG ID="it-IT">LMO - Spundeer</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ride around PlayStation®Home on Father Spun's favourite festive steed! By equipping this Locomotion Item, your avatar's run speed will be faster. LMO (Locomotion) is a Portable Item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Reite mit Väterchen Spuns Lieblings-Festtagsross durch PlayStation®Home! Spundeer Wenn Sie sich mit einem Bewegungsobjekt ausrüsten, wird die Laufgeschwindigkeit Ihres Avatars schneller. Bewegungsobjekte sind tragbare Gegenstände. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ride around PlayStation®Home on Father Spun's favourite festive steed! Not suitable for avatars with vertigo. By equipping this Locomotion Item, your avatar's run speed will be faster. LMO (Locomotion) is a Portable Item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Cabalga por PlayStation®Home sobre el corcel favorito de Papá Spun! Al equipar este objeto de locomoción, la velocidad de carrera de tu avatar aumentará. LMO (locomoción) es un objeto portátil. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Enfourchez le fier destrier du père Spun et parcourez PlayStation®Home au grand galop ! La vitesse de déplacement de votre avatar sera bien plus importante si vous équipez cet objet de locomotion. LMO (Locomotion) è un oggetto portatile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sfreccia in PlayStation®Home sul festoso destriero preferito di Babbo Spun! Spundeer Equipaggiando questo accessorio di movimento, la velocità di corsa del tuo avatar aumenterà. LMO (Locomotion) è un oggetto portatile. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>