<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Neon Accessories Bundle (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble d'accessoires fluorescents (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kostümpaket "Neon-Accessoires" (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set accessori neon (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de accesorios animados de neón (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">네온 액세서리 번들 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Neon Accessories Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">螢光配件組合包（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">螢光配件組合包（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Neon Accessories Bundle (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Highlight yourself with these animated neon accessories. Bundle includes animated neon star earrings, animated neon glasses, and animated neon bracelets. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mettez-vous en valeur avec ces accessoires fluorescents. L'ensemble comprend des boucles d'oreilles fluorescentes en forme d'étoile, des lunettes fluorescentes et des bracelets fluorescents animés. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bring dich mit diesen Neon-Accessoires zum Strahlen. Das Paket beinhaltet Neon-Sternohrringe, eine Neon-Brille und animierte Neon-Armbänder. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Illuminati con questi accessori al neon. Il set è composto da un paio di orecchini al neon a forma di stella, un paio di occhiali al neon e dei braccialetti al neon animati. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Destaca entre la multitud gracias a estos accesorios de neón. El conjunto incluye pendientes de neón, gafas de neón y pulseras animadas de neón. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">네온 액세서리 번들과 함께 당신의 삶에 빛을 불어 넣으세요. 이 번들은 귀걸이, 안경, 그리고 팔찌를 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Highlight your self with these neon accessories. Bundle includes neon star earrings, neon glasses, and animated neon bracelets. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用這些螢光配件突出你的個性。組合包包括螢光星耳環、螢光眼鏡及動態螢光手鐲。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用這些螢光配件突出你的個性。組合包包括螢光星耳環、螢光眼鏡及動態螢光手鐲。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Highlight your self with these neon accessories. Bundle includes neon star earrings, neon glasses, and animated neon bracelets. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>