<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Unidentified Squadron U-Man Mask 2-piece Set (U-Man Blue, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de 2 pièces masque d'U-Man (U-man bleu, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">2-teiliges Set: Unidentifizierte Einsatztruppe U-Man-Masken (blauer U-Man, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set 2 maschere di U-Man dello Squadrone non identificato (U-Man blu, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos máscaras del Hombre U del Escuadrón Encubierto (Hombre U Azul, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">未確認戦隊ユーマンのお面２点セット（ユーマブルー・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Unidentified Squadron U-Man Mask 2-piece Set (U-Man Blue, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Unidentified Squadron U-Man Mask 2-piece Set (U-Man Blue, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Unidentified Squadron U-Man masks. A 2-piece set with a properly worn type and a type worn in a crooked position.\nHeroism: ★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Unidentified Squadron U-Man Mask, Straight (U-Man Blue, Women) (Accessory)\n- Unidentified Squadron U-Man Mask, Crooked (U-Man Blue, Women) (Accessory)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Des masques d'U-man, escadron inconnu. Un set de 2 pièces avec un masque porté correctement et un porté de travers.\nHéroïsme : ★\nCe set contient les objets suivants :\n\n- Masque d'U-Man, escadron inconnu, droit (U-man bleu, femme) (Accessoires)\n- Masque d'U-Man, escadron inconnu, côté (U-man bleu, femme) (Accessoires)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 2-teiliges Set von normal und seitlich getragenen Masken des U-Man der unidentifizierten Einsatztruppe.\nHeldenmut: ★\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Unidentifizierte Einsatztruppe U-Man-Maske, normal (blauer U-Man, für Frauen) (Accessoires)\n- Unidentifizierte Einsatztruppe U-Man-Maske, seitlich (blauer U-Man, für Frauen) (Acessoires)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set comprendente 2 tipi di maschere di U-Man dello Squadrone non identificato, una indossata nel modo corretto e una di lato.\nValore: ★\nQuesto set comprende i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Maschera di U-Man dello Squadrone non identificato, dritta (U-Man blu, da donna) (accessori)\n- Maschera di U-Man dello Squadrone non identificato, di fianco (U-Man blu, da donna) (accessori)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, gli oggetti elencati verranno aggiunti nella loro categoria specifica.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Máscaras del Hombre U del Escuadrón Encubierto. Juego de dos artículos con una de ellas puesta correctamente y otra de manera torcida.\nHeroísmo: ★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Máscara del Hombre U del Escuadrón Encubierto, derecha (Hombre U Azul, mujer) (complemento)\n- Máscara del Hombre U del Escuadrón Encubierto, torcida (Hombre U Azul, mujer) (complemento)\n\n* Al adquirir este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su categoría correspondiente.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">未確認戦隊ユーマンのお面。正面からかぶるタイプと頭の斜め上に引っ掛けるタイプの２点セット。\nヒーロー度：　★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・未確認戦隊ユーマンのお面・正面（ユーマブルー・女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n・未確認戦隊ユーマンのお面・斜め（ユーマブルー・女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Unidentified Squadron U-Man masks. A 2-piece set with a properly worn type and a type worn in a crooked position.\nHeroism: ★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Unidentified Squadron U-Man Mask, Straight (U-Man Blue, Women) (Accessory)\n- Unidentified Squadron U-Man Mask, Crooked (U-Man Blue, Women) (Accessory)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Unidentified Squadron U-Man masks. A 2-piece set with a properly worn type and a type worn in a crooked position.\nHeroism: ★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Unidentified Squadron U-Man Mask, Straight (U-Man Blue, Women) (Accessory)\n- Unidentified Squadron U-Man Mask, Crooked (U-Man Blue, Women) (Accessory)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
