<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Release Bundle - Volume 06</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Lot de sortie - Volume 06</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Release Set - Volume 06</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Set di lancio - Volume 06</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Pack de lanzamiento - Volumen 06</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This bundle contains:\n
(1) Billabong - Invert Trucker Cap - Black (Men)\n
(2) Billabong - Surf Naked Printed Tee - Black (Men)\n
(3) Billabong - All Day Blaze Boardshorts - Black (Men)\n
(4) Billabong - Suzanne Fringe Cheeky - Black - Top (Women)\n
(5) Billabong - Suzanne Fringe Cheeky - Black - Bottom (Women)\n
(6) Billabong - Cabana Sun Hat - Natural (Women)\n
(7) Billabong - Drifting Mini Skirt - Sunny Dayz (Women)\n
(8) Billabong - Hello Bondi Top - Cool Wip (Women)\n
\n
※Upon purchase, the items will be placed into their respective categories. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce lot contient :\n
(1) Billabong – Casquette de camionneur Invert – Noir (homme)\n
(2) Billabong – T-shirt imprimé Surf Naked – noir (homme)\n
(3) Billabong – Short de bain surfer All Day Blaze – Noir (homme)\n
(4) Billabong – Suzanne Fringe Cheeky – Noir – Haut (femme)\n
(5) Billabong – Suzanne Fringe Cheeky – Noir – Bas (femme)\n
(6) Billabong – Chapeau de soleil Cabana – Naturel (femme)\n
(7) Billabong – Jupe Drifting Mini – Jours ensoleillés (femme)\n
(8) Billabong – Haut Hello Bondi – Crème fouettée (femme)\n
\n
※Une fois achetés, les articles sont placés dans leur catégorie respective. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Bündel enthält:\n
(1) Billabong - Invert Trucker Cap - Schwarz (Herren)\n
(2) Billabong - Surf Naked Bedrucktes T-Shirt - Schwarz (Herren)\n
(3) Billabong - All Day Blaze Boardshorts - Schwarz (Herren)\n
(4) Billabong - Suzanne Fringe Cheeky - Schwarz - Oberteil (Damen)\n
(5) Billabong - Suzanne Fringe Cheeky - Schwarz - Hose (Damen)\n
(6) Billabong - Cabana Sonnenhut - Natur (Damen)\n
(7) Billabong - Drifting Mini Rock - Sunny Dayz (Damen)\n
(8) Billabong - Hello Bondi Top - Cool Wip/Weiß (Damen)\n
\n
※Beim Kauf werden die Artikel in deren jeweiligen Kategorien platziert. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il set comprende:\n
(1) Billabong - Cappello con retina modello Truck Invert - Nero (Uomo)\n
(2) Billabong - T-shirt stampata Surf Naked  - Nero (Uomo)\n
(3) Billabong - Short da mare Blaze All Day  - Nero (Uomo)\n
(4) Billabong - Suzanne Fringe Cheeky - Nero - Pezzo sopra (Donna)\n
(5) Billabong - Suzanne Fringe Cheeky - Nero - Pezzo sotto (Donna)\n
(6) Billabong - Cappello da sole Cabana  - Beige (Donna)\n
(7) Billabong - Drifting Mini Gonna - Sunny Dayz (Donna)\n
(8) Billabong - Maglia Hello Bondi - Panna (Donna)\n
\n
※Al momento dell'acquisto, gli articoli saranno posizionati nelle loro rispettive categorie. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este pack contiene:\n
(1) Billabong - Gorra de camionero Invert  - Negro (Hombre)\n
(2) Billabong - Camiseta estampada Surf Naked - Negro (Hombre)\n
(3) Billabong - Bermudas All Day Blaze - Negro (Hombre)\n
(4) Billabong - Suzanne Fringe Cheeky - Negro - Top (Mujer)\n
(5) Billabong - Suzanne Fringe Cheeky - Negro - Braguita (Mujer)\n
(6) Billabong - Sombrero de sol Cabana - Natural (Mujer)\n
(7) Billabong - Minifalda Drifting - Días soleados (Mujer)\n
(8) Billabong - Camisola Hello Bondi - Color crema batida (Mujer)\n
\n
※Una vez adquiridos, los artículos se ubicarán en sus categorías respectivas. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>