<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ghostbusters™ Locker Room Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot salle du personnel S.O.S. Fantômes™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ghostbusters™ Locker Room Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completo Spogliatoio Ghostbusters™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto Sala de taquillas Cazafantasmas™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴーストバスターズ™ ロッカールーム・パック</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ghostbusters™ Locker Room Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">With this Ghostbusters™ inspired bundle you can create your very own locker room in your LOOT™ Stage Set personal space! Not only does this bundle come with the Ghostbusters™ Lockers (open and closed) and the bathroom stall, exclusive to this bundle only, you’ll also get the Ghostbusters™ toilet! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avec ce lot inspiré de S.O.S. Fantômes™ vous pouvez créer votre salle du personnel dans votre espace personnel des décors de plateau LOOT™ ! Ce lot contient non seulement les casiers S.O.S. Fantômes™ (ouverts et fermés) et la cloison de salle de bains, mais aussi en exclusivité, les toilettes S.O.S. Fantômes™ ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit diesem von Ghostbusters™ inspirierten Bundle kannst du deinen ganz eigenen Locker Room in deinem persönlichen Raum des LOOT™ Stage Set erstellen! Dieses Bundle enthält nicht nur die Ghostbusters™ Lockers (geöffnet und geschlossen) und das Badezimmer, sondern exklusiv für dieses Bundle gibt es auch die Ghostbusters™ Toilette! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Con questo Completo ispirato a Ghostbusters™, puoi creare un tuo spogliatoio nel tuo spazio personale Scenografia LOOT™! Il Completo comprende non soltanto gli Spogliatoi Ghostbusters™ (aperti e chiusi) e un Separatore da Bagno, esclusiva di questo Completo, ma anche un Water Ghostbusters™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Con este conjunto inspirado en Cazafantasmas™ puedes crear tu propia sala de taqullas en el espacio personal del estudio de LOOT™! ¡Este conjunto no solo viene con las Taquillas Cazafantasmas™ (abiertas y cerradas) y el compartimento de baño, exclusivo de este conjunto, sino que puedes conseguir el váter Cazafantasmas™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴーストバスターズ™ ロッカールーム・パックを使えばロッカールームを作り上げることができます！\n本コンテンツには、以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n\n・「ゴーストバスターズ™ ロッカー （開）」（収納家具）\n・「ゴーストバスターズ™ ロッカー （閉）」（収納家具）\n・「ゴーストバスターズ™ バスルーム個室」（装飾品）\n・「ゴーストバスターズ™ トイレ」（チェア）\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">With this Ghostbusters™ inspired bundle you can create your very own locker room in your LOOT™ Stage Set personal space! Not only does this bundle come with the Ghostbusters™ Lockers (open and closed) and the bathroom stall, exclusive to this bundle only, you’ll also get the Ghostbusters™ toilet! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>