<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Utopian Gladiatorial Blade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Épée de gladiateur Utopian</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Utopia-Gladiatorenklinge (Männer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Spada da gladiatore utopico</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Espada de gladiador utópico</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Utopian Gladiatorial Blade</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Built for the close-quarters combat style of a Mercian Fighter.\n\nOriginating from the proud warriors of the Utopian islands who use this close-quarters weapon in gladiatorial combat.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Conçu pour le style de combat rapproché propre au guerrier mercian.\n\nElle vient des fiers guerriers des îles Utopian qui l'utilisent pour les combats en corps à corps dans le style des gladiateurs.\n\nDÉBLOQUE DES ARTICLES DU JEU MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS – N'OFFRE PAS DE COMPOSANTS D'AVATAR POUR UN USAGE GÉNÉRAL SUR PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBLE POUR LES UTILISATEURS DU JAPON ET DE L'ASIE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Speziell auf den Nahkampf-Stil der Mercia-Kämpfer ausgelegt.\n\nStammt von den stolzen Kriegern der Utopia-Inseln, die diese Nahkampfwaffe in Gladiatorenkämpfen einsetzen.\n\nZUM FREISCHALTEN VON GEGENSTÄNDEN IN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS - NICHT ZUM ERHALT VON AVATAR-KOMPONENTEN ZUR ALLGEMEINEN NUTZUNG AUF PLAYSTATION®HOME. NICHT VERFÜGBAR FÜR BENUTZER IN JAPAN UND ASIEN [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Perfetta per il combattimento corpo a corpo del guerriero Mercian.\n\nCreata dagli orgogliosi guerrieri delle isole del Utopiche che usano queste armi da corpo a corpo nei combattimenti tra gladiatori.\n\nSBLOCCA OGGETTI ALL'INTERNO DEL GIOCO MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS. NON REGALA COMPONENTI PER AVATAR PER USO GENERICO CON PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBILE PER GLI UTENTI IN ASIA E GIAPPONE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Creada para el estilo de combate cuerpo a cuerpo de un luchador de Mercia.\n\nCreada por los orgullosos guerreros de las islas de Utopía que utilizan esta arma cuerpo a cuerpo en combates de gladiadores.\n\nDESBLOQUEARÁ ELEMENTOS EN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS GAME. NO REGALARÁ COMPONENTES DE AVATAR PARA EL USO GENERAL EN CASA DE PLAYSTATION. NO DISPONIBLE PARA LOS USUARIOS DE JAPÓN Y ASIA. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Built for the close-quarters combat style of a Mercian Fighter.\n\nOriginating from the proud warriors of the Utopian islands who use this close-quarters weapon in gladiatorial combat.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>