<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Apollo DX Engine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Moteurs Apollo DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Apollo DX-Triebwerk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Motori Apollo DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Motores Apolo DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Apollo DX エンジン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Apollo DX 엔진</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Apollo DX Engine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Apollo DX 引擎</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Apollo DX 引擎</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Apollo DX Engine</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A noticeable jump in top speed to pull your Sodium2 racer away from its competition on the straights. An increase in weight will slow you down through the turns. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un bond en avant significatif en termes de vitesse de pointe, qui permettra à votre véhicule d'éliminer toute concurrence dans les lignes droites. Un surpoids vous ralentira dans les virages. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein merklicher Anstieg der Höchstgeschwindigkeit lässt deinen Sodium2-Gleiter auf Geraden an der Konkurrenz vorbeiziehen. Durch das erhöhte Gewicht wirst du in Kurven langsamer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un notevole aumento di velocità massima consentirà al tuo veicolo da corsa Sodium2 di staccare gli avversari con irrisoria facilità. L'aumento di peso potrà rTITANtarti in curva. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un importante aumento en la velocidad máxima para alejar al corredor de Sodium2 de sus competidores en las rectas. El aumento de peso te ralentizará en las curvas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">トップスピードでの急加速に優れています。直線で一挙に飛び出して、競争相手たちにサヨナラ。車体全体の重量が重くなるので、コーナーで減速してしまうのが弱点です。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">최고 속력이 눈에 띄게 증가하여, 직선 구간에서 앞으로 치고 나가는 Sodium2 레이서를 볼 수 있습니다. 하지만 증가한 엔진의 무게는 코너링의 저해 요소가 됩니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A noticeable jump in top speed to pull your Sodium2 racer away from its competition on the straights. An increase in weight will slow you down through the turns. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">大幅提升最高速度，讓你的Sodium2飛船在直路上拋離其他對手。重量的增加會減慢你的轉彎速度。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">大幅提升最高速度，讓你的Sodium2飛船在直路上拋離其他對手。重量的增加會減慢你的轉彎速度。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A noticeable jump in top speed to pull your Sodium2 racer away from its competition on the straights. An increase in weight will slow you down through the turns. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>