<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Omniplex DX Chassis</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Châssis Omniplex DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Omniplex DX-Chassis</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Carrozzeria Omniplex DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chasis Omniplex DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Omniplex DX シャシー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Omniplex DX 차대</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Omniplex DX Chassis</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Omniplex DX 車身</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Omniplex DX 車身</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Omniplex DX Chassis</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A heavy, sturdy frame for your Sodium2 racer will notably increase stability but the increased weight will create a greater loss of momentum following race impacts. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un châssis robuste et lourd pour votre véhicule de course Sodium2 qui augmentera votre stabilité de façon significative, mais le surpoids vous fera perdre plus de vitesse lors des impacts. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein sehr schweres und robustes Chassis für deinen Sodium2-Gleiter. Es verbessert die Stabilität erheblich, doch das größere Gewicht führt zu einem erhöhten Geschwindigkeitsverlust bei Zusammenstößen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un telaio pesante e resistente consente al tuo veicolo da corsa Sodium2 una notevole stabilità ma l'aumento di peso riduce considerevolmente la velocità acquisita dopo una collisione. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un marco robusto y pesado para tu corredor de Sodium2 aumentará notablemente la estabilidad, pero el aumento de peso supondrá mayor pérdida de impulso tras un impacto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">重く頑丈なフレームゆえに、安定性には目を見張るものがある。だが機体重量が増える分、衝撃を受けた時の減速量には目を覆いたくなるだろう。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">무겁고 단단한 프레임입니다. Sodium2 레이서의 안정성이 향상되지만, 증가한 무게 덕분에 경주 중의 충돌로부터 빠르게 회복하기 어렵습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A heavy, sturdy frame for your Sodium2 racer will notably increase stability but the increased weight will create a greater loss of momentum following race impacts. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這個沉重、堅固的支架能明顯提升穩定性，但額外的重量會導致撞擊後失去更大的動力。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這個沉重、堅固的支架能明顯提升穩定性，但額外的重量會導致撞擊後失去更大的動力。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A heavy, sturdy frame for your Sodium2 racer will notably increase stability but the increased weight will create a greater loss of momentum following race impacts. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>