<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Nis_Dots_No017</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Personnage 2D: Mao</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドットオブジェ　マッドな魔界優等生　マオ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">도트 오브제 미친 마계 우등생 마오</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Mao: The Mad Honor Student" Sprite Statue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">像素雕像 瘋狂的魔界優等生MAO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">像素雕像 瘋狂的魔界優等生MAO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">2D Character Objects: Mao</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nis_dot_No017</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Untitled</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La statuette d'un personnage que tu peux mettre dans ta chambre pour décorer.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">今日も魔立邪悪学園の改造されたトイレでは、探求心に満ち溢れた邪心をもつ悪魔が、超勇者の大研究！彼は魔王の息子、その名もマオ。父親である魔王を倒すため、邪悪指数180万の頭脳によって導き出された答えとは、自らが勇者になって魔王を倒すことだった！？その手にするのは勇者の力か？邪悪なココロか？メチャクチャな野望で周囲を巻き込み邪悪学園探索開始！マッドなお友達がほしい君には是非とも置いてほしいオブジェだ！「ハァハァ、じゅるり・・・」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">오늘도 마립 사악학원의 개조된 화장실에서는 탐구심으로 가득찬 악한 마음을 가진 악마가 초용사를 연구! 그는 마왕의 아들, 그 이름은 마오. 아버지인 마왕을 쓰러뜨리기 위해 사악 지수 180만의 두뇌로 찾아낸 답은 스스로 용사가 되어 마왕을 쓰러뜨리는 것이었다!? 그 손에 넣으려는 것은 용사의 힘인가? 사악한 마음인가? 뒤죽박죽되어 버린 야망으로 주위를 둘러싸고 사악학원 탐색 시작! 미친 친구가 필요한 당신에게 꼭 추천하는 오브제!「하아하아, 주르륵・・・」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A demon with an evil heart, brimming with curiosity, continues his Super Hero research in the Nether Institute, Evil Academy's remodeled restroom. This demon is the Overlord's son, and his name is Mao. In order to topple his father, Mao's 1.8 million EQ has led him to the conclusion that he must become a hero himself to gain the "Power of Heroes". Does that make him a hero, or does it make him evil? For those of you who want a mad little friend in your personal space, this Sprite Statue is highly recommended. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">被改造的魔立邪惡學園廁所中，今天充滿探究心，且擁有邪心的惡魔，超勇者的大研究！他是魔王的兒子，名字也是Mao。為了打倒父親魔王，依邪惡指數180萬的頭腦所引出的答案，竟然是親自成為勇者來打敗魔王！？在他手中的，是勇者的力量？還是邪惡的心？因亂七八糟的野心將周遭捲入，開始搜尋魔立邪惡學園！希望擁有瘋狂朋友的你一定想擁有的雕像！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">被改造的魔立邪惡學園廁所中，今天充滿探究心，且擁有邪心的惡魔，超勇者的大研究！他是魔王的兒子，名字也是Mao。為了打倒父親魔王，依邪惡指數180萬的頭腦所引出的答案，竟然是親自成為勇者來打敗魔王！？在他手中的，是勇者的力量？還是邪惡的心？因亂七八糟的野心將周遭捲入，開始搜尋魔立邪惡學園！希望擁有瘋狂朋友的你一定想擁有的雕像！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A small character statue that you can place to decorate your own room.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>