<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Radec's Helmet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Casque de Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Radecs Helm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Elmetto di Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Casco de Radec</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">라덱 대령의 헬멧</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Radec's Helmet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Radec頭盔</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Radec頭盔</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Radec's Helmet</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Descr</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">After his demise, Colonel Radec’s custom-made combat helmet was submitted to ISA Command for analysis. Initial tests have revealed that it contains built-in respiration and communication facilities, but a sudden increase in security breaches at the ISA facility has delayed further analysis. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">À la mort du colonel Radec, son casque de combat personnalisé a été envoyé à l'ISA pour analyse. Les premiers examens ont révélé qu'il est équipé de systèmes de respiration et de communication intégrés, mais les analyses ont été suspendues à cause de la hausse soudaine des manquements aux règles de sécurité dans le bâtiment de l'ISA. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tras la muerte del coronel Radec, su casco de combate, hecho a medida, se envió al mando ISA para ser analizado. Las pruebas iniciales revelaron que integra un sistema de respiración y comunicación. No obstante, el aumento de los problemas de seguridad en las instalaciones de los ISA ha imposibilitado un análisis más profundo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">라덱 대령이 최후를 맞은 다음, 그의 커스텀 헬멧은 ISA 지휘부로 넘겨져 분석되었습니다. 호흡과 통신 기능이 내장되었다는 사실이 처음 밝혀진 후, ISA의 연구소에 계속되는 보안 습격으로 인해 그 이상의 연구는 진척된 바가 없습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">After his demise, Colonel Radec’s custom-made combat helmet was submitted to ISA Command for analysis. Initial tests have revealed that it contains built-in respiration and communication facilities, but a sudden increase in security breaches at the ISA facility has delayed further analysis. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Radec上校死後，他的特製戰鬥頭盔被送至ISA司令部進行分析。初部測試顯示，該頭盔內置呼吸和通訊設備。但由於ISA設施的保安系統突然遭到入侵，進一步的分析被逼推遲。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Radec上校死後，他的特製戰鬥頭盔被送至ISA司令部進行分析。初部測試顯示，該頭盔內置呼吸和通訊設備。但由於ISA設施的保安系統突然遭到入侵，進一步的分析被逼推遲。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">After his demise, Colonel Radec’s custom-made combat helmet was submitted to ISA Command for analysis. Initial tests have revealed that it contains built-in respiration and communication facilities, but a sudden increase in security breaches at the ISA facility has delayed further analysis. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>