<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MotorStorm® Car Seat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MotorStorm® Car Seat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Banquette de voiture MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MotorStorm®-Autositz</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sedile d'auto MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Asiento de coche de MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">MotorStorm® 車の座席</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">MotorStorm® 자동차 좌석</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">MotorStorm™ Car Seat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">MotorStorm™ 車座位</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">MotorStorm™ 車座位</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MotorStorm® Car Seat</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">One careful owner – no, two – actually make that twelve. The rest of the car went on to see greatness at the first MotorStorm® but is sadly no longer with us, so why not pimp out your apartment with this leftover rear seat.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">One careful owner – no, two – actually make that twelve. The rest of the car went on to see greatness at the first MotorStorm® but is sadly no longer with us, so why not pimp out your apartment with this leftover rear seat.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une banquette de seconde (ou troisième) main. Le reste de la voiture a participé au premier MotorStorm® dans l'espoir de trouver la gloire mais n'est malheureusement plus des nôtres. Alors, pourquoi ne pas embellir votre appartement avec cette banquette orpheline ?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein liebevoller Besitzer, nein zwei … oder auch zwölf. Der Rest des Wagens hat seinen Triumph im ersten Teil der MotorStorm®-Reihe gefeiert, weilt jedoch nicht länger unter uns. Also schmücke doch dein Apartment mit diesem übrig gebliebenen Rücksitz.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usato con cura da un solo proprietario... o meglio due... facciamo dodici. Il resto dell'auto ha avuto i suoi momenti di gloria al primo MotorStorm®, ma purtroppo non è più con noi, perciò perchè non arredare il tuo appartamento con questo vecchio sedile posteriore?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ha pasado por unas... no, dos... bueno, realmente, doce cuidadosas manos. El resto del coche pasó a mejor vida en el primer MotorStorm®... así que, ¿por qué no darle un toque de estilo a tu apartamento con esta vieja gloria de los asientos traseros? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">１人、いや２人・・・じゃなくて１２人が愛着した座席。この初代のモーターストームで使われていたマシンの座席で部屋をリフォームしよう！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">첫 번째 MotorStorm을 보러 갔다가 미처 돌아오지 못한 어느 버스의 유일한 잔해입니다. 이제 아파트의 장식품으로는 제격입니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">One careful owner – no, two – actually make that twelve. The rest of the car went on to see greatness at the first MotorStorm but is sadly no longer with us, so why not pimp out your apartment with this leftover rear seat.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">一個，不，兩個細心的人原本做了12張這樣的椅子。但餘下的都去了欣賞刺激精彩的MotorStorm第一集，且不幸一去不返。既然這樣，你何不用這些被剩下的後座來裝飾你的房間？[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">一個，不，兩個細心的人原本做了12張這樣的椅子。但餘下的都去了欣賞刺激精彩的MotorStorm第一集，且不幸一去不返。既然這樣，你何不用這些被剩下的後座來裝飾你的房間？[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">One careful owner – no, two – actually make that twelve. The rest of the car went on to see greatness at the first MotorStorm® but is sadly no longer with us, so why not pimp out your apartment with this leftover rear seat.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>