<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">2-wheeled Mini-Bike 2-piece Set (White)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de 2 pièces mini-moto à 2 roues (blanche)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">2-teiliges Minibike-Set (weiß)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set minimoto a due ruote (bianco)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos artículos con minimoto de dos ruedas (blanca)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ポケットバイク２点セット（ホワイト単色）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">2-wheeled Mini-Bike 2-piece Set (White)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 2-piece set with 2-wheeled type minibikes: a Locomotion item you can ride and a furniture piece you can place in your room.\nSpeed increases while pressing □.\nLocomotion Speed: ★★★★~★★★★★\n*Locomotion is a portable item.\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- 2-wheeled Minibike Figurine (White) (Ornaments)\n- Locomotion - 2-wheeled Minibike (White) (Portables)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 2 pièces avec des mini-motos à 2 roues : un objet de locomotion sur lequel vous pouvez monter et un meuble que vous pouvez placer dans votre chambre.\nLa vitesse augmente en appuyant sur □.\nVitesse : ★★★★~★★★★★\n*Un objet de locomotion est un objet portable.\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Figurine de mini-moto à 2 roues (blanche) (Décoration)\n- Locomotion - Mini-moto à 2 roues (blanche) (Objet portable)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 2-teiliges Set von Minibikes. Es enthält einen Bewegungsgegenstand, mit dem du herumfahren kannst, und einem Gegenstand zur Dekoration deines Zimmers.\nGeschwindigkeit erhöht sich durch das Drücken von □.\nGeschwindigkeit: ★★★★~★★★★★\n*Bewegungsgegenstände sind tragbare Gegenstände.\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Miniatur eines zweirädrigen Minibikes (weiß) (Verzierungen)\n- Zweirädriges Bewegungs-Minibike (weiß) (Tragbare Objekte)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set composto da 2 elementi comprendente 2 minimoto a due ruote, di cui una è un oggetto Locomotion utilizzabile come mezzo di locomozione, e l'altra è un oggetto da arredamento da sistemare nel proprio Spazio personale.\nTenendo premuto il tasto □, la velocità di spostamento aumenta.\nVelocità di spostamento: ★★★★~★★★★★\n* Gli oggetti Locomotion sono oggetti portatili.\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Modellino minimoto a due ruote (bianco) (Decorazioni)\n- Locomotion - Minimoto a due ruote (bianca) (Oggetti portatili)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettiva categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos minimotos de dos ruedas: un artículo de locomoción que podrás conducir para desplazarte, y un artículo de mobiliario para decorar tu habitación.\nSe incrementará la velocidad al presionar □.\nVelocidad de locomoción: ★★★★~★★★★★\n*Locomoción es un artículo portátil.\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Minimoto de dos ruedas en miniatura (blanca) (Adornos)\n- Locomoción - Minimoto de dos ruedas (blanca) (Portátiles)\n\n* Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">２輪タイプのポケットバイク。乗って移動できるロコモーションと、部屋に置ける家具の２点セット。\n※LMO(ロコモーション)はポータブルアイテムです。\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・ポケットバイクの置物（ホワイト単色）/装飾品\n・LMO-ポケットバイク（ホワイト単色）/ポータブルアイテム\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 2-piece set with 2-wheeled type minibikes: a Locomotion item you can ride and a furniture piece you can place in your room.\nSpeed increases while pressing □.\nLocomotion Speed: ★★★★~★★★★★\n*Locomotion is a portable item.\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- 2-wheeled Minibike Figurine (White) (Ornaments)\n- Locomotion - 2-wheeled Minibike (White) (Portables)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
