<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Icaras Trophy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Icaras Trophy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Trophée Icaras</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Icaras-Trophäe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Trofeo Icaras</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Trofeo de Icaras</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Icaras Trophy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Icaras 트로피</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Icaras Trophy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Icaras 獎盃</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Icaras 獎盃</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Icaras Trophy</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Icaras wants their fans to feel a part of the team and what better way than to offer this delightful scale model trophy of their fastest ship to date? Marvel at its unique lines, its distinctive front-end, its brazen colour scheme. It surely is Icaras.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Icaras wants their fans to feel a part of the team and what better way than to offer this delightful scale model trophy of their fastest ship to date? Marvel at its unique lines, its distinctive front-end, its brazen colour scheme. It surely is Icaras. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Icaras veut que ses fans se sentent faire partie de l'écurie, et leur propose donc ce ravissant modèle réduit du plus rapide de ses navires. Extasiez-vous sur ses lignes uniques, son nez inimitable et ses couleurs inspirées... Une œuvre magistrale d'Icaras, sans aucun doute. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Icaras möchte seinen Fans das Gefühl geben, ein Teil des Teams zu sein. Was gibt es da besseres als dieses exzellente Modell unseres bisher schnellsten Schiffes? Seine einzigartige Form, der unverkennbare Bug und seine bronzene Farbgebung werden jeden in Staunen versetzen. Das ist eben Icaras! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Icaras vuole donare ai fan la sensazione di far parte della squadra e per questo ha creato un delizioso modellino in scala della propria nave più veloce. Ammirate la linea straordinaria, il muso distintivo e la colorazione sfrontata. Un perfetto esempio di stile Icaras. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Icaras quiere que los fans se sientan parte del equipo. ¿Qué mejor forma de hacerlo que con este precioso trofeo, que reproduce a escala su nave más rápida fabricada hasta el momento? Maravíllate con sus inconfundibles líneas, su característico frontal y su descarado esquema de colores. Es de Icaras, sin duda. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Icaras wants their fans to feel a part of the team and what better way than to offer this delightful scale model trophy of their fastest ship to date? Marvel at its unique lines, its distinctive front-end, its brazen colour scheme. It surely is Icaras. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Icaras의 팬들은 언제나 팀 역사의 일부분이 되기를 기다려 왔습니다. 이젠 현존하는 최고속 기체의 모델 트로피와 함께 그 유려한 곡선과 디자인, 그리고 강렬한 색상을 음미할 수 있습니다. 역시 Icaras가 멋집니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Icaras wants their fans to feel a part of the team and what better way than to offer this delightful scale model trophy of their fastest ship to date? Marvel at its unique lines, its distinctive front-end, its brazen colour scheme. It surely is Icaras. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Icaras希望他們的支持者可以有身為車隊一份子的歸屬感，於是以他們車隊目前最高速的賽車為主題，設計了這個令人眼前一亮的比例模型獎盃。來仔細欣賞這個獎盃與別不同的線條、別緻的車頭設計和黃銅色的用色，絕對充滿Icaras的味道。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Icaras希望他們的支持者可以有身為車隊一份子的歸屬感，於是以他們車隊目前最高速的賽車為主題，設計了這個令人眼前一亮的比例模型獎盃。來仔細欣賞這個獎盃與別不同的線條、別緻的車頭設計和黃銅色的用色，絕對充滿Icaras的味道。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Icaras wants their fans to feel a part of the team and what better way than to offer this delightful scale model trophy of their fastest ship to date? Marvel at its unique lines, its distinctive front-end, its brazen colour scheme. It surely is Icaras. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>