<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Atari Super Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble arcade Atari</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Atari Arcade-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Atari versione arcade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack Atari Arcade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Atari Super Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Atari Super Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Atari Super Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Atari Super Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Atari Super Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Includes: 1. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 2. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in table top form. 3. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 4. Atari's Centipede arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 5. Atari's Centipede arcade game in table top form. 6. Atari's Centipede arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 7. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 8. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in table top form. 9. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 10. A classic '70s TV set accompanied by an Atari 2600 and the Adventure game cartridge. 11. Atari 2600's Adventure in exclusive arcade cabinet form. 12. Atari 2600's Adventure in exclusive arcade table top form. 13. Atari's Computer Assisted Troubleshooter is an essential tool for arcade game owners. Use the CAT Box to adjust settings in your arcade games. 14. Slippers in tribute to Atari's Asteroids arcade game. 15. A headpiece in the style of Atari's Centipede arcade art. 16. A classic astronaut helmet for players of Atari's Lunar Lander. 17. Dress up as a classic Atari 2600 cartridge featuring Adventure. 18. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Asteroids arcade game (Male/Female). 19. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Centipede arcade game (Male/Female). 20. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Lunar Lander arcade game (Male/Female). 21. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Adventure arcade game (Male/Female). 22. A gold chain featuring Atari Asteroids' iconic UFO art, on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 23. A gold chain featuring Atari Centipede's shooter on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 24. A gold chain featuring Atari's classic Lunar Lander vector style, on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 25. A gold chain featuring Atari 2600 Adventure's iconic dragon on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® are trademarks owned by Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Comprend : 1. Jeu Asteroids d’Atari en borne d’arcade grandeur nature. 2. Jeu d’arcade Asteroids d’Atari en borne de table horizontale. 3. Jeu d’arcade Asteroids d’Atari en borne compacte. 4. Jeu Centipede d’Atari en borne d’arcade grandeur nature. 5. Jeu d’arcade Centipede d’Atari en borne de table horizontale. 6. Jeu d’arcade Centipede d’Atari en borne compacte. 7. Jeu Lunar Lander d’Atari en borne d’arcade grandeur nature. 8. Jeu d’arcade Lunar Lander d’Atari en borne de table horizontale. 9. Jeu d’arcade Lunar Lander d’Atari en borne compacte. 10. Téléviseur classique des années 70 accompagné d’un Atari 2600 et de la cartouche du jeu Adventure. 11. Adventure pour Atari 2600 en borne d’arcade exclusive. 12. Adventure pour Atari 2600 en borne de table horizontale exclusive. 13. Computer Assisted Troubleshooter d’Atari est un outil essentiel aux propriétaires de jeux d’arcade. Utilisez la boîte CAT pour ajuster les paramètres de vos jeux d’arcade. 14. Chaussons inspirés par le jeu d’arcade Asteroids d’Atari. 15. Masque dans le style du jeu d’arcade Centipede d’Atari. 16. Casque d’astronaute classique pour les joueurs du jeu Lunar Lander d’Atari. 17. Déguisez-vous en cartouche du jeu Adventure pour Atari 2600. 18. T-shirt animé avec motifs du jeu d’arcade classique Asteroids (Homme/Femme). 19. T-shirt animé avec motifs du jeu d’arcade classique Centipede (Homme/Femme). 20. T-shirt animé avec motifs du jeu d’arcade classique Lunar Lander (Homme/Femme). 21. T-shirt animé avec motifs du jeu d’arcade classique Adventure (Homme/Femme). 22. Chaîne en or avec OVNI emblématique du jeu Asteroids d’Atari sur T-shirt noir (Homme/Femme). 23. Chaîne en or avec tireur du jeu Centipede d’Atari sur T-shirt noir (Homme/Femme). 24. Chaîne en or avec motif vectoriel classique du jeu Lunar Lander d’Atari sur T-shirt noir (Homme/Femme). 25. Chaîne en or avec dragon emblématique du jeu Adventure de l’Atari 2600 sur T-shirt noir (Homme/Femme). Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® © 2012, Atari Interactive Inc. Tous droits réservés. Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® sont des marques déposées d’Atari Interactive, Inc. Technologie d’émulation FOCAL © 2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beinhaltet: 1. Ataris Asteroids-Arcade-Spiel als klassischer Automat in voller Größe. 2. Ataris Asteroids-Arcade-Spiel als Tischversion. 3. Ataris Asteroids-Arcade-Spiel als kompakter Cabaret-Automat. 4. Ataris Centipede-Arcade-Spiel als klassischer Automat in voller Größe. 5. Ataris Centipede-Arcade-Spiel als Tischversion. 6. Ataris Centipede-Arcade-Spiel als kompakter Cabaret-Automat. 7. Ataris Lunar-Lander-Arcade-Spiel als klassischer Automat in voller Größe. 8. Ataris Lunar-Lander-Arcade-Spiel als Tischversion. 9. Ataris Lunar-Lander-Arcade-Spiel als kompakter Cabaret-Automat. 10. Ein klassischer Fernseher aus den 70er Jahren mit einem Atari 2600 und einer Spiel-Cartridge von Adventure. 11. Atari 2600s Adventure in exklusiver Arcade-Automatenform. 12. Atari 2600s Adventure als exklusiver Arcade-Tisch. 13. Ataris Computer Assisted Troubleshooter ist ein notwendiges Werkzeug für alle Besitzer von Arcade-Spielen. Verändere mit der CAT Box die Einstellungen deiner Arcade-Spiele. 14. Pantoffeln im Stil von Ataris Asteroids-Arcade-Spiel. 15. Eine Kopfbedeckung im Stil von Ataris Centipede. 16. Ein klassischer Astronautenhelm für Spieler von Ataris Lunar Lander, 17. Verkleide dich als eine Atari-2600-Cartridge von Adventure. 18. Animiertes T-Shirt mit Bildern von dem klassischen Asteroids-Spiel (Männlich/Weiblich). 19. Animiertes T-Shirt mit Bildern von dem klassischen Centipede-Spiel (Männlich/Weiblich). 20. Animiertes T-Shirt mit Bildern von dem klassischen Lunar-Lander-Spiel (Männlich/Weiblich). 21. Animiertes T-Shirt mit Bildern von dem klassischen Adventure-Spiel (Männlich/Weiblich). 22. Eine Goldkette mit dem kultigen UFO von Atari 2600 Asteroids auf einem schwarzen T-Shirt (Männlich/Weiblich). 23. Eine Goldkette mit Ataris 2600 Centipede auf einem schwarzen T-Shirt (Männlich/Weiblich). 24. Eine Goldkette mit dem klassischen Vektor-Stil von von Ataris Lunar Lander auf einem schwarzen T-Shirt (Männlich/Weiblich). 25. Eine Goldkette mit dem kultigen Drachen von Atari 2600 Adventure auf einem schwarzen T-Shirt (Männlich/Weiblich). Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. Alle Recht vorbehalten. Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® sind Markenzeichen im Besitz von Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Contiene: 1. Asteroids di Atari in versione mobile arcade classico. 2. Asteroids in versione tavolo. 3. Gioco arcade Asteroids di Atari in versione mobile compatto. 4. Centipede di Atari in versione mobile arcade classico. 5. Centipede in versione tavolo. 6. Centipede di Atari in versione mobile compatto. 7. Lunar Lander di Atari in versione mobile arcade classico. 8. Lunar Lander in versione tavolo. 9. Lunar Lander di Atari in versione mobile compatto. 10. Televisore stile anni 70 con console Atari 2600 e cartuccia del gioco Adventure. 11. Adventure per Atari 2600 nell'esclusiva versione mobile arcade. 12. Adventure per Atari 2600 nell'esclusiva versione tavolo. 13. Computer Assisted Troubleshooter di Atari è uno strumento essenziale in quanto consente, tramite la casella CAT, di regolare le impostazioni del gioco. 14. Pantofole ispirate ad Asteroids. 15. Maschera ispirata ai disegni di Centipede di Atari. 16. Un classico casco da astronauta per giocatori di Lunar Lander di Atari. 17. Indossa il costume che riproduce una cartuccia di Adventure per Atari 2600. 18. T-shirt animata con disegni tratti dal classico videogioco arcade Asteroids (Maschio/Femmina). 19. T-shirt animata con disegni tratti dal classico videogioco arcade Centipede (Maschio/Femmina). 20. T-shirt animata con disegni tratti dal classico videogioco arcade Lunar Lander (Maschio/Femmina). 21. T-shirt animata con disegni tratti dal classico videogioco arcade Adventure (Maschio/Femmina). 22. Una catena d'oro con l'UFO di Asteroids su una t-shirt nera (Maschio/Femmina). 23. Catena d'oro con il cannone laser di Centipede su una t-shirt nera (Maschio/Femmina). 24. Catena d'oro con il vettore di Lunar Lander su una t-shirt nera (Maschio/Femmina). 25. Una catena d'oro con il drago di Adventure per Atari 2600 su una t-shirt nera (Maschio/Femmina). Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. Tutti i diritti riservati. Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® sono marchi registrati proprietà di Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Incluye: 1. Máquina arcade a tamaño completo de Asteroids, de Atari. 2. Juego de Asteroids, de Atari, en forma de tablero. 3. Máquina arcade compacta de Asteroids, de Atari. 4. Máquina arcade a tamaño completo de Centipede, de Atari. 5. Juego de Centipede, de Atari, en forma de tablero. 6. Máquina arcade compacta de Centipede, de Atari. 7. Máquina arcade a tamaño completo de Lunar Lander, de Atari. 8. Juego de Lunar Lander, de Atari, en forma de tablero. 9. Máquina arcade compacta de Lunar Lander, de Atari. 10. Televisor clásico de los 70 acompañado de una Atari 2600 y el cartucho de Adventure. 11. Adventure, de la Atari 2600, en forma de máquina arcade exclusiva. 12. Juego de Adventure, de la Atari 2600, en forma de tablero exclusivo. 13. Computer Assisted Troubleshooter de Atari es una herramienta básica para todo poseedor de juegos arcade. Usa la Caja CAT para ajustar la configuración de tus juegos arcade. 14. Zapatillas tributo al juego arcade de Atari, Asteroids. 15. Máscara al estilo de los dibujos de Centipede, de Atari. 16. Clásico casco de astronauta para jugadores de Lunar Lander, de Atari. 17. Disfrázate de cartucho de Adventure, clásico de la Atari 2600. 18. Camiseta animada con dibujos del clásico arcade Asteroids (Hombre/Mujer). 19. Camiseta animada con dibujos del clásico arcade Centipede (Hombre/Mujer). 20. Camiseta animada con dibujos del clásico arcade Lunar Lander (Hombre/Mujer). 21. Camiseta animada con dibujos del clásico arcade Adventure (Hombre/Mujer). 22. Cadena de oro con el icónico ovni de Asteroids de la Atari en una camiseta negra (Hombre/Mujer). 23. Cadena de oro con el disparador de Centipede de la Atari en una camiseta negra (Hombre/Mujer). 24. Cadena de oro con la clásica flecha de Luna Lander de la Atari en una camiseta negra (Hombre/Mujer). 25. Cadena de oro con el icónico dragón de Adventure de la Atari 2600 en una camiseta negra (Hombre/Mujer). Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. Todos los derechos reservados. Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® son marcas registradas propiedad de Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Includes: 1. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 2. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in table top form. 3. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 4. Atari's Centipede arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 5. Atari's Centipede arcade game in table top form. 6. Atari's Centipede arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 7. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 8. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in table top form. 9. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 10. A classic '70s TV set accompanied by an Atari 2600 and the Adventure game cartridge. 11. Atari 2600's Adventure in exclusive arcade cabinet form. 12. Atari 2600's Adventure in exclusive arcade table top form. 13. Atari's Computer Assisted Troubleshooter is an essential tool for arcade game owners. Use the CAT Box to adjust settings in your arcade games. 14. Slippers in tribute to Atari's Asteroids arcade game. 15. A headpiece in the style of Atari's Centipede arcade art. 16. A classic astronaut helmet for players of Atari's Lunar Lander. 17. Dress up as a classic Atari 2600 cartridge featuring Adventure. 18. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Asteroids arcade game (Male/Female). 19. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Centipede arcade game (Male/Female). 20. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Lunar Lander arcade game (Male/Female). 21. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Adventure arcade game (Male/Female). 22. A gold chain featuring Atari Asteroids' iconic UFO art, on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 23. A gold chain featuring Atari Centipede's shooter on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 24. A gold chain featuring Atari's classic Lunar Lander vector style, on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 25. A gold chain featuring Atari 2600 Adventure's iconic dragon on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® are trademarks owned by Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Includes: 1. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 2. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in table top form. 3. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 4. Atari's Centipede arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 5. Atari's Centipede arcade game in table top form. 6. Atari's Centipede arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 7. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 8. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in table top form. 9. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 10. A classic '70s TV set accompanied by an Atari 2600 and the Adventure game cartridge. 11. Atari 2600's Adventure in exclusive arcade cabinet form. 12. Atari 2600's Adventure in exclusive arcade table top form. 13. Atari's Computer Assisted Troubleshooter is an essential tool for arcade game owners. Use the CAT Box to adjust settings in your arcade games. 14. Slippers in tribute to Atari's Asteroids arcade game. 15. A headpiece in the style of Atari's Centipede arcade art. 16. A classic astronaut helmet for players of Atari's Lunar Lander. 17. Dress up as a classic Atari 2600 cartridge featuring Adventure. 18. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Asteroids arcade game (Male/Female). 19. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Centipede arcade game (Male/Female). 20. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Lunar Lander arcade game (Male/Female). 21. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Adventure arcade game (Male/Female). 22. A gold chain featuring Atari Asteroids' iconic UFO art, on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 23. A gold chain featuring Atari Centipede's shooter on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 24. A gold chain featuring Atari's classic Lunar Lander vector style, on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 25. A gold chain featuring Atari 2600 Adventure's iconic dragon on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® are trademarks owned by Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Includes: 1. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 2. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in table top form. 3. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 4. Atari's Centipede arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 5. Atari's Centipede arcade game in table top form. 6. Atari's Centipede arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 7. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 8. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in table top form. 9. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 10. A classic '70s TV set accompanied by an Atari 2600 and the Adventure game cartridge. 11. Atari 2600's Adventure in exclusive arcade cabinet form. 12. Atari 2600's Adventure in exclusive arcade table top form. 13. Atari's Computer Assisted Troubleshooter is an essential tool for arcade game owners. Use the CAT Box to adjust settings in your arcade games. 14. Slippers in tribute to Atari's Asteroids arcade game. 15. A headpiece in the style of Atari's Centipede arcade art. 16. A classic astronaut helmet for players of Atari's Lunar Lander. 17. Dress up as a classic Atari 2600 cartridge featuring Adventure. 18. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Asteroids arcade game (Male/Female). 19. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Centipede arcade game (Male/Female). 20. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Lunar Lander arcade game (Male/Female). 21. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Adventure arcade game (Male/Female). 22. A gold chain featuring Atari Asteroids' iconic UFO art, on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 23. A gold chain featuring Atari Centipede's shooter on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 24. A gold chain featuring Atari's classic Lunar Lander vector style, on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 25. A gold chain featuring Atari 2600 Adventure's iconic dragon on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® are trademarks owned by Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Includes: 1. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 2. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in table top form. 3. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 4. Atari's Centipede arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 5. Atari's Centipede arcade game in table top form. 6. Atari's Centipede arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 7. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 8. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in table top form. 9. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 10. A classic '70s TV set accompanied by an Atari 2600 and the Adventure game cartridge. 11. Atari 2600's Adventure in exclusive arcade cabinet form. 12. Atari 2600's Adventure in exclusive arcade table top form. 13. Atari's Computer Assisted Troubleshooter is an essential tool for arcade game owners. Use the CAT Box to adjust settings in your arcade games. 14. Slippers in tribute to Atari's Asteroids arcade game. 15. A headpiece in the style of Atari's Centipede arcade art. 16. A classic astronaut helmet for players of Atari's Lunar Lander. 17. Dress up as a classic Atari 2600 cartridge featuring Adventure. 18. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Asteroids arcade game (Male/Female). 19. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Centipede arcade game (Male/Female). 20. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Lunar Lander arcade game (Male/Female). 21. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Adventure arcade game (Male/Female). 22. A gold chain featuring Atari Asteroids' iconic UFO art, on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 23. A gold chain featuring Atari Centipede's shooter on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 24. A gold chain featuring Atari's classic Lunar Lander vector style, on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 25. A gold chain featuring Atari 2600 Adventure's iconic dragon on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® are trademarks owned by Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Includes: 1. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 2. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in table top form. 3. Atari's Asteroids arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 4. Atari's Centipede arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 5. Atari's Centipede arcade game in table top form. 6. Atari's Centipede arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 7. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in a full-sized classic arcade cabinet. 8. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in table top form. 9. Atari's Lunar Lander arcade game in compact cabaret cabinet form. 10. A classic '70s TV set accompanied by an Atari 2600 and the Adventure game cartridge. 11. Atari 2600's Adventure in exclusive arcade cabinet form. 12. Atari 2600's Adventure in exclusive arcade table top form. 13. Atari's Computer Assisted Troubleshooter is an essential tool for arcade game owners. Use the CAT Box to adjust settings in your arcade games. 14. Slippers in tribute to Atari's Asteroids arcade game. 15. A headpiece in the style of Atari's Centipede arcade art. 16. A classic astronaut helmet for players of Atari's Lunar Lander. 17. Dress up as a classic Atari 2600 cartridge featuring Adventure. 18. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Asteroids arcade game (Male/Female). 19. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Centipede arcade game (Male/Female). 20. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Lunar Lander arcade game (Male/Female). 21. Animated T-shirt featuring art from the classic Adventure arcade game (Male/Female). 22. A gold chain featuring Atari Asteroids' iconic UFO art, on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 23. A gold chain featuring Atari Centipede's shooter on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 24. A gold chain featuring Atari's classic Lunar Lander vector style, on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). 25. A gold chain featuring Atari 2600 Adventure's iconic dragon on a black T-shirt (Male/Female). Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Adventure®, Asteroids®, Centipede®, Lunar Lander® are trademarks owned by Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>