<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Golden Shark Aqua Mount</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aqua Mount Requin Doré</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Goldener Hai Wasser-Reittier</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aqua Mount squalo d'oro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tiburón Dorado Aqua Mount</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LMO-ゴールデン・シャーク・アクアマウント</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Golden Shark Aqua Mount</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Golden Shark Aqua Mount</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Swim effortlessly through the air and boost your speed to 150% with your personal Aqua Mount! Your speed boost will automatically engage when moving at full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nagez sans efforts dans les airs et obtenez un boost de vitesse jusqu'à 150% avec votre Aqua Mount personnelle ! Votre boost de vitesse se déclenchera automatiquement quand vous vous déplacerez à la vitesse maximale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schwebe mühelos durch die Luft und verbessere deine Geschwindigkeit auf 150% mit deinem individuellen Wasser-Reittier! Der Geschwindigkeitsschub setzt automatisch ein, wenn du dich mit voller Geschwindigkeit bewegst. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Muoviti con leggerezza attraverso l'aria e incrementa la tua velocità fino al 150% con il tuo Aqua Mount personale! La velocità aumenta automaticamente quando ci si sposta a tutta velocità. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Nada cómodamente por los aires e incrementa tu velocidad al 150% con tu Aqua Mount personal!  El incremento de tu velocidad entrará en marcha automáticamente cuando vayas a máxima velocidad. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">泳ぐように楽に、あなたのアクアマウントでスピードを150%までブーストさせよう！フルスピードでの走行時は自動的にスピードはブーストします。\n移動速度アップ：◆◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆\nLMO（ロコモーション）はポータブルアイテムです。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Swim effortlessly through the air and boost your speed to 150% with your personal Aqua Mount! Your speed boost will automatically engage when moving at full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Swim effortlessly through the air and boost your speed to 150% with your personal Aqua Mount! Your speed boost will automatically engage when moving at full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>