<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cowboy Boots</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bottes de Cowboy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Cowboy-Stiefel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stivali da Cowboy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Botas de Vaquero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_Feet_WesternBoots</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_Feet_WesternBoots</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Male01_Feet_WesternBoots</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_Feet_WesternBoots</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_Feet_WesternBoots</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cowboy Boots</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Yehaw cowboy! Keep your feet protected from all the critters roamin around outside. And with them shiny spurs your horse'll be riding like the wind. Just watch out no one has gone and put a snake in them. That would be mighty rough! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Yihaa cowboy ! Garde tes pieds à l'abri de toutes ces créatures errantes dehors. Et avec ces éperons tout neufs, ton cheval cavalera comme le vent. Fais juste attention que personne n'ait mis de serpent à l'intérieur. Ça pourraît ne pas être joli à voir ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Yeah Cowboy! Bring Deine Füße in Sicherheit vor dem Getier, das da so kreucht und fleucht. Und mit den glänzenden Sporen wird Dein Pferd rennen wie der Wind. Paß nur auf, daß Dir niemand eine Klapperschlange in den Stiefel gelegt hat. Das wäre ein wenig unangenehm. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Yehaw cowboy! Proteggi i tuoi piedi da tutte quelle creature che gironzolano al di fuori. E con quegli speroni scintillanti il tuo cavallo correrà come il vento. Fai solo attenzione che nessuno sia andato a metterci un serpente dentro. Sarebbe veramente sgarbato! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Yehaw vaquero! Mantén tus pies protegidos de las alimañas que hay afuera alrededor. Y con esas brillantes espuelas tu caballo será tan rápido como el viento. Solo mira que nadie meta una serpiente en ellas. ¡Eso podría ser muy rudo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_Feet_WesternBoots [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_Feet_WesternBoots [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Male01_Feet_WesternBoots [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_Feet_WesternBoots [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_Feet_WesternBoots [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Yehaw cowboy! Keep your feet protected from all the critters roamin around outside. And with them shiny spurs your horse'll be riding like the wind. Just watch out no one has gone and put a snake in them. That would be mighty rough! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>