<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A force to be reckoned with.  The Robolon 6 model seems to have advanced intelligence matrices whilst being a heavyweight brawler.  Built to protect and to serve.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une force à prendre en compte. Le Robolon 6 semble pourvu de matrices intelligentes avancées tout en étant un bagarreur poids lourd. Conçu pour protéger et servir. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nicht zu unterschätzen: Das Model des Robolon 6 scheint über fortgeschrittene Intelligenzroutinen zu verfügen, ist aber gleichzeitig auch ein Schwergewichtsausteiler. Als Freund und Helfer gebaut. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una potenza con cui fare i conti. Il modello Robolon 6 sembra dotato di matrici di intelligenza avanzata pur essendo un pesante attaccabrighe. Costruito per proteggere e servire.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una virtud a tener en cuenta. El Robolon 6 parece tener una inteligencia avanzada, al tiempo que es un luchador peso pesado.  Nacido para proteger y servir.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Robolon 6には重量感がありながら最新の人工知能マトリクスがあり、あなたを守るために作られた強力なロボットです。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">막강한 존재입니다. 로보론 6 모델은 중량의 싸움꾼임과 동시에 고급 지능 매트릭스를 보유하고 있습니다. 봉사와 보호를 위해 제작되었습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A force to be reckoned with.  The Robolon 6 model seems to have advanced intelligence matrices whilst being a heavyweight brawler.  Built to protect and to serve.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">一股不可忽視的力量。Robolon 6似乎擁有進階智慧程式，並屬於重量級戰士。專為服務和保護你而造。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">一股不可忽視的力量。Robolon 6似乎擁有進階智慧程式，並屬於重量級戰士。專為服務和保護你而造。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A force to be reckoned with.  The Robolon 6 model seems to have advanced intelligence matrices whilst being a heavyweight brawler.  Built to protect and to serve.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Robolon 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Robolon 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Robolon 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Robolon 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Robolon 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Robolon 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">로보론 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Robolon 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Robolon 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Robolon 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Robolon 6</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>