<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Palace of the Seven Winds Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Palais des sept vents – Club-house</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Palast der sieben Winde – Clubhaus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Palazzo dei sette venti – Sedi di club</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Palacio de los Siete Vientos – Sedes de clubes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Palace of the Seven Winds Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Palace of the Seven Winds Clubhouse</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Reign over your own celestial paradise with the Palace of the Seven Winds! Exert your influence over the heavens themselves to alter time,  break free of your earthly shackles and take to the skies, lounge in your own personal harem-style apartments, have wishes granted by your personal genie, unlock rewards and much more! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Régnez sur votre propre paradis céleste avec le palais des sept vents ! Exercez votre influence sur les cieux pour altérer le temps, vous libérer de vos entraves terrestres et parcourir le firmament, vous détendre dans vos appartements personnels de style harem, voir vos souhaits exaucés par votre génie personnel, déverrouiller des récompenses et bien plus encore ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Regieren Sie über Ihr eigenes himmlisches Paradies im Palast der sieben Winde! Machen Sie Ihren Einfluss über den Himmel selbst gelten, um die Zeit zu verändern, die Fesseln der Erde abzuschütteln und sich in den Himmel zu erheben, in ihren eigenen, individuell eingerichteten Appartments im Harem-Stil relaxen und sich ihre Wünsche von Ihrem persönlichen Flaschengeist erfüllen lassen, Belohnungen freischalten und noch vieles mehr! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Domina un paradiso celeste dal Palazzo dei sette venti! Potrai esercitare la tua autorità sui cieli per alterare il tempo, liberarti dai vincoli terreni ed esplorare i cieli, oziare in stanze arredate come harem, esaudire ogni tuo desiderio per mano di un genio personale, sbloccare premi e molto altro ancora! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Reina en tu propio paraíso celestial con el Palacio de los Siete Vientos! Ejerce tu influencia sobre los cielos para alterar el tiempo, liberarte de tus grilletes terrenales y elevarte hasta el cielo, disfrutar en tus apartamentos personales al estilo del más puro harén, hacer que tu genio personal cumpla tus deseos, liberar recompensas, ¡y mucho más! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Reign over your own celestial paradise with the Palace of the Seven Winds! Exert your influence over the heavens themselves to alter time,  break free of your earthly shackles and take to the skies, lounge in your own personal harem-style apartments, have wishes granted by your personal genie, unlock rewards and much more! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Reign over your own celestial paradise with the Palace of the Seven Winds! Exert your influence over the heavens themselves to alter time,  break free of your earthly shackles and take to the skies, lounge in your own personal harem-style apartments, have wishes granted by your personal genie, unlock rewards and much more! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>