<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Desert Haven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Oasis du désert</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wüstenoase</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Rifugio del deserto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Remanso del desierto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Desert Haven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사막의 안식처</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Desert Haven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">沙漠度假村</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">沙漠度假村</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Desert Haven</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take a minute and unwind at the charming Desert Haven clubhouse. Catch a couple sun-rays poolside while socialising with friends or meeting new ones. Take a nap beneath the cabanas or even catch a fireside chat next to the bonfires. The Desert Haven space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Prenez une minute pour profiter du charmant club-house de l'Oasis du désert. Prenez le soleil au bord de la piscine tout en discutant avec vos amis ou en faisant de nouvelles connaissances. Faites une sieste à l'ombre des cabines puis, la nuit tombée, allez vous réchauffer au coin du feu en bonne compagnie. Dans l'espace Oasis du désert, tout le monde est toujours le bienvenu. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nimm dir eine Minute Zeit und entspanne dich im bezaubernden Klubhaus der Wüstenoase. Lass dich am Pool von ein paar Sonnenstrahlen kitzeln, während du dich mit alten Freunden triffst oder neue findest. Mach in den Pavillons ein Nickerchen oder halte einen Plausch am Lagerfeuer. Der "Wüstenoase"-Bereich ist ein Klubhaus, das alle einlädt, einzutreten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fermati un minuto e rilassati nel magico circolo del Rifugio del deserto. Prendi un po' di sole ai bordi della piscina mentre socializzi con gli amici, o te ne fai di nuovi. Schiaccia un pisolino dentro ai gazebo da spiaggia, o fai quattro chiacchiere vicino ai falò. Il Rifugio del deserto è un circolo dove chiunque è ben accetto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tómate un minuto y relájate en el encantador club Remanso del desierto. Atrapa rayos de sol junto a la piscina mientras charlas con los amigos o conoces otros nuevos. Echa una siesta entre las cabañas o conversa tranquilamente junto a una chimenea. El Remanso del desierto es un club al que todos están invitados. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Take a minute and unwind at the charming Desert Haven clubhouse. Catch a couple sun-rays poolside while socialising with friends or meeting new ones. Take a nap beneath the cabanas or even catch a fireside chat next to the bonfires. The Desert Haven space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">매혹적인 사막의 안식처 클럽하우스에서 잠시 쉬어 가십시오. 오래된, 혹은 새로운 친구들과 이야기하며 수영장 옆에서 햇빛을 쬐거나, 그늘 아래서 낮잠을 잘 수도 있습니다. 모두가 초대된 사막 안식처에서 모닥불을 만들고 즐거운 시간을 보내세요. 
※주의: 클럽하우스에 입장하려면 먼저 클럽을 구매해야 합니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Take a minute and unwind at the charming Desert Haven clubhouse. Catch a couple sun-rays poolside while socialising with friends or meeting new ones. Take a nap beneath the cabanas or even catch a fireside chat next to the bonfires. The Desert Haven space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. ※Please note, in order to access the clubhouse you will need to have purchased the Club Slot.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">抽點時間在迷人的沙漠度假村俱樂部裡放鬆休息一下。你可在池畔曬曬太陽，跟好友交流或認識新朋友。在小屋中午睡或在營火旁聊天。沙漠度假村空間是一個歡迎任何人加入的聯盟俱樂部。 ※請注意，要使用聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">抽點時間在迷人的沙漠度假村俱樂部裡放鬆休息一下。你可在池畔曬曬太陽，跟好友交流或認識新朋友。在小屋中午睡或在營火旁聊天。沙漠度假村空間是一個歡迎任何人加入的聯盟俱樂部。 ※請注意，要使用聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Take a minute and unwind at the charming Desert Haven clubhouse. Catch a couple sun-rays poolside while socializing with friends or meeting new ones. Take a nap beneath the cabanas or even catch a fireside chat next to the bonfires. The Desert Haven space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>