<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Raven House Furniture Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Corbeau Maison paquet de meubles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rabehaus Möbel-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Casa Corvino pacchetto mobili</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Casa Cuervo paquete de muebles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">家庭用家具のカラスのパッケージ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">가정용 가구 까마귀의 패키지</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Raven House Furniture Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">家家具乌鸦包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">家家具乌鸦包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Raven House Furniture Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A loyal banner-man of House Dumont should own all of the finely crafted furniture pertaining to that house. It's basic respect. Or you just like the color palette! Includes House Dumont Throne, House Dumont Ottoman, House Dumont Circular Coffee Table, House Dumont Rectangular Coffee Table, House Dumont Grand Vase, House Dumont Daybed, House Dumont King Bed, House Dumont Grand Chair, House Dumont Chair, House Dumont Loveseat, House Dumont  Grand Dining Chair, House Dumont Dining Chair, House Dumont Wardrobe, and House Dumont Shield.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un fidèle porte-bannière de la Maison Dumont devrait posséder tous les meubles de belle facture se rapportant à cette maison. C'est le respect fondamental. Ou vous aimez tout simplement la palette de couleurs! Maison Dumont Trône, Maison Dumont pouf, Maison Dumont table à café circulaire, Maison Dumont table à café rectangulaire, Maison Dumont grande vase, Maison Dumont Méridienne, Maison Dumont roi lit, Maison Dumont chaise grande, Maison Dumont chaise, Maison Dumont petit canapé, Maison Dumont chaise dinante, Grand
Maison Dumont chaise dinante, Maison Dumont Armoire, et Maison Dumont Bouclier.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein treuer Bannerträger des Hauses Dumont sollten alle Möbel, schön gemacht im Zusammenhang mit diesem Haus. Dies ist der grundlegende Respekt. Liebe oder einfach nur die Farbe! Haus Dumont Thron, Haus Dumont Ottomane, Haus Dumont kreisförmigen Couchtisch, Haus Dumont rechteckiger Couchtisch, Haus Dumont große Vase, Haus Dumont Schlafcouch, Haus Dumont Königs Bett, Haus Dumont großartigen Stuhl, Haus Dumont Stuhl, Haus Dumont kleines Sofa, Haus Dumont großen Speisesaal Stuhl, Haus Dumont Speisesaal Stuhl, Haus Dumont Schrank, und Haus Dumont Wappenschild.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un fedele alfiere della Dumont casa dovrebbe avere tutti i mobili, ben fatto appartenenti a questa casa. Questo è il rispetto fondamentale. O semplicemente ama il colore! Casa Dumont Trono, Casa Dumont pouf, Casa Dumont circolare tavolino, Casa Dumont tavolino rettangolare, Casa Dumont grande vaso, Casa Dumont divanoletto, Casa Dumont letto del re, Casa Dumont grande sedia, Casa Dumont sedia, Casa Dumont piccolo divano, Casa Dumont gran pranzo sedia, Casa Dumont pranzo sedia, Casa Dumont armadio, e Casa Dumont scudo.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un fiel estandarte de la Casa Dumont deben tener todos los muebles, muy bien hecho concernientes a esta casa. Este es el aspecto fundamental. O me encanta el color! Casa Dumont Trono, Casa Dumont otomana, Casa Dumont mesa de café circular, Casa Dumont mesa de café rectangular, Casa Dumont de gran jarrón, Casa Dumont sofá cama, Casa Dumont la cama del rey, Casa Dumont gran silla, Casa Dumont silla, Casa Dumont pequeño sofá, Casa Dumont gran silla de comedor, Casa Dumont silla de comedor, Casa Dumont armario, y Casa Dumont escudo.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ハウスデュモンの忠実なバナー男はその家に関連する精巧な家具のすべてを所有する必要があります。これは、基本的な敬意です。または、カラーパレットを単に好きです！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">하우스 뒤몽의 충성도 배너 - 사람이 그 집에 관련된 잘게 만들어진 가구를 모두 소유해야합니다. 그것은 기본 예의입니다. 또는 색상 팔레트를 똑같아![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A loyal banner-man of House Dumont should own all of the finely crafted furniture pertaining to that house. It's basic respect. Or you just like the color palette! Includes House Dumont Throne, House Dumont Ottoman, House Dumont Circular Coffee Table, House Dumont Rectangular Coffee Table, House Dumont Grand Vase, House Dumont Daybed, House Dumont King Bed, House Dumont Grand Chair, House Dumont Chair, House Dumont Loveseat, House Dumont  Grand Dining Chair, House Dumont Dining Chair, House Dumont Wardrobe, and House Dumont Shield.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">一位忠诚的旗帜内务杜蒙人应该拥有的所有有关那家精心制作的家具。这是基本的尊重。或者你只是想调色板！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">一位忠诚的旗帜内务杜蒙人应该拥有的所有有关那家精心制作的家具。这是基本的尊重。或者你只是想调色板！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A loyal banner-man of House Dumont should own all of the finely crafted furniture pertaining to that house. It's basic respect. Or you just like the color palette! Includes House Dumont Throne, House Dumont Ottoman, House Dumont Circular Coffee Table, House Dumont Rectangular Coffee Table, House Dumont Grand Vase, House Dumont Daybed, House Dumont King Bed, House Dumont Grand Chair, House Dumont Chair, House Dumont Loveseat, House Dumont  Grand Dining Chair, House Dumont Dining Chair, House Dumont Wardrobe, and House Dumont Shield.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>