<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Weapon Pad – Death Ray </LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plateforme d'arme – Rayon de la mort</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Waffenpad – Todesstrahl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pedana armi - Raggio della morte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Panel de armas - Rayo mortal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Weapon Pad – Death Ray </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Place this item in your MiniBots Training Facility to allow Death Rays to be equipped. Anyone who owns the Death Ray hand item can equip the Death Ray at this pad during a multiplayer game. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Placez cet élément dans votre centre d'entraînement MiniBots pour qu'il soit possible de s'équiper avec les rayons de la mort. N'importe qui peut s'équiper avec le rayon de la mort de cette plateforme pendant une partie multijoueur s'il possède l'élément de main rayon de la mort. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Platzieren Sie dieses Objekt in Ihre MiniBots-Trainingsanlage, damit Todesstrahl damit ausgestattet werden kann. Jeder der das Todesstrahl-Handobjekt besitzt, kann das Todesstrahl in diesem Pad in einem Multiplayer-Spiel bestücken. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Colloca questo elemento nella struttura di addestramento Minibot per consentire l'equipaggiamento con Raggio della morte. Chiunque possieda l'elemento Raggio della morte può dotarsene in questa pedana durante una partita in modalità multigiocatore. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Coloca este artículo en tus instalaciones de entrenamiento de MiniBots para permitir que los Rayos mortales estén equipados. Cualquier propietario del artículo de mano Rayo mortal puede equipar el Rayo mortal en este panel durante una partida para varios jugadores. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Place this item in your MiniBots Training Facility to allow Death Rays to be equipped. Anyone who owns the Death Ray hand item can equip the Death Ray at this pad during a multiplayer game. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>