<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nebulon Storage Backpack (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sac à dos de stockage de nébulons (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rucksack zur Speicherung von Nebulon  (männliche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Zaino per lo stoccaggio di nebulon (per uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mochila de almacenamiento de Nebulón (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ネブロン・ストレージ・パック（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Nebulon Storage Backpack (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Nebulon Storage Backpack (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">For those that need a lot of Nebulon on the go, this backpack-style storage unit can safely contain a sizeable amount of compressed Nebulon.  This device has a purification effect, effectively increasing all Nebulon gains gathered from defeated enemies in Novus Prime by 10%.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour ceux qui ont besoin de beaucoup de nébulons en chemin, ce style d'unité de sac à dos de stockage peut contenir en toute sécurité une importante quantité de nébulons. Ce dispositif a un effet de purification, ce qui augmente tous les gains en nébulons recueillies auprès des ennemis vaincus à Novus Prime de 10%.   [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jenen, die unterwegs viel Nebulon benötigen, bietet diese rucksackähnliche Speichereinheit die Möglichkeit, sicher eine beträchtliche Menge an komprimierten Nebulon zu speichern. Dieses Gerät verfügt außerdem über einen Reinigungseffekt, der die Menge an Nebulon, die man von besiegten Feinden erhält, effektiv um 10% erhöht.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa unità per lo stoccaggio di nebulon portatile può contenere in tutta sicurezza una consistente quantità di energia nebulon compressa.  Questo dispositivo ha un effetto purificante, che incrementa la quantità di nebulon accumulata dai nemici sconfitti in Novus Prime del 10%.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Para todo aquel que necesite Nebulón para llevar, esta unidad de almacenamiento con forma de mochila puede contener de forma segura una cantidad considerable de Nebulón compreso.  Este dispositivo tiene un efecto de purificación, incrementado efectivamente todas las ganancias de Nebulón de los enemigos derrotados en Novus Prime en un 10%.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">移動中にたくさんのネブロンを必要とする人にとって、このリュックサックスタイルのストレージユニットは、かなりの量の圧縮されたネブロンを安全に格納することが出来ます。このデバイスには浄化作用があり、ノーバス・プライムで倒した敵から回収したネブロンの量を効率的に10％増加させます。    [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">For those that need a lot of Nebulon on the go, this backpack-style storage unit can safely contain a sizeable amount of compressed Nebulon.  This device has a purification effect, effectively increasing all Nebulon gains gathered from defeated enemies in Novus Prime by 10%.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">For those that need a lot of Nebulon on the go, this backpack-style storage unit can safely contain a sizeable amount of compressed Nebulon.  This device has a purification effect, effectively increasing all Nebulon gains gathered from defeated enemies in Novus Prime by 10%.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>