<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Henry Jones Sr. Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble costume Henry Jones Sr.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Henry Jones Sr.-Outfit-Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Costume Henry Jones Senior Pacchetto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de Henry Jones Sr. Conjunto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Henry Jones Sr. Costume Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">(Bundle) I hadn't spoken to my son in what seemed like many lifetimes. As I sat back in my chair, I looked over my journal - inside was the work of as many lifetimes collected on the simple paper pages. Scribbles, puzzles, codes, notes - every little thing I could have conceived that might one day lead me to that prize I had been searching for. So deeply involved in thought, I didn't notice the thugs who had snuck their way into my study. All it took was a single blow, and the next thing I knew my surroundings were suddenly that of a castle. Glad I had purchased my Henry Jones Sr avatar outfit so I would be dressed for the occasion. Includes Henry Jones Sr. Costume, Hat and Hair. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">(Ensemble) Je n'avais parlé à mon fils depuis ce qui me semblait une éternité. Assis sur ma chaise, je regardai mon journal, le travail de toute une vie ramassé sur de simples feuilles de papier. Des gribouillis, des énigmes, des codes, des notes… Tout ce que j'avais bien pu concevoir et qui mènerait peut-être un jour à la récompense que je recherchais. J'étais si engagé dans mes pensées que je n'ai pas entendu les voyous se faufiler dans mon bureau. Il n'a fallu qu'un coup, et l'instant d'après je me suis retrouvé dans un château. Heureusement, j'avais acheté ma tenue d'Henry Jones Sr, ce qui était approprié pour l'occasion. Comprend le costume, le chapeau et les cheveux d'Henry Jones Sr. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">(Pack) Ich hatte seit einer Ewigkeit nicht mehr mit meinem Sohn gesprochen. Ich lehnte mich in meinem Stuhl zurück und betrachtete mein Tagebuch. Es enthielt die Arbeit einer solchen Ewigkeit auf einfachen Papierseiten. Kritzeleien, Rätsel, Codes, Notizen, kurz: alles, was mir auf der Suche nach der Trophäe, die ich mein Leben lang suchte, helfen könnte. Ich war so in Gedanken versunken, dass ich die Schläger nicht bemerkte, die sich in mein Arbeitszimmer schlichen. Ein einziger Schlag, und ich fand mich in einer Burg wieder. Gott sei Dank habe ich das Henry-Jones-Sr-Avatar-Outfit erworben, um für die Gelegenheit angemessen gekleidet zu sein. Beinhaltet die Henry Jones Sr.-Kleidung, Hut &amp; Frisur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">(Pacchetto) Non parlavo con mio figlio ormai da diverse vite. Seduto nella mia poltrona, esaminavo il mio diario - dentro al quale si trovava il lavoro di altrettante vite collezionate sulle pagine di carta. Scarabocchi, rompicapi, codici, appunti - qualsiasi cosa che forse un giorno avrebbe potuto condurmi a quel premio che cercavo. Ero così assorto nel pensiero, che non mi accorsi dei tipi loschi che si erano introdotti nel mio studio. Ci volle un colpo soltanto, e all'improvviso mi risvegliai in un castello. Fortunatamente avevo comprato il completo avatar di Henry Jones Sr, così ero vestito per l'occasione. Include Costume, Cappello e Capelli da Henry Jones Senior. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">(Conjunto) Hace años que no me hablo con mi hijo. Me siento en el sillón y reviso mi diario, una vida dedicada al trabajo de recolectar datos en simples hojas de papel. Garabatos, puzles, códigos, notas… Todo lo que se me ha podido ocurrir que algún día me pudiese servir para conseguir el tan preciado premio que ando buscando. Ando tan ensimismado que no me entero de que dos thugs han entrado en mi estudio. Un simple golpe y cuando me despierto me encuentro secuestrado en un castillo. Me alegro de haber comprado el traje avatar de Henry Jones Sr., por lo menos estoy vestido para la ocasión. Incluye el traje, el sombrero y el pelo de Henry Jones Sr. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">(Bundle) I hadn't spoken to my son in what seemed like many lifetimes. As I sat back in my chair, I looked over my journal - inside was the work of as many lifetimes collected on the simple paper pages. Scribbles, puzzles, codes, notes - every little thing I could have conceived that might one day lead me to that prize I had been searching for. So deeply involved in thought, I didn't notice the thugs who had snuck their way into my study. All it took was a single blow, and the next thing I knew my surroundings were suddenly that of a castle. Glad I had purchased my Henry Jones Sr avatar outfit so I would be dressed for the occasion. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>