<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Elegant Table with Chairs</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Table élégante avec chaises</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eleganter Tisch mit Stühlen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Elegante tavolo con sedie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Elegante mesa con sillas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Elegant Table with Chairs</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A simple but elegant table with four chairs. Great for coffee with a friend, a business meeting, or an intimate rendezvous with someone special. This is an interactive active object item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une table simple mais élégante avec quatre chaises. Parfaite pour un café avec un ami, un rendez-vous professionnel, ou un moment intime avec quelqu'un de particulier. Il s'agit d'un objet actif interactif. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein einfacher, jedoch eleganter Tisch mit vier Stühlen. Gut geeignet für den Nachmittagskaffee mit Freunden, eine Geschäftsbesprechung oder ein intimes Rendezvous mit jemand Besonderem. Dies ist ein interaktiver, aktiver Gegenstand. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un tavolo semplice ed elegante con quattro sedie. Perfetto per prendere un caffè con un amico, per un incontro d'affari o per un appuntamento galante con una persona speciale. Questo è un oggetto attivo interattivo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una simple pero elegante mesa con cuatro sillas. Perfecta para un café con un amigo, una reunión de negocios o una cita íntima con alguien especial. Es un artículo-objeto interactivo activo.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A simple but elegant table with four chairs. Great for coffee with a friend, a business meeting, or an intimate rendezvous with someone special. This is an interactive active object item. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">sit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">S'asseoir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sitzen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Siedi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sentarse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>