<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - On The Fence Skirt - Black (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Jupe On The Fence - Noire (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - On The Fence Rock - Schwarz (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - On The Fence Gonna - Nero (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - On The Fence Falda - Negro (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong has recently partnered with Alexandra Spencer on a capsule collection that reflects her jet-set lifestyle. This modern denim mini is a sought after look on both coasts for its wrap-over design accented with faux leather trim. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong s'est associé récemment à Alexandra Spencer pour créer une collection capsule reflétant son mode de vie « jet-set ». Cette minijupe moderne en denim confère un look convoité sur les deux côtes pour son design enroulé accentué par des ornements en faux cuir. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong hat sich mit Alexandra Spencer zusammengetan, um eine Kollektion zu entwickeln, die speziell auf ihren mobilen Lifestyle zugeschnitten ist. Dieser modisch kurze Jeans-Wickelrock mit Verzierungen aus Lederimitat ist ein gutes Beispiel für den neuen Look dieser Kollektion. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong ha recentemente realizzato in collaborazione con Alexandra Spencer  una collezione di articoli intramontabili che riflettono il suo stile di vita da jet-set. Questa moderna minigonna di jeans offre un look ricercato grazie al suo design a portafoglio caratterizzato da rifiniture in finta pelle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong se ha asociado recientemente con Alexandra Spencer para una colección exclusiva que refleja su modo de vida de alto standing. Esta moderna minifalda en tela vaquera es lo más deseado de una costa a otra, por su diseño superpuesto enfatizado con adornos en falso cuero. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>