<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Trick or Treatin' Candy Cauldron (for Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Marmite à Bonbons d'Halloween (pour Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Trick-or-Treat-Bonbonkessel (für Frauen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Calderone con caramelle Dolcetto o Scherzetto (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Caldero de chucherías Truco o trato (para mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사탕 줄래, 골탕 먹을래 캔디 가마솥 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Trick or Treatin' Candy Cauldron (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">不給糖就搗蛋糖罐(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">不給糖就搗蛋糖罐(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Trick or Treatin' Candy Cauldron (for Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Trick or Treating is a tradition in PlayStation®Home too ya' know. This handy candy receptacle is just what your friends need to dress up, have a swell time and fill up on spooky sweets. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La tournée déguisée est une tradition à PlayStation®Home aussi vous savez. Cette marmite à bonbons est exactement ce dont vos amis ont besoin pour sortir, passer du bon temps et revenir chargés de sucreries macabres. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Trick-or-Treat ist auch in PlayStation®Home eine Tradition. Dieser praktische Behälter ist genau das Richtige für deine Freunde, damit sie Süßigkeiten sammeln und Halloween so richtig genießen können. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dolcetto o scherzetto è una tradizione anche qui su PlayStation®Home. Questo contenitore per caramelle è proprio quello di cui hanno bisogno i tuoi amici per mascherarsi, divertirsi e fare il pieno di dolcetti spaventosi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Truco o trato es una tradición en muchos lugares. Este útil receptáculo para las chucherías es justo lo que tus amigos necesitan para disfrazarse, divertirse como el que más y empacharse con dulces aterradores. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사탕 줄래, 골탕 먹을래는 아시는 것처럼 PlayStation®Home에서도 전통의 하나랍니다. 이처럼 편리한 캔디 담는 용기는 바로 당신의 친구들이 의상을 차려입고 멋진 시간을 보내며. 으스스한 사탕을 담아 올 때 딱 필요하지요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Trick or Treating is a tradition in PlayStation®Home too ya' know. This handy candy receptacle is just what your friends need to dress up, have a swell time and fill up on spooky sweets. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">其實PlayStation®Home也有「不給糖就搗蛋」的習俗哦。您的朋友只需要這個好用的糖果容器，就能穿特別服裝玩個痛快，同時裝滿一大堆奇奇怪怪的糖果。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">其實PlayStation®Home也有「不給糖就搗蛋」的習俗哦。您的朋友只需要這個好用的糖果容器，就能穿特別服裝玩個痛快，同時裝滿一大堆奇奇怪怪的糖果。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Trick or Treating is a tradition in PlayStation®Home too ya' know. This handy candy receptacle is just what your friends need to dress up, have a swell time and fill up on spooky sweets. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>