<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Clone Helmet (pedestal) 3 Gree</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Casque de clone (socle) 3 Gree</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Klon-Helm (Sockel) 3 Gree</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Elmo Clone (piedistallo) 3 Gree</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Casco de clon (pedestal) 3 Gree</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Clone Helmet (pedestal) 3 Gree</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Travelling through the cities of Kamino, I felt myself lost in a sea of familiarity. Aside from the striking appearance of the odd Kaminoan, it had become quite apparent I was standing amongst the next wave that will come to the defense of the Republic. They all looked identical, and I pondered how sad it was that though they may modify their look with a simple haircut or some other affectation, they still will don identical uniforms dedicated to destroying any semblance of identity they had created. But one had struck my eye. I watched him as he put on his helmet, and realized he had decorated it. The deep green and silver was like nothing I had seen, and I smiled to myself. It would seem no two stories are as identical as I might think. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En parcourant les villes de Kamino, je me sentis perdu dans une mer familière. A part l'aspect des étranges Kaminoans, il était évident que j'étais parmi la nouvelle vague des défenseurs de la République. Ils étaient tous identiques, et je trouvais bien triste que bien qu'ils puissent modifier leur look par la coiffure ou autre chose, ils portaient tous un même uniforme visant à détruire tout semblant d'identité. Mais l'un d'eux frappa mon regard. Je le regardais mettre son casque et je vis qu'il l'avait décoré. Le vert et l'argent du casque ne ressemblaient à rien de ce que j'avais vu et je souris intérieurement. Après tout, il n'y avait donc peut-être pas deux histoires semblables. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Als ich durch die Städte von Kamino reiste, fühlte ich mich verloren in einem Meer der Vertrautheit. Außer dem beeindruckenden Aussehen der Kaminoaner wurde mir auch immer klarer, dass ich inmitten der nächsten Welle stand, die die Republik verteidigen würde. Sie sahen alle gleich aus, und ich dachte, wie traurig es war, dass sie ihr Aussehen mit einer Frisur verändern konnten, aber identische Uniformen anziehen würden, um jegliche Identität, die sie erschaffen hatten, zu zerstören. Einer war mir aufgefallen. Ich sah zu, wie er seinen Helm anzog und sah, dass er ihn geschmückt hatte. Das tiefe Grün und Silber fiel auf. Ich lächelte. Es schien, als seien sie doch nicht so identisch, wie ich gedacht hatte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tra le città di Kamino, mi sentii come in un mare di familiarità. A parte l'aspetto sorprendendo di qualche kaminoano, notavo di essere circondato dalla prossima ondata che presto sarebbe giunta in aiuto della Repubblica. Erano tutti identici d'aspetto, e io pensai a quanto fosse triste il fatto che, anche se riuscivano a modificare il loro look con un taglio di capelli o altro, essi indossavano uniformi identiche progettate per distruggere qualsiasi parvenza di individualità. Ma uno di loro catturò la mia attenzione. Lo osservai mentre si metteva l'elmo e mi resi conto che lo aveva decorato. Le strisce blu spiccavano nella folla, e mi venne da sorridere. Sembra che non esistano due storie identiche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Viajando a través de las ciudades de Kamino, me encontré perdido en un mar de familiaridad. Aparte del chocante aspecto de los kaminoanos, había quedado bastante claro que estaba entre el siguiente ejército que acudiría a defender la República. Todos parecían idénticos, y me pareció triste que aunque pudieran modificar su aspecto con un simple corte de pelo u otra característica, vestirían uniformes idénticos que destruirían cualquier rasgo de identidad que hubieran creado. Pero uno me llamó la atención. Le había visto ponerse el casco y vi que lo había decorado. Las rayas azules resaltaban con fuerza, y sonreí para mí mismo. Se ve que no hay dos historias tan idénticas como yo podría pensar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Travelling through the cities of Kamino, I felt myself lost in a sea of familiarity. Aside from the striking appearance of the odd Kaminoan, it had become quite apparent I was standing amongst the next wave that will come to the defense of the Republic. They all looked identical, and I pondered how sad it was that though they may modify their look with a simple haircut or some other affectation, they still will don identical uniforms dedicated to destroying any semblance of identity they had created. But one had struck my eye. I watched him as he put on his helmet, and realized he had decorated it. The deep green and silver was like nothing I had seen, and I smiled to myself. It would seem no two stories are as identical as I might think. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>