<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gograk’s Light Up Floor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sol éclairé de Gograk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gograk’s Leuchtboden</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pavimento Luminoso Gograk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Suelo de luces Gograk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴグラックの光るフロア</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gograk’s Light Up Floor</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This dazzling light up piece comes from the best in Alien technology. It adds the perfect bit of flair to any Mad Scientist laboratory. Check out the Mad Scientist Starter Kit for an exclusive item!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cet éblouissant élément éclairé est à la pointe de la technologie extraterrestre. Ça apporte une touche de classe à tout laboratoire de Savant Fou. Allez voir le kit du débutant Savant Fou pour découvrir l'élément exclusif !  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese blendende Beleuchtung ist das Beste vom Besten der Alientechnologie. Es verleiht dem Labor des Verrückten Wissenschaftlers den besonderen Touch. Einen exklusiven Artikel findet ihr im Verrückter Wissenschaftler Anfängerset!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo incredibile elemento luminoso è frutto della migliore tecnologia aliena. Crea l'atmosfera giusta per il tuo laboratorio da Scienziato Pazzo. Trova un elemento esclusivo nel Kit Iniziale dello Scienziato Pazzo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este deslumbrante juego de luces tiene la mejor tecnología alienígena. Aporta el tono perfecto a cualquier laboratorio de Científico Loco. ¡Busca el Juego de iniciación de Científico Loco para conseguir un producto exclusivo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">エイリアンの技術の粋を結集して作られたきらびやかに輝く作品。マッドサイエンティストのセンスが加わって完成しました。マッドサイエンティスト スターターキットで限定アイテムをチェックしましょう！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This dazzling light up piece comes from the best in Alien technology. It adds the perfect bit of flair to any Mad Scientist laboratory. Check out the Mad Scientist Starter Kit for an exclusive item!  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>