<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">AT-AT Pilot Suit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Combinaison de pilote TB-TT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">AT-AT-Pilotenanzug</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tuta pilota AT-AT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de piloto AT-AT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">AT-ATパイロット・スーツ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">AT-AT 파일럿 수트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">AT-AT Pilot Suit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">AT-AT駕駛員裝</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">AT-AT駕駛員裝</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">AT-AT Pilot Suit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Selected from hardened combat troopers, AT-AT pilots were specialized soldiers that were trained to pilot the All Terrain Armored Transport.  Their blatant "shock" combat tactics proved too much for the defending Rebels at the great Battle of Hoth.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Choisis parmi les combattants endurcis, les pilotes TB-TT sont des soldats spécialisés entraînés au pilotage de ce transport tout terrain blindé. Leurs tactiques "de choc" ont eu raison des défenseurs Rebelles lors de la grande Bataille de Hoth.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">AT-AT-Piloten werden aus den besten Soldaten ausgewählt und speziell trainiert, um Imperiale Läufer zu steuern. Ihre radikalen "Schock"-Kampftaktiken waren zu viel für die verteidigenden Rebellen in der großen Schlacht von Hoth.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Selezionati fra gli inveterati combattenti, i piloti AT-TA erano soldati specializzati, addestrati per pilotare i veicoli di Trasporto Armato Per Ogni Terreno. Le loro sfrontate tattiche "shock" di combattimento hanno provato troppo i Ribelli durante la difesa nella Battaglia di Hoth.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Seleccionados de entre curtidos soldados de combate, los pilotos AT-AT eran soldados especializados entrenados para pilotar Transportes Blindados Todoterreno. Sus descaradas tácticas de combate “de choque” demostraron ser demasiado para los rebeldes que se defendían en la Gran Batalla de Hoth.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">熟練のコンバット・トルーパーの中から選ばれ、全地形装甲トランスポートの操縦訓練を受けたパイロット。その無防備なショック作戦は、ホスの戦いで防御に回った反乱軍の前にもろくも崩れた。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">강화된 전투 기병에서 선발된 AT-AT 파일럿은 전천후 무장 수송차량을 조정하는 특수 군인입니다. 호스 대전투에서 화려한 전술을 앞세운 이들을 막느라 저항군은 애를 먹었다죠.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Selected from hardened combat troopers, AT-AT pilots were specialized soldiers that were trained to pilot the All Terrain Armored Transport.  Their blatant "shock" combat tactics proved too much for the defending Rebels at the great Battle of Hoth.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">由冷酷的裝甲戰士中選拔而出，AT-AT駕駛員是訓練有素的全地形裝甲運輸駕駛。他們直截了當的〝驚嚇〞式戰略在霍斯戰役中使反抗軍潰不成軍。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">由冷酷的裝甲戰士中選拔而出，AT-AT駕駛員是訓練有素的全地形裝甲運輸駕駛。他們直截了當的〝驚嚇〞式戰略在霍斯戰役中使反抗軍潰不成軍。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Selected from hardened combat troopers, AT-AT pilots were specialized soldiers that were trained to pilot the All Terrain Armored Transport.  Their blatant "shock" combat tactics proved too much for the defending Rebels at the great Battle of Hoth.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>