<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Cruiser Crew Neck Shirt - Golden (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - T-shirt ras-de-cou Cruiser - Doré (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Cruiser Hemd mit Rundhalsauschnitt - Gold (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Cruiser Maglia con scollo tondo - Oro (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Cruiser Camiseta de cuello redondo - Dorado (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Cruiser short sleeve crewneck keeps offers a smooth fit and innovative detailing. Made with engineered yarn dyed raglan jersey with a front colourblocked chest pocket. Includes a chest pockets and a woven label at the side seam. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le t-shirt Cruiser ras de cou à manches courtes offre une coupe fluide et des détails innovants. Fabriqué en jersey raglan tissé-teint élaboré avec une poche poitrine contrastée. Comprend une poche poitrine et une étiquette tissée sur la couture latérale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Cruiser Kurzarmhemd mit Rundhalsausschnitt besticht durch seinen hohen Tragekomfort und innovative Details wie Garnfärbung, Raglanärmel, farblich abgesetzte Brusttasche und Webe-Etikett an der Seitennaht. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La maglia a maniche corte Cruiser con scollo tondo offre un taglio morbido e dettagli innovativi. Realizzata in jersey raglan tinto in filo ingegnerizzato con tasca a tinta unita sul petto. Comprende una tasca sul petto e un'etichetta in tessuto sul lato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La camiseta Cruiser, de cuello redondo y manga corta, ofrece un tacto suave con unos detalles innovadores. Fabricada con tela jersey de hilos teñidos mediante ingeniería, con manga raglán y bolsillo monocolor en el pecho. Incluye bolsillos en pecho y etiqueta cosida en la costura lateral. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>