<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Amaterasu Speakers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Enceintes de l'Amaterasu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Amaterasu-Lautsprecher</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Altavoces Amaterasu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Casse Amaterasu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「LOOT™パラダイス・クルーズ」スピーカー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Amaterasu Speakers</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The great thing about blasting music on a boat is that you don’t have to worry about downstairs neighbors banging on their ceiling. However, we at Loot™ suggest turning it down if something starts banging on the bottom of your Yacht… probably not a good sign.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'avantage de mettre de la musique à fond sur un bateau, c'est qu'on n'a pas à se soucier de voisins du dessous qui tapent au plafond. Mais notre équipe de LOOT™ vous conseille de baisser un peu le son si vous commencez à entendre cogner sous le bateau...peut-être pas bon signe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das gute an lauter Musik auf einem Boot ist, dass keine Leute unter einem wohnen, die an die Decke klopfen. Wenn jedoch irgendetwas von unten an dein Boot klopft, empfiehlt LOOT™, die Musik leiser zu stellen. Denn das ist vermutlich kein gutes Zeichen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lo bueno de poner la música a todo trapo en un barco es que no tienes que preocuparte por que los vecinos de abajo den golpes en el techo. Sin embargo, en LOOT™ te sugerimos que bajes la música si algo empieza a golpear los bajos de tu barco. Puede ser un mal indicio... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La cosa formidabile di una barca è che puoi mettere la musica a palla senza doverti preoccupare dei vicini del piano di sotto. Comunque noi di LOOT™ consigliamo vivamente di abbassare il volume se dovessero provenire dei colpi dal basso... non sarebbe proprio un ottimo segno. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ボートで音楽をガンガンかけても下の階に文句言われなくて済むからいいよね。ただし、私たちLOOT™からのアドバイスなんだけど：ボート自体の下にいるモノに文句言われたら、確かにボリュームを下げた方が良さそう。。。危ないよ？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The great thing about blasting music on a boat is that you don’t have to worry about downstairs neighbors banging on their ceiling. However, we at Loot™ suggest turning it down if something starts banging on the bottom of your Yacht… probably not a good sign.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>