<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Neptune Tank Top - White (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Débardeur Neptune - Blanc (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Neptune Tanktop - Weiß (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Neptune Canottiera - Bianco (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Neptune Camiseta sin mangas - Blanco (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Neptune tank top has a floral printed chest with a mid-stripe printed colorblocked panel and chest pocket. The top is detailed with contrast ribbing at the sleeves and neck, and a garage collection woven label on the sideseam. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le débardeur Neptune comporte un imprimé floral au niveau de la poitrine avec un panneau mi-rayé en blocs de couleur à mi-hauteur et une poche poitrine. Ce débardeur comporte des rayures contrastées aux emmanchures et au col, et une étiquette tissée garage collection au niveau de la couture latérale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Neptune Tanktop besticht durch das Blumenmuster auf der Vorderseite und den auffällig breiten Streifen in kontrastierenden Farben. Mit farblich abgesetzten Säumen am Hals und an den Ärmelöffnungen und einem Stoffetikett der Garage Collection auf der Seitennaht. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La canottiera Neptune presenta una stampa floreale sul petto con una fascia a mezza altezza a tinta unita e taschina sul petto. Presenta dettagli a costine contrastanti sul giromanica e sullo scollo, e un-etichetta in tessuto sulla cucitura laterale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La camiseta Neptune tiene un estampado floral en el pecho, con una amplia franja horizontal en color liso y un bolsillo en el pecho. Con detalle de bordes en cuello y hombros de color en contraste y etiqueta "garage collection" cosida sobre la costura lateral. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>