<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mystic Arcade Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble Arcade mystique</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mystikarkaden-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Sala giochi mistica</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack recreativos místicos</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Mystic Arcadeセット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Mystic Arcade Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mystic Arcade Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take a trip back in time to the lobby of the Mystic Theatre. It's a great place for old-style arcade video games. Visit often and check out the movie marquee for a new '80s-tribute movie title each week. Complete your personal arcade with classics like Frogger, Centipede, Time Pilot, Asteroids, Lunar Lander, Adventure, and more, sold separately. Includes:\n1. Mystic Arcade personal space.\n2. An animated glow-in-the-dark T-shirt exclusive to owners of the Mystic Arcade.\n3. Mystic Arcade Theatre Poster.\n4. Mystic Arcade Garbage Can. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Faites un voyage dans le temps et revenez dans le hall du Cinéma mystique. C’est un endroit idéal pour les jeux vidéo d’arcade à l’ancienne. Visitez-le souvent et découvrez chaque semaine l’annonce d’un nouveau film en hommage aux années 80. Complétez votre arcade personnelle avec des classiques tels que Frogger, Centipede, Time Pilot, Asteroids, Lunar Lander, Adventure, et d’autres (vendus séparément). Comprend :\n1. Espace personnel de Mystic Arcade\n2. T-shirt exclusif brillant dans le noir réservé aux propriétaires de l’Arcade mystique.\n3. Affiche de cinéma Arcade mystique.\n4. Corbeille Arcade mystique. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Reise in der Zeit zurück zur Lobby des Mystikkinos. Sie ist ein toller Ort für altmodische Arcade-Videospiele. Besuche sie oft und sieh in der Filmanzeige für neue Filme der Woche als Hommage an die 80er Jahre nach. Richte deine persönliche Spielhalle mit Frogger, Centipede, Time Pilot, Asteroids, Lunar Lander, Adventure und weiteren einzeln verkauften Spielen ein. Beinhaltet:\n1. Mystic Arcade persönlichen Raum\n2. Ein animiertes und im Dunkeln leuchtendes T-Shirt für Besitzer der Mystikarkaden.\n3. Mystikarkaden-Kinoplakat.\n4. Mystikarkaden-Mülleimer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fai un salto indietro nel tempo e visita l'atrio del Cinema mistico. Un autentico paradiso per gli amanti dei videogiochi arcade. Torna ogni volta che puoi e dai un'occhiata all'insegna per scoprire ogni settimana un nuovo film tributo agli anni 80. Completa la tua personale sala giochi con classici come Frogger, Centipede, Time Pilot, Asteroids, Lunar Lander, Adventure e molti altri, ciascuno venduto separatamente. Contiene:\n1. Spazio personale di Mystic Arcade.\n2. T-shirt animata che si illumina al buio. Un'esclusiva per i proprietari della Sala giochi mistica.\n3. Cinema della "Sala giochi mistica".\n4. Contenitore per rifiuti della "Sala giochi mistica". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Viaja en el tiempo hasta la sala del cine místico, el mejor lugar para disfrutar de las máquinas recreativas clásicas. Visita la sala de cine cada semana para comprobar la película de los años 80 destacada. Completa tus recreativos personales con clásicos como  Frogger, Centipede, Time Pilot, Asteroids, Lunar Lander, Adventure y muchos más que se venden por separado.  Incluye:\n1. Espacio personal de Mystic Arcade.\n2. Una camiseta animada que brilla en la oscuridad exclusiva para los dueños de los recreativos místicos.\n3. Póster del cine de los recreativos místicos.\n4. Cubo de la basura de los recreativos místicos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Mystic Theaterのロビーにタイムトリップしよう。昔スタイルのアーケードビデオゲームのための、巣晴らしい場所だ。頻繁に訪問し、80年代に捧げる毎週の新しい映画を見てみよう。Frogger、Centipede、Time Pilot, Asteroids、 Lunar Lander、Adventureといった別売りのクラシック作品を君のゲームセンターにそろえよう。内容：\nMystic Arcadeパーソナルスペース。\nMystic Arcadeのオーナー専用、暗闇で光るアニメTシャツ。\nMystic Arcade劇場ポスター。\nMystic Arcadeゴミ箱。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Take a trip back in time to the lobby of the Mystic Theatre. It's a great place for old-style arcade video games. Visit often and check out the movie marquee for a new '80s-tribute movie title each week. Complete your personal arcade with classics like Frogger, Centipede, Time Pilot, Asteroids, Lunar Lander, Adventure, and more, sold separately. Includes:\n1. Mystic Arcade personal space.\n2. An animated glow-in-the-dark T-shirt exclusive to owners of the Mystic Arcade.\n3. Mystic Arcade Theatre Poster.\n4. Mystic Arcade Garbage Can. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Take a trip back in time to the lobby of the Mystic Theatre. It's a great place for old-style arcade video games. Visit often and check out the movie marquee for a new '80s-tribute movie title each week. Complete your personal arcade with classics like Frogger, Centipede, Time Pilot, Asteroids, Lunar Lander, Adventure, and more, sold separately. Includes:\n1. Mystic Arcade personal space.\n2. An animated glow-in-the-dark T-shirt exclusive to owners of the Mystic Arcade.\n3. Mystic Arcade Theatre Poster.\n4. Mystic Arcade Garbage Can. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>