<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ion Stream Power Armor (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Armure de puissance à faisceau ionique (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ionenstrom-Powerrüstung (männliche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Armatura alimentata a ioni (per uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Armadura energizada de rayos de ion (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">イオンストリームパワースーツ（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ion Stream Power Armor (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ion Stream Power Armor (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Inspired by the Nebulon Interweave Power Suit, this neck-to-toe mesh bodysuit utilizes a heavily-modified ion core taken from a Bot infiltration drone.  Its designer, Dr. Alan Ames, claims that the kinetic barrier generated by the core can withstand more than ten times the impact force that the best composite armor could possibly handle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Inspirée par l'armure de puissance entrelacée à Nébulon, cette combinaison mécha couvre le porteur des pieds à la tête et utilise un cœur ionique lourdement modifié récupéré d'un drone d'infiltration Bot. Son inventeur, le Dr. Alan Ames, clame que la barrière cinétique générée par le cœur peut supporter plus de dix fois la force d'impact que la meilleure des armures composites peut encaisser. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Inspiriert durch den Nebulon-Poweranzug verwendet dieser Maschen-Ganzkörperanzug einen stark modifizierten Ionenkern, der von einer Bot-Infiltrationsdrone entfernt wurde. Sein Entwickler Dr. Alan Ames behauptet, dass die kinetische Barriere, die vom Kern ausgeht, zehnmal mehr Einschlagskraft aushält, als es die beste Verbundrüstung je täte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ispirata alla Tuta potenziata a filamenti di Nebulon, questa barriera che protegge tutto il corpo sfrutta un nucleo a ioni minuziosamente modificato, estratto da un drone-spia Bot. Il dottor Alan Ames, autore del progetto di quest'armatura, afferma che la barriera cinetica generata dal nucleo può resistere a una sollecitazione dieci volte più forte rispetto a quella sopportata dalla migliore armatura composita. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Inspirados en los Trajes de poder entretejidos Nebulón, este traje de malla del cuello a los pies utiliza un núcleo altamente modificado de ion tomado de un drone de infiltración Robot. Su diseñador, Dr. Alan Ames, clama que la barrera quinética  generada por el núcleo puede soportar diez veces más la fuerza de impacto que la mejor armadura compuesta puede soportar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">首から足のつま先までを覆うボディスーツはボットの侵入無人機から回収されて徹底的に改良されたイオンコアを使用しています。設計者であるアラン・エイメス博士は、コアから発生する速度障壁は、最高峰の複合装甲が耐えうるであろう衝撃力の10倍以上の衝撃に耐えられると主張している。※このアイテムには特別な効果はありません。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* kDesc [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Inspired by the Nebulon Interweave Power Suit, this neck-to-toe mesh bodysuit utilizes a heavily-modified ion core taken from a Bot infiltration drone.  Its designer, Dr. Alan Ames, claims that the kinetic barrier generated by the core can withstand more than ten times the impact force that the best composite armor could possibly handle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* kDesc [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* kDesc [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Inspired by the Nebulon Interweave Power Suit, this neck-to-toe mesh bodysuit utilizes a heavily-modified ion core taken from a Bot infiltration drone.  Its designer, Dr. Alan Ames, claims that the kinetic barrier generated by the core can withstand more than ten times the impact force that the best composite armor could possibly handle. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>