<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cutteridge Estate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Immobilier Cutteridge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Cutteridge-Herrenhaus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Palazzo Cutteridge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mansión Cutteridge</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cutteridge Estate</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Unlock the mysteries of Cutteridge Estate. This elegant Victorian estate is rumored to be the final resting place of many dark and depraved souls. Do you dare to venture into these forsaken halls in search of the secrets which lie within? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Découvrez les mystères du Immobilier Cutteridge. Cette élégante demeure victorienne est répandu pour être le lieu du dernier repos de plusieurs âmessombres et dépravés. Oserez-vous de s'aventurer dans ces salles abandonnées à la recherche des secrets qui se trouvent à l'intérieur? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Entdecken Sie die Geheimnisse des Cutteridge-Herrenhauses. Dieses elegante viktorianische Herrenhaus soll angeblich die letzte Ruhestätte vieler dunkler und verderbter Seelen sein. Wagen Sie sich in diese verlassenen Hallen vor, um die Geheimnisse darin zu entschlüsseln? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scopri i misteri di Palazzo Cutteridge. Si dice che questa elegante magione vittoriana sia l'ultima dimora di molti esseri oscuri e depravati. Hai l'ardire di esplorare queste sale deserte per scoprirne i segreti? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Revela los misterios de la Mansión Cutteridge. Las malas lenguas dicen que esta elegante mansión victoriana es la última morada que depara a muchas almas oscuras y depravadas. ¿Te atreves a aventurarte en estos abandonados pasillos en búsqueda de todos los secretos que éstos encierran? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Unlock the mysteries of Cutteridge Mansion. This elegant Victorian mansion is rumored to be the final resting place of many dark and depraved souls. Do you dare to venture into these forsaken halls in search of the secrets which lie within? [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>