<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Casket Of Doom</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cerceuil de la mort</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schatulle der Verdamnis</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Portagioielli Infernale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cofre de la perdición</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Casket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Casket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Casket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Casket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Casket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Casket Of Doom</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You saved Princess Daphne  from having  the Death Ring placed upon her finger. Now's your chance to make sure it never leaves your sight. Purchase the Casket of Doom before it falls in to the wrong hands! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez empêché que la princesse Daphné n'ait l'anneau de mort placé sur son doigt. C'est maintenant à vous assurer qu'il ne quitte jamais votre surveillance. Acheter le Cercueil de la Mort avant qu'il ne tombe entre de mauvaises mains! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast Prinzessin Daphne vor dem Ring des Todes errettet. Behalte in immer im Auge und bewahre ihn in der Schatulle auf, bevor in ein anderer in die Hände bekommt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai salvato la Principessa Daphne dalla minaccia di avere al dito l'Anello della Morte. Ora hai l'occasione per assicurarti di averlo sempre sott'occhio. Compra il Portagioielli Infernale prima che cada in mani sbagliate! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tú has salvado a la princesa Daphne de tener el anillo de la muerte en su dedo. Ahora es tu oportunidad de asegurarte de nunca perderla de vista. ¡Compra el cofre de la perdición antes de que caiga en las manos equivocadas! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Casket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Casket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Casket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Casket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Casket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You saved Princess Daphne  from having  the Death Ring placed upon her finger. Now's your chance to make sure it never leaves your sight. Purchase the Casket of Doom before it falls in to the wrong hands! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>