<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Shadow Assassin (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Assassin De L'Ombre (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schattenassassine (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Assassino D'Ombra (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Asesina en la Sombra (Mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_141</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_141</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_141</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_141</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_141</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Shadow Assassin (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You aren't just your average secret agent, you come outfitted with a top of the line armour suit that enhances your stamina and strength. The outfit comes with custom animations.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous n'êtes pas un agent secret comme les autres. Vous êtes équipé d'une armure haut de gamme qui améliore votre endurance et votre force. Cette tenue comprend des animations personnalisables.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit diesem Outfit sieht man nicht nur aus wie ein Geheimagent, sondern ist außerdem mit einem Panzeranzug der Spitzenklasse ausgestattet, der Ausdauer und Stärke verbessert. Das Outfit bietet benutzerdefinierte Animationen.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non sei un normale agente segreto, sei vestito con il meglio della linea di armature che migliorano la tua resistenza e la tua forza. L'aspetto prevede animazioni personalizzate.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No eres la agente secreta media, estás equipada con una armadura de última tecnología que mejora tu resistencia y tu fuerza. El conjunto incluye animaciones personalizadas.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_141 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_141 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_141 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_141 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_141 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You aren't just your average secret agent, you come outfitted with a top of the line armor suit that enhances your stamina and strength. The outfit comes with custom animations.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>