<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Valor Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaise Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Valor-Stuhl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sedia Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Silla de Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">椅子 ベイラー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Valor 의자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Valor Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Valor椅子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Valor椅子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Valor Chair</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Valor chair may be lightweight, strong and efficient, but if the Squad Leader catches you sitting around, he may not need the footlocker to store his shoe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette chaise Valor est peut-être légère, résistante et bien conçue, mais si jamais un Chef d'escouade vous trouvait les fesses dessus... il n'aurait peut-être pas besoin de la malle pour ranger ses bottes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser Valor-Stuhl ist zwar leicht, stabil und praktisch, aber wenn Ihr Trupp-Anführer Sie beim Rumsitzen erwischt ... dann landet sein Schuh bestimmt nicht in der Truhe ... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La sedia Valor potrebbe sembrare leggera, resistente ed efficace ma se il leader squadra vi coglie seduti a poltrire... potreste ritrovarvi a "riposare" nella sua scarpiera. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta silla de Valor es ligera, fuerte y eficaz, pero como el líder del escuadrón te pille sentado... no va a necesitar el baúl para guardar las botas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ベイラーの椅子は軽くて丈夫だが、実際に座っているのを分隊長に見つかったら...。常に訓練を怠るな！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Valor의 의자는 가볍고 단단하고 효율적입니다. 그렇지만 앉아서 노는 것을 분대장이 본다면... 생각만 해도 끔찍하군요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This Valor chair may be lightweight, strong, and efficient, but if the Squad Leader catches you sitting around... he may not need the footlocker to store his shoe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這張Valor椅子也許比較輕巧、強靭和高效能，但是如果你在坐著時遭隊長逮住...他也許不再需要拿裝備箱來放鞋子。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這張Valor椅子也許比較輕巧、強靭和高效能，但是如果你在坐著時遭隊長逮住...他也許不再需要拿裝備箱來放鞋子。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This Valor chair may be lightweight, strong, and efficient, but if the Squad Leader catches you sitting around... he may not need the footlocker to store his shoe. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>