<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Dragon's Lair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Dragon's Lair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Drachenhöhle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Tana del Drago</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La Dragon's Lair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Dragon's Lair</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You've conquered the dragon so why not take up his lair as your own? The Dragon's Lair is the perfect place to host your friends, show off your rewards or simply relax with your riches surrounding you. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez vaincu le dragon alors pourquoi ne pas faire de sa tanière la votre? La Tanière du Dragon est l'endroit idéal pour accueillir vos amis, se vanter de ses récompenses ou simplement se détendre entouré de vos richesses. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast den Drachen besiegt, also warum nicht seine Höhle in Besitz nehmen? Die Drachenhöhle ist der perfekte Ort, um Freunde zu empfangen, Deine Preise zu präsentieren, oder einfach nur Deine Reichtümer aufzubewahren. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai sconfitto il drago quindi perché non prendere possesso della sua tana? La Tana del Drago è un posto perfetto per intrattenere gli amici, mettere in mostra  i tuoi riconoscimenti o semplicemente rilassarti con le tue ricchezze che ti circondano. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Has conquistado el dragón por qué no tomar posesión de su guarida como propio? La Dragon's Lair es el lugar perfecto para alojar a sus amigos, mostrar tus recompensas o simplemente relajarse con sus riquezas que le rodea. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You've conquered the dragon so why not take up his lair as your own? The Dragon's Lair is the perfect place to host your friends, show off your rewards or simply relax with your riches surrounding you. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>