<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Sardine Seller's Garb, Top, No Carrying Pole (Pale Blue, Men)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Tenue de poissonnier, haut, sans perche (bleu pâle, homme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Kleidung eines Sardinenverkäufers, Oberteil, ohne Tragestange (hellblau, für Männer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Vestiti da venditore di sardine, parte superiore, senza asta (blu chiaro, da uomo)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Atuendo de vendedor de sardinas, parte superior, sin bastón (azul pálido, hombre)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">鰯売り着物・上・天秤棒なし（薄青・男性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">정어리 장수 기모노, 상의, 천칭 없음(연한 파랑, 남성)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Sardine seller kimino, Top, No pole (Pale blue, Men)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">賣魚和服/上身/沒有天秤棒(淺藍色/男用)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">賣魚和服/上半身/沒有天秤棒(淺藍色/男用)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Sardine Seller's Garb, Top, No Carrying Pole (Pale Blue, Men)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A distinctive style top with the right arm removed, making it easier to move. This type doesn't have a carrying pole slung over the shoulder.\nStylishness: ★★\nDefensive Strength: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un haut de style distinctif sans manche droite, le rendant plus facile pour bouger. Ce modèle n'a pas de perche de transport sur l'épaule.\nStyle : ★★\nDéfense : ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein charakteristisches Oberteil, ohne rechten Ärmel für mehr Bewegungsfreiheit. Bei dieser Version ist keine Tragestange über der Schulter dabei.\nEleganz: ★★\nVerteidigung: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un vestito molto caratteristico a cui è stata rimossa la manica destra per agevolare i moventi di chi lo indossa. Questo tipo non è provvisto di asta da caricare sulle spalle.\nRaffinatezza: ★★\nDifesa: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Prenda de estilo característico sin hombro derecho, para facilitar el movimiento. Este tipo no tiene un bastón colgado del hombro.\nBuen gusto: ★★\nDefensa:  ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">右腕を抜いた、動きやすいスタイルが特徴の着物のトップス。天秤棒を肩に担いでいないタイプ。\n粋：　★★\n防御力：　★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">오른쪽 팔을 내놓은, 움직이기 쉬운 스타일이 특징인 기모노의 상의. 천칭 봉을 어깨에 메지 않은 타입. \n
멋: ★★\n
방어력: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">A kimono top without right sleeve and features easy movement. This  type does not come with balance pole on the shoulder.\n
Stylishness: ★★\n
Defensive strength: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">和服上身，特徵是它沒有右臂的手袖、能方便活動。這是沒有肩負著天秤棒的種類。\n
時尚指數：★★\n
防禦力：★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">和服上半身，特徵是它沒有右臂的手袖、能方便活動。這是沒有肩負著天秤棒的種類。\n
時尚指數：★★\n
防禦力：★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A distinctive style top with the right arm removed, making it easier to move. This type doesn't have a carrying pole slung over the shoulder.\nStylishness: ★★\nDefensive Strength: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
