<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Shrinkinator 6000</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rétrécinator 6000</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schrumpfomat 6000</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Rimpicciolitore 6000</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Encogedor 6000</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Shrinkinator 6000</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Shrinkinator 6000</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Shrink yourself instantly to get into those hard-to-reach places and amaze your friends with the Shrinkinator 6000! Includes custom walk, run, and idle animations. The speed boost is engaged when the avatar is moving at its full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rétrécissez en un éclair pour pouvoir atteindre les endroits les plus inaccessibles et épatez vos amis avec le Rétrécinator 6000 ! Inclut des animations de marche, de course et d'inactivité personnalisées. Le boost de vitesse est activé quand l'avatar se déplace à sa vitesse maximale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schrumpfe dich selbst, um schlecht erreichbare Orte zu erkunden und deine Freunde zu beeindrucken - alles mit dem Schrumpfomat 6000! Enthält spezielle Lauf-, Renn- und Pausen-Animationen für jede Gelegenheit! Der Geschwindigkeitsschub setzt automatisch ein, wenn der Avatar sich mit voller Geschwindigkeit bewegt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Rimpicciolisci le tue dimensioni fino a poterti infiltrare nelle zone più difficili da raggiungere e stupisci i tuoi amici con il Rimpicciolitore 6000! Include animazioni personalizzate per la corsa, la camminata e lo stop. Potrai dare una spinta di accelerazione quando l'avatar avrà raggiunto la massima velocità. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Encógete a ti mismo instantáneamente para colarte en esos sitios difíciles de alcanzar y sorprende a tus amigos con el Encogedor 6000! ¡Incluye animaciones personalizadas de caminar, correr y de reposo! El turbo se activa cuando el avatar se mueve a su velocidad de carrera completa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Shrink yourself instantly to get into those hard-to-reach places and amaze your friends with the Shrinkinator 6000! Includes custom walk, run, and idle animations. The speed boost is engaged when the avatar is moving at its full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Shrink yourself instantly to get into those hard-to-reach places and amaze your friends with the Shrinkinator 6000! Includes custom walk, run, and idle animations. The speed boost is engaged when the avatar is moving at its full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>