<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Shooting Hoops</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tirs au panier</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Shooting Hoops</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pallacanestro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Baloncesto</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take five free-throws or against another player. Can you make it to the top of the Leaderboards?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tirez cinq lancers-francs ou affrontez un autre joueur. Hissez-vous jusqu'en haut du tableau des scores !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Treten Sie gegen einen anderen Spieler an oder werfen Sie fünf Freiwürfe. Schaffen Sie es auf die Bestenliste?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Effettua cinque lanci liberi o contro un altro giocatore. Riuscirai ad arrivare in vetta alla classifica?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Realiza cinco tiros libres o contra otro jugador. ¿Puedes llegar a lo alto de las clasificaciones?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SCORE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Punkte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Punti</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Puntos</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BONUS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bonus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bonus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bonus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bonus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bonus</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TURN_CHANGE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Your Turn</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">À vous</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie sind dran!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tocca a te</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tu turno</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">POWER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Power</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Puissance</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kraft</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Potenza</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Energía</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SINGLE_MULTI</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Would you like to play multiplayer? Time out in %d seconds.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Voulez-vous faire une partie multijoueur ? Temps écoulé dans %d secondes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Im Mehrspieler-Modus spielen? Zeit läuft in %d Sekunden ab.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vuoi giocare in modalità multigiocatore? Tempo rimasto: %d secondi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Te gustaría jugar en modo multijugador? Tiempo restante: %d segundos.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MULTI</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Play Multiplayer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Partie Multijoueur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mehrspieler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Multigiocatore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Partida multijugador</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SINGLE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Play Singleplayer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Partie Solo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Einzelspieler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Giocatore singolo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Partida individual</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">EXIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Exit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">WAIT_FOR_MULTI</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Please wait for a second player. Time out in %d seconds.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Veuillez attendre un deuxième joueur. Temps écoulé dans %d secondes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bitte auf zweiten Spieler warten. Zeit läuft in %d Sekunden ab.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">In attesa del secondo giocatore. Tempo rimasto: %d secondi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Espera al segundo jugador. Tiempo restante: %d segundos.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">LEADERBOARD</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Leaderboard</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Scores</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bestenliste</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Classifica</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Clasificación</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MOST_POINTS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Most points</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plus de points</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Höchstpunktzahl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Punteggio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mayor número de puntos</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MOST_WINS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Most wins</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plus de victoires</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Meiste Siege</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maggior numero di vittorie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mayor número de victorias</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">STRING_THROWTIMEOUT_YOU</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You timed out for taking too long to throw the ball.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Temps écoulé. Vous avez attendu trop longtemps avant de tirer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeit abgelaufen. Sie haben zu lange für den Wurf gebraucht.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tempo esaurito. Hai aspettato troppo prima di lanciare la palla.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Se agotó el tiempo porque tardaste demasiado en lanzar la pelota.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">STRING_THROWTIMEOUT_OTHER</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The other player  timed out for taking to long too throw the ball.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'autre utilisateur a mis trop de temps à lancer la balle. Il passe son tour.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der andere Spieler wurde gesperrt, weil er zu lange gebraucht hat, um den Ball zu werfen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tempo esaurito per l'altro giocatore. Ha aspettato troppo prima di lanciare la palla.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El otro jugador pierde su turno por tardar demasiado en lanzar la pelota.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">STRING_ERROR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There was a network error, sorry!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une erreur de réseau est survenue, désolé !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Netzwerkfehler ist aufgetreten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Si è verificato un errore di rete.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ha habido un error de red. ¡Perdón!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">STRING_PLAYERLEFT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The other player has left the game.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'autre joueur a quitté la partie.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der andere Spieler hat das Spiel verlassen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'altro giocatore ha abbandonato la partita.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El otro jugador abandonó la partida.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MINIGAME_TIMEOUT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Minigame will timeout in %d seconds.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le mini-jeu finira dans %d secondes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeit für Minispiel läuft in %d Sekunden ab.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tempo rimasto per il minigioco: %d secondi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La minipartida terminará en %d segundos.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">INSTRUCTIONS_TITLE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Shooting Hoops - Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tirs au panier - Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Shooting Hoops – Anleitung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pallacanestro - Istruzioni</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Baloncesto: Instrucciones</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">INSTRUCTIONS_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Every player gets 5 shots from 5 different spots on the basketball court. You can practice your skills in Single Player or take on another player in Multi Player. Your scores and multi player wins will be uploaded to the Leaderboard.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaque joueur a droit à 5 tirs depuis 5 endroits différents du terrain. Vous pouvez vous entraîner en mode Solo ou affronter un autre joueur en mode Multijoueur. Vos scores et le nombre de vos victoires en mode Multijoueur apparaîtront au tableau des scores.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jeder Spieler hat 5 Würfe von 5 Punkten auf dem Basketball-Feld. Trainieren Sie Ihre Fähigkeiten im Einzelspieler-Modus oder treten Sie im Mehrspieler-Modus gegen einen anderen Spieler an. Punkte und Mehrspieler-Siege werden zur Bestenliste hochgeladen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ogni giocatore può effettuare 5 tiri da 5 diverse posizioni nel campo di pallacanestro. Puoi allenarti in modalità Giocatore singolo oppure competere contro un altro giocatore in modalità Multigiocatore. Il tuo punteggio e il numero di vittorie verranno caricati nella Classifica.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cada jugador dispone de 5 tiros desde 5 puntos diferentes de la cancha de baloncesto. Puedes practicar en el juego individual o enfrentarte a un rival en la opción multijugador. Tu puntuación y tus victorias en el modo multijugador quedarán registradas en la clasificación.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">INSTRUCTIONS_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Aim your shot with the Left or Right analog stick. Hold down [CROSS] and watch the power meter to see how hard your shot is going to be. Let go of [CROSS] to release the ball.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Orientez votre tir avec le joystick gauche ou droit. Maintenez la touche [CROSS] enfoncée et regardez la barre de puissance pour visualiser la force du tir. Relâchez la touche [CROSS] pour lancer le ballon.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zielen Sie mit dem linken oder rechten Stick. Halten Sie die [CROSS]-Taste gedrückt und bestimmen Sie mit der Kraftanzeige, wie fest Ihr Wurf wird. Lassen Sie zum Werfen die [CROSS]-Taste los.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prendi la mira con la levetta sinistra o destra. Tieni premuto il tasto [CROSS] e osserva il potenziometro per calibrare la potenza del tiro. Per lanciare la palla, rilascia il tasto  [CROSS].</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apunta utilizando el joystick izquierdo o el derecho. Mantén pulsado el botón [CROSS] y fíjate en el medidor de energía para comprobar la fuerza de tu tiro. Deja de pulsar el botón [CROSS] para soltar la pelota.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">INSTRUCTIONS_3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Whenever you score a shot your bonus multiplier will go up. Score multiple shots in a row for a big combo bonus. But... miss a shot and your bonus multiplier will reset. When you are taking your shot you will see a timer count down. Try to make your shot as fast as you can for extra bonus points.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quand vous marquez un panier, votre bonus multiplicateur augmente. Marquez plusieurs paniers à la suite pour obtenir un bonus combo. Mais... si vous ratez un tir, votre bonus multiplicateur retombe à zéro. Quand vous préparez votre tir, un chrono apparaît. Tirez le plus vite possible pour obtenir des points bonus supplémentaires.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn Sie punkten, steigt Ihr Bonus-Multiplikator. Bei mehreren Treffern in Folge erhalten Sie einen Combo-Bonus. Verfehlen Sie einen Wurf, wird der Multiplikator zurückgesetzt. Bei Ihrem Wurf erscheint ein Timer-Countdown. Werfen Sie so schnell wie möglich, um Extra-Bonuspunkte zu erhalten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ogni volta che il tiro va a segno, il moltiplicatore bonus aumenterà. Per ottenere un bonus combo, manda a segno più tiri consecutivamente. Basta un errore e il moltiplicatore bonus verrà azzerato. Mentre tiri comparirà il conto alla rovescia. Cerca di tirare più velocemente possibile per ottenere altri bonus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuando anotes subirá tu multiplicador de bonificación. Logra varias canastas seguidas y recibirás un gran combo como bonificación. Pero si fallas un lanzamiento, se reiniciará tu multiplicador. Cuando te dispongas a lanzar, podrás ver un temporizador que marca una cuenta atrás. Intenta realizar tu tiro tan rápido como puedas para obtener puntos de bonificación extra.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">INSTRUCTIONS_4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If the court is occupied you can enter the queue and wait until there's an open spot in the game.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si le terrain est occupé, vous pouvez faire la queue et attendre qu'une place se libère.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn das Feld besetzt ist, können Sie in der Warteschleife warten, bis ein Platz frei wird.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se il campo è già occupato, puoi metterti in coda e aspettare fino a quando non si sarà liberato un posto nel gioco.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si la cancha está ocupada, puedes esperar en la cola hasta que haya una plaza libre.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">FLOAT_TEXT_GOAL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">goal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">panier</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Treffer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">canestro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">canasta</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">FLOAT_TEXT_TIME_BONUS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">time bonus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">bonus temps</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeitbonus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">bonus di tempo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">bonificación de tiempo</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">FLOAT_TEXT_MULTIPLIER_BONUS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">multi bonus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">bonus multiplicateur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Multi-Bonus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">bonus moltiplicatore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">bonificación múltiple</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">FLOAT_TEXT_TOTAL_SCORE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">total score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">score total</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gesamtpunktzahl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">punteggio totale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">puntuación total</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>