<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Lakeside Log Cabin</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Lakeside Log Cabin</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Chalet rustico sul lago</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Lakeside Log Cabin</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">호반 통나무집</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">湖邊小木屋</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Blockhaus am See</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Chalet de bord de lac</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">湖邊小木屋</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ログキャビン</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Cabaña de madera</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Admire the stunning sunset across a mountain lake from this modern log cabin. The residence provides two large living areas with beautiful fire places in each and exquisite lighting throughout. These are elegantly joined by a large decked area that takes you right up to the lake side. Simply spectacular.   [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Admirez d'incroyables couchers de soleil depuis ce chalet moderne au bord d'un lac de montagne. La résidence comprend deux grandes pièces à vivre très lumineuses équipées chacune d'une magnifique cheminée. Elles sont élégamment reliées par une terrasse donnant sur le lac. Simplement spectaculaire. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Betrachten Sie von diesem modernen Blockhaus aus den atemberaubenden Sonnenuntergang über dem Bergsee. Das Haus bietet zwei große Bereiche mit schönen Kaminen. Die beiden Bereiche sind durch ein großes überdachtes Areal, das direkt zum See führt, elegant mit-einander verbunden. Einfach spektakulär. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Goditi dei magnifici tramonti su un lago di montagna da questo chalet rustico ma moderno. Al suo interno troverai due ampie zone giorno luminosissime e dotate di splendidi camini. All'esterno, un'elegante e spaziosa veranda si affaccia direttamente sul lago. Semplicemente spettacolare. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Admira el fascinante atardecer desde esta moderna cabaña de madera en un lago en la montaña. La residencia consta de dos estancias extensas con dos bonitas chimeneas en cada una de ellas y una luz espectacular. Están unidas elegantemente por una zona cubierta que te llevará directamente al lado del lago. Espectacular aunque sencillo  [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">暖炉付きの2つのリビングルームを持ち、湖に面したログキャビンのパーソナルスペース。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">이 현대적인 통나무집에서 호수 위로 내려앉는 노을을 즐기세요. 두 개의 커다란 거실과 부드러운 조명시설이 준비되어 있습니다. 호수와 연결되어 있는 출입구 또한 편리하게 설치되었습니다. 최고의 휴양지입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Admire the stunning sunset across a mountain lake from this modern log cabin. The residence provides two large living areas with beautiful fire places in each and exquisite lighting throughout. These are elegantly joined by a large decked area that takes you right up to the lake side. Simply spectacular.   [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">在這間充滿現代感的小木屋中可欣賞迷人的湖光山色和日落景致。屋內是兩個寬敞的居住區，備有暖洋洋的火爐和精緻的燈光配襯。屋外是寬闊的露台，可直通湖邊。完美無瑕的建築傑作。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">在這間充滿現代感的小木屋中可欣賞迷人的湖光山色和日落景致。屋內是兩個寬敞的居住區，備有暖洋洋的火爐和精緻的燈光配襯。屋外是寬闊的露台，可直通湖邊。完美無瑕的建築傑作。 [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Admire the stunning sunset across a mountain lake from this modern log cabin. The residence provides two large living areas with beautiful fire places in each and exquisite lighting throughout. These are elegantly joined by a large decked area that takes you right up to the lake side. Simply spectacular.   [#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>