<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Crystal Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack de meubles en cristal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Paket: Kristallmöbel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completo di mobili in cristallo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mobiliario de cristal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Crystal Furniture Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Toss your old furniture out the window and replace it with this brand new set of crystal furniture. Bundle includes a desk, sofa, clock, chair, lamp, and entertainment center all made of crystal. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jetez les vieux meubles par la fenêtre et remplacez-les par ce tout nouvel ensemble de meubles en cristal. Le pack comprend un bureau, un canapé, une horloge, une chaise, une lampe, et un centre de divertissement, le tout entièrement en cristal. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Werfen Sie Ihre alten Möbel aus dem Fenster und ersetzen Sie sie mit diesem brandneuen Kristallmöbel-Set. Das Paket enthält Schreibtisch, Sofa, Uhr, Stuhl, Lampe und TV-Wand, alles aus reinstem Kristall. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Buttate fuori dalla finestra i vostri vecchi mobili e rimpiazzateli con questo completo di mobili in cristallo nuovo di zecca. L'insieme comprende una scrivania, un divano, un orologio, una sedia, una lampada e un mobile TV, il tutto interamente in cristallo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tira esos viejos muebles por la ventana y reemplázalos con este nuevo set de muebles de cristal. El conjunto se compone de escritorio, sofá, reloj, silla, lámpara y centro de ocio, todo hecho de cristal. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Toss your old furniture out the window and replace it with this brand new set of crystal furniture. Bundle includes a desk, sofa, clock, chair, lamp, and entertainment center all made up of crystal. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>