<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Connected Sunglasses 2-item Set (Orange Frames, Men)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de 2 pièces Lunettes de Soleil Mono-Écran (montures oranges, homme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Durchgehende Sonnenbrillen 2-teiliges Set (orange, für Männer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set 2 paia di occhiali da sole con lente unica (montatura arancione, da uomo)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos gafas de sol monolentes (montura naranja, hombre)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ワンレンズサングラス２点セット（オレンジフレーム・男性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Connected Sunglasses 2-item Set (Orange Frames, Men)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Orange-framed sunglasses designed with one connected lens.2-piece set of sunglasses worn normally and on top of the head.\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Connected Sunglasses (Orange Frames, Men) (Face Accessory)\n- Connected Sunglasses, Placed on Head (Orange Frames, Men) (Face Accessory)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Lunettes de soleil oranges conçues avec un seul verre. Set de 2 pièces portées normalement et sur la tête.\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Lunettes de Soleil Mono-Écran (monture orange, homme) (accessoire de visage)\n- Lunettes de Soleil Mono-Écran, sur la Tête (monture orange, homme) (accessoire de visage)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Orange Sonnenbrillen gestaltet mit einer durchgehender Linse. 2-teiliges Sonnenbrillen Set, normal und hochgesetzt getragen.\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Durchgehende Sonnenbrille (orange, für Männer) (Zubehör für das Gesicht)\n- Durchgehende Sonnenbrille, hochgesetzt (orange, für Männer) (Zubehör für das Gesicht)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Occhiali da sole con montatura arancione con lente unica. Set formato da 2 paia di occhiali da sole indossati normalmente o appoggiati sulla testa.\nQuesto set include i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Occhiali da sole con lente unica (montatura arancione, da uomo) (accessorio per il viso)\n- Occhiali da sole con lente unica appoggiati sulla testa (montatura arancione, da uomo) (accessorio per il viso)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettiva categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Gafas de sol de un solo cristal con montura naranja. Juego de dos artículos con gafas de sol, puestas normalmente y en la cabeza.\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Gafas de sol monolente (montura naranja, hombre) (accesorio cara)\n- Gafas de sol monolente, colocadas en la cabeza (montura naranja, hombre) (accesorio cara)\n\n*Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">レンズがつながったデザインのオレンジのフレームのサングラス。普通にかけたものと頭の上に乗せたものの２点セット。\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・ワンレンズサングラス（オレンジフレーム・男性）/フェイスアクセサリ\n・ワンレンズサングラス・頭乗せ（オレンジフレーム・男性）/フェイスアクセサリ\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Orange-framed sunglasses designed with one connected lens.2-piece set of sunglasses worn normally and on top of the head.\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Connected Sunglasses (Orange Frames, Men) (Face Accessory)\n- Connected Sunglasses, Placed on Head (Orange Frames, Men) (Face Accessory)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
