<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Indigo Luv Dress - Blue Indigo (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Robe Indigo Luv - Bleu indigo (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Indigo Luv Kleid - Indigoblau (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Indigo Luv Vestito - Blu indaco (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Indigo Luv Vestido - Azul índigo (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It's a hot mix of emotions for the Indigo Luv dress as its '90's baby doll silhouette is mixed with '60's tie-dye print. You'll agree, the look is fresh and futuristic. Special details include crochet insets at the sleeves and criss cross cut outs at back. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un mélange d'émotions fortes pour la robe Indigo Luv car sa silhouette de poupée années 90 se fond avec son imprimé tissé-teint années 60. Vous en conviendrez, ce look est rafraîchissant et futuriste. Parmi les détails caractéristiques figurent les incrustations au crochet au niveau des manches et les découpes en treillis dans le dos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Indigo Luv Kleid verbindet die Babydoll-Silhouette der '90er emotionsvoll mit dem Batikdruck der '60er zu einem frischen, futuristischen Look. Zu besonderen Details zählen die Häkeleinsätze an den Ärmeln und die Kreuzausschnitte auf dem Rücken. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il vestito Indigo Luv è un mix di forti emozioni in cui il taglio anni '90 in stile baby doll si mescola alla stampa psichedelica anni '60, per un look moderno e futuristico. I dettagli speciali comprendono inserti ricamati sulle maniche e scollatura con lacci incrociati sulla schiena. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El vestido Indigo Luv es una mezcla fulgurante de emociones, con su contorno de muñeca "años 90" combinada con un estampado de teñido anudado "años 60". Reconoce que tiene un "look" fresco y futurista. Sus detalles especiales incluyen incrustaciones de ganchillo en las mangas y espalda recortada y entrecruzada. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>