<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Yokke Hat (men's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Coiffe Yokke (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Yokke-Hut (Männer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cappello (Yokke) da uomo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sombrero de Yokke (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ヨッケ帽子（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">욧케 모자（남성）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Yokke Hat (men's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">優客帽子（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">優客帽子（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Yokke Hat (men's)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This hat depicts a Yokke chick hiding in its shell and waiting for mum.\n
Show the world that you are in need of love!\n
\n
Purchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space.\n
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette coiffe représente un poussin Yokke qui se cache dans sa coquille en attendant sa maman.\n
Montre au monde que tu as besoin d'affection ! \n
\n
Acheter cet objet ajoute 1 LocoRoco à ton espace personnel de l'île Loco.
Tu peux ajouter jusqu'à 20 LocoRoco à l'île Loco. Une fois le maximum atteint, tu ne peux plus ajouter d'unités.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser Hut zeigt ein Yokke-Küken in seiner Schale, das auf seine Mutter wartet.\n
Zeige der Welt, wie liebesbedürftig du bist.\n
\n
Dieser Gegenstand fügt deinem Loco-Insel-Apartment 1 LocoRoco hinzu.
Du kannst bis zu 20 LocoRoco hinzufügen. Ist das Maximum erreicht, können keine weiteren Einheiten hinzugefügt werden.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo cappello raffigura un cucciolo di Yokke che aspetta la sua mamma nel nido.\n
Mostra a tutti che hai bisogno di affetto!\n
\n
Acquistando questo oggetto, aggiungerai un LocoRoco al tuo spazio personale su Loco Island.
Puoi aggiungere fino a 20 LocoRoco su Loco Island. Una volta raggiunto il numero massimo, non potrai aggiungerne altri.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">En este sombrero vemos a un polluelo Yokke escondiéndose en su cascarón esperando a su mamá.\n
¡Muéstrale al mundo que necesitas amor!\n
\n
Comprar este objeto añade 1 LocoRoco a tu espacio personal en la Loco Isla.
Puedes añadir un máximo de 20 LocoRoco a la Loco Isla. Cuando hayas alcanzado este número, no podrás añadir más unidades.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">カラに隠れてお母さんを待っているヒナ鳥のヨッケの帽子。\n
さみしがり屋のあなたにピッタリです！\n
\n
このアイテムを購入するとパーソナルスペース”ロコアイランド”に”ロコロコ”が１匹追加されます。
”ロコアイランド”には最大20匹まで”ロコロコ”を追加できます。最大数に達した場合は、それ以上の追加はされません。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">옷깃에 숨어 어미를 기다고 있는 아기 새, 욧케 모양의 모자\n
외로움을 많이 타는 당신에게 안성맞춤이겠네요!\n
\n
이 아이템을 구입하면 퍼스널 스페이스 '로코 아일랜드'에 '로코로코'가 1마리 추가됩니다. '로코 아일랜드'에는 최대 20마리까지 '로코로코'를 추가할 수 있습니다.  최대치에 다다르면 더 이상은 추가할 수 없습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This hat depicts a Yokke chick hiding in its shell and waiting for mum.\n
Show the world that you are in need of love!\n
\n
Purchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space.\n
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">躲在蛋殼裡等待母親的雛鳥優客的帽子。\n
最適合不甘寂寞的你！\n
\n
購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">躲在蛋殼裡等待母親的雛鳥優客的帽子。\n
最適合不甘寂寞的你！\n
\n
購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This hat depicts a Yokke chick hiding in its shell and waiting for mom.\n
Show the world that you are in need of love!\n
\n
Purchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your LocoIsland personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to LocoIsland. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>