<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">RaceOn Garage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RaceOn Garage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">RaceOn Garage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">RaceOn Garage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">RaceOn Garage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">RaceOn Garage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">RaceOn Garage</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This garage is not just for cars, it's the pinnacle of cool when it comes to a meeting place for people in PlayStation®HOME. Be one of the edgy first to own this stunning space and decide what you want to use it for! Organize an underground party or convert it into the most modern of living space or keep it as a working space, the choices are endless! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce garage n'est pas seulement pour les voitures, c'est l'apogée du cool lorsque les gens se réunissent dans Home. Soyez l'un des premiers propriétaires de cet espace impressionnant et décidez de l'usage que vous en ferez ! Organisez une fête clandestine, convertissez-le en un espace moderne de loisirs ou de travail, le choix est infini ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese Garage ist nicht nur für Autos. Es gibt nichts Cooleres als einen besonderen Platz zum Treffen von Freunden, usw. im PShome zu haben. Seien Sie einer der ersten Besitzer von diesem einzigartigen „Platz“, den Sie vielfältig nutzen können. Organisieren Sie eine unterirdische Party oder nutzen Sie die Garage als Arbeitsplatz. Sie können sie sogar in einen hochmodernen, gemütlichen Wohnraum umwandeln. Die Möglichkeiten sind endlos! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non è solo uno spazio dove riporre le proprie auto..è un luogo "cool" dove potersi riunire ! Sii uno dei primi proprietari di questo spazio e decidi tu come utilizzarlo! Un festa clandestina...uno studio di registrazione..o convertilo in un modernissimo luogo di relax..le opzioni sono infinite! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este garaje no es sólo para coches, es el apogeo de lo “cool” cuando se trata de reunirse en Home. Sea uno de los primeros propietarios de este impresionante espacio y decida para que quiera usarlo! Organice una fiesta clandestina o conviértalo en un moderno espacio para el ocio, las opciones son infinitas! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This garage is not just for cars, it's the pinnacle of cool when it comes to a meeting place for people in PlayStation®HOME. Be one of the edgy first to own this stunning space and decide what you want to use it for! Organize an underground party or convert it into the most modern of living space or keep it as a working space, the choices are endless! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This garage is not just for cars, it's the pinnacle of cool when it comes to a meeting place for people in PlayStation®HOME. Be one of the edgy first to own this stunning space and decide what you want to use it for! Organize an underground party or convert it into the most modern of living space or keep it as a working space, the choices are endless! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>