<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Famous Sword, Onimaru Kunitsuna (For Large-sized Clothes, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Épée célèbre, Onimaru Kunitsuna (vêtements larges, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Bekanntes Schwert, Onimaru Kunitsuna (für weite Kleidung, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Spada famosa, Onimaru Kunitsuna (per vestiti larghi, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Espada famosa, Onimaru Kunitsuna (grande, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">名刀・鬼丸国綱（大型衣装用・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Famous Sword, Onimaru Kunitsuna (For Large-sized Clothes, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">One of the world-famous swords that slices evil  spirit. Bestowed with the power of fire. (Sword worn on waist.)\nAttacking Strength: ★★★-[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">L'une des épées les plus célèbres qui peut découper les fantômes démoniaques. Elle porte le pouvoir du feu. (Épée portée à la taille.)\nPuissance d'attaque : ★★★-[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Eines der weltbekannten Schwerter, das böse Geister durchschneidet. Es besitzt die Kraft des Feuers. (Schwert, das an der Taille getragen wird.)\nAngriff: ★★★-[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Una delle spade più famose al mondo in grado di eliminare i demoni. Vi è infuso il potere del fuoco. (Portata alla vita)\nAttacco: ★★★-[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Una de las espadas mundialmente famosas que rebana a los fantasmas malévolos. (Espada que se porta a la cadera.)\nAtaque: ★★★-[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">物の怪を切り裂く天下の名刀の一つ。火属性を帯びている。（帯刀状態）\n攻撃力　：★★★-[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">One of the world-famous swords that slices  spirit  spirit. Bestowed with the power of fire. (Sword worn on waist.)\nAttacking Strength: ★★★-[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
