<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Novus Prime Concept: The Witch Doctor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Concept de Novus Prime : Le Witch Doctor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Novus Prime Konzept: The Witch Doctor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Design Novus Prime: Witch Doctor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Concepto de Novus Prime: Witch Doctor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムのコンセプト：ウィッチドクター</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임 컨셉: 위치 닥터</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Novus Prime Concept: The Witch Doctor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Novus Prime概念畫：Witch Doctor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Novus Prime概念畫：Witch Doctor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Novus Prime Concept: The Witch Doctor</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. The Witch Doctor plays a valuable support role on the battlefield, supercharging its allies with enhanced offensive and defensive capabilities. It also supercharges itself, becoming quite a force to be reckoned with in a dogfight. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ornez vos murs de peintures conceptuelles de Novus Prime. Le Witch Doctor joue un rôle de soutien majeur sur le champ de bataille, boostant les capacités offensives et défensives de ses alliés. Il peut également se booster lui-même, se transformant ainsi en vrai chien de combat. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schmücke deine Wände mit den Konzeptzeichnungen von Novus Prime. Der Witch Doctor spielt eine wichtige Rolle auf dem Schlachtfeld. Er unterstützt seine Verbündeten, indem er ihre Angriffe verstärkt und ihre Verteidigung verbessert. Er hat auch selbst ein paar Tricks auf Lager, was ihn zu einem gefährlichen Gegner im Kampf macht! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Decora le tue pareti con il design della Novus Prime. La Witch Doctor gioca un importante ruolo di supporto in battaglia, aumentando le abilità di attacco e difesa degli alleati. Può anche aumentare le proprie abilità, divenendo una vera potenza nel combattimento aereo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Adorna tus paredes con las pinturas conceptuales de Novus Prime. Witch Doctor tiene un papel importante como apoyo en el campo de batalla, sobrecargando a sus aliados con una mejorada ofensiva y capacidades defensivas. Sobrecargado, se convierte en una fuerza que puede vérselas en un combate aéreo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ノーバス・プライムのコンセプト絵画を壁に飾ろう。ウィッチドクターは戦場で補助的な役目を果たし、重要な活躍をする。味方の攻撃能力や防御能力を向上させる。自分自身を補強することもできる、激しい空中戦では一目置かれる存在。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">노부스 프라임의 컨셉화로 벽을 장식합니다. 위치 닥터는 전장에서 다양한 보조 역할을 수행하는 함선으로, 아군의 공격력 및 방어력을 증대시키는 충전 능력을 지니고 있습니다. 또한 자기 자신을 충전해 난전에서 강력한 힘을 발휘할 수도 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. The Witch Doctor plays a valuable support role on the battlefield, supercharging its allies with enhanced offensive and defensive capabilities. It also supercharges itself, becoming quite a force to be reckoned with in a dogfight. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用Novus Prime的概念繪畫裝飾你的牆壁。Witch Doctor在戰場上能使用其進攻及防衛能力來為戰友增加能量，亦能自我充電，在近距離空戰中頗有威脅。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用Novus Prime的概念繪畫裝飾你的牆壁。Witch Doctor在戰場上能使用其進攻及防衛能力來為戰友增加能量，亦能自我充電，在近距離空戰中頗有威脅。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Adorn your walls with the concept paintings of Novus Prime. The Witch Doctor plays a valuable support role on the battlefield, supercharging its allies with enhanced offensive and defensive capabilities. It also supercharges itself, becoming quite a force to be reckoned with in a dogfight. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>