<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Inflatable Dolphin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Dauphin gonflable</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aufblasbarer Delfin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Delfino Gonfiabile</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Delfín hinchable</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴムのイルカ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Inflatable Dolphin</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You’ve completed the LOOT™ LUBBER Caper. Because you own a version of Cabin Boy: Trout Trouble and LOOT’s Amaterasu Experience, you’ve unlocked a shiny inflatable dolphin and dolphin sea-life in your LOOT’s Amaterasu Experience. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez déjoué la combine MARIN D'EAU DOUCE de LOOT™. Comme vous possédez une des versions de Cabin Boy: Trout Trouble et l'Expérience Amaterasu de LOOT, vous avez libéré un dauphin gonflable brillant et un vrai dauphin dans votre Expérience Amaterasu de LOOT.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast das LOOT™ LUBBER Caper abgeschlossen.
Da du auch eine Version von Cabin Boy: Trout Trouble und LOOT's Amaterasu Experience besitzt, hast du in LOOT's Amaterasu Experience dadurch einen schmucken, aufblasbaren Delfin freigeschaltet und dem Ökosyste [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai completato l'Avventura di LUBBER di LOOT™. Siccome hai una copia di Cabin Boy: Trout Trouble e LOOT’s Amaterasu Experience, hai sbloccato un favoloso delfino gonfiabile e i delfini per LOOT’s Amaterasu Experience. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Has completado la prueba LOOT™ LUBBER. Como tienes una versión de Cabin Boy: Trout Trouble y de LOOT's Amaterasu Experience, has desbloqueado un flamante delfín hinchable y un delfín marino en tu LOOT’s Amaterasu Experience. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LOOT™ラバー作戦をコンプリートしました。トラウト・トラブルとLOOTアマテラス・エクスペリエンスでキャビン・ボーイのバージョンを手に入れたからです。あなたのLOOTアマテラス・エクスベリエンスにおけるキラキラのゴムのイルカとドルフィン・シーライフが開放されました。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You’ve completed the LOOT™ LUBBER Caper. Because you own a version of Cabin Boy: Trout Trouble and LOOT’s Amaterasu Experience, you’ve unlocked a shiny inflatable dolphin and dolphin sea-life in your LOOT’s Amaterasu Experience. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>