<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Techno Peep - Static Mini - Robot Red</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Techno Peep - Static Mini - Rouge Robot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Techno Peep - Statische Miniatur - Roboter-Rot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Techno Peep - Static Mini - Rosso Robot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Techno Peep - Static Mini - Rojo Robot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_27</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Techno Peep - Static Mini - 로보트 레드</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Techno Peep - Static Mini - Robot Red</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Techno Peep 靜態迷你公仔 – 金屬紅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Techno Peep 靜態迷你公仔 – 金屬紅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Techno Peep - Static Mini - Robot Red</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Move to the groove with Techno Peep!  As the hottest gadget on the market, you can put your Mini-Peep on display in your apartment in his own Peep-A-Boo Box!  Collect them all and stack them up for all to see![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Va t'éclater avec Techno Peep! Comme le gadget le plus en vogue sur le marche, tu peux exposer ton Mini-Peep  à ton appartement dans sa propre boite Peep-A-Boo. Rassemble les tous et entasse les pour que tous puissent les voit![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tanz dich in den Groove mit Techno Peep! Als heißestes Zubehör überhapt kannst du dein Mini-Peep in deiner Wohnung in seiner Peep-A-Boo Kiste ausstellen! Sammle sie alle und stelle sie für Alle zur Schau aus![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Muoviti al tempo con Techno Peep!  Come il gadget piú desiderato sul mercato, puoi mettere il tuo Mini-Peep in mostra nel tuo appartamento nella sua scatola Peep-A-Boo!  Colleziona tutti quanti e mettili in mostra perché tutti possano vederli![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Muévete al ritmo con Techno Peep!  Siendo el gadget más deseado en el mercado, puedes poner a tu Mini-Peep de muestra en tu departamento en su propia caja Peep-A-Boo!  Colecciónalos todos y amontónalos para que los vea todo el mundo![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_27 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Techno Peep과 함께 신나는 댄스를! 마켓에서 가장 인기 있는 친구로, Peep-A-Boo 박스에 디스플레이된 Mini-Peep을 아파트에 모아 보세요! Mini-Peep을 모두 모아 친구들에게 자랑해 보세요![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Move to the groove with Techno Peep!  As the hottest gadget on the market, you can put your Mini-Peep on display in your apartment in his own Peep-A-Boo Box!  Collect them all and stack them up for all to see![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Techno Peep令您輕鬆快活！作為市面上最受歡迎的機械人，您可以將Mini-Peep放進專用Peep-A-Boo盒子並成為家居擺設！集齊全套，向朋友炫耀一下吧！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Techno Peep令您輕鬆快活！作為市面上最受歡迎的機械人，您可以將Mini-Peep放進專用Peep-A-Boo盒子並成為家居擺設！集齊全套，向朋友炫耀一下吧！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Move to the groove with Techno Peep!  As the hottest gadget on the market, you can put your Mini-Peep on display in your apartment in his own Peep-A-Boo Box!  Collect them all and stack them up for all to see![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>