<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Dream Yacht: Arctic Voyage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le yacht de rêve : voyage arctique</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Traumyacht: Reise in die Arktis</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lo yacht dei sogni: viaggio nell'Artico</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Yate de ensueño "Travesía por el Ártico"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">The Dream Yacht: Arctic Voyage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">꿈의 요트: 북극 항해</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Dream Yacht: Arctic Voyage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">夢幻遊艇：北極之旅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">夢幻遊艇：北極之旅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Dream Yacht: Arctic Voyage</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Treat them to the sights of breathtaking glaciers, giant ice formations and crystal blue waters with the Dream Yacht: Arctic Voyage. Explore three decks, chill out on the private ice shelf and collect 20 unique rewards. Live the dream!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Faites-leur découvrir les panoramas de glaciers à couper le souffle, des formations de glace géantes et des eaux d'un bleu cristal avec le yacht de rêve : voyage arctique. Explorez les trois ponts, détendez-vous sur la corniche de glace privée et collectez 20 récompenses uniques. Vivez votre rêve !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lade deine Freunde mit der Traumyacht: Reise in die Arktis zu atemberaubenden Gletschern, riesigen Eisgebilden und kristallklarem Wasser ein. Erkunde drei Decks, chill am privaten Eisschelf und sammle 20 einmalige Belohnungen. Lebe den Traum!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Regalagli la vista dei ghiacciai mozzafiato, delle gigantesche formazioni di ghiaccio e delle acque color blu cristallo con lo yacht dei sogni: viaggio nell'Artico. Esplora i tre ponti, rilassati sul banco di ghiaccio privato e colleziona 20 premi unici. Vivi il sogno!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Embárcate en un crucero por los glaciares mas sorprendentes y las aguas más cristalinas a bordo del yate de ensueño "Travesía por el Ártico". Asómate a las tres cubiertas, relájate en tu mini iceberg privado y consigue 20 premios exclusivos. ¡Esto es vida!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Treat them to the sights of breathtaking glaciers, giant ice formations and crystal blue waters with the Dream Yacht: Arctic Voyage. Explore three decks, chill out on the private ice shelf and collect 20 unique rewards. Live the dream!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">꿈의 요트를 타고 숨을 멎게 하는 빙하, 거대한 결빙, 수정같이 푸른 바다의 장관을 그들에게 선사하세요: 북극 항해. 3층의 갑판을 모두 둘러 보고, 개인 얼음 칸에서 몸을 식히면서 20개의 진귀한 보상품도 수집하세요. 꿈을 실현해봐요!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Treat them to the sights of breathtaking glaciers, giant ice formations and crystal blue waters with the Dream Yacht: Arctic Voyage. Explore three decks, chill out on the private ice shelf and collect 20 unique rewards. Live the dream!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">招待他們來趟「夢幻遊艇：北極之旅」，一睹壯觀冰河、巨大冰層，以及清澈見底的湛藍海水。本遊艇共有三層甲板，不但可在私人冰棚透心涼，也可以收集20種寶物。快來實現夢想吧！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">招待他們來趟「夢幻遊艇：北極之旅」，一睹壯觀冰河、巨大冰層，以及清澈見底的湛藍海水。本遊艇共有三層甲板，不但可在私人冰棚透心涼，也可以收集20種寶物。快來實現夢想吧！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Treat them to the sights of breathtaking glaciers, giant ice formations and crystal blue waters with the Dream Yacht: Arctic Voyage. Explore three decks, chill out on the private ice shelf and collect 20 unique rewards. Live the dream!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>