<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Hand holding a lucky charm for defence (Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Main portant un porte-bonheur protecteur (femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Eine Hand, die einen schützenden Talisman hält (Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Mano che stringe un amuleto protettivo (da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Mano portando un amuleto protector (mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">守護の御守りを握りしめた手（女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">수호의 부적을 쥔 손 (여성)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Hand holding a lucky charm for defense (Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">握著護身符的手（女用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">握著護身符的手（女用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Hand holding a lucky charm for defense (Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Hold this lucky charm in hand to boost your defensive strength. \nEffect: It can only be used once in the "Operation: Defend Edo" lounge. During a fixed period of time your defensive strength will be raised.\nIncrease in Defensive Strength: ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un porte-bonheur qui augmente votre défense pour une période de temps définie.\nEffet : peut être utilisé une fois par combat dans le lounge "Opération : Défense d’Edo". Augmente votre défense pour une période de temps définie.\n
Augmentation Défense : ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Talisman erhöht die Verteidigung für eine bestimmte Zeitspanne.\nWirkung: Kann ein Mal während eines Kampfes im Lounge "Operation: Edo verteidigen" benutzt werden. Seine Benutzung erhöht Verteidigung für eine eingeschränkte Zeit.\nErhöhung der Verteidigung: ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Tieni in mano questo amuleto protettivo per aumentare la difesa.\nEffetto: Può essere utilizzato una volta durante una battaglia nella stanza "Operazione: Difendere Edo". Utilizzandolo, la difesa aumenta per un periodo di tempo limitato.\nAumento difesa: ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Portar un amuleto de protección incrementa la defensa por un período de tiempo.\nEfecto: sólo puede usarse una vez durante una batalla en el salón "Operación: Defender Edo". Utilizar esto incrementa la defensa por tiempo limitado.\n
Incremento de defensa: ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">一定時間、防御力が上昇する御守りを握りしめている。\n効果：　　ラウンジ「大江戸・モノノケ退治」にて一回の戦闘に一度のみ使用可能で、使うと一定時間防御力が上昇する。\n
防御力増加　　：★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">일정시간 방어력이 상승하는 부적을 쥐고 있다. \n효과: 라운지「대에도, 요괴퇴치」의 한번의 전투에서만 사용할 수 있으며, 사용하면 일정시간 방어력이 상승한다.\n방어력 증가: ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Hold this lucky charm in hand and during a fixed period of time your defensive strength. \nEffect: It can only be used once in the "Operation: Defend Edo" lounge. During a fixed period of time your defensive strength will be raised.\nIncrease in Defensive Strength: ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">於一定時間內手握護身符，便能提升防禦力。\n效果：只能在「大江戶：消滅妖怪」大廳內的一次戰鬥中使用一次，使用後於一定時間內能提升防禦力。\n防禦力提升度：★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">於一定時間內手握護身符，便能提升防禦力。\n效果：只能在「大江戶：消滅妖怪」大廳內的一次戰鬥中使用一次，使用後於一定時間內能提升防禦力。\n防禦力提升度：★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Hold this lucky charm in hand and during a fixed period of time your defensive strength. \nEffect: It can only be used once in the "Operation: Defend Edo" lounge. During a fixed period of time your defensive strength will be raised.\nIncrease in Defensive Strength: ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
