<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Butler companion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Majordome</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Butler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maggiordomo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mayordomo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Butler companion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Butler companion</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Show your social standing with a butler at your side: the ultimate status symbol! Your butler companion will always be at your service for refreshments. But watch that he doesn't drink from the bottle when you're not looking...[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Affirmez votre statut social avec ce compagnon majordome: toujours à votre service pour vous proposer un rafraîchissement, il sera le symbole de votre standing! Mais ne le quittez pas des yeux: Il serait capable de boire à la bouteille dès que vous aurez le dos tourné... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeigen Sie Ihre soziale Stellung mit einem Butler an Ihrer Seite: das ultimative Statussymbol! Ihr Butler Begleiter wird immer an Ihrem Service für Erfrischungen. Aber Vorsicht, dass er nicht aus der Flasche trinken, wenn Sie nicht auf der Suche...[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Affermare il proprio stato con questo maggiordomo compagno sempre al vostro servizio per offrirvi un drink, è il simbolo della vostra posizione! Ma attenzione: sarebbe in grado di bere dalla bottiglia non appena si accende la schiena... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Afirme su situación con este mayordomo compañero, siempre a su servicio para ofrecerle una copa. Pero sería capaz de beber de la botella tan pronto como le das la espalda... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Show your social standing with a butler at your side: the ultimate status symbol! Your butler companion will always be at your service for refreshments. But watch that he doesn't drink from the bottle when you're not looking...[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Show your social standing with a butler at your side: the ultimate status symbol! Your butler companion will always be at your service for refreshments. But watch that he doesn't drink from the bottle when you're not looking...[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kCompanionName1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Butler companion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Majordome</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Butler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maggiordomo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mayordomo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Butler companion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Butler companion</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>