<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Nis_Dots_No024</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Personnage 2D: Salvatore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドットオブジェ　追従必須！　極上のサルバトーレ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">도트 오브제 추종필수! 최상급의 살바토레</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Salvatore the Magnificent" Sprite Statue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">像素雕像 必需奉承！SALVATORE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">像素雕像 必需奉承！SALVATORE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">2D Character Objects: Salvatore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nis_dot_No024</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Untitled</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La statuette d'un personnage que tu peux mettre dans ta chambre pour décorer.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">誰が呼んだか十紳士。その１紳士が今、ドットオブジェとなって降臨！ナイスな見た目で判断するな！実は“紳士”には男も女も関係ないのだ！！そう、必要なのは“紳士なるココロ”であるからして！敵味方構わず荒唐無茶な命令を飛ばす、軍隊に所属していない軍人サルバトーレ！冷酷さと、ギャグの寒さに関して、彼女と競うのは命取り！※過酷な訓練を受けたいお客様推奨。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">누가 불렀는가 10신사. 그 1신사가 지금, 도트 오브제가 되어 강림! 나이스한 외모로 판단하지마! 사실 "신사"에는 남자도 여자도 관계없다!! 그래, 필요한 것은 "신사의 마음"이기 때문이지! 적이든 아군이든 상관없이 황당무계한 명령을 내리는, 군대에 소속되어 있지 않은 군인 살바토레! 냉혹함과 썰렁한 개그에 관해서, 그녀와 겨루는 것은 목숨걸기! ※과혹한 훈련을 받고 싶은 유저에게 추천.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">One of the Diez Gentlemen, Salvatore the Magnificent has descended to your world as a nice looking Sprite Statue. But don't let the word "gentleman" fool you. It has nothing to do with male or female, but what's in the heart! And Salvatore has an icy heart. She is a soldier without an army who barks reckless orders and tells stale jokes. Going up against her is a dance with death. Recommended for those who want to suffer through harsh training. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">所謂的十紳士之一，現在成為了像素雕像的一員！不要以外表來判斷，其實“紳士”跟男女無關！是的，重要的是從擁有“紳士心”開始！敵我不分、亂下荒唐命令、不屬於軍隊的軍人的Salvatore！如果想和她比冷酷無情及凶殘，可是要賭上一條命的！※推薦給想要接受嚴格訓練的您。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">所謂的十紳士之一，現在成為了像素雕像的一員！不要以外表來判斷，其實“紳士”跟男女無關！是的，重要的是從擁有“紳士心”開始！敵我不分、亂下荒唐命令、不屬於軍隊的軍人的Salvatore！如果想和她比冷酷無情及凶殘，可是要賭上一條命的！※推薦給想要接受嚴格訓練的您。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A small character statue that you can place to decorate your own room.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>