<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wise Man</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Homme sage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weiser</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Saggio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hombre sabio</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wisdom is hard earned and even harder kept. Luckily this wise man is on hand to remind you! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La sagesse est une chose difficile à gagner et encore plus à conserver. Heureusement, cet homme sage est là pour te le rappeler ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weisheit ist schwer zu erlangen und noch schwerer zu bewahren. Zum Glück hilft Ihnen dieser weise Mann dabei, Ihr Gedächtnis aufzufrischen! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La saggezza è difficile da ottenere, ed ancor più da conservare. Fortunatamente questo saggio ti aiuterà a ricordartelo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La sabiduría es difícil de adquirir, pero aún más difícil de conservar. ¡Por suerte este hombre está dispuesto a ayudarte! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CONTINUE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Continuer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weiter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Continua</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Continuar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BREAK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Break Cookie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Casser gâteau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Keks aufbrechen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Spezza Biscotto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Romper galleta</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">For them to perceive the advantage of defeating the enemy, they must also have their rewards.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour que le soldat mesure l'intérêt de vaincre son ennemi, une récompense est nécessaire.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Damit sie im Besiegen des Feindes einen Vorteil erkennen, müssen sie auch Belohnungen bekommen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Anche coloro che intuiscono il vantaggio nella sconfitta del nemico devono ricevere la loro ricompensa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Para que logren comprender las ventajas de derrotar al enemigo, es necesario que tengan una recompensa.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">He who is prudent and lies in wait for an enemy who is not, will be victorious.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Celui qui, prudent, reste tapi, prêt à affronter un ennemi qui ne l'est pas ; celui-là même sera victorieux.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Vorsichtige, der sich gegenüber einem unvorsichtigen Feind auf die Lauer legt, wird sicher siegen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chi è prudente e attende il nemico che non lo è, sarà vincitore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Quien sea prudente y aguarde tranquilamente a un enemigo que no lo es, saldrá victorioso.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">He who knows when he can fight and when he cannot, will be victorious.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Celui qui sait quand il est à propos de combattre, et quand il convient de se retirer sera victorieux.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Derjenige, der genau weiss, wann er kämpfen darf und wann nicht , wird sicher siegen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Colui che sa quando combattere e quando evitare il combattimento, sarà vincitore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aquel que sepa cuándo puede combatir y cuándo no, saldrá victorioso.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A jug fills drop by drop.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C'est goutte à goutte que se remplit une jarre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tropfen um Tropfen füllt sich der Krug.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La caraffa si riempie goccia a goccia.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una jarra se llena gota a gota.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ambition is like love, impatient both of delays and rivals.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'ambition est comme l'amour, jalouse et impatiente.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Streben ist wie die Liebe, es duldet weder Aufschub noch Rivalen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'ambizione è come l'amore, impaziente per i ritardi e infastidita dai rivali.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La ambición es como el amor, impaciente ante los retrasos y los rivales.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Do not dwell in the past, do not dream of the future, concentrate the mind on the present moment.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ne demeurez pas dans le passé, ne rêvez pas du futur, concentrez votre esprit sur le moment présent.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Laufe nicht der Vergangenheit nach und verliere dich nicht in der Zukunft. Das Leben ist hier und jetzt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non voltarti al passato e non sognare il futuro, ma concentra la mente sul presente.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No te encierres en el pasado, no sueñes con el futuro, que tu mente se centre en el momento presente.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">I do not believe in a fate that falls on men however they act; but I do believe in a fate that falls on them unless they act.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Je ne crois pas en un destin qui frappe l'homme selon ses actions ; mais je crois en un destin qui le frappe pour son inaction.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ich glaube nicht an ein Schicksal, das Menschen trifft, weil sie auf eine bestimmte Weise handeln, sondern an ein Schicksal, das Menschen trifft, die nicht handeln.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non credo in un destino che travolge gli uomini comunque essi agiscano. Credo in un destino che travolge gli uomini che non agiscono.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No creo en un destino que caiga sobre el hombre actúe como actúe. Pero sí creo en un destino que caiga sobre él si no actúa.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The mind is everything. What you think you become.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'esprit est tout. On devient ce que l'on pense.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das, was du heute denkst, wirst du morgen sein.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La mente può ogni cosa: diventerai ciò che pensi di diventare.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La mente lo es todo. Te conviertes en aquello que piensas.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE9</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">By three methods we may learn wisdom: First, by reflection, which is noblest; Second, by imitation, which is easiest; and third by experience, which is the bitterest.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il existe trois méthodes pour atteindre la sagesse : d'abord, par la réflexion, qui est la plus noble ; en second lieu, par l'imitation, qui est la plus facile ; et enfin, par l'expérience, qui est la plus amère.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Mensch hat dreierlei Wege klug zu handeln: Erstens durch Nachdenken, das ist der edelste. Zweitens durch Nachahmung, das ist der leichteste. Drittens durch Erfahrung, das ist der bitterste.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ci sono tre modi per imparare a essere saggi: il primo è con la riflessione, che è il più nobile; il secondo è con l'imitazione, che è il più semplice; e il terzo con l'esperienza, che è il più amaro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La sabiduría se puede obtener mediante tres métodos: primero, por reflexión, que es el más noble; segundo, por imitación, que es el más fácil; y tercero, por experiencia, que es el más amargo.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE10</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Faced with what is right, to leave it undone shows a lack of courage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quand on sait ce qui est juste, ne pas le faire démontre une absence de courage.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer eine Gelegenheit zu rechtschaffenem Tun sieht, sie aber nicht ergreift, der ist ein Feigling.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vedere ciò che è giusto fare, e non farlo, denota mancanza di coraggio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Percibir lo correcto y no hacerlo muestra falta de coraje.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Death and life have their determined appointments; riches and honors depend upon heaven.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vie et mort sont fixées par le destin, richesses et honneurs dépendent du Ciel.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Leben und Tod sind Angelegenheiten des Schicksals, Reichtum und Ehre hängen vom Himmel ab.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La vita e la morte sono momenti predestinati; la ricchezza e l'onore dipendono dal Cielo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La vida y la muerte tienen sus citas fijadas; riquezas y honores dependen del cielo.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE12</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Everything has beauty, but not everyone sees it.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La beauté est en toute chose, mais tous ne la voit pas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Alles hat seine Schönheit, doch nicht jeder sieht sie.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ogni cosa ha una propria bellezza, ma non tutti riescono a scorgerla.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cada cosa tiene su belleza, pero no todos pueden verla.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">For to win one hundred victories in one hundred battles is not the acme of skill. To subdue the enemy without fighting is the acme of skill.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Remporter cent victoires en cent combats n'est pas ce qu'il y a de mieux, soumettre l'ennemi sans combat est ce qu'il y a de mieux.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Einhundert Siege in einhundert Schlachten zu erringen, ist nicht der Gipfel der Vortrefflichkeit. Die Armee des Feindes ohne Kampf zu besiegen, ist der wahre Höhepunkt der Vorzüglichkeit.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il culmine del valore non è conquistare cento vittorie in cento battaglie bensì sottomettersi al nemico senza combattere.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Obtener cien victorias en cien batallas no es el colmo de la habilidad. Someter al enemigo sin combatir es el colmo de la habilidad.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE14</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If ignorant both of your enemy and yourself, you are certain to be in peril.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La défaite est assurée à celui qui ne connait ni lui-même, ni son ennemi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer weder den Feind noch sich selbst kennt, wird in jeder Schlacht unterliegen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se ignori te stesso quanto il tuo nemico, sei certamente in grande pericolo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si no conoces ni a tu enemigo ni a ti mismo, estarás en peligro.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE15</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Victorious warriors win first and then go to war, while defeated warriors go to war first and then seek to win.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un guerrier victorieux gagne la bataille avant de partir pour la guerre, un guerrier voué à la défaite combat dans l'espoir de gagner.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der siegreiche Stratege sucht den Kampf erst dann, wenn der Sieg bereits errungen ist, wogegen einer, der zum Untergang verurteilt ist, zuerst kämpft und danach den Sieg sucht.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I guerrieri vittoriosi prima vincono e poi vanno in guerra, mentre i perdenti vanno prima in guerra e poi cercano il modo di vincere.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los guerreros victoriosos primero vencen y después van a la guerra, mientras que los guerreros derrotados van primero a la guerra e intentan obtener la victoria después.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE16</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Do not overrate what you have received, nor envy others. He who envies others does not obtain peace of mind.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ne surestimez pas ce que vous avez, et n'enviez pas non plus votre prochain. L'esprit de celui qui envie son prochain n'est jamais en paix.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weder überschätze, was du erlangt hast, noch beneide andere. Wer andere beneidet, erlangt keinen geistigen Frieden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non attribuire troppa importanza a ciò che ricevi e non invidiare gli altri. L'invidioso vive in una perenne inquietudine.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No sobrevalores lo que has recibido, ni envidies a los demás. Aquel que envidie a los demás no obtendrá la paz mental.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE17</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">However many holy words you read, however many you speak, what good will they do you if you do not act upon them?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quel que soit le nombre de saintes paroles que vous lisez, que vous prononcez, quel bien vous feront-elles si vos actes ne s'y conforment pas ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">So viele heilige Worte du auch liest, so viele du auch sprichst, was sollen sie Gutes bewirken, wenn du nicht nach ihnen handelst?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per quante parole tu possa leggere, e per quante tu ne possa pronunciare, che bene possono procurarti se ad esse non fai seguire l'azione?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Puedes leer muchas palabras sagradas y puedes pronunciar muchas palabras sagradas, pero, ¿de qué valen si no actúas en consecuencia?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE18</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our greatest glory is not in never falling, but in rising every time we fall.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La plus grande gloire n'est pas de ne jamais tomber, mais de se relever à chaque chute.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stark zu sein bedeutet nicht, nie zu fallen, sondern immer wieder aufzustehen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La nostra gloria più grande non consiste nel non cadere mai ma nel rialzarsi dopo ogni caduta.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nuestra mayor gloria no es no haber caído nunca, sino levantarnos cada vez que caemos.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE19</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Real knowledge is to know the extent of one's ignorance.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le vrai savoir est de connaître l'étendue de sa propre ignorance.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Erkenntnis der eigenen Unwissenheit ist der erste Schritt zum Wissen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La vera sapienza è conoscere il limite del proprio sapere.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La verdadera sabiduría está en reconocer la propia ignorancia.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">COOKIE20</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Study the past, if you would divine the future.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Étudiez le passé si vous voulez connaître le futur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer in der Zukunft lesen will, muss in der Vergangenheit blättern.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Studia il passato, se vuoi anticipare il futuro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estudia el pasado si quieres pronosticar el futuro.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>