<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Long Range Plasma Emitter x 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Canon à plasma longue portée x 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Langstrecken-Plasma-Emitter x 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cannone al plasma a lungo raggio x 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cañón de plasma de largo alcance x 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">長距離プラズマエミッター x 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">장거리 플라즈마 발사기 x 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Long Range Plasma Emitter x 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">遠距離電漿發射器（2支）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">遠距離電漿發射器（2支）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Long Range Plasma Emitter x 2</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Display in your apartment for all your friends to see or attach it to your Salt Shooter hover tank and rip apart your enemies with this accurate, high velocity variant of the plasma cannon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">À exposer dans votre appartement pour que tous vos amis le voient ou à fixer à votre tank Salt Shooter pour réduire vos ennemis en pièces : version à haute précision et grande vitesse du canon à plasma [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Den Emitter kannst du in deiner Wohnung zur Geltung bringen, damit ihn alle deine Freunde sehen, oder du kannst ihn an deinem Salt Shooter-Luftkissenpanzer befestigen, um deine Feinde mit dieser zielgenauen Hochgeschwindigkeitsversion der Plasma-Kanone in Stücke zu reißen [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mostralo agli amici nel tuo appartamento, oppure installalo sul tuo aerocorazzato di Salt Shooter e disintegra i nemici con una versione di precisione a fuoco rapido del cannone al plasma [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Exponlo en tu apartamento para que lo vean tus amigos o acóplalo a tu tanque de Salt Shooter y acaba con tus enemigos con esta versión de gran precisión y velocidad del cañón de plasma [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">友達みんなに見えるように部屋に飾るか、または Salt Shooter ホバータンクに装着して、この正確で高速可変なプラズマキャノンで敵を八つ裂きにしよう。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">플라즈마 기관포의 고속 버전으로, 집안에 장식품으로 두고 친구들에게 자랑하셔도 좋고, Salt Shooter 호버 탱크에 장착해 적을 섬멸하는 용도로도 그만입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Display in your apartment for all your friends to see or attach it to your Salt Shooter hover tank and rip apart your enemies with this accurate, high velocity variant of the plasma cannon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">可供您在住所展示給所有朋友看，或者在 Salt Shooter 空浮坦克上使用，以精準、高速的電漿砲殲滅敵人。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">可供您在住所展示給所有朋友看，或者在 Salt Shooter 空浮坦克上使用，以精準、高速的電漿砲殲滅敵人。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Display in your apartment for all your friends to see or attach it to your Salt Shooter hover tank and rip apart your enemies with this accurate, high velocity variant of the plasma cannon. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>