<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Chrome Personal Transporter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Transporteur personnel chromé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Chrom Träger</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Transportatore cromo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Transportador cromo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Chrome Personal Transporter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Chrome Personal Transporter</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Explore PlayStation®Home in style, on this slick and modern vehicle! The wheels feature a pulsating neon light, which cycles through all colours. Hear the buzz of the electric engine as you travel around, and press square to turbo to the top speed! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Explorez PlayStation®Home avec style, aux commandes de ce véhicule moderne et élégant! Les roues sont ornées d'une lumière néon qui change de couleur et varie en intensité. Ecoutez le bourdonnement du moteur électrique, et pressez carré pour atteindre la vitesse maximale! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Entdecken Sie über PlayStation®Home in modernem Stil: fahren Sie dieser futuristische animierte Fahrzeug! Die pulsierende Neoneffekten durchlaufen alle Farben.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esplora PlayStation®Home con stile, con questo veiculo futuristica! Le luci al neon cambiano colore. Premere quadrato per andare a velocità 150%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Explora PlayStation®Home con estilo, con esto vehículo futuristo. Las luces de neón cambian de color. Pulse cuadrado para ir a la velocidad de 150%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Explore PlayStation®Home in style, on this slick and modern vehicle! The wheels feature a pulsating neon light, which cycles through all colors. Hear the buzz of the electric engine as you travel around, and press square to turbo to the top speed! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Explore PlayStation®Home in style, on this slick and modern vehicle! The wheels feature a pulsating neon light, which cycles through all colors. Hear the buzz of the electric engine as you travel around, and press square to turbo to the top speed! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>