<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hollywood Celebrity Bundle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack star hollywoodienne (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hollywood-Promi - Paket (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completo VIP di Hollywood (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de famoso de Hollywood (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">헐리우드 스타 세트 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Hollywood Celebrity Bundle (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">荷里活名人組合包（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">好萊塢名人組合包（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hollywood Celebrity Bundle (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It's not enough to look good in a crowd, you have to take it to the next level. Bundle includes a pair of glasses, top, bottom, shoes, a watch and earrings. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avoir du style au milieu de la foule, c'est bien, mais ça ne suffit pas. Le pack contient une paire de lunettes, un haut et un bas de vêtement, des chaussures, une montre et des boucles d'oreilles. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es reicht nicht, in der Menge nur gut auszusehen - man muss noch mehr bringen. Zum Paket gehören Brille, Oberteil, Unterteil, Schuhe, eine Uhr und Ohrringe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non basta solo essere belli, bisogna andare oltre. Il completo include un paio di occhiali, parte superiore e inferiore, scarpe, orologio e orecchini. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No basta con tener buen aspecto entre la multitud: hay que ir más allá si cabe. El conjunto incluye: gafas, chaqueta, pantalones, zapatos, reloj y pendientes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">사람들 속에서 멋진 모습을 보이는 것 만으로는 충분하지 않습니다. 이제 다음 단계로 넘어 가십시오. 이 세트는 헐리우드 스타 안경, 헐리우드 스타 상의, 헐리우드 스타 하의, 헐리우드 스타 신발, 헐리우드 스타 시계, 그리고 헐리우드 스타 귀걸이를 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">It's not enough to look good in a crowd, you have to take it to the next level. Bundle includes the Hollywood Celebrity Glasses, Hollywood Celebrity Top, Hollywood Celebrity Bottom, Hollywood Celebrity Shoes, Hollywood Celebrity Watch and Hollywood Celebrity Earrings. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">以衣著鶴立雞群是不足夠的，你需要提升到下一個層次。組合包包括荷里活名人眼鏡、荷里活名人服裝-上身、荷里活名人服裝-下身、荷里活名人鞋、荷里活名人手錶、及荷里活名人耳環。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">以衣著鶴立雞群是不足夠的，你需要提升到下一個層次。組合包包括好萊塢名人眼鏡、好萊塢名人服裝-上半身、好萊塢名人服裝-下半身、好萊塢名人鞋、好萊塢名人手錶、及好萊塢名人耳環。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">It's not enough to look good in a crowd, you have to take it to the next level. Bundle includes a pair of glasses, top, bottom, shoes, a watch and earrings. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>