<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Weapon Pad – The Devastator</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plateforme d'arme – Le dévastateur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Waffenpad – Der Zerstörer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pedana armi – Devastatore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Panel de armas - El Devastador</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Weapon Pad – The Devastator</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Place this item in your MiniBots Training Facility to allow Devastators to be equipped. Anyone who owns the Devastator hand item can equip the Devastator at this pad during a multiplayer game. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Placez cet élément dans votre centre d'entraînement MiniBots pour qu'il soit possible de s'équiper avec les dévastateurs. N'importe qui peut s'équiper avec le dévastateur de cette plateforme pendant une partie multijoueur s'il possède l'élément de main dévastateur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Platzieren Sie dieses Objekt in Ihre MiniBots-Trainingsanlage, damit Zerstörer damit ausgestattet werden kann. Jeder der das Zerstörer-Handobjekt besitzt, kann das Der Zerstörer in diesem Pad in einem Multiplayer-Spiel bestücken. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Colloca questo elemento nella struttura di addestramento Minibot per consentire l'equipaggiamento con Devastatore. Chiunque possieda l'elemento Devastatore può dotarsene in questa pedana durante una partita in modalità multigiocatore. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Coloca este artículo en tus instalaciones de entrenamiento de MiniBots para permitir que los Devastadores estén equipados. Cualquier propietario del artículo de mano Devastador puede equipar el Devastador en este panel durante una partida para varios jugadores. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Place this item in your MiniBots Training Facility to allow Devastators to be equipped. Anyone who owns the Devastator hand item can equip the Devastator at this pad during a multiplayer game. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>