<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Street Style 3 - Mega Bundle 02 (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Street Style 3 - Méga lot 02 (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Street Style 3 - Mega-Paket 02 (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Street Style 3 - Mega Set 02 (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Street Style 3 - Mega Pack 02 (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hit the streets in style with this selection of Hip Hop inspired outfits!\n
\n
This bundle contains:\n
(1) Street Style - Shine Cropped Jacket - Maroon (Women)\n
(2) Street Style - Shine Cropped Jacket - Silver (Women)\n
(3) Street Style - Shine Cropped Jacket - Purple (Women)\n
(4) Street Style - Shine Leather Pants and Boots - Purple (Women)\n
(5) Street Style - Shine Leather Pants and Boots - Turquoise (Women)\n
(6) Street Style - Shine Leather Pants and Boots - Red (Women) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Parcourez les rues avec style grâce à cette sélection de tenus d'inspiration Hip Hop !\n
\n
Ce lot contient :\n
(1) Street Style - Blouson court brillant - Bordeaux (femme)\n
(2) Street Style - Blouson court brillant - Argent (femme)\n
(3) Street Style - Blouson court brillant - Mauve (femme)\n
(4) Street Style - Pantalon et bottes de cuir brillant - Mauve (femme)\n
(5) Street Style - Pantalon et bottes de cuir brillant - Turquoise (femme)\n
(6) Street Style - Pantalon et bottes de cuir brillant - Rouge (femme) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erobern Sie die Straßen mit Stil in diesen vom Hip Hop inspirierten Outfits!\n
\n
Dieses Paket enthält:\n
(1) Street Style - Shine Kurze Jacke - Braun (Damen)\n
(2) Street Style - Shine Kurze Jacke - Silber (Damen)\n
(3) Street Style - Shine Kurze Jacke - Lila (Damen)\n
(4) Street Style - Shine Lederhose und Stiefel - Lila (Damen)\n
(5) Street Style - Shine Lederhose und Stiefel - Türkis (Damen)\n
(6) Street Style - Shine Lederhose und Stiefel - Rot (Damen) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scendi in strada con un look super trendy grazie a questa selezione di abbigliamento di ispirazione hip hop!\n
\n
Il set comprende:\n
(1) Street Style - Giacca Corta Lucida - Bordeaux (Donna)\n
(2) Street Style - Giacca Corta Lucida - Argento (Donna)\n
(3) Street Style - Giacca Corta Lucida - Viola (Donna)\n
(4) Street Style - Pantaloni e Stivali di pelle Lucidi - Viola (Donna)\n
(5) Street Style - Pantaloni e Stivali di pelle Lucidi - Turchese (Donna)\n
(6) Street Style - Pantaloni e Stivali di pelle Lucidi - Rosso (Donna) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Sal a la calle con estilo gracias a esta selección de ropa inspirada en el Hip-hop!\n
\n
Este pack contiene:\n
(1) Street Style - Shine Chaqueta corta - Granate (Mujer)\n
(2) Street Style - Shine Chaqueta corta - Plata (Mujer)\n
(3) Street Style - Shine Chaqueta corta - Violeta (Mujer)\n
(4) Street Style - Shine Pantalón y botas de cuero - Violeta (Mujer)\n
(5) Street Style - Shine Pantalón y botas de cuero - Turquesa (Mujer)\n
(6) Street Style - Shine Pantalón y botas de cuero - Rojo (Mujer) [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>