<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Jewel of the Skies</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Joyau des Cieux</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Himmelsjuwel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Gioiello dei Cieli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La joya celestial</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">空の宝石</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">천상의 보석</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Jewel of the Skies</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">天空之珠</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">天空之珠</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Jewel of the Skies</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Jewel of the Skies was once a flourishing village in the clouds, each palace and dwelling accessible only by flying carpet. Long ago this magical knowledge was lost and the towers and spires gradually fell into disrepair until only a few remained. Awaken the Genie, unleash his magic and reap the rewards!\n\n
• Flying Carpet Gem Collection Mini-game\n
• Interactive Genie\n 
• Unlockable rewards and apartment customisations\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Joyau des Cieux était autrefois un village prospère dans les nuages et dont les palaces et les habitations n'étaient accessibles qu'en tapis volants. Il y a longtemps, ce savoir magique fut perdu, et les tours et les flèches tombèrent en ruines jusqu'à ce qu'il n'en reste que quelques unes. Réveillez le génie, libérez sa magie et récoltez les bénéfices !\n\n
• Mini-jeu Tapis volant de la collection Pierre précieuse\n
• Génie interactif\n 
• Personnalisations d'appartement et récompenses indéverrouillables\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Himmelsjuwel war einst florierendes Dorf in den Wolken, in dem jeder Palast und jedes Haus nur mit einem fliegenden Teppich zu erreichen war. Vor langer, langer Zeit ging dieses magische Wissen verloren und die Türme der Paläste verfielen, bis nur noch wenige übrig waren. Erwecke den Flaschengeist, entfessele seinen Zauber und du wirst belohnt werden!\n\n
• Minispiel: Fliegender-Teppich-Juwelenjagd\n
• Interaktiver Flaschengeist\n 
• Freischaltbare Belohnungen und Appartementanpassungen\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Gioiello dei Cieli era uno dei villaggi più fiorenti nelle nuvole, ogni palazzo e dimora era accessibile solo grazie ai tappeti volanti. Tanto tempo fa questa sapienza magica è andata perduta e le torri e le guglie gradualmente sono cadute in rovina e ormai ne rimangono pochissime. Risveglia il genio, libera la sua magia e raccogli le ricompense!\n\n
• Mini gioco Raccogli le gemme con il tappeto volante\n
• Genio interattivo\n 
• Ricompense sbloccabili e personalizzazione dell'appartamento\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La joya celestial fue una antigua y próspera aldea situada en las alturas a cuyos palacios y viviendas solo se podía acceder mediante alfombra voladora. Su magia y tecnología desapareció hace mucho tiempo y apenas unos cuantos chapiteles y torres de sus edificios se mantienen hoy en pie. Despierta al genio, libera su poder y consigue tu recompensa.\n\n
• Minijuego de recolección de joyas en alfombra voladora.\n
• Genio interactivo.\n 
• Nuevos premios y mejoras para tu apartamento.\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">空の宝石はかつて誰にも知られていませんでした。空飛ぶ絨毯でしかいけない。しかし徐々に消えてゆく中ジーニーの魔法によってよみがえりました！\n\n
•空飛ぶ絨毯ゲーム\n
• インタラクティブジーニー\n 
• アパートカスタマイズと賞品をゲットしよう。\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">천상의 보석은 한 때 오직 공중을 나는 카페트로만 모든 궁전과 거주지에 접근할 수 있는 구름 속의 번성한 마을이었어요. 오래 전에 이런 마법의 지식이 자취를 감추면서 타워와 첨탑들이 점점 무너져 황폐해지고, 이제는 일부만이 남아 있답니다. 지니를 깨워 그의 마법을 풀고 보상품을 획득하세요!\n\n

이 스페이스에는 다음이 포함됩니다:
● 마법의 카페트 보석 콜렉션 미니게임\n
● 인터액티브 지니\n 
● 해제 가능한 보상품과 아파트 꾸미기 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Jewel of the Skies was once a flourishing village in the clouds, each palace and dwelling accessible only by flying carpet. Long ago this magical knowledge was lost and the towers and spires gradually fell into disrepair until only a few remained. Awaken the Genie, unleash his magic and reap the rewards!\n\n
• Flying Carpet Gem Collection Mini-game\n
• Interactive Genie\n 
• Unlockable rewards and apartment customisations\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">天空之珠曾經是天際雲端的繁華村莊，必須乘坐飛毯才能到達每座宮殿和住所。天空之城的秘密早已失傳，這些高樓、尖塔因為年久失修最後墜入地面，現在只剩下斷垣殘壁。只要叫醒精靈，就能發現奧妙所在，並且獲得獎品道具！\n\n

此空間包括：\n
●飛毯蒐寶迷你遊戲\n
●互動精靈\n 
●獎品道具和公寓自訂功能 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">天空之珠曾經是天際雲端的繁華村莊，必須乘坐飛毯才能到達每座宮殿和住所。天空之城的秘密早已失傳，這些高樓、尖塔因為年久失修最後墜入地面，現在只剩下斷垣殘壁。只要叫醒精靈，就能發現奧妙所在，並且獲得獎品道具！\n\n

此空間包括：\n
●飛毯蒐寶迷你遊戲\n
●互動精靈\n 
●獎品道具和公寓自訂功能 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Jewel of the Skies was once a flourishing village in the clouds, each palace and dwelling accessible only by flying carpet. Long ago this magical knowledge was lost and the towers and spires gradually fell into disrepair until only a few remained. Awaken the Genie, unleash his magic and reap the rewards!\n\n
• Flying Carpet Gem Collection Mini-game\n
• Interactive Genie\n 
• Unlockable rewards and apartment customisations\n [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>