<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Kicking In Top - Mo-Mint (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Haut Kicking In - Mo-Mint (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Kicking In Oberteil - Minze (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Kicking In Maglia - Mo-Mint (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Kicking In Camiseta - Color menta Mo (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our Shine On collection radiates with fashions that are inspired by the adventure-seeker in all of us. Playful and lighthearted, each design is ready to travel the globe in search of treasures, enlightenment, and like-minded souls. This super soft knit top features a henley placket with a scallop hemline and a patch pocket at the chest. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Notre collection Shine On rayonne avec des articles de mode inspirés par l'aventurière qui sommeille en nous. Espiègle et enjouée, chaque création est prête à traverser le monde en quête de trésors, d'éveil spirituel et d'âmes sœurs. Ce haut tricoté super doux comporte une patte de boutonnage « henley » avec un ourlet ondulé et une poche rapportée sur la poitrine. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unsere Shine On Kollektion besticht durch modische Details, die die Abenteuerlust in uns allen ansprechen. Die verspielt fröhlichen Designs sind ideal für die Reise und die Suche nach Schätzen, Erleuchtung und Gleichgesinnten geeignet. Superweiches Strickoberteil mit Henley-Knopfleiste, attraktivem Rollsaum und Flickenbrusttasche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La nostra collezione Shine On emana uno stile ispirato all'amante dell'avventura che c'è in ognuno di noi. Sbarazzino e leggero, ogni design è pronto a viaggiare il mondo in cerca di tesori, ispirazione e anime gemelle. Questa maglia ultra morbida presenta una scollatura in stile serafina, orlo stondato e tasca sul petto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nuestra colección Shine On brilla con estilos inspirados en la aventurera que todas llevamos dentro. Traviesos y desenfadados, cada uno de los diseños está hecho para viajar por el mundo en busca de tesoros, conocimiento y almas gemelas.  Esta camiseta de punto súper suave presenta  una abertura vertical con botones en el cuello, el bajo en curva y bolsillo exterior en el pecho. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>