<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CS2_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome, young traveller. This is the land we cannot leave.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue, jeune voyageur. Voici les terres que nous ne pouvons quitter.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen. Dieses Land können wir nicht verlassen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuto, giovane viaggiatore. Questa è la terra che non possiamo abbandonare.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido, joven viajero. Esta es la tierra de la que no podemos salir.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CS2_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The sea is vast. We will need the most powerful magic to summon the Great Ice to carry us home.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La mer est vaste. Nous aurons besoin de la plus puissante des magies pour demander à la Grande glace de nous ramener chez nous.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Meer ist zu groß. Wir werden die mächtigste Magie brauchen, um das Große Eis heraufzubeschwören und nach Hause gelangen zu können.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il mare è enorme. Per evocare il Grande Gelo che ci porterà a casa ci servirà la magia più potente di tutte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El mar es inmenso. Necesitaremos la magia más poderosa para invocar al Gran Hielo que nos llevará a casa.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CS2_3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You and your kind have reclaimed many Hearts. But now they must be filled with the strongest magic.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous et les vôtres avez récupéré beaucoup de cœurs, mais à présent il faut les remplir avec la plus grande des magies.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du und deine Leute haben viele Herzen zurückgebracht. Doch nun müssen sie mit der stärksten Magie gefüllt werden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tu e la tua gente avete recuperato molti Cuori. Ma ora devono essere riempiti con la magia più potente.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tú y los tuyos habéis reunido muchos corazones. Pero ahora hay que llenarlos con la magia más potente.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CS2_4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">When this is done, our quest will be complete and the Bears of the Northern Kingdom will forever sing your song.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quand ce sera fait, notre quête sera terminée et les Ours du Royaume du Nord chanteront à jamais vos louanges.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sobald dies vollbracht ist, wird unsere Mission abgeschlossen sein und die Bären des Nördlichen Königreichs werden bis in alle Ewigkeit dein Lied singen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una volta fatto ciò, la nostra ricerca sarà completa e gli Orsi del Regno del Nord tesseranno per sempre le tue lodi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuando lo hagamos, nuestra misión habrá terminado y los osos del reino del Norte cantarán para siempre tu canción.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CS3_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Thank you, young traveller. With your help we have called the Great Ice. The sea is frozen and now we must depart.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Merci, jeune voyageur. Grâce à votre aide, nous avons pu appeler la Grande glace. La mer est gelée et à présent nous devons partir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vielen Dank. Mit deiner Hilfe konnten wir das Große Eis heraufbeschwören. Das Meer ist zugefroren und jetzt müssen wir uns verabschieden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Grazie, giovane viaggiatore. Con il tuo aiuto abbiamo evocato il Grande Gelo. Il mare è ghiacciato e adesso dobbiamo partire. </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Gracias, joven viajero. Con tu ayuda, hemos llamado al Gran Hielo. El mar se ha congelado y ahora debemos marcharnos.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CS3_2A</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our way Home is long but our path is assured.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le chemin du retour sera long, mais la voie est assurée.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unser Weg nach Hause ist zwar weit, aber er ist sicher.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La via del ritorno è lunga, ma la strada è segnata.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El camino a casa es largo, pero la senda ya es segura.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CS3_2B</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">For that, we have you and your people to thank.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Merci à vous et aux vôtres.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dafür müssen wir dir und deinesgleichen danken.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per questo, dobbiamo ringraziare te e la tua gente.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Debemos agradecéroslo a ti y a tu gente.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CS3_3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The help that you have given us will never be forgotten. </LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nous n'oublierons jamais l'aide que vous nous avez apportée.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Deine Hilfe wird auf ewig unvergessen bleiben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'aiuto che ci hai dato non sarà mai dimenticato.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Jamás olvidaremos la ayuda que nos habéis prestado. </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">CS3_4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">I sense that one day we will see each other again and that this land will become a place for all of our people. </LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Je pressens qu'un jour nous nous reverrons et que nous nous retrouverons tous sur cette terre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ich spüre, dass wir uns eines Tages wiedersehen werden, und dass dieses Land einmal ein Ort für alle Völker sein wird.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sento che un giorno ci rivedremo e questa terrà diventerà un posto dove tutti noi potremo vivere assieme. </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Presiento que un día volveremos a vernos y que esta tierra será un lugar para todos nuestros pueblos. </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Frozen Waste [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Désert de glace [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gefrorene Einöde [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Distesa Di Ghiaccio [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Páramo helado [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Frozen Waste </LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Désert de glace</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gefrorene Einöde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Distesa Di Ghiaccio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Páramo helado </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
