<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Torso_bi_soldier_Re</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Black Irem Brigade Shirt (Replica, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">T-Shirt de la Brigade Noire Irem (Réplique, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Black Irem Brigade"-T-Shirt (Replik, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maglia della Brigata Black Irem (replica, da uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta ajustada del Escuadrón Irem Negro (réplica, H)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブラックアイレム団戦闘員　トップス（レプリカ・男性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블랙 아이렘단 전투원 상의（레플리카, 남성）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Combatant of the Black Irem Brigade - Top (Replica/Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">黑色Irem團戰鬥員 上衣（複製品/男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">黑色Irem團戰鬥員 上衣（複製品/男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Black Irem Brigade Shirt (Replica, M)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Torso_bi_soldier_Re_description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A hi-tech combat suit worn by combatants in the Black Irem Brigade that offers amazing levels of maneuverability. However, due to its formfitting design, the suit isn't very popular with combatants who have a less than desirable physique.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une tenue de combat high-tech portée par les combattants de la Brigade Noire Irem offrant des options incroyables de manœuvrabilité. Cependant, à cause de son design près du corps, la tenue n'est pas très populaire auprès des combattants qui ont un physique moins avantageux. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Hightech-Kampfanzug, der von den Kämpfern der Black Irem Brigade getragen wird und einzigartige Bewegungsmöglichkeiten bietet. Aufgrund des körperbetonten Designs ist der Anzug bei Kämpfern mit schlechter trainierten Körpern eher weniger beliebt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tuta da combattimento ad alto contenuto tecnologico, indossata dai combattenti della Brigata Black Irem, che offre un'incredibile libertà di movimento. Per il fatto di essere estremamente aderente, però, non gode di una grande popolarità tra quei soldati che non hanno una linea diciamo perfetta.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una prenda de combate de alta tecnología utilizada por los combatientes del Escuadrón Irem Negro que permite un impresionante nivel de movimiento. Sin embargo, debido a su ceñido diseño, el traje no es del agrado de los combatientes que tienen un físico no muy agraciado.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブラックアイレム団の戦闘員たちが着用するスーツ。身軽に行動できるよう驚くほど軽く作られた万能スーツ。ただし、体にぴったりフィットするため、自分の体形に自信がない戦闘員からの評判が悪い。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블랙 아이렘단의 전투원들이 착용하는 의상. 가볍게 움직일 수 있도록 놀라울 정도로 가볍게 만들어진 만능 의상. 단, 몸에 딱 맞게 피트되므로 스스로의 체형에 자신이 없는 전투원의 평가는 그다지 좋지 않다.[#Legal]
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The suit worn by Combatants of the Black Irem Brigade. This multifunctional suit was made surprisingly light to allow for easy movement. However, since it fits really tightly, Combatants with low confidence in their body shapes don't like it much.[#Legal]
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">黑色Irem團的戰鬥員們所穿的衣服。為了讓行動方便而製作出的輕便萬能衣。但因為很貼身，所以不受對自己身材沒自信的戰鬥員喜愛。[#Legal]
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">黑色Irem團的戰鬥員們所穿的衣服。為了讓行動方便而製作出的輕便萬能衣。但因為很貼身，所以不受對自己身材沒自信的戰鬥員喜愛。[#Legal]
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A hi-tech combat suit worn by combatants in the Black Irem Brigade that offers amazing levels of maneuverability. However, due to its formfitting design, the suit isn't very popular with combatants who have a less than desirable physique.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>