<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Behemoth Ship Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack Vaisseau Behemoth</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Koloss-Schiff-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pack Navicella Behemoth</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack Nave Behemoth</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This pack unlocks the large and powerful Behemoth ship for use in Killer Plants from Outer Space. The Behemoth ship is deceptively fast and with a huge capacity to carry power-ups. Also included in this pack is a Behemoth ship T-shirt (both male and female versions included), and a Behemoth ship model to place in your apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce pack déverrouille l'impressionnant et puissant Behemoth à utiliser dans Killer Plants From Outer Space. Il est incroyablement rapide et peut embarquer d'innombrables power-ups. Vous trouverez également dans ce pack un t-shirt vaisseau Behemoth (versions homme et femme incluses) et un vaisseau Behemoth miniature pour décorer votre appartement. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Paket schaltet für "Killer Plants from Outer Space" das mächtige Koloss-Schiff frei. Es ist überraschend schnell und kann Unmengen von Power-ups transportieren. Ebenfalls im Paket enthalten ist ein Koloss-Schiff-Shirt (Damen und Herren) und ein Koloss-Schiff-Modell für Ihr Apartment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo pack consente di sbloccare la grande e potente navicella Behemoth, utilizzabile in Killer Plants from Outer Space. Si tratta di un veicolo insospettabilmente veloce ed enormemente potenziabile. Il pack include anche una t-shirt raffigurante la navicella Behemoth (in doppia versione per uomo e donna) e un modellino da sfoggiare nel tuo appartamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este pack desbloquea la grande y poderosa nave Behemoth para usarla en Killer Plants from Outer Space. La nave Behemoth es engañosamente rápida y con una gran capacidad para llevar potenciadores. También se incluye en el pack una camiseta de nave Behemoth (para hombre y mujer) y una reproducción a escapa de la nave Windrush para colocarla en tu apartamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>