<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sapphire - Sparkle Hair (for her)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Saphir - Coiffure Étincelante (pour femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Saphir - Glitzerhaar (für Sie)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Zaffiro - Capelli Scintillio (per lei)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Zafiro - Peinado Brillante (para ella)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sapphire - Sparkle Hair (for her)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ever wanted to be a star of the glitter ball? Ever wanted to grab your partner and sparkle in the limelight? Now you can!  So shine bright like a diamond, sparkle with success and bring on the bling! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez toujours rêvé de briller de mille feux ? Vous mourrez d'envie de rayonner sous les feux de la rampe avec votre partenaire ? C'est maintenant à votre portée !  Brillez de mille feux et éblouissez le monde entier grâce à votre côté bling-bling ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Träumst du davon der Star des Glitzer-Tanzes zu sein? Wolltest du schon immer deinen Partner schnappen und mit ihm im Rampenlich tanzen? Jetzt kannst du das!  Strahle also wie ein Diamant, glitzere mit Erfolg und zeige deine Klunkern! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai mai desiderato essere una star della sfera specchiata? Hai mai desiderato afferrare il tuo partner e brillare insieme nelle luci della ribalta? Ora puoi!  Brilla come un diamante, illuminati di successo e scegli il luccichio! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Alguna vez has soñado con ser la estrella de la pista de baile? ¿Has querido deslumbrar a todos bailando con tu pareja bajo los focos? ¡Pues ahora puedes! ¡Ponte tus joyas, reluce como un diamante y brilla de éxito! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ever wanted to be a star of the glitter ball? Ever wanted to grab your partner and sparkle in the limelight? Now you can!  So shine bright like a diamond, sparkle with success and bring on the bling! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>