<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Seal Point Siamese Girl Kitten</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chatte Siamoise Colourpoint</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Seal Point Siam-Kätzchen, weiblich</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cucciolo di siamese seal point (femmina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Gatita siamesa de pelo corto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">シャム子猫　雌</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">실 포인트 샴 암컷 아기고양이</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Seal Point Siamese Girl Kitten</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">海豹色幼暹邏貓（母）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">海豹色幼暹邏貓（母）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Seal Point Siamese Girl Kitten</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Siamese cats are known for their grace and beauty. This little 'un isn't quite there yet, but a playful youngster's much more fun than a stuck up adult anyway! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les chats siamois sont connus pour leur grâce et leur beauté. Ce chaton n'en est pas encore là, mais un jeune joueur est bien plus amusant qu'un adulte hautain quoi qu'il arrive !  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Siamkatzen sind für ihre Anmut und Schönheit bekannt. Dieser kleine Schatz ist zwar noch nicht soweit, doch ein verspielter Halbwüchsiger macht sowieso viel mehr Spaß als ein hochnäsiges erwachsenes Tier. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I siamesi sono famosi per la loro grazia e bellezza. Questo cucciolo è ancora piccolino per mostrare queste doti, ma è un grande giocherellone, di certo molto più divertente di un adulto presuntuoso! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los gatos siameses son conocidos por su elegancia y belleza. Esta gatita todavía es demasiado pequeña, ¡pero es muy juguetona y mucho más divertida que un gato adulto estirado! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">シャム猫はそのエレガントさで飼い主を満たします。まだ赤ちゃんのこの子はまだまだ遊び足りない子猫ちゃんです。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">샴고양이는 그 우아함과 아름다움이 널리 알려져 있습니다. 이 새끼 고양이는 아직 그 정도는 아니지만 점잖게 앉아 있는 큰 고양이보다는 훨씬 활발해서 재미 있을 거에요! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Siamese cats are known for their grace and beauty. This little 'un isn't quite there yet, but a playful youngster's much more fun than a stuck up adult anyway! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">暹邏貓以外型美麗優雅著稱。這個小傢伙雖然還沒長成，卻是一個開心果，比那些擺架子的成貓好玩多了！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">暹邏貓以外型美麗優雅著稱。這個小傢伙雖然還沒長成，卻是一個開心果，比那些擺架子的成貓好玩多了！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Siamese cats are known for their grace and beauty. This little 'un isn't quite there yet, but a playful youngster's much more fun than a stuck up adult anyway! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>