<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Space Ace Outfit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Costume Space Ace</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Space Ace - Outfit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completo da Space Ace</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Atuendo de Space Ace</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_AceSt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_AceSt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_AceSt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_AceSt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_AceSt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Space Ace Outfit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Now's it's your turn to take on Borf! Ace's outfit has been perfectly designed with you in mind. Form fitting for those late night space battles and extra tough should a laser blast get a little closer than you thought it would. It's a good thing you had on this classic Space Ace jumpsuit...the galaxy is a dangerous place! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C'est maintenant à votre tour de vous battre contre Borf! La tenue de Ace a été spécialement conçue pour vous. Coupée pour ces batailles dans l'espace du bout de la nuit et super résistante au cas où un laser vous approcherait plus près que vous ne l'auriez pensé. C'est une bonne chose que vous ayiez cette combinaison classique Space Ace ... La galaxie est un endroit dangereux! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nun ist es an Dir, gegen Borf anzutreten! Aces Outfit wurde perfekt auf Deinen Leib angepaßt. Der Schnitt ist perfekt für die spät Nachts stattfindenen Raumkämpfe und das Material extra stark für den Fall, daß Dir ein feindlicher Laserstrahl etwas zu nahe kommt. Gut, daß Du diesen klassischen Raumanzug anhast, die Galaxie ist ein gefährlicher Ort! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ora tocca a te affrontare Borf! Il completo da Ace è stato realizzato con te in mente. Forme adeguate a quelle battaglie spaziali a notte fonda e rinforzi extra in caso un laser colpisca un po' più vicino di dove pensavi che arrivasse. Meno male che hai questao classico completo da Space Ace... la galassia è un posto pericoloso! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Ahora es tu turno de enfrentarte a Borf! El traje de Ace ha sido perfectamente diseñado pensando en ti. De forma ajustada para aquellas batallas espaciales nocturnas y extra resistente, por si un disparo láser se acerca más de lo que tu pensabas. ¡Qué bueno que tienes este clásico traje de Space Ace... la galaxia es un lugar peligroso! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_AceSt [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_AceSt [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_AceSt [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_AceSt [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_AceSt [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Now's it's your turn to take on Borf! Ace's outfit has been perfectly designed with you in mind. Form fitting for those late night space battles and extra tough should a laser blast get a little closer than you thought it would. It's a good thing you had on this classic Space Ace jumpsuit...the galaxy is a dangerous place! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>