<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Apprentice Outfit Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble tenue d'apprenti</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schüler Outfit-Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Costume Apprendista Pacchetto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de aprendiz Conjunto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Apprentice Outfit Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">(Bundle) A powerful, almost primal Force wielder, Darth Vader's secret apprentice has been trained by the Dark Lord of the Sith to hunt down the last remaining Jedi.  Includes the Apprentice Costume and Hair. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">(Ensemble) Doté d'une force puissante, presque primaire, l'apprenti secret de Dark Vador a été formé par le Seigneur Noir des Sith pour traquer les derniers Jedi. Comprend les cheveux et le costume d'apprenti.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">(Pack) Ein machtvoller, fast ursprünglicher Machtwurf. Darth Vaders geheimer Schüler wurde vom Dunklen Lord der Sith ausgebildet, um die letzten verbleibenden Jedi aufzuspüren. Beinhaltet die Schüler-Kleidung und Frisur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">(Pacchetto) Potente e abile nel controllare la Forza, l'apprendista segreto di Dart Fener è stato addestrato dal misterioso signore dei Sith affinché dia la caccia all'ultimo Jedi. Include Costume e Capelli da Apprendista. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">(Conjunto) Poderoso, autoridad fundamental poseedora de la Fuerza, el aprendiz secreto de Darth Vader ha sido entrenado por el Señor Oscuro de los Sith para acabar con los últimos Jedi. Incluye el traje y el pelo del aprendiz. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">(Bundle) A powerful, almost primal Force wielder, Darth Vader's secret apprentice has been trained by the Dark Lord of the Sith to hunt down the last remaining Jedi.  Includes the Apprentice Costume and Hair. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>