<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Window Flat – White</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Châssis avec fenêtre - Blanc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fensterwand – Weiß</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Parete con Finestra - Bianca</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ventana lisa - Blanca</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ウィンドウ・フラット - ホワイト</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Window Flat – White</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A perfectly designed wall flat for your LOOT™ Stage Set! Go ahead, you can hug us, we know you want to. Check out the Stage Set – Flat Collection for an exclusive item! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un châssis parfait pour votre décor de plateau LOOT™ ! Vous pouvez nous embrasser, vous en mourez d'envie. Allez voir la Collection décors - Châssis pour découvrir l'élément exclusif ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine perfekt entworfene Wandfläche für dein LOOT™ Stage Set! Na, umarme uns schon, wir wissen, dass du das willst! In der Stage Set – Wand-Kollektion findest du einen exklusiven Artikel! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una parete perfetta per la tua Scenografia LOOT™! Abbracciaci pure, se vuoi. Sappiamo che desideri farlo. Trova un elemento esclusivo in Scenografia - Set Completo di Pareti! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Una pared perfectamente diseñada para tu estudio LOOT™! Adelante, puedes abrazarnos, sabemos que quieres hacerlo. ¡Busca la colección de paredes de estudio para conseguir un producto exclusivo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">本コンテンツは、パーソナルスペース「LOOT™スタジオ・ステージ・セット・バンドル」用にカスタマイズされております。このため、パーソナルスペース「ベーシック」などの天井の低いプライベートラウンジ（パーソナルスペース/クラブハウス）において、正常に設置できない場合があります。予めご了承ください。\n\n
映画のセットにぴったりのウォール・フラット！これをお望みだったのでしょう？さあ、ハグしましょう。限定アイテムのステージ・セット – フラット・コレクションをチェック！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A perfectly designed wall flat for your LOOT™ Stage Set! Go ahead, you can hug us, we know you want to. Check out the Stage Set – Flat Collection for an exclusive item! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>