<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Midas Reactive Defense Leggings (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Collants de défense réactive Midas (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Midas reaktive Verteidigungsleggins (weibliche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Difesa reattiva Mida - Gambali (per donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mallas de reactivación de defensa Midas (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ミダス反応防御システムレギンス（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Midas Reactive Defense Leggings (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Midas Reactive Defense Leggings (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">These are the leggings for the Midas Reactive Defense System.\n\n Co-developed by Obsidian and Earth Fleet scientists, the Midas Reactive Defense System utilizes the core components from Obsidian armor, forming a metallic substance that is soft and pliable at room temperature.  The final compound binds directly to a human pilot's skin, instantly absorbing most energy-based attacks when a gentle charge of Nebulon energy is applied.  This item passively absorbs Nebulon, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base Nebulon gains by about 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce sont les collants pour le système de défense réactive Midas.\n\n Co-développé par les scientifiques des forces obsidienne et terriennes, le système de défense réactive Midas utilise les composants cœur d'une armure obsidienne, formant une substance métallique molle et malléable à température ambiante. Le composant final se colle directement sur la peau d'un pilote humain, absorbant instantanément la plupart des attaques basées sur l'énergie lorsqu'une légère charge d'énergie Nébulon est appliquée. Cet objet absorbe passivement le Nébulon, augmentant efficacement vos gains en Nébulon de base Novus Prime d'approximativement 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hierbei handelt es sich um die Leggins von Midas reaktivem Verteidigungssystem.\n\n Mitentwickelt von Wissenschaftlern der Obsidian- und Erdenflotte verwendet Midas reaktives Verteidigungssystem Kernkomponenten der Obsidian-Rüstung und bildet eine metallische Substanz, die bei Zimmertemperatur sowohl weich als auch biegsam ist. Die letzte Verbindung heftet sich direkt an die menschliche Haut der Piloten und absorbiert umgehend die meisten energiebasierten Angriffe, sobald eine leichte Ladung Nebulon-Energie angelegt wird. Dieser Ausrüstungsgegenstand absorbiert zusätzlich Nebulon und erhöht die Zufuhr von Nebulon deiner Novus Prime Basis effektiv um ca. 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questi sono i gambali del Sistema di difesa reattivo Mida.\n\n Frutto della collaborazione tra gli Obsidian e gli scienziati della flotta terrestre, il Sistema di difesa reattivo Mida sfrutta i componenti del nucleo dell'Armatura Obsidian, che creano una sostanza metallica soffice e flessibile a temperatura ambiente. Il composto finale si avvinghia direttamente alla pelle del pilota umano e assorbe all'istante la maggior parte degli attacchi energetici presentanti una carica di energia nebulon moderata. Questo oggetto assorbe passivamente l'energia nebulon, incrementando l'assorbimento della stessa da parte della base Novus Prime di circa il 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estas son las mallas del sistema de reactivación de defensa Midas.\n\n Desarrollado en conjunto por científicos de Obsidián y la Flota Terrestre, el sistema de reactivación de defensa Midas utiliza componentes del núcleo de la armadura Obsidiana, formando una sustancia metálica que es suave y  Femaleable a temperatura ambiente. El compuesto final se une directamente a la piel del piloto humano, absorbiendo instantáneamente la mayor parte de los ataques de energía cuando una suave carga de energía Nebulón es aplicada. Este objeto absorbe Nebulón pasivamente, incrementado efectivamente tu base Novus Prime cerca de un 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オブシディアンと地球艦隊の科学者による共同開発によって生み出されたミダス反応防御システムはオブシディアンの装甲からのコア構成要素を利用し、柔らかくて室温に影響されやすい金属物質で形成されている。最終的な化合物は人間のパイロットの皮膚に直接絡みつき、瞬間的にエナジーを基本とした殆どの攻撃を吸収します。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* kDesc [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">These are the leggings for the Midas Reactive Defense System.\n\n Co-developed by Obsidian and Earth Fleet scientists, the Midas Reactive Defense System utilizes the core components from Obsidian armor, forming a metallic substance that is soft and pliable at room temperature.  The final compound binds directly to a human pilot's skin, instantly absorbing most energy-based attacks when a gentle charge of Nebulon energy is applied.  This item passively absorbs Nebulon, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base Nebulon gains by about 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* kDesc [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* kDesc [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">These are the leggings for the Midas Reactive Defense System.\n\n Co-developed by Obsidian and Earth Fleet scientists, the Midas Reactive Defense System utilizes the core components from Obsidian armor, forming a metallic substance that is soft and pliable at room temperature.  The final compound binds directly to a human pilot's skin, instantly absorbing most energy-based attacks when a gentle charge of Nebulon energy is applied.  This item passively absorbs Nebulon, effectively increasing your Novus Prime base Nebulon gains by about 5%. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>