<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Raven Sofa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Canapé Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Raven-Sofa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Divano Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sofá de Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ソファ レーヴン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Raven 소파</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Raven Sofa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raven沙發</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raven沙發</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Raven Sofa</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Raven Sofa can be found in the Platoon Leader's quarters. If you're not playing MAG™ right now, you should just buy this sofa and pretend you are powerful enough to run an army platoon.        [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous trouverez ce canapé Raven dans les quartiers du Chef de section. Si vous ne jouez pas à MAG™ en ce moment, achetez-le et iMAG™inez que vous êtes assez fort pour gérer une section. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Raven-Sofa finden Sie im Quartier des Platoon-Anführers. Wenn Sie zurzeit nicht MAG™ spielen, sollten Sie sich einfach dieses Sofa kaufen und vorgeben, dass Sie mächtig genug sind, um ein Platoon zu leiten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo divano Raven può essere trovato principalmente nelle abitazioni dei leader plotone. Se non state giocando a MAG™ dovreste acquistarlo comunque per lasciar intendere di essere talmente forti da comandare un intero plotone. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este sofá de Raven pertenece a la habitación de un líder de sección. Si ahora mismo no estás jugando a MAG™, deberías comprártelo y fingir que tienes tanto poder como para dirigir a tu propia sección.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このソファは現在レーヴン小隊長の営舎に置いてある。MAG™を遊んでいないなら、このソファを買って小隊を指揮できる気分だけでも味わえ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">소대장의 숙소에서 발견할 수 있는 소파입니다. 지금 이 순간, MAG™를 플레이하고 있지 않다면 차라리 이 소파를 구입해서 소대장인척 하는 것이 나을지도 모릅니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This Raven Sofa can be found in the Platoon Leader's quarters. If you're not playing MAG™ right now, you should just buy this sofa and pretend you are powerful enough to run an army platoon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這款Raven沙發可以在排長宿舍之中找到。如果你現時不是在玩MAG™，你應該買下這張沙發，假裝夠資格成為排長。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這款Raven沙發可以在排長宿舍之中找到。如果你現時不是在玩MAG™，你應該買下這張沙發，假裝夠資格成為排長。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This Raven Sofa can be found in the Platoon Leader's quarters. If you're not playing MAG™ right now, you should just buy this sofa and pretend you are powerful enough to run an army platoon. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>