<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Escape The Virus Aquarium Virus (Stress)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Virus en aquarium Gare au virus (Stress)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Entkomme dem Virus"-Aquarium mit Virus (Stress)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Acquario virus di Sfuggi al virus (stress)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acuario de Virus (Énfasis) de Escape The Virus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">エスケープウイルス水槽 ウイルス(ストレス)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이스케이프 바이러스 수조 바이러스 (스트레스)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Escape Virus Aquarium Virus (Stress)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">逃離病毒遊戲水槽 病毒（直走型）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">逃離病毒遊戲水槽 病毒（直走型）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Escape The Virus Aquarium Virus (Stress)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Giant aquarium containing the Virus (Stress) appearing in Escape The Virus. This is an animated active furniture item. There is a limit to how many items of this type you can put in place.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aquarium géant contenant Virus (Stress) de Gare au virus. Cet objet offre des animations et diverses fonctions. Le nombre d'objets de ce type que vous pouvez conserver est limité.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Riesiges Aquarium mit Virus (Stress), das in "Entkomme dem Virus" vorkommt. Das Objekt bietet aktive Animationen und Funktionen. Von diesem Objekt kann nur eine begrenzte Anzahl aufgestellt werden.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Acquario gigante contenente il virus (stress) che appare in Sfuggi al virus. Questo oggetto è un mobile dotato di funzionalità e animazioni attive. Il numero di oggetti di questo tipo che puoi introdurre è limitato.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acuario gigante que contiene el Virus Énfasis que aparece en Escape The Virus. Este objeto de decoración tiene animaciones y funciones asociadas. El número de objetos de este tipo que puedes colocar en un sitio está limitado.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">エスケープウイルスに登場するウイルス(ストレス)が入った巨大水槽。このアイテムは、アニメーションや機能が追加されているアドバンスド家具です。この種類のアイテムは配置できる数に制限があります。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이스케이프 바이러스에 등장하는 바이러스(스트레스)를 넣은 거대 수조. 이 아이템은 애니메이션이나 기능이 추가된 액티브 가구입니다. 이 종류의 아이템은 배치할 수 있는 수에 제한이 있습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Giant aquarium containing the Virus (Stress) appearing in Escape Virus. This item is the furniture that has active animations and functions associated with it. There is a limit to how many items of this type you can put in place.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這個巨型水槽內含在逃離病毒遊戲中登場的病毒（直走型）。這款家具具有動態功能，所以在設置數目上有限制。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這個巨型水槽內含在逃離病毒遊戲中登場的病毒（直走型）。這款家具具有動態功能，所以在設置數目上有限制。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Giant aquarium containing the Virus (Stress) appearing in Escape The Virus. This is an animated active furniture item. There is a limit to how many items of this type you can put in place.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>