<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Royal Cygnus Feathered Gown</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Robe de plume de cygne royal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Königsschwanen-Federkleid</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Abito lungo con piume Cigno Reale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de noche de plumas Cisne real</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ロイヤル白鳥ガウン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">로열 시그너스 깃털 장식 가운 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Royal Cygnus Feathered Gown (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">皇家天鵝羽毛衣（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">皇家天鵝羽毛衣（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Royal Cygnus Feathered Gown</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You worked hard to help Lucy out. In return, she's asked her friends to make this for you. Turns out swans are pretty handy with a sewing machine. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tu as travaillé dur pour aider Lucie. En retour, elle a demandé à ses amis de faire quelque chose pour toi. Il semble que les cygnes soient plutôt doués avec une machine à coudre. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast hart gearbeitet, um Lucy zu helfen. Als Dank hat sie ihre Freunde gebeten, dieses Geschenk zu fertigen. Anscheinend sind Schwäne ganz schön flink im Umgang mit der Nähmaschine. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aiutare Lucy è stato molto faticoso. In cambio lei ha chiesto ai suoi amici di realizzare questo per te. Sembra proprio che i cigni siano abilissimi con la macchina da cucire. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Has trabajado duro para ayudar a Lucy. A cambio, ha pedido a sus amigos que te confeccionen este traje. Resulta que los cisnes son muy diestros con la máquina de coser. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ルーシーを助けてるためによく頑張ってくれました。そのお返しにルーシーのお友達達がこれを作ってくれました。やはり白鳥となると裁縫も得意ですね。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">루시를 돕느라 수고 많았습니다. 보답의 뜻으로 루시의 친구들이 이 턱시도를 만들었답니다. 백조들이 재봉에 소질이 있다는 것, 알고 계셨나요?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">You worked hard to help Lucy out. In return, she's asked her friends to make this for you. Turns out swans are pretty handy with a sewing machine. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">你為了幫露西忙挺辛苦的。為了報答你，她特地請朋友做了這套衣服。沒想到天鵝操作縫紉機也挺行的。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">你為了幫露西忙挺辛苦的。為了報答你，她特地請朋友做了這套衣服。沒想到天鵝操作縫紉機也挺行的。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You worked hard to help Lucy out. In return, she's asked her friends to make this for you. Turns out swans are pretty handy with a sewing machine. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>