<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MiniBots: Battlebox Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">MiniBots: Paquete de Battlebox</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MiniBots: Battlebox-Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto MiniBots: Battlebox</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ensemble MiniBots : Battlebox</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MiniBots: Battlebox Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Break out of the box with the MiniBots: Battlebox! This active item transforms any  personal space into a third person shooter for 1 player. Bundle also includes 11 MiniBot scale furniture items to design a custom battlefield: Modular Wall, R.A.M.P., Energy Bridge, Red and Blue Flags, Pillar, “Explosive” Barrel, Power Shield, Blast Shield, Platform, and Energy Barrier.  Learn to love your avatar's robotic alter-ego! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sortez du carcan grâce à MiniBots : Battlebox ! Cet élément actif transforme n'importe quel espace personnel en jeu de tir objectif pour 1 joueur. L'ensemble inclut également 11 éléments de mobilier MiniBot afin de concevoir un champ de bataille personnalisé : mur modulaire, R.A.M.P.E., pont d'énergie, drapeaux rouge et bleu, pilier, tonneau "explosif", bouclier d'énergie, écran de protection, plateforme et barrière énergétique. Vous allez adorer l'alter ego robotique de votre avatar ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Brechen Sie aus der Box aus – mit dieser MiniBots: Battlebox! Diese aktive Objekt verwandelt jeden persönlichen Raum in einen Third-Person-Shooter für 1 Spieler. Das Bundle enthält ferner 11 maßstabsgetreue MiniBot-Einrichtungsgegenstände für den Entwurf eines Schlachtfeldes: Modulare Wand, R.A.M.P., Energiebrücke, Rote und Blaue Fahnen, Säule, „Sprengstoff“-Fass, Energieschild, Energiestoßschild, Plattform und Energiebarriere.  Sie werden das Roboter-Alter-Ego Ihres Avatars lieben lernen!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esci dalla mischia con MiniBots: Battlebox! Questo elemento dinamico trasforma qualsiasi spazio personale in uno sparatutto in terza persona per 1 giocatore. Il pacchetto include inoltre 11 arredi di gioco in scala per i MiniBot per creare un campo di battaglia personalizzato: Muro modulare, R.A.M.P., Ponte di energia, Bandiere rosse e blu, Colonna, Barile "esplosivo", Scudo di energia, Scudo blindato, Piattaforma e Barriera di energia. Impara ad amare l'alter-ego robotizzato del tuo avatar! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Rompe los moldes con MiniBots: Battlebox! Este elemento activo transforma cualquier espacio personal en un disparador de terceros para 1 jugador. El paquete también incluye 11 artículos complementarios MiniBot a escala para diseñar un campo de batalla personalizado: pared modular, P.R.M.A., puente de energía, banderas rojas y azules, pilar, barril "explosivo", escudo de poder, escudo explosivo, plataforma y barrera energética.  ¡Cada vez te gustará más el álter ego robótico de tu avatar! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Break out of the box with the MiniBots: Battlebox! This active item transforms any  personal space into a third person shooter for 1 player. Bundle also includes 11 MiniBot scale furniture items to design a custom battlefield: Modular Wall, R.A.M.P., Energy Bridge, Red and Blue Flags, Pillar, “Explosive” Barrel, Power Shield, Blast Shield, Platform, and Energy Barrier.  Learn to love your avatar's robotic alter-ego! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>