<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">All Monkey Island Items Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tous les objets de Monkey Island dans un baluchon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vollständiges Monkey Island Gegenstände-Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completo di tutti gli Articoli Monkey Island</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de Todos los Artículos de Monkey Island</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* All Monkey Island Items Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* All Monkey Island Items Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* All Monkey Island Items Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* All Monkey Island Items Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* All Monkey Island Items Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">All Monkey Island Items Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Massive bundle includes LeChuck's Pirate Ship plus all Monkey Island furniture and clothing items.  In total this bundle includes 1 Personal Space, 16 Male Clothing items, 12 Female Clothing items, and 42 Furniture items.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce mega pack inclus  le bateau de pirate de LeChuck plus tous les meubles et tous les vêtements de Monkey Island. Au total ce pack inclus 1 Espace Personnel, 16 vêtements d’homme, 12 vêtements de femmes et 42 meubles.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Riesen-Paket beinhaltet LeChucks Piratenschiff und alle Monkey Island Möbel- und Bekleidungsgegenstände. Insgesamt beinhaltet dieses Paket: 1 Persönlichen Bereich, 16 Bekleidungsgegenstände für Männer, 12 Bekleidungsgegenstände für Frauen und 42 Möbelgegenstände.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo grande completo comprende la Nave Pirata di LeChuck più tutti gli articoli di mobilio e abbigliamento Monkey Island. In totale, questo completo include 1 Spazio Personale, 16 capi di Abbigliamento Maschile, 12 capi di Abbigliamento Femminile, e 42 articoli di mobilio.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El paquete masivo incluye el barco pirata de LeChuck, además de todos los muebles y artículos de ropa de Monkey Island. En total este paquete incluye 1 espacio personal, 16 artículos de ropa masculina, 12 artículos de ropa femenina y 42 muebles.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Massive bundle includes LeChuck's Pirate Ship plus all Monkey Island furniture and clothing items.  In total this bundle includes 1 Personal Space, 16 Male Clothing items, 12 Female Clothing items, and 42 Furniture items.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>