<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mad Scientist Starter Kit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Kit du débutant Savant Fou</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verrückter Wissenschaftler Anfängerset</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Kit Iniziale dello Scienziato Pazzo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de iniciación de Científico Loco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">マッドサイエンティスト スターターキット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mad Scientist Starter Kit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The power! The power! The –oooh, the floor lights up! With this Mad Scientist Starter Kit from LOOT™ you get Gograk’s light up wall and floor pieces as well as the Ghostbusters™ Computer Console 1 and bundle exclusive Console 2. Start working on your evil laugh! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La puissance ! La puissance ! La –hou, le sol s'allume ! Avec le Kit du débutant Savant Fou de LOOT™ vous aurez le mur et le sol éclairé de Gograk, ainsi que les consoles informatiques S.O.S. Fantômes™, dont la 2 en exclusivité. Il va falloir vous trouver un rire sadique ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Energie! Die Energie! Die - oohh, der Boden leuchtet! Mit diesem Anfängerset Verrückter Wissenschaftler von LOOT™ erhältst du  Gograk’s leuchtende Wand und Bodenstücke und außerdem die Ghostbusters™ Computer Console 1 und exklusiv mit diesem Bundle Console 2. Arbeite schon mal an deinem bösen Gelächter! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Potere ! Potere! Po... Oooh, il pavimento si illumina! Con questo Kit Iniziale dello Scienziato Pazzo di LOOT™, avrai la Parete e il Pavimento Luminosi di Gograk, la Console per Computer 1 di Ghostbusters™ e anche la Console per Computer 2 di Ghostbusters™, esclusiva di questo completo. Inizia a lavorare con una risata malefica! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡El poder! ¡El poder! ¡Las… oooh, las luces del suelo encendidas! Con este juego de iniciación de Científico Loco de LOOT™ puedes conseguir las luces de pared y suelo de Gograk así como la Consola de ordenador 1 de Cazafantasmas™ y el conjunto exclusivo de la Consola 2. ¡Empieza a practicar tu risa diabólica! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">エネルギーを！もっとエネルギーを！…おお、床が光りだした！\n本コンテンツには、以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n\n・「ゴーストバスターズ™ コンピューター機器1」（装飾品）\n・「ゴーストバスターズ™ コンピューター機器2」（装飾品）\n・「ゴグラックの光る壁」（装飾品）\n・「ゴグラックの光るフロア」（ラグ）\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The power! The power! The –oooh, the floor lights up! With this Mad Scientist Starter Kit from LOOT™ you get Gograk’s light up wall and floor pieces as well as the Ghostbusters™ Computer Console 1 and bundle exclusive Console 2. Start working on your evil laugh! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>