<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Nis_Dots_No019</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Personnage 2D: Champloo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドットオブジェ　ココロの料理師範　チャンプル先生</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">도트 오브제 마음의 요리 사범 참프루 선생</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Passionate Chef: Mr. Champloo Sprite Statue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">像素雕像 真心的廚師MR. CHAMPLOO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">像素雕像 真心的廚師MR. CHAMPLOO</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">2D Character Objects: Champloo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nis_dot_No019</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Untitled</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La statuette d'un personnage que tu peux mettre dans ta chambre pour décorer.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">伝説の料理人にして家諦科凶師（かていかきょうし）！一ヶ月絶食、熱湯・油風呂入浴、包丁上睡眠！そんなことで食材のココロがわかるのか！？登場の仕方は食材まみれで、わけわからん！物事のすべてを料理に例えて、わけわからん！ただ、明確なのは見た目とセリフの熱さのみ！強いココロを育むために、最凶の料理を君に伝授するかもしれないオブジェ！強火流混沌派厨房拳！味道求心！考えるな！ココロで感じろ！「料理のココロは、人生のココロと知れ！！！」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">전설의 요리인을 가정과 교사로! 1개월 금식, 열탕, 기름탕 입욕, 주방칼 위에서 수면! 이렇게 하면 식재료의 마음을 알 수 있는걸까!? 들고 나오는 것들이 식재료 투성이로 뭐가 뭔지 모르겠음! 세상사 모든 것을 요리에 비유해, 뭐가 뭔지 모르겠엉! 확실한 것은 외모와 말에서 느껴지는 열정 뿐! 강한 마음을 기르기 위해, 최강의 요리를 당신에게 전수하는 것일지도 모르는 오브제! 강화류 혼돈파 주방권! 맛의 길을 추구하는 마음! 생각하지마! 마음으로 느껴라! 요리의 마음은, 인생의 마음으로 알아라!! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Mr. Champloo is the Home Economics teacher at Evil Academy and is a legendary chef. He uses one-month fasting, bathing in hot water or oil, and cooking knife hypnosis to relay the finer points of cooking, and always shows up with his hands full of cooking ingredients. Mr. Champloo compares everything in life to cooking one way or another, which makes him quite confusing at times, but one thing for sure is he's got a lot of heart. This statue just might teach you how to cook with more heart! Fire Chaos Style, Kitchen Fist! Follow the path of taste! Don't think! Feel your heart! The heart of cooking is the heart of life![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">傳說的料理人家諦科教師！一個月絕食、用開水及熱油入浴、睡在菜刀上！做這些真的了解食材的真心嗎！？登場方式是全身佈滿食材，有點不知所謂，只能確定他熱烈的眼神及說話方式！為了培育出堅定的意志也只能靠他來傳授你！強火流混沌派廚房拳！味道求心！不要用腦袋思考，要用心去感受！「料理在於真心，去體驗人生的真心！」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">傳說的料理人家諦科教師！一個月絕食、用開水及熱油入浴、睡在菜刀上！做這些真的了解食材的真心嗎！？登場方式是全身佈滿食材，有點不知所謂，只能確定他熱烈的眼神及說話方式！為了培育出堅定的意志也只能靠他來傳授你！強火流混沌派廚房拳！味道求心！不要用腦袋思考，要用心去感受！「料理在於真心，去體驗人生的真心！」[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A small character statue that you can place to decorate your own room.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>