<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LYNX Excite Falling Angels Game</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jeu Axe Excite : les anges tombent du ciel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Axe Excite: "Fallende Engel"-Spiel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gioco Axe Excite: Anche gli angeli cadono</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Juego AXE Excite: Hasta los ángeles caerán</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kLegend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [CROSS] to continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyez sur [CROSS] pour continuer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücke [CROSS], um fortzufahren.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi [CROSS] per proseguire</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa [CROSS] para continuar.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">CAN YOU HELP ME?\nIF YOU CAN CATCH MY FALLING FRIENDS, I PROMISE TO REWARD YOU GENEROUSLY. I’LL GIVE YOU THE POWER OF TEMPTATION THAT NO ANGEL WILL BE ABLE TO RESIST.\nPRESS [CROSS] TO JOIN THE GAME AND HELP ME.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">VOUS POUVEZ M'AIDER ? \nSI VOUS RÉUSSISSEZ À ATTRAPER MES AMIS DANS LEUR CHUTE, VOUS SEREZ LARGEMENT RÉCOMPENSÉ. JE VOUS DONNERAI LE POUVOIR DE TENTATION, ET AUCUN ANGE NE SERA EN MESURE D'Y RÉSISTER.\nAPPUYEZ SUR LA TOUCHE [CROSS] POUR JOUER ET M'AIDER.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">KANNST DU MIR HELFEN?\nWENN DU MEINE FALLENDEN FREUNDINNEN FANGEN KANNST, WERDE ICH DICH REICH BELOHNEN: ICH WERDE DIR DIE MACHT DER VERFÜHRUNG SCHENKEN, DER KEIN ENGEL WIDERSTEHEN KANN.\nDRÜCKE [CROSS], UM ZU SPIELEN UND MIR ZU HELFEN.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">PUOI AIUTARMI?\nSALVA I MIEI AMICI CHE CADONO DAL CIELO E TI PROMETTO UNA GENEROSA RICOMPENSA. RICEVERAI IL POTERE DELLA TENTAZIONE A CUI NESSUN ANGELO POTRÀ RESISTERE.\nPREMI [CROSS] PER GIOCARE E AIUTARMI.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿PUEDES AYUDARME?\nSI ATRAPAS A MIS AMIGAS CUANDO CAIGAN, PROMETO RECOMPENSARTE GENEROSAMENTE: TE DARÉ EL PODER DE LA TENTACIÓN. NI SIQUIERA LOS ÁNGELES PODRÁN RESISTIRSE.\nPULSA [CROSS] PARA ENTRAR EN EL JUEGO Y AYUDARME.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OK LET’S GET STARTED… YOU WILL HAVE ONE-MINUTE TO MAKE SURE MY TEN FRIENDS GET A SOFT LANDING WHEN THEY FALL TO EARTH.\n\nCATCH AT LEAST EIGHT OF THEM WITH 10 PILLOWS AND I’LL GIVE YOU THE POWER TO TEMPT ANGELS WHENEVER YOU WANT. IF YOU CAN CATCH ALL TEN OF MY FRIENDS, YOU’LL WIN ANOTHER REWARD FOR YOUR PERFECT PERFORMANCE.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">BIEN, ALLONS-Y... VOUS AUREZ UNE MINUTE POUR FAIRE EN SORTE QUE MES DIX AMIS NE SE FASSENT PAS MAL EN TOMBANT SUR TERRE.\n\nRATTRAPEZ AU MOINS HUIT D'ENTRE EUX AVEC 10 COUSSINS ET JE VOUS OFFRIRAI LE POUVOIR DE TENTER LES ANGES. RATTRAPEZ MES DIX AMIS, ET VOUS AUREZ DROIT À UNE AUTRE RÉCOMPENSE POUR UNE PERFORMANCE PARFAITE.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">OKAY, FANGEN WIR AN. DU HAST EINE MINUTE, UM MEINEN ZEHN FREUNDINNEN EINE SANFTE LANDUNG ZU VERSCHAFFEN, WENN SIE AUF DIE ERDE FALLEN.\n\nFANGE MINDESTENS ACHT VON IHNEN MIT ZEHN KISSEN, UND ICH VERLEIHE DIR DIE KRAFT, ENGEL NACH BELIEBEN ZU VERFÜHREN. WENN DU ALLE ZEHN MEINER FREUNDINNEN FANGEN KANNST, ERHÄLTST DU NOCH EINE BELOHNUNG FÜR DEINE PERFEKTE LEISTUNG.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">BENE, INIZIAMO... AVRAI UN MINUTO DI TEMPO PER FARE IN MODO CHE I MIEI DIECI AMICI ATTERRINO SUL MORBIDO CADENDO DAL CIELO.\n\nSALVANE ALMENO OTTO CON 10 CUSCINI E TI REGALERÒ IL POTERE DI TENTARE GLI ANGELI IN QUALSIASI MOMENTO. SALVALI TUTTI E DIECI E OTTERRAI UN'ULTERIORE RICOMPENSA.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">BIEN, EMPECEMOS… TIENES UN MINUTO PARA ASEGURARTE DE QUE MIS DIEZ AMIGAS ATERRIZAN SUAVEMENTE CUANDO CAIGAN A LA TIERRA.\n\nATRAPA AL MENOS A OCHO CON DIEZ ALMOHADAS Y TE DARÉ EL PODER DE TENTAR A LOS ÁNGELES CUANDO QUIERAS. SI LOGRAS ATRAPAR A LAS DIEZ, GANARÁS OTRO PREMIO POR TU ACTUACIÓN IMPECABLE.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO2_p2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">HERE’S HOW TO PLAY:\n-  WHEN YOU SEE A PINK 'X' LIKE THIS, YOU WILL NEED TO RUN OVER AND PLACE A PILLOW DOWN BY PRESSING THE [CROSS] BUTTON.\n-  MAKE SURE YOU PLACE IT CORRECTLY OR YOU WILL MISS THE FALLING ANGEL.\n-  PRESS THE [CROSS] BUTTON TO START THE GAME!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">VOICI COMMENT JOUER:\n-  LORSQUE VOUS VOYEZ UNE ROSE 'X' COMME CELLE-CI, VENEZ VITE Y POSER UN COUSSIN EN APPUYANT SUR LA TOUCHE [CROSS]\n-  PLACEZ-LE CORRECTEMENT, OU L'ANGE TOMBERA À CÔTÉ.\n-  APPUYEZ SUR LA TOUCHE [CROSS] POUR COMMENCER !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">SO FUNKTIONIERT'S:\n- WENN DU EIN PINKES "X" WIE DIESES SIEHST, MUSST DU HINRENNEN UND EIN KISSEN HINLEGEN, INDEM DU DIE [CROSS]-TASTE DRÜCKST.\n- DAS KISSEN MUSS RICHTIG LIEGEN, SONST FÄLLT DER FALLENDE ENGEL DANEBEN.\n- DRÜCKE DIE [CROSS]-TASTE, UM DAS SPIEL ZU STARTEN!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">ECCO COME GIOCARE:\n- QUANDO VEDI UNA "X" ROSA COME QUESTA, DOVRAI CORRERE E POSIZIONARE UN CUSCINO PREMENDO IL TASTO [CROSS].\n- ASSICURATI DI POSIZIONARLO CORRETTAMENTE, O RISCHIERAI DI NON PRENDERE L'ANGELO CADUTO DAL CIELO.\n- PREMI IL TASTO [CROSS] PER INIZIARE IL GIOCO!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">SE JUEGA ASÍ:\n- CUANDO VEAS UNA “X” ROSA COMO ESTA, DEBERÁS CORRER HASTA ELLA Y COLOCAR UNA ALMOHADA PULSANDO EL BOTÓN [CROSS].\n- ASEGÚRATE DE COLOCARLA CORRECTAMENTE O EL ÁNGEL QUE CAIGA SE ESTRELLARÁ.\n- ¡PULSA EL BOTÓN [CROSS] PARA EMPEZAR A JUGAR!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">WHAT CAN I SAY? YOU REALLY HAVE A WAY WITH ANGELS SO YOU’VE EARNED THIS SPECIAL GIFT. NOW EVERYONE WILL KNOW JUST HOW IRRESISTABLE YOU ARE. PLAY AGAIN AND TRY CATCHING US ALL FOR ANOTHER SURPRISE.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">QUE DIRE ? LES ANGES N'ONT PAS DE SECRETS POUR VOUS, ET VOUS AVEZ BIEN MÉRITÉ CE CADEAU. TOUT LE MONDE SAURA ENFIN À QUEL POINT VOUS ÊTES IRRÉSISTIBLE. REJOUEZ ET ESSAYEZ DE RATTRAPER TOUS LES ANGES POUR UNE AUTRE SURPRISE.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">WAS SOLL ICH SAGEN? DU WEISST, WIE MAN MIT ENGELN UMGEHEN MUSS. DU HAST DIR DIESES BESONDERE GESCHENK VERDIENT. JETZT WIRD JEDER WISSEN, WIE UNWIDERSTEHLICH DU BIST. SPIELE NOCH MAL UND VERSUCHE, UNS ALLE ZU FANGEN, UM NOCH EINE ÜBERRASCHUNG ZU ERHALTEN.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">CHE DIRE? CI SAI PROPRIO FARE CON GLI ANGELI E QUINDI HAI GUADAGNATO QUESTO DONO SPECIALE. ORA TUTTI SAPRANNO QUANTI SEI IRRESISTIBILE. GIOCA ANCORA E PROVA A SALVARE DI NUOVO TUTTI GLI ANGELI PER RICEVERE UN'ALTRA SORPRESA.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿QUÉ PUEDO DECIR? TIENES BUENA MANO PARA LOS ÁNGELES. TE HAS GANADO ESTE REGALO ESPECIAL. AHORA TODOS SABRÁN LO IRRESISTIBLE QUE ERES. ¡VUELVE A JUGAR, INTENTA ATRAPARNOS A TODAS Y RECIBIRÁS OTRA SORPRESA!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">YOU WERE INCREDIBLE!  YOU DIDN’T MISS A SINGLE ANGEL SO I THINK YOU’VE EARNED THIS REWARD. WHENEVER YOU EQUIP THIS ITEM ANGELS WILL 'FALL' FOR YOU!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">VOUS ÊTES INCROYABLE !  VOUS N'AVEZ LAISSÉ TOMBER AUCUN ANGE, VOUS AVEZ BIEN MÉRITÉ CETTE RÉCOMPENSE. LORSQUE VOUS VOUS ÉQUIPEREZ DE CET OBJET, LES ANGES TOMBERONT POUR VOUS !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">DU WARST UNGLAUBLICH! DU HAST KEINEN EINZIGEN ENGEL VERFEHLT. DIESE BELOHNUNG HAST DU DIR VERDIENT. WENN DU DIESEN GEGENSTAND EINSETZT, BRINGST DU ENGEL ZUM "FALLEN".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">INCREDIBILE! NON TI È SFUGGITO NEANCHE UN ANGELO, E TI SEI GUADAGNATO QUESTO PREMIO. ATTIVANDO QUESTO ELEMENTO, GLI ANGELI "CADRANNO AI TUOI PIEDI"!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡LO HAS HECHO GENIAL! NO HAS FALLADO NI UNA SOLA VEZ. CREO QUE TE HAS GANADO ESTE PREMIO. CUANDO LO USES, ¡LOS ÁNGELES “CAERÁN” A TUS PIES!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">WOW! A PERFECT SCORE ON YOUR FIRST TRY! YOU DIDN’T MISS A SINGLE ANGEL, SO YOU’VE EARNED BOTH REWARDS! WHENEVER YOU EQUIP YOURSELF WITH THESE ITEMS, ANGELS WILL 'FALL' FOR YOU!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">BRAVO !  UN SCORE PARFAIT DÈS LE PREMIER ESSAI ! VOUS N'AVEZ RATÉ AUCUN ANGE, VOUS AVEZ GAGNÉ LES DEUX RÉCOMPENSES !  LORSQUE VOUS VOUS ÉQUIPEREZ DE CES OBJETS, LES ANGES TOMBERONT POUR VOUS !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">WOW! EINE REIFE LEISTUNG BEIM ERSTEN VERSUCH! DU HAST NICHT EINEN ENGEL VERFEHLT. DU HAST BEIDE BELOHNUNGEN VERDIENT! WENN DU DIESE GEGENSTÄNDE EINSETZT, "VERFÄLLT" DIR JEDER ENGEL.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">WOW! RISULTATO PERFETTO AL PRIMO COLPO! NON TI È SFUGGITO NEANCHE UN ANGELO, E TI SEI GUADAGNATO ENTRAMBI I PREMI! ATTIVANDO QUESTI ELEMENTI, GLI ANGELI "CADRANNO AI TUOI PIEDI"!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡VAYA! ¡UNA PUNTUACIÓN PERFECTA EN EL PRIMER INTENTO! NO HAS FALLADO NI UNA SOLA VEZ. TE HAS GANADO LOS DOS PREMIOS. SIEMPRE QUE LOS USES, ¡LOS ÁNGELES “CAERÁN” A TUS PIES!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OUCH, THAT LOOKED LIKE A ROUGH LANDING! DON’T GIVE UP! IF YOU BREAK OUR FALL, YOU’LL GET A SPECIAL SURPRISE.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">AÏE, ÇA DOIT FAIRE UN PEU MAL !  NE BAISSEZ PAS LES BRAS ! SI VOUS AMORTISSEZ NOTRE CHUTE, VOUS RECEVREZ UNE JOLIE SURPRISE.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">AUTSCH! DAS SAH NACH EINER HARTEN LANDUNG AUS! GIB NICHT AUF! WENN DU UNSEREN FALL AUFFÄNGST, ERHÄLTST DU EINE BESONDERE ÜBERRASCHUNG.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">CAVOLO, CHE BRUTTO ATTERRAGGIO! NON TI ABBATTERE! SE RIUSCIRAI AD ATTUTIRE L'IMPATTO RICEVERAI UNA SORPRESA SPECIALE.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡VAYA! PARECE QUE HA TENIDO UN MAL ATERRIZAJE. ¡NO TE RINDAS! SI NOS SALVAS, OBTENDRÁS UN REGALO ESPECIAL.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kVO7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MY HERO! THANKS AGAIN FOR SAVING MY FRIENDS… ANY ANGEL WOULD BE HAPPY TO LAND ON YOUR PILLOW!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">MON HÉROS ! MERCI ENCORE D'AVOIR SAUVÉ MES AMIS... C'EST TOUJOURS UN PLAISIR DE TOMBER SUR VOTRE COUSSIN !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MEIN HELD! DANKE, DASS DU MEINE FREUNDINNEN GERETTET HAST ... AUF DEINEM KISSEN WÜRDE SICHER JEDER ENGEL GERNE LANDEN!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">CHE EROE! GRAZIE ANCORA PER AVER SALVATO I MIEI AMICI... QUALSIASI ANGELO SAREBBE FELICE DI POTER ATTERRARE SUL TUO CUSCINO!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡MI HÉROE! GRACIAS DE NUEVO POR SALVAR A MIS AMIGAS... ¡CUALQUIER ÁNGEL SE MORIRÍA POR ATERRIZAR EN TU ALMOHADA!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kAngelName01</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Frances</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Frances</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Frances</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Frances</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Frances</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kAngelName02</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Magda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Magda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Magda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Magda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Magda</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kAngelName03</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Faye</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Faye</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Faye</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Faye</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Faye</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>