<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Magical Leaf Rug</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tapis de feuilles magiques</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Magischer Blätterteppich</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tappeto di foglie magiche</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Alfombra mágica de hojas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Magical Leaf Rug</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Colored leaves make a beautiful floor setting. As you walk across it, the leaves magically part creating a clear path for you. Once you pass, the leaves blow back and cover your path. Any room you put this in is instantly more extraordinary. This is an active item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Des feuilles colorées qui forment un magnifique tapis. Lorsque l'on marche dessus, les feuilles se déplacent par magie pour former un chemin. Une fois que l'on est passé, les feuilles se remettent en place. N'importe quelle pièce qui contiendra cet objet deviendra instantanément plus étonnante. Il s'agit d'un objet actif. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Farbige Blätter sind ein wunderschöner Bodenbelag. Wenn du über sie läufst, schaffen sie wie durch Magie einen Weg für dich. Wenn du am Ende deines Weges bist, werden die Blätter zurück an ihren Ausgangspunkt geweht. Jeder Raum verwandelt sich durch diese Blätter in etwas ganz Besonderes. Dies ist ein aktiver Gegenstand. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Queste foglie variopinte danno grande stile al pavimento. Se ci cammini sopra, le foglie creano automaticamente un sentiero per te. Dopo il tuo passaggio si risistemano come prima. Qualsiasi stanza con questo tappeto diventa immediatamente un po' più straordinaria. Questo è un oggetto attivo interattivo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las hojas de distintos colores embellecen el diseño del suelo. A medida que caminas sobre ellas, las hojas se apartan mágicamente creando un sendero para ti. Una vez que pasas, las hojas vuelven atrás y cierran tu camino. Cualquier habitación con esta alfombra se hace al instante más extraordinaria. Es un artículo activo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Colored leaves make a beautiful floor setting. As you walk across it, the leaves magically part creating a clear path for you. Once you pass, the leaves blow back and cover your path. Any room you put this in is instantly more extraordinary. This is an active item. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>