<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">inVerse Special Edition Sneakers Colour Bundle - Female</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot inVerse Special Edition Sneakers couleur – Femme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">inVerse Special Edition Sneakers Farbbündel - Damen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set colorato di inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Donna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pack inVerse Special Edition Sneakers en colores - Mujer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">inVerse Special Edition Sneakers Colour Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">inVerse Special Edition Sneakers Colour Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">inVerse Special Edition Sneakers Colour Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">inVerse Special Edition Sneakers Colour Bundle (Women)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The inVerse Special Edition Sneakers Colour Bundle has the perfect shoe to compliment any outfit.\n
\n
This bundle contains:\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Cobalt Blue - Female\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Forest Green - Female\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Sunflower Yellow - Female\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Pink Frosting - Female\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Tactical Black - Female\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Rich Maroon - Female\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Perfect White - Female\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Checkboard - Female\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Red Plaid - Female\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Jolly Rodger - Female [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le lot de baskets de toile inVerse Special Edition Sneakers couleur rassemble des chaussures idéales pour compléter votre tenue, quelle qu'elle soit.\n
\n
Ce lot contient :\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers – Bleu cobalt – Femme\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers – Vert forêt – Femme\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers – Jaune tournesol – Femme\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers – Rose dépoli – Femme\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers – Noir tactique – Femme\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers – Marron profond – Femme\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers – Blanc immaculé – Femme\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers – Damier – Femme\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers – Rouge plaid – Femme\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers – Jolly Rodger – Femme [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Im inVerse Special Edition Sneakers Farbbündel finden Sie Sneakers, die perfekt zu jedem Outfit passen.\n
\n
Dieses Bündel enthält:\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Kobaltblau - Damen\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Waldgrün - Damen\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Sonnenblumengelb - Damen\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Zuckerwattenpink - Damen\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Taktikschwarz - Damen\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Schokoladenbraun - Damen\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Schneeweiß - Damen\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Schwarzweiß kariert - Damen\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Rot kariert - Damen\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Totenkopfmotiv - Damen [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il set colorato di inVerse Special Edition Sneakers ha la scarpa da ginnastica perfetta per ogni abbigliamento.\n
\n
Il set comprende:\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Blu cobalto - Donna\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Verde foresta - Donna\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Giallo girasole - Donna\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Rosa glassa - Donna\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Nero Tactical - Donna\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Bordeaux - Donna\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Bianco perfetto - Donna\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Scacchi - Donna\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Rosso scozzese - Donna\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Jolly Rodger - Donna [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Pack inVerse Special Edition Sneakers en colores ofrece el calzado perfecto para complementar cualquier vestimenta.\n
\n
Este pack contiene:\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Azul cobalto - Mujer\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Verde bosque - Mujer\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Amarillo girasol - Mujer\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Glaseado rosa - Mujer\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Negro táctico - Mujer\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Granate intenso - Mujer\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Blanco puro - Mujer\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Cuadros de ajedrez - Mujer\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Cuadros rojos - Mujer\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Bandera pirata - Mujer [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">The inVerse Special Edition Sneakers Colour Bundle has the perfect shoe to compliment any outfit.\n
\n
This bundle contains:\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Cobalt Blue (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Forest Green (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Sunflower Yellow (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Pink Frosting (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Tactical Black (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Rich Maroon (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Perfect White (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Checkboard (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Red Plaid (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Jolly Rodger (Women)\n
\n
※Upon purchase, the items will be placed into their respective categories. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The inVerse Special Edition Sneakers Colour Bundle has the perfect shoe to compliment any outfit.\n
\n
This bundle contains:\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Cobalt Blue (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Forest Green (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Sunflower Yellow (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Pink Frosting (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Tactical Black (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Rich Maroon (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Perfect White (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Checkboard (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Red Plaid (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Jolly Rodger (Women)\n
\n
※Upon purchase, the items will be placed into their respective categories. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">The inVerse Special Edition Sneakers Colour Bundle has the perfect shoe to compliment any outfit.\n
\n
This bundle contains:\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Cobalt Blue (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Forest Green (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Sunflower Yellow (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Pink Frosting (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Tactical Black (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Rich Maroon (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Perfect White (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Checkboard (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Red Plaid (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Jolly Rodger (Women)\n
\n
※Upon purchase, the items will be placed into their respective categories. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">The inVerse Special Edition Sneakers Colour Bundle has the perfect shoe to compliment any outfit.\n
\n
This bundle contains:\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Cobalt Blue (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Forest Green (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Sunflower Yellow (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Pink Frosting (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Tactical Black (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Rich Maroon (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Perfect White (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Checkboard (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Red Plaid (Women)\n
inVerse Special Edition Sneakers - Jolly Rodger (Women)\n
\n
※Upon purchase, the items will be placed into their respective categories. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>