<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Death Ray (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rayon de la mort (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Todesstrahl (Weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Raggio della morte (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Rayo mortal (femenino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Death Ray (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Using some really amazingly complicated technology, the Death Ray projects a volatile blast of amazingly simple deadly energy. BONUS: Unlocks the Death Ray for use in MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Grâce à une technologie extraordinairement compliquée, le rayon de la mort projette une explosion d'énergie extraordinairement mortelle. BONUS : Déverrouille le rayon de la mort utilisable dans MiniBots multijoueur. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unter Verwendung einer wirklich erstaunlichen und komplexen Technologie gibt der Todesstrahl einen Stoß von erstaunlich einfacher tödlicher Energie ab. BONUS: Gibt den Todesstrahl für den Einsatz im MiniBots-Multiplayer-Modus frei. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Grazie ad alcune tecnologie sorprendentemente complesse, il Raggio della morte proietta una raffica incorporea di energia letale sorprendentemente semplice. BONUS: sblocca il Raggio della morte per l'uso in modalità multigiocatore in MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Gracias una tecnología tremendamente complicada, el Rayo mortal proyecta un haz volátil de energía mortal sumamente simple. BONUS: Desbloquea el Rayo mortal para usarlo en modo de varios jugadores de los MiniBots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Using some really amazingly complicated technology, the Death Ray projects a volatile blast of amazingly simple deadly energy. BONUS: Unlocks the Death Ray for use in MiniBots multiplayer. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>