<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Savage Manor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le manoir sauvage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Savage Manor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maniero selvaggio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mansión salvaje</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">戦慄の館</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">공포의 저택</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Savage Manor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">野蠻莊園</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">野蠻莊園</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Savage Manor</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Enter if you dare! This tormented manor is steeped in grim history, history that will not remain in the past. Explore this mysterious apartment, but beware of the dangers that lurk within. Can you solve the cryptic riddles and learn the horrible truths ingrained within the structure's living, breathing walls? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Entrez à vos risques et périls ! Ce manoir hanté au sombre passé vous ramènera vers ses heures les plus noires. Explorez cet appartement mystérieux, tout en évitant les dangers tapis dans l'ombre. Pourrez-vous résoudre les énigmes et mettre à jour les horreurs dont sont impregnés les murs bien vivants ? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Betreten auf eigene Gefahr! Dieser kummervolle Landsitz zeugt von einer düsteren Vergangenheit - einer Vergangenheit, die äußerst lebendig erscheint. Erkunde dieses geheimnisvolle Apartment, aber nimm dich vor den Gefahren in Acht, die darin lauern. Kannst du die kryptischen Rätsel lösen und die schauderhaften Wahrheiten ans Tageslicht bringen, die in diesem sagenumwobenen Gemäuer hausen? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Entra se ne hai il coraggio! La storia di questo tormentato maniero è ricca di episodi lugubri, che non resteranno sepolti nel passato. Esplora questo misterioso appartamento, ma attenzione ai pericoli in agguato al suo interno. Riuscirai a risolvere i criptici enigmi e a scoprire le terrificanti verità scolpite nei muri di questa struttura? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Entra, ¡si es que te atreves! Esta mansión tormentosa está plagada de historia lúgubre que no se quedará en el pasado. Explora este misterioso lugar, pero ten cuidado con los peligros que acechan dentro. ¿Podrás resolver los entresijos crípticos y aprender las terribles verdades que forman parte de las paredes vivientes de la estructura? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">勇気ある者、この扉を開けよ! 誰も知らない残忍な過去が隠された呪いの館。この謎の洋館の探検には数々の危険が潜む。不可解な難問を解き、息をする壁に染みついたおぞましい真実を暴きだそう。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">【18세 미만의 청소년은 이용할 수 없습니다】용기가 있는 자만 들어오세요! 이 고통으로 가득한 저택은 결코 과거에만 머물러 있지 않을 음울한 역사로 물들어 있습니다. 이 수수께끼의 아파트를 탐험하세요. 하지만 그 안에 도사리고 있는 위험 요소를 조심하는 것이 좋을 겁니다. 모호한 수수께끼를 풀고 건물의 살아 숨쉬는 벽 안에 깊이 베어든 끔찍한 진실을 알아낼 수 있겠습니까? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">【For Age 18 and Above】Enter if you dare! This tormented manor is steeped in grim history, history that will not remain in the past. Explore this mysterious apartment, but beware of the dangers that lurk within. Can you solve the cryptic riddles and learn the horrible truths ingrained within the structure's living, breathing walls? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">【限定18歲以上】有膽量你就進來！這座飽受摧殘的莊園瀰漫著腥風血雨的歷史。但這一切並非過去塵埃，而是活生生地展現在你的眼前。探索這座神秘的莊園時，千萬要注意隱藏在其中的危險。你能解開含糊隱蔽的謎題嗎？你能從有生命，會呼吸的牆壁中了解到可怕的事實嗎？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">【限定18歲以上】有膽量你就進來！這座飽受摧殘的莊園瀰漫著腥風血雨的歷史。但這一切並非過去塵埃，而是活生生地展現在你的眼前。探索這座神秘的莊園時，千萬要注意隱藏在其中的危險。你能解開含糊隱蔽的謎題嗎？你能從有生命，會呼吸的牆壁中了解到可怕的事實嗎？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Enter if you dare! This tormented manor is steeped in grim history, history that will not remain in the past. Explore this mysterious apartment, but beware of the dangers that lurk within. Can you solve the cryptic riddles and learn the horrible truths ingrained within the structure's living, breathing walls? [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>