<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">VEEMEE Wacky Wavy Inflatable Balloon Man</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Homme ballon VEEMEE Wacky Wavy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verrückter, winkender, aufblasbarer VEEMEE-Ballonmann</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pupazzo gonfiabile che saluta VEEMEE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Muñeco hinchable bailarín de VEEMEE</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Attract customers to your business, make a splash at your next presentation, keep grandma company, protect your crops, confuse your neighbours or just raise the roof! Exclusive to the VEEMEE 3D Printer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Attirez l'attention des clients, faites sensation lors de votre prochaine présentation, tenez compagnie à grand-mère, protégez vos cultures, stupéfiez vos voisins ou soulevez tout simplement le toit ! Une exclusivité imprimante VEEMEE 3D. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mach Kunden auf dein Unternehmen aufmerksam, fall bei deiner nächsten Präsentation auf, leiste Omi Gesellschaft, schütz deine Ernte, verwirr deine Nachbarn oder lass es einfach krachen!  Exklusiv vom VEEMEE 3D-Drucker. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Attrae clienti nel tuo negozio, fa furore alla tua prossima presentazione, tiene compagnia alla nonna, protegge il raccolto, confonde i vicini o alza semplicemente il tetto! In esclusiva per la stampante 3D VEEMEE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Atrae clientes a tu negocio, sorprende en la próxima presentación, haz compañía a tu abuela, protege las cosechas, confunde a los vecinos o simplemente para dar la nota! En exclusiva para la Impresora VEEMEE 3D. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="Type">4th July 2014 [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>