<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Yellow Heart-Shaped Sunglasses Set (F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Paires de lunettes de soleil jaunes en forme de cœur (F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gelbes Herzsonnenbrillen-Set (F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set occhiali da sole a cuore gialli (da donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de gafas de sol amarillas con forma de corazón (M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ハート型サングラスセット（黄・女性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">하트모양 선글래스 세트(옐로우, 여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Yellow Heart Shaped Sunglasses Set (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">心型太陽眼鏡組（黃／女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">心型太陽眼鏡組（黃／女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Yellow Heart-Shaped Sunglasses Set (F)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Two pairs of heart-shaped sunglasses with yellow-tinted lenses.\n*This set includes a pair worn over the eyes and a pair worn raised.\nPurchasing this set will add 2 Glasses items to your Wardrobe.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Deux paires de lunettes de soleil en forme de cœur et aux verres teintés jaunes.\n*L'une des  paires se porte sur les yeux tandis que l'autre se porte relevée sur la tête.\nAcquérir ces deux paires ajoutera 2 objets Lunettes à votre Armoire.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zwei Sonnenbrillen mit herzförmigem Rahmen und gelb getönten Gläsern.\n*Dieses Set enthält eine Sonnenbrille, die vor den Augen getragen, und eine Sonnenbrille, die hochgesteckt getragen wird.\nWenn du dieses Set kaufst, werden deiner Garderobe 2 Sonnenbrillen-Gegenstände hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Due paia di occhiali da sole a forma di cuore con lenti gialle.\n*Questo set include un paio indossato sugli occhi e uno sulla fronte.\nL'acquisto del set aggiunge 2 oggetti Occhiali al tuo Guardaroba.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dos pares de gafas de sol con forma de corazón con lentes teñidas de amarillo.\n*Este juego incluye un par para llevar en los ojos y otro para llevar levantado.\nAl comprar este juego se añaden dos gafas al armario.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">フレームがハート型の黄色いサングラス。\n
※本セットには、「顔にかけるタイプ」と「頭に載せるタイプ」が含まれます。\n
購入すると「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の「メガネ」のカテゴリにアイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">프레임이 하트모양인 옐로우 선글래스.\n
※본 세트에는 「얼굴에 쓰는 타입」과「머리에 얹는 타입」이 포함됩니다.\n
구입하면 「아바타 꾸미기」내의 「안경」카테고리에 아이템이 추가됩니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Two pairs of heart-shaped sunglasses with yellow-tinted lenses.\n*This set includes a pair worn over the eyes and a pair worn raised.\nPurchasing this set will add 2 Glasses items to your Wardrobe.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">心型的黃色太陽眼鏡。\n
※本道具可戴在臉上或放在頭頂。\n
購入後，道具會追加至[前往衣帽間]的[眼鏡]。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">心型的黃色太陽眼鏡。\n
※本道具可戴在臉上或放在頭頂。\n
購入後，道具會追加至[前往更衣室]的[眼鏡]。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Two pairs of heart-shaped sunglasses with yellow-tinted lenses.\n*This set includes a pair worn over the eyes and a pair worn raised.\nPurchasing this set will add 2 Glasses items to your Wardrobe.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>