<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LOOT™ Sports Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot Sport LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LOOT™ Sport-Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto LOOT™ Sports</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lote deportivo de LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LOOT™ Sports Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This incredible sports bundle includes all four colours of the Longboard, Shortboard, Snowboard and all EIGHT colours of the Mountain Bike. We’re also throwing in, exclusive to this bundle only, the LOOT™ Skateboard to make it a lovely uneven 21 items in one righteous bundle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce formidable Lot Sport comprend les quatre couleurs de Longboard. Shortboard, Snowboard et les HUIT couleurs de VTT. Et on rajoute aussi en exclusivité dans ce lot, le Skateboard LOOT™ pour faire de ces charmants et impairs 21 articles, un lot d'une justesse parfaite.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses unglaubliche Sport-Bundle enthält alle vier Farben für das Longboard, das Shortboard und das Snowboard, sowie alle ACHT Farben des Mountain Bikes. Und obendrein gibt es, exklusiv in diesem Paket, das LOOT™ Skateboard um die 21 voll zu machen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo fantastico pacchetto include tutti e quattro i colori del Longboard, Shortboard, Snowboard e tutti gli OTTO colori della Mountain Bike. E noi ci aggiungiamo pure, in esclusiva per questo pacchetto solamente, il LOOT™ Skateboard per un bel numero dispari di articoli (21) in un unico pacchetto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este increíble lote deportivo incluye los cuatro colores de la tabla larga, la tabla corta, la tabla de snowboard y los OCHO colores de bicicleta de montaña. También incluimos, en exclusiva con este lote, la skateboard de LOOT™: 21 artículos fabulosos en un lote completísimo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This incredible sports bundle includes all four colors of the Longboard, Shortboard, Snowboard and all EIGHT colors of the Mountain Bike. We’re also throwing in, exclusive to this bundle only, the LOOT™ Skateboard to make it a lovely uneven 21 items in one righteous bundle. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>