<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Yukata Top (Hagoita, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Haut de Yukata (Hagoita, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Yukata-Oberteil (Hagoita, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Yukata parte superiore (Hagoita, D)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Parte superior de Yukata (Hagoita, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">浴衣・上（女性・羽子板）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">유카타 상의(여성, 부채)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Yukata Top (Women/Hagoita)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">日式浴衣 上 (女用／羽子板）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">日式浴衣 上 (女用／羽子板）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Yukata Top (Hagoita, F)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A single-layer kimono dyed a light red, with a motif commonly found on hagoita (ornamental New Year's paddles) featured on the hem. This is only the top half, above the obi belt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un kimono composé d'une seule couche teint en rouge clair et orné d'un motif typique des hagoita (raquettes en bois ornementales). C'est seulement le haut, au-dessus de la ceinture obi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein einfacher, hellrot eingefärbter Kimono aus Baumwolle mit einem Hagoita-Motiv auf dem Saum. So wie man es von einem Hagoita (dekorierter Neujahrsfächer) kennt. Dies ist nur die obere Hälfte, die sich oberhalb des Obigürtels befindet.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un kimono leggero tinto in rosso pallido e decorato con un motivo tradizionale degli hagoita (racchette da volano usate durante il Capodanno). Solo la parte superiore, dalla cintola (obi) in su.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un kimono de algodón de una sola capa teñido de color rojo claro con un motivo que se suele encontrar en los hagoita (paletas decorativas del Año Nuevo) en el dobladillo. Esto solo es la parte superior, por encima del cinturón obi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">淡い赤色に染めた浴衣の裾に、羽子板（はごいた）が描かれている、ひとえの着物。帯より上の半身。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">희미한 적색에 물들인 유카타의 옷자락에 부채가 그려진 전통 복장. 허리띠 위의 상의.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">An unlined kimono top with light red dyed hemming and a hagoita (Japanese battledore) drawn on it.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在染成淺紅色的下擺印上羽子板的一重和服。腰帶之上的上半身部份。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在染成淺紅色的下擺印上羽子板的一重和服。腰帶之上的上半身部份。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A single-layer kimono dyed a light red, with a motif commonly found on hagoita (ornamental New Year's paddles) featured on the hem. This is only the top half, above the obi belt.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>