<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ObjectName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Lucky Flag Cap (Womens)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Casquette Drapeau de la chance (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Glücksfahnen-Kappe (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cappello Bandiera Lucky (Per donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Gorra Bandera Afortunada (Femenina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">女性用ラッキーフラッグ帽子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">행운의 깃발모자 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Lucky Flag Cap (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">幸運便帽（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">幸運便帽（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Lucky Flag Cap</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ObjectDescription</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A Luck Flag Hat which can only be purchased at the shop. Wow your friends with this cool looking fashion accessory! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un Chapeau Drapeau de la chance pouvant uniquement être acheté dans la boutique. Épatez vos amis avec ce nouvel accessoire de mode très classe ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Glücksflaggen-Hut, der nur im Shop erhältlich ist. Beeindrucken Sie Ihre Freunde mit diesem super gut aussehenden Modeaccessoire! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un Cappello Bandiera Lucky che può essere acquistato solo al negozio. Sbalordisci i tuoi amici con questo fantastico accessorio di moda! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sombrero Bandera de la Suerte que solo puede comprarse en la tienda. ¡Alucina a tus amigos con este accesorio tan guay! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ショップ限定ラッキーフラッグ帽子です。注目されること間違いなし！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">샵 한정 판매 행운의 깃발모자입니다. 이목을 집중시키기 딱이죠! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A Luck Flag Hat which can only be purchased at the shop. Wow your friends with this cool looking fashion accessory! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">本店限定的幸運便帽。戴上後必定吸引眾人的目光！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">本店限定的幸運便帽。戴上後必定吸引眾人的目光！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A cut above the regular yellow flag, the Lucky Flag was the hard-earned secret bonus for classic Namco gamers around the world! Now you can take a walk down memory lane, and show off your gaming prowess with this quirky cap that tells the world just how much of a hardcore gamer you are![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>