<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Street Style - Mega Bundle 03 (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Street Style - Méga lot 03 (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Street Style - Megapaket 03 (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Street Style 3 - Mega Set 03 (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Street Style - Mega Pack 03 (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hit the streets in style with this selection of Hip Hop inspired outfits!\n
\n
This bundle contains:\n
(1) Street Style - Bling snapback Cap - Pink (Women)\n
(2) Street Style - Bling snapback Cap - Black (Women)\n
(3) Street Style - Bling snapback Cap - White (Women)\n
(4) Street Style - One Up Cargo Pants - Black (Women)\n
(5) Street Style - One Up Cargo Pants - White (Women)\n
(6) Street Style - One Up Cargo Pants - Cargo (Women) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Parcourez les rues avec style grâce à cette sélection de tenus d'inspiration Hip Hop !\n
\n
Ce lot contient :\n
(1) Street Style - Casquette snapback bling-bling - Rose (femme)\n
(2) Street Style - Casquette snapback bling-bling - Noir (femme)\n
(3) Street Style - Casquette snapback bling-bling - Blanc (femme)\n
(4) Street Style - Pantalon cargo One Up - Noir (femme)\n
(5) Street Style - Pantalon cargo One Up - Blanc (femme)\n
(6) Street Style - Pantalon cargo One Up - Cargo (femme) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erobern Sie die Straßen mit Stil in diesen vom Hip Hop inspirierten Outfits!\n
\n
Dieses Paket enthält:\n
(1) Street Style - Bling Snapback-Kappe - Pink (Damen)\n
(2) Street Style - Bling Snapback-Kappe - Schwarz (Damen)\n
(3) Street Style - Bling Snapback-Kappe - Weiß (Damen)\n
(4) Street Style - One Up Cargo-Pants - Schwarz (Damen)\n
(5) Street Style - One Up Cargo-Pants - Weiß (Damen)\n
(6) Street Style - One Up Cargo-Pants - Cargo (Damen) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scendi in strada con un look super trendy grazie a questa selezione di abbigliamento di ispirazione hip hop!\n
\n
Il set comprende:\n
(1) Street Style - Cappello Snapback luccicante - Rosa (Donna)\n
(2) Street Style - Cappello Snapback luccicante - Nero (Donna)\n
(3) Street Style - Cappello Snapback luccicante - Bianco (Donna)\n
(4) Street Style - Pantaloni con tasche laterali - Nero (Donna)\n
(5) Street Style - Pantaloni con tasche laterali - Bianco (Donna)\n
(6) Street Style - Pantaloni con tasche laterali - Cargo (Donna) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Sal a la calle con estilo gracias a esta selección de ropa inspirada en el Hip-hop!\n
\n
Este pack contiene:\n
(1) Street Style - Gorra lujosa con cierre trasero - Rosa (Mujer)\n
(2) Street Style - Gorra lujosa con cierre trasero - Negro (Mujer)\n
(3) Street Style - Gorra lujosa con cierre trasero - Blanco (Mujer)\n
(4) Street Style - Pantalón cargo enrollado - Negro (Mujer)\n
(5) Street Style - Pantalón cargo enrollado - Blanco (Mujer)\n
(6) Street Style - Pantalón cargo enrollado - Color cargo (Mujer) [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>