<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Disco Hairstyle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Coiffure Disco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Disco Frisur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Acconciatura Disco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Peinado Disco</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The return to the 1970s! Inspired by the hippy and disco movement, this collection gives you the freedom to combine your favourite colours, fabrics and prints. This line represents a whole life style. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le retour aux années 1970! Inspiré par le mouvement hippy et disco, cette collection vous donne la liberté de combiner vos couleurs, tissus et imprimés préférés. Cette ligne représente tout un style de vie. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zurück in die 1970s! Diese Kollektion, inspiriert von der Hippie- und Diskobewegung, gibt dir Freiheit deine Lieblingsfarben, -materialien und –drucke selbst zusammenzustellen. Diese Reihe verkörpert eine ganze Lebenseinstellung. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il ritorno agli anni Settanta! Questa collezione, che si ispira al movimento hippie e disco, ti offre tutta la libertà di abbinare i colori, i tessuti e le stampe che preferisci. Questa linea rappresenta un intero stile di vita. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El regreso de los años 70! Inspirada en el movimiento hippie y disco, esta colección te da libertad para combinar todos los colores así como las telas y estampados que más te gusten. Una línea que representa todo un estilo de vida. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The return to the 1970s! Inspired by the hippy and disco movement, this collection gives you the freedom to combine your favourite colors, fabrics and prints. This line represents a whole life style. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>