<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Group animations bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bundle des animations de groupe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bundle der Gruppe Animationen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bundle delle animazioni di gruppo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bundle de las animaciones de grupo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Group animations bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This bundle contains 11 group animations: Line Dancing, Cossak jump-style, Bollywood, Disco Inferno, Chicken Dance, Zombie, Cha-Cha Step, Modern Country, Latin Routine, K-pop and Mexican Wave. Once you have equipped the item, up to 7 other users can then join, by walking up to the disco ball and pressing the X button. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce bundle contient 11 animations de groupe: Danse en ligne, danse militaire russe, Bollywood, Disco,	danse des canards, Zombie, Cha-Cha,	Country, danse latine, K-pop et la ola. Equipez l'animation, et jusqu'à 7 utilisateurs pourront danser avec vous, en marchant jusqu'à la boule disco et en appuyant sur X.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser Bundle enthält 11 Gruppe Animationen: Line-Dancing, russisch Jumpstyle, Bollywood, Disco, Vogerltanz, Zombie, Cha-Cha, Country, Latin Tanz, K-pop und die Mexikanische Welle. Sobald Sie dieser Artikel ausgestattet ist, können bis zu 7 andere Benutzer dann beitreten: sie müssen zu Fuß bis zu der Discokugel, und X drücken.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo bundle contiene 11 animazioni di gruppo: Linea Danza, russo-salto, Bollywood, Disco, Ballo del qua qua, Zombie, Cha-Cha, Country, Ballo latino, K-pop e la ola. Dopo aver dotato questo articolo, fino a 7 altri utenti possono poi unirsi, a piedi fino al disco ball e premendo X. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esto bundle contiene 11 animaciones de grupo: Line dancing, estilo ruso, Bollywood, Disco, Baile de los pajaritos, Zombie, Cha-Cha, Country, Baile latino, K-pop y la ola. Una vez que haya equipado este artículo, otros hasta 7 usuarios pueden unirse, por caminar hasta el la bola de discoteca y pulsando X. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This bundle contains 11 group animations: Line Dancing, Cossak jump-style, Bollywood, Disco Inferno, Chicken Dance, Zombie, Cha-Cha Step, Modern Country, Latin Routine, K-pop and Mexican Wave. Once you have equipped the item, up to 7 other users can then join, by walking up to the disco ball and pressing the X button. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>