<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Red on White</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Rouge sur Blanc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Rot auf Weiß</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Rosso su Bianco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Rojo sobre Blanco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - 레드온화이트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Red on White</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - 白間紅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - 白間紅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Red on White</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">More fun than a barrel of monkeys is Chim Peep!  Dressed to the nines in his monkey suit, bring him into your apartment and get down to business!  You can control him with custom animations and special Peep moves![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chim Peep est plus amusant qu'une bande de singes! Habillé à quatre épingles, en costume, ramène-le dans ton appartement et passons aux choses sérieuses! Tu peux le contrôler avec des animations personnalisées et manœuvres spéciales Peep![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mehr Spaß als ein Affenhaus verspricht Chim-Peep! Bring ihn in seinem Affenoutfit mit in deine Wohnung und der Spaß beginnt! Du kannst ihn mit benutzerdefinierten Animationen und speziellen Peep-Bewegungen steuern![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chim Peep é piú divertente di tante scimmie messe insieme!  Vestito alla grande con il suo vestito di scimmia, portalo dentro il tuo appartamento e dateci sotto! Puoi controllarlo con animazioni fatte a posta e movimenti speciali Peep![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chim Peep es más divertido que un barril lleno de monos!  Vestido de fiesta en su traje de mono, llévalo a tu departamento y a lo que les truje chenchas!  Lo puedes controlar con animaciones personalizadas y movimientos Peep especiales![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_2 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">원숭이보다 더 재미있는 원숭이 Chim Peep!  우아한 수트를 입혀 아파트에 데려와 사업을 시작해 보세요!  사용자 지정 애니메이션과 특수 Peep 모션으로 컨트롤할 수 있습니다![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">More fun than a barrel of monkeys is Chim Peep!  Dressed to the nines in his monkey suit, bring him into your apartment and get down to business!  You can control him with custom animations and special Peep moves![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Chim是非常有趣的Peep！他精心打扮，帶他進入您家，開始工作吧!您可以用自訂動態和專屬Peep動作來控制他！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Chim是非常有趣的Peep！他精心打扮，帶他進入您家，開始工作吧!您可以用自訂動態和專屬Peep動作來控制他！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">More fun than a barrel of monkeys is Chim Peep!  Dressed to the nines in his monkey suit, bring him into your apartment and get down to business!  You can control him with custom animations and special Peep moves![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>