<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bunny Bundle (female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Set Lapin (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kaninchen Bundle (frau)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set Coniglio (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lote Conejo (mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Reinvent the Pyjama Party! 

Change your boring outfits and add a touch of colour to your nights. Fun and different the Kigurumis suits your personality. Are you daring, curious, agile or strong? No matter who you are! There is always a Kigurumis for you! Become the focus of attention in the most original way, engage your instincts and start your wildest parties!
 \n
This bundle contains: \n
 \n
- Kigu Bunny Hat (female) \n
- Kigu Bunny Suit (female) \n
- Kigu Bunny Shoes (female) \n
- Kigu Bunny Gloves (female) \n

[#Legal]</LANG>

    <LANG ID="en-US">Reinvent the Pajama Party! 

Change your boring outfits and add a touch of color to your nights. Fun and different the Kigurumis suits your personality. Are you daring, curious, agile or strong? No matter who you are! There is always a Kigurumis for you! Become the focus of attention in the most original way, engage your instincts and start your wildest parties!
 \n
This bundle contains: \n
 \n
- Kigu Bunny Hat (female) \n
- Kigu Bunny Suit (female) \n
- Kigu Bunny Shoes (female) \n
- Kigu Bunny Gloves (female) \n

[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Réinventez la pyjama party ! 

Remplacez vos tenues ennuyeuses et ajoutez de la couleur à vos nuits. Amusant et différent, il y a un Kigurumis pour chaque personnalité. Audacieux, curieux, agile ou fort ? Qu’importe qui vous êtes, il y a un Kigurumis fait pour vous ! Devenez le centre d’attention de la manière la plus originale, utilisez vos instincts, et organisez les fêtes les plus folles ! 
 \n
Cet ensemble contient: \n
 \n
- Kigu Chapeau Lapin (femme) \n
- Kigu Costume de Lapin (femme) \n
- Kigu Chaussures de Lapin (femme) \n
- Kigu Lapin Gants (femme) \n

[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erfinden Sie die Pajama-Party neu! 

Ändern Sie Ihre langweiligen Outfits und bringen Sie ein bisschen Farbe in Ihre Nächte. Sie bereiten Freude und sind etwas ganz Besonders, wir haben den richtigen Kigurumi für Jeden! Sind Sie kühn, neugierig, lebhaft oder stark? Ganz egal wer Sie sind, wir haben Kigurumis für Jedermann! Stellen Sie sich auf originelle Weise in Mittelpunkt, binden Sie Ihre Instinkte ein und schmeißen Sie die wildesten Parties! 
 \n
Dieses Set enthält: \n
 \n
- Kigu Kaninchen Hut (frau) \n
- Kigu Kaninchen Anzug (frau) \n
- Kigu Kaninchen Schuhe (frau) \n
- Kigu Kaninchen Handschuhe (frau) \n

[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Reinventa il Pigiama Party! 

Cambia il tuo abbigliamento noioso e aggiungi un tocco di colore alle tue serate. Divertente e diverso, c'è un Kigurumis per ogni personalità. Sei coraggioso, curioso, agile o forte? Non importa chi tu sia, c'è sempre un Kigurumis per te! Mettiti al centro dell'attenzione nel modo più originale, dai spazio ai tuoi istinti e organizza party sensazionali! 
 \n
Questo set contiene: \n
  \n
- Kigu Capello Coniglio (donna) \n
- Kigu Vestito Coniglio (donna) \n
- Kigu Scarpe di Coniglio (donna) \n
- Kigu Guanti di Coniglio (donna) \n

[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Reinventa las Fiestas Pijama! 

Cambia tus aburridos atuendos y dale un toque de color a tus noches. Divertidos y diferentes los Kigurumis se adaptan a tu personalidad. ¿Eres atrevido, curioso, ágil o fuerte? No importa cómo seas! Siempre habrá un Kigurumis para ti. Conviértete en el centro de atención de la forma más original, busca tus instintos más primitivos y dale rienda suelta a tus fiestas más salvajes! 
 \n
Este set contiene: \n
 \n
- Kigu Sombrero Conejo (mujer) \n
- Kigu Traje de Conejo (mujer) \n
- Kigu Zapatos de Conejo (mujer) \n
- Kigu Guantes de Conejo (mujer) \n

[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>