<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Elegant Klondike Solitaire</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Solitaire élégant</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Elegantes Klondike Solitär</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Elegante Solitario Klondike</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Elegante solitario Klondike</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Elegant Klondike Solitaire</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Classic Klondike solitaire! The only way to get this game is to play it and win it. You win a game and you are rewarded with a copy of the game to take back and play anytime in your spaces. Then invite your friends over to win their copy. This is truly win-win! This is an interactive active object item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un solitaire classique ! La seule façon d'obtenir ce jeu est d'y jouer et de gagner. Si vous gagnez une partie, vous obtiendrez une version du jeu à laquelle vous pourrez jouer quand vous voudrez dans vos espaces. Vous pourrez ensuite inviter vos amis à venir y jouer chez vous pour qu'ils puissent gagner leur propre solitaire. Tout le monde y gagne ! Il s'agit d'un objet actif interactif. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das klassische Klondike Solitär! Du kannst dieses Spiel nur erhalten, wenn du es spielst und gewinnst. Wenn du gewinnst, erhältst du das Spiel als Belohnung und du kannst es mitnehmen und jederzeit in deinen persönlichen Räumen spielen. Lade dann deine Freunde ein, um wiederum ihr Spiel zu gewinnen! Dies ist ein interaktiver, aktiver Gegenstand. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il classico solitario Klondike! L'unico modo per ottenere questo gioco è giocarci e vincere. Se vinci una partita, verrai premiato con una copia del gioco, che potrai prendere per giocare quando vuoi nei tuoi spazi. Invita i tuoi amici per vincere la loro copia. Una vittoria totale! È un oggetto attivo interattivo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡El clásico solitario Klondike! La única forma de conseguir este juego es jugar y ganar. Si ganas, recibirás una copia del juego para llevártelo y jugar en cualquier momento en tus espacios. Invita luego a tus amigos para ganar su copia. ¡Esto es ganar-ganar de verdad! Es un artículo-objeto interactivo activo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Classic Klondike solitaire! The only way to get this game is to play it and win it. You win a game and you are rewarded with a copy of the game to take back and play anytime in your spaces. Then invite your friends over to win their copy. This is truly win-win! This is an interactive active object item. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Full Description 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Klondike Solitaire Rules\n\nPlayers: 1 player\n\nDeck: A standard 52 card deck (no jokers).\n\nGoal:\n\nStack all four suits up, from Ace to King, in separate piles called the "Foundations".\n\nSetup:\n\nShuffle the deck. Deal out seven piles (the "Tableau") with the first pile getting one card, the second pile gets two cards, and so forth, until the last pile has seven cards. Turn the top card on each pile face up, so that there are 7 face-up cards. Set the remaining cards aside, forming the "Stock" pile.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Règles du solitaire\n\nJoueurs : 1 joueur\n\nJeu : un jeu de cartes standard de 52 cartes (sans jokers).\n\nBut :\n\n Empilez les quatre couleurs de l'as au roi en piles séparées appelées "bases".\n\nInstallation :\n\nCommencez par battre les cartes. Faites sept piles de cartes (le "tapis") dont la première contiendra une carte, la deuxième deux cartes, et ainsi de suite jusqu'à la dernière pile de sept cartes. Retournez la carte au-dessus de chaque pile pour qu'il y ait 7 cartes face visible sur le tapis. Placez les cartes restantes à côté, pour en faire la pile de la "pioche".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Regeln für Klondike Solitär\n\nSpieler: 1 Spieler\n\nKarten: Ein Standard-Kartenspiel mit 52 Karten (ohne Joker).\n\nZiel:\n\nStaple alle vier Farben von Ass bis König auf getrennte Stapel, die "Fundamente" genannt werden. \n\nVorbereitung:\n\nMisch die Karten. Teile 7 Stapel aus ("Das Tableau"). Der erste Stapel besteht aus einer Karte, der zweite aus zwei usw., bis der letzte Stapel sieben Karten hat. Dreh die oberste Karte jedes Stapels um, sodass du 7 Karten mit der Bildseite nach oben hast. Leg die übrigen Karten beiseite- sie sind der "Vorrat".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Regole del Solitario Klondike \n\nGiocatori: 1giocatore\n\nMazzo: Un mazzo standard da 52 carte (senza joker).\n\nScopo:\n\nImpila tutte le quattro figure, dall'Asso al Re, in mazzi separati chiamati le "Basi". \n\nImpostazione:\n\nMescola il mazzo. Dividi in sette pile (il "Tableau") con la prima formata da una carta, la seconda da due, e via così, con l'ultima pila formata da sette carte. Gira la carta in cima ad ogni pila con la faccia all'insù, così che ci siano 7 carte scoperte. Metti da parte la carte rimanenti, formando così il "Mucchio".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Reglas del solitario Klondike\n\nJugadores: 1 jugador\n\nBaraja: Baraja estándar de 52 cartas (sin comodines).\n\n\Objetivo:\n\nApila los cuatro palos desde el as al rey en diferentes montones, llamados "fundaciones".\n\nDisposición:\n\nBaraja. Haz siete montones (el "tablero") en los cuales el primero tenga una carta, el segundo dos cartas y así sucesivamente hasta que el último montón tenga siete cartas. Pon boca arriba la carta superior de cada montón de manera que haya siete cartas boca arriba. Guarda las demás cartas del "taco" aparte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Klondike Solitaire Rules\n\nPlayers: 1 player\n\nDeck: A standard 52 card deck (no jokers).\n\nGoal:\n\nStack all four suits up, from Ace to King, in separate piles called the "Foundations".\n\nSetup:\n\nShuffle the deck. Deal out seven piles (the "Tableau") with the first pile getting one card, the second pile gets two cards, and so forth, until the last pile has seven cards. Turn the top card on each pile face up, so that there are 7 face-up cards. Set the remaining cards aside, forming the "Stock" pile.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Full Description 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Foundations\n\nAs they become available, the four Aces should be moved to the four Foundations. Cards of the same suit may be played on each Ace in ascending order, from low (2) to high (King).\n\nNOTE: Some versions of Klondike Solitaire do not allow you to move cards back from the Foundations and the Tableau. This alternative rule makes the game harder to win. We do not enforce this restriction but players can restrict themselves at their discretion.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bases\n\nAu fur et à mesure que les quatre as sont retournés, ils doivent chacun être placés sur les quatre bases. Les cartes de la même couleur doivent être placées sur chaque as dans l'ordre croissant, du plus petit (2) au plus grand (roi).\n\nNOTE : certaines versions du solitaire ne vous permettent pas de replacer les cartes de la base sur le tapis. Cette règle alternative rend le jeu plus difficile à gagner ; nous ne l'appliquons pas, mais les joueurs peuvent le faire s'ils le souhaitent.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fundamente\n\nSobald du sie hast, solltest du die vier Asse auf die vier Fundamente legen. Karten derselben Farbe werden von Ass in absteigender Reihenfolge vom  niedrigsten Wert (2) bis zum höchsten Wert (König) gespielt.\n\nANMERKUNG: In einigen Versionen von Klondike Solitär darfst du Karten nicht von den Fundamenten und dem Tableau zurücknehmen. Diese alternative Regel macht es schwerer, das Spiel zu gewinnen.  Wir wenden diese Regel nicht an, aber Spieler können sie nach eigenem Ermessen aufstellen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Basi\n\nQuando diventano disponibili, i quattro Assi devono essere spostati sulle quattro Basi. Le carte con la stessa figura devono essere posate sul proprio Asso corrispondente in ordine ascendente, dal più basso (2) al più alto (Re).\n\nNOTE: Alcune versioni del Solitario Klondike non ti permettono di spostare carte dalle Basi al Tableau. Questa regola alternativa rende il gioco più difficile. Noi non poniamo questa restrizione ma ogni giocatore può decidere da solo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fundaciones\n\nTan pronto como estén disponibles, los cuatro ases deberán ser movidos a las cuatro fundaciones. Las cartas del mismo palo deberán jugarse sobre cada as en orden ascendente desde abajo (2) hacia arriba (rey).\n\nNOTA: Algunas versiones del solitario Klondike no permiten mover cartas hacia atrás desde las fundaciones y el tablero. Esta regla alternativa hace que sea más difícil ganar. Nosotros no imponemos esta regla aunque los jugadores pueden seguirla según su criterio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Foundations\n\nAs they become available, the four Aces should be moved to the four Foundations. Cards of the same suit may be played on each Ace in ascending order, from low (2) to high (King).\n\nNOTE: Some versions of Klondike Solitaire do not allow you to move cards back from the Foundations and the Tableau. This alternative rule makes the game harder to win. We do not enforce this restriction but players can restrict themselves at their discretion.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Full Description 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tableau\n\nOn the Tableau, cards are played in descending order, alternating between red and black.\n\nEXAMPLE: The 10 of hearts may be played on either the Jack of clubs or the Jack of spades. The 5 of clubs may be played on either the 6 of hearts or 6 of diamonds.\n\nAnytime you move all the face up cards from one pile of the Tableau to another, the top face down card is turn over. This card is now in play.\n\nIf a column in the Tableau is emptied, any visible King (or a visible King with other cards on top of it) can be moved to fill that space.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tapis\n\nSur le tapis, les cartes sont jouées dans l'ordre décroissant, en alternant entre une couleur rouge et noire.\n\nEXEMPLE : le 10 de cur peut être placé soit sur le valet de trèfle, soit sur le valet de pique. Le 5 de trèfle peut être placé soit sur le 6 de cur, soit sur le 6 de carreau.\n\nLorsque vous aurez déplacé toutes les cartes face visible d'une pile du tapis à une autre, la dernière carte de la pile est retournée face visible, et cette carte est alors jouable.\n\nSi une pile du tapis est vide, alors tout roi visible (ou tout roi visible avec des cartes sur lui) peut y être placé pour remplir l'espace.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tableau\n\nAuf dem Tableau werden abwechselnd rote und schwarze Karten in absteigender Reihenfolge gespielt.\n\nBEISPIEL: Herz 10 kann entweder auf Pik Bube oder Kreuz Bube gelegt werden. Kreuz 5 kann entweder auf Herz 6 oder Karo 6 gelegt werden.\n\nJedes Mal, wenn du alle aufgedeckten Karten von einem Stapel des Tableaus auf einen anderen legst, wird die oberste aufgedeckte Karte umgedreht. Diese Karte ist jetzt im Spiel.\n\nWenn eine Reihe des Tableaus leer ist, kann jeder sichtbare König (oder sichtbare König mit anderen Karten darauf) bewegt werden, um die Stelle einzunehmen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tableau\n\nSul Tableau, le carte sono giocate in ordine discendente, alternando il rosso e il nero.\n\nEXAMPLE: Il 10 di cuori può essere giocato sul Jack di fiori o sul Jack di picche. Il 5 di fiori può essere giocato sul 6 di cuori o sul 6 di quadri. \n\nOgni volta che muovi tutte le carte scoperte da una pila del Tableau all'altra, la prima carta coperta viene voltata. In quel momento la carta entra in gioco. \n\nSe una colonna del Tableau viene svuotata, ogni Re visibile (o un Re visibile ma con altre carte sopra) può essere spostato per riempire quello spazio.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tablero\n\nEn el tablero las cartas se juegan en orden descendente alternando entre rojas y negras.\n\nEJEMPLO: El 10 de corazones puede jugarse sobre la sota de tréboles o la de picas. El 5 de tréboles puede jugarse sobre el 6 de corazones o el 6 de diamantes.\n\nCada vez que muevas todas las cartas descubiertas de un montón a otro del tablero se descubre la carta superior que estaba boca abajo. Esta carta estará entonces en juego.\n\nSi se vacía una columna del tablero, cualquier rey a la vista (o un rey a la vista con otras cartas encima) puede moverse para llenar ese espacio. </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Tableau\n\nOn the Tableau, cards are played in descending order, alternating between red and black.\n\nEXAMPLE: The 10 of hearts may be played on either the Jack of clubs or the Jack of spades. The 5 of clubs may be played on either the 6 of hearts or 6 of diamonds.\n\nAnytime you move all the face up cards from one pile of the Tableau to another, the top face down card is turn over. This card is now in play.\n\nIf a column in the Tableau is emptied, any visible King (or a visible King with other cards on top of it) can be moved to fill that space.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Full Description 4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gameplay\n\nTurn cards from the Stock pile over one at a time or three at a time and placed on the face-up discard pile (the "Waste"). If the top card on the Waste is playable (either on a Foundation or the Tableau), you may do so. The top card on the Waste pile is always available to be played. Cards underneath it are not. You continue flipping cards from the Stock to the Waste and playing cards as appropriate. Once you have gone through all the cards in the Stock, the Waste is flipped back onto the Stock and play continues. There is no restriction on the number of times you may go through the Stock.\n\nALTERNATIVE: Some versions of Klondike Solitaire only allow you to go through the Stock once for Turn 1 and three times for Turn 3. These restrictions are applicable by the player at their own discretion.\n\nWinning\n\nYou win Klondike Solitaire by moving all the cards to the four Foundations.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Style de jeu\n\nRetournez les cartes de la pioche une à la fois, ou trois à la fois, et placez-les face visible sur la pile des cartes défaussées (la "défausse"). Si la carte au-dessus de la défausse est jouable (sur une base ou sur le tapis), alors vous pouvez l'utiliser. La carte du dessus de la défausse peut toujours être jouée à n'importe quel moment ; celles qui sont en dessous ne le sont pas. Vous pouvez continuer à retourner les cartes de la pioche dans la défausse et les jouer si nécessaire. Une fois que toutes les cartes de la pioche ont été retournées, la défausse est retournée sur la pioche, et le jeu continue. Il n'y a pas de limite au nombre de fois où vous pouvez retourner la pioche.\n\nALTERNATIVE : certaines versions du solitaire ne vous permettent de tirer les cartes de la pile qu'une fois pendant le premier tour, et trois fois pendant le troisième tour. Ces restrictions sont applicables par le joueur s'il le souhaite.\n\nGagner\n\nVous aurez gagné le jeu lorsque toutes les cartes seront sur les quatre bases.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spielverlauf\n\nNimm entweder eine oder drei Karten auf einmal und lege sie mit der Bildseite nach oben auf den Stapel für abgelegte Karten (der "Abfall"). Wenn die oberste Karte auf dem Abfall spielbar ist (entweder auf dem Fundament oder dem Tableau), kannst du sie einfach verwenden. Die oberste Karte auf dem Abfall kann immer gespielt werden. Karten darunter jedoch nicht. Drehe Karten weiter vom Vorrat auf den Abfallstapel und spiele die Karten, wenn möglich. Wenn du alle Karten des Vorratsstapels durch hast, wird der Abfallstapel umgedreht und er bildet den neuen Vorrat.  Du kannst den Vorrat so oft du möchtest durchgehen.\n\nALTERNATIV: Bei einigen Versionen von Klondike Solitär darf man nur einmal in der ersten Runde und drei Mal in der dritten Runde durch den Vorrat gehen. Ob du nach dieser Regel spielst oder nicht, liegt in deinem eigenen Ermessen.\n\nSieg\n\nDu hast das Spiel gewonnen, wenn du alle Karten auf die vier Fundamente verteilt hast.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gioco\n\nGira le carte dal Mucchio, una alla volta o tre alla volta, e mettile nella pila di quelle scoperte e messe da parte (lo "Scarto"). Se la prima carta dello Scarto è giocabile (sia sulle Basi che sul Tableau), la puoi sfruttare. La prima carta del mazzo degli Scarti è sempre pronta per essere giocata, mentre le carte al di sotto non lo sono. Continua a muovere carte dal Mucchio allo Scarto e giocale quando ti sembra il momento giusto. Una volta finite le carte del Mucchio, tutto lo Scarto diventa Mucchio e il gioco continua. Non ci sono restrizioni sul numero di volte che puoi scorrere tutto il Mucchio.\n\nALTERNATIVA: Alcune versione del solitario Klondike ti permettono di scorrere tutto il Mucchio una volta per il Primo Turno e 3 volte per il Terzo Turno. Queste restrizioni sono applicabili a discrezione del giocatore.\n\nVincere\n\nVinci il solitario Klondike spostando tutte le carte sulle quattro Basi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mecánica del juego\n\nSaca las cartas del montón de una en una o de tres en tres y colócalas boca arriba en el taco de cartas descartadas (el "sobrante"). Puedes usar la carta superior del sobrante (en una fundación o en el tablero) si es jugable. Siempre se puede usar la carta superior del sobrante pero no las que están debajo. Continúa dándole la vuelta a las cartas desde el taco al sobrante y usando las cartas según corresponda. Una vez que las cartas del taco se terminen, al sobrante se le da la vuelta pasando a ser taco de nuevo y el juego continúa. No hay ninguna restricción en cuanto al número de veces que uses el taco.\n\nALTERNATIVA: Algunas versiones del solitario Klondike solo permiten sacar una vez las cartas de una en una y tres veces de tres en tres. Esta restricción solo se aplica según el criterio del jugador.\n\n Ganas al solitario Klondike moviendo todas las cartas a las cuatro fundaciones.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gameplay\n\nTurn cards from the Stock pile over one at a time or three at a time and placed on the face-up discard pile (the "Waste"). If the top card on the Waste is playable (either on a Foundation or the Tableau), you may do so. The top card on the Waste pile is always available to be played. Cards underneath it are not. You continue flipping cards from the Stock to the Waste and playing cards as appropriate. Once you have gone through all the cards in the Stock, the Waste is flipped back onto the Stock and play continues. There is no restriction on the number of times you may go through the Stock.\n\nALTERNATIVE: Some versions of Klondike Solitaire only allow you to go through the Stock once for Turn 1 and three times for Turn 3. These restrictions are applicable by the player at their own discretion.\n\nWinning\n\nYou win Klondike Solitaire by moving all the cards to the four Foundations.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Choose Game - Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Choose Game:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Choisir le jeu :</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spiel wählen:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scegli il Gioco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Elige juego:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Choose Game:</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Choose Game - Draw 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Draw 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tirer 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">1 Ziehen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Estrai 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Saca 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Draw 1</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Choose Game - Draw 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Draw 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tirer 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">3 Ziehen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Estrai 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Saca 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Draw 3</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Control - Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Controls:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Contrôles :</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Steuerung:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Comandi:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Controles:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Controls:</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Control - Selection Up</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[UP] Selection Up</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[UP] Sélection en haut</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[UP] Auswahl oben</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[UP] Selezione sopra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[UP] Selección arriba</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[UP] Selection Up</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Control - Selection Down</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DOWN] Selection Down</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DOWN] Sélection en bas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DOWN] Auswahl unten</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DOWN] Selezione sotto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DOWN] Selección abajo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DOWN] Selection Down</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Control - Selection Left</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFT] Selection Left</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFT] Sélection à gauche</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFT] Auswahl links</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFT] Selezione sinistra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFT] Selección izquierda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[LEFT] Selection Left</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Control - Selection Right</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[RIGHT] Selection Right</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[RIGHT] Sélection à droite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[RIGHT] Auswahl rechts</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[RIGHT] Selezione destra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[RIGHT] Selección derecha</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[RIGHT] Selection Right</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Control - Select</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] Select</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] Sélectionner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] Wählen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] Seleziona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] Seleccionar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[CROSS] Select</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Control - Deal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[SQUARE] Deal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[SQUARE] Distribuer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[SQUARE] Austeilen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[SQUARE] Dai le carte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[SQUARE] Repartir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[SQUARE] Deal</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Control - Auto Complete</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[L1] Auto Complete</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[L1] Réalisation automatique</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[L1] Autom. fertigstellen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[L1] Completa Automaticamente</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[L1] Autocompletar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[L1] Auto Complete</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Control - Select Stock</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CIRCLE] Draw Cards</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CIRCLE] Tirer des cartes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CIRCLE] Karten ziehen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CIRCLE] Pesca le Carte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CIRCLE] Saca cartas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[CIRCLE] Draw Cards</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Control - Help</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[L2] Help</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[L2] Aide</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[L2] Hilfe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[L2] Aiuto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[L2] Ayuda</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[L2] Help</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Control - Undo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[R1] Undo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[R1] Annuler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[R1] Rückgängig</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[R1] Annulla</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[R1] Deshacer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[R1] Undo</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Control - Redo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[R2] Redo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[R2] Refaire</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[R2] Wiederholen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[R2] Rifai</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[R2] Rehacer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[R2] Redo</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Control - Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE] Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE] Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] Salir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Help Legend 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">\n\n[RIGHT] 1/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">\n\n[RIGHT] 1/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">\n\n[RIGHT] 1/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">\n\n[RIGHT] 1/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">\n\n[RIGHT] 1/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">\n\n[RIGHT] 1/5  </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Help Legend 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 2/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 2/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 2/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 2/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 2/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 2/5  </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Help Legend 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 3/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 3/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 3/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 3/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 3/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 3/5  </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Help Legend 4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 4/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 4/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 4/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 4/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 4/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">\n\n[LEFT][RIGHT] 4/5  </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Help Legend 5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">\n\n[LEFT] 5/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">\n\n[LEFT] 5/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">\n\n[LEFT] 5/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">\n\n[LEFT] 5/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">\n\n[LEFT] 5/5  </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">\n\n[LEFT] 5/5  </LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">End Game - Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">End this game?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Arrêter cette partie ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spiel beenden?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vuoi concludere il gioco?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Acabar el juego?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">End this game?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">End Game - Yes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Yes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Oui</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ja</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sì</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sí</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Yes</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">End Game - No</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">No</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Non</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nein</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">No</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">No</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">won</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You Won!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez gagné !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie gewann!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai vinto!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ha ganado usted!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You Won!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Move Selection</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[UP][DOWN][LEFT][RIGHT] Move Selection</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[UP][DOWN][LEFT][RIGHT] Déplacer la sélection</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[UP][DOWN][LEFT][RIGHT] Auswahl bewegen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[UP][DOWN][LEFT][RIGHT] Muovi la Selezione</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[UP][DOWN][LEFT][RIGHT] Mover selección</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[UP][DOWN][LEFT][RIGHT] Move Selection</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Left Menu Legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[UP][DOWN] Move Selection</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[UP][DOWN] Déplacer la sélection</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[UP][DOWN] Auswahl bewegen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[UP][DOWN] Muovi la Selezione</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[UP][DOWN] Mover selección</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[UP][DOWN] Move Selection</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Choose Game - Right Menu Legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Select  [DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Sélectionner  [DECLINE] Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Wählen  [DECLINE] Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Seleziona  [DECLINE] Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Seleccionar [DECLINE] Salir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Select  [DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">End Game - Right Menu Legend</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Select</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Sélectionner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Wählen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Seleziona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Seleccionar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[ACCEPT] Select</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>