<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">F.U.B.A.R. Apartment (+DOUBLE POINTS)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appartement F.U.B.A.R. (+ POINTS DOUBLÉS)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">F.U.B.A.R.-Apartment (+DOPPELTE PUNKTZAHL)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Appartamento F.U.B.A.R.(+PUNTI DOPPI)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apartamento F.U.B.A.R. (EL DOBLE DE PUNTOS)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">F.U.B.A.R. アパートメント（+ダブルポイント）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">F.U.B.A.R. 아파트 (+더블 포인트)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">F.U.B.A.R. Apartment (+DOUBLE POINTS)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">F.U.B.A.R. 公寓（+雙倍點數）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">F.U.B.A.R. 公寓（+雙倍點數）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">F.U.B.A.R. Apartment (+DOUBLE POINTS)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This unique outdoor apartment contains a scaled copy of your own amazing military base from the FREE game F.U.B.A.R. (Fight Until Blood And Ruin) and earns you DOUBLE POINTS in key sections of the game, helping you rank up much faster. Observe your master piece of war from the comfort of your own home and show it off to your friends. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cet appartement ouvert unique comporte une copie de votre propre base militaire formidable tirée du jeu GRATUIT F.U.B.A.R. (Lutte jusqu'au sang et la ruine) et vous fera gagner LE DOUBLE DE POINTS à des endroits clés du jeu, vous faisant augmenter de niveau beaucoup plus rapidement. Observez votre chef d'œuvre de guerre bien au chaud chez vous et impressionnez vos amis. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses einzigartige Outdoor-Apartment beinhaltet eine maßstabsgetreue Kopie deiner tollen Militärbasis aus dem Spiel F.U.B.A.R. (Fight Until Blood and Ruin), was dir bei besonders wichtigen Spielabschnitten die DOPPELTE PUNKTZAHL einbringt, wodurch du in den Rängen weitaus schneller aufsteigst. Beobachte dein Kriegsmeisterwerk bequem von zu Hause aus und zeige es deinen Freunden. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo appartamento unico contiene una copia in scala ridotta della tua base militare presente nel gioco GRATUITO F.U.B.A.R. (lotta all'ultimo sangue) e ti garantisce PUNTI DOPPI in sezioni chiave del gioco, aiutandoti così a salire di rango più velocemente. Osserva il tuo capolavoro bellico comodamente da casa tua e impressiona i tuoi amici. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este apartamento único contiene una copia a escala de tu increíble campamento militar del juego gratuito de F.U.B.A.R. (Lucha hasta que corran la sangre y la ruina). Con solo tenerlo, conseguirás EL DOBLE DE PUNTOS en las secciones clave del juego y, así, podrás subir de rango aún más rápido. Observa tu obra maestra bélica desde la comodidad de tu hogar y presume de ello ante tus amigos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この屋外風パーソナルスペースには、ゲーム『F.U.B.A.R.（命尽きるまで戦え）』であなたが築きあげた軍事基地の模型が飾られています。そして、ゲーム内の主要セクションで獲得するポイントが2倍となり、ランク昇進をスピードアップさせることができます。自分の傑作をくつろぎながら鑑賞したり、フレンドに自慢したりしましょう [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 독특한 야외 아파트는 무료 게임 F.U.B.A.R. (Fight Until Blood And Ruin)의 놀라운 군기지 복사본을 포함하고 있으며 게임의 주요 섹션에서 더블 포인트를 획득할 수 있어서 계급 상승에 큰 도움을 줍니다. 집에서 편안하게 전쟁의 걸작품을 지켜보고 친구들에게 자랑하세요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This unique outdoor apartment contains a scaled copy of your own amazing military base from the FREE game F.U.B.A.R. (Fight Until Blood And Ruin) and earns you DOUBLE POINTS in key sections of the game, helping you rank up much faster. Observe your master piece of war from the comfort of your own home and show it off to your friends. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">本款獨特戶外公寓包括您在免費遊戲 F.U.B.A.R.（血戰到底）中擁有的超強軍事基地複製模型，並在遊戲關鍵區域贏取雙倍點數，這有助於您更快速地升級。在舒適的家中欣賞自己的戰爭傑作，並且還可以向朋友炫耀一下。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">本款獨特戶外公寓包括您在免費遊戲 F.U.B.A.R.（血戰到底）中擁有的超強軍事基地複製模型，並在遊戲關鍵區域贏取雙倍點數，這有助於您更快速地升級。在舒適的家中欣賞自己的戰爭傑作，並且還可以向朋友炫耀一下。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This unique outdoor apartment contains a scaled copy of your own amazing military base from the FREE game F.U.B.A.R. (Fight Until Blood And Ruin) and earns you DOUBLE POINTS in key sections of the game, helping you rank up much faster. Observe your master piece of war from the comfort of your own home and show it off to your friends. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>