<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Pajama Top, Short (Star &amp; Moon Pattern on Light Blue, Men)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Haut de pyjama, court (motifs étoiles et lunes sur bleu ciel, homme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Pyjama-Oberteil, kurz ("Mond und Sterne"-Motiv, hellblau, für Männer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Giacca pigiama corta (azzurra con motivo a stelle e lune, da uomo)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Parte superior corta de pijama (estampado de estrellas y luna sobre fondo celeste, hombre)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">パジャマの上着・短（水色地月星柄・男性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Pajama Top, Short (Star &amp; Moon Pattern on Light Blue, Men)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Pajama top worn while sleeping. Short length type to make the lower hem look nicer when sitting. Best suited for sitting on "Dreamy Bed" advanced furniture.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nSleepiness: ★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un haut de pyjama porté pendant le sommeil. Ce modèle est plus court pour que le bord du bas ait l'air plus joli en position assise. Idéal pour s'asseoir sur les objets avancés "lit rêveur".\nDéfense : ★\nSommeil : ★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Pyjama-Oberteil, das beim Schlafen getragen wird. Durch die kurze Länge liegt der Saum beim Sitzen besser. Passt sehr gut zum Sitzen auf dem fortgeschrittenen Möbelstück "Verträumtes Bett".\nVerteidigung: ★\nSchläfrigkeit: ★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Giacca del pigiama indossata mentre si dorme, leggermente accorciata in modo che risalti meglio l'orlo inferiore. Perfetta per sedersi sull'articolo di arredamento avanzato "Letto da sogno".\nDifesa: ★\nLivello sonnolenza: ★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Parte superior del pijama que se usa para dormir. Queda mejor al estar sentado, ya que su longitud es más corta. Perfecta para sentarse en el mobiliario avanzado "Camas de ensueño".\nDefensa: ★\nLetargo: ★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">寝るときに着るパジャマの上着。座ったときに裾がきれいに見えるように丈を短めにしているタイプ。アドバンスド家具「夢見るベッド」に腰掛けるときに最適。\n防御力：　★\n安眠度：　★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Pajama top worn while sleeping. Short length type to make the lower hem look nicer when sitting. Best suited for sitting on "Dreamy Bed" advanced furniture.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nSleepiness: ★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
