<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LittleBigPlanet™ Karting Home Square Races</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Courses LittleBigPlanet™ Karting du Square Home</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"LittleBigPlanet™ Karting"-Rennen für den Home-Platz</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gare di LittleBigPlanet™ Karting nella Piazza Home</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Carreras de LittleBigPlanet™ Karting en la Plaza Home</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">LittleBigPlanet™ Karting 홈 스퀘어 레이스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">LittleBigPlanet™ Karting Home Square Races</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「小小大星球™ 布娃娃也賽車」Home Square賽車</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「小小大星球™ 布娃娃也賽車」Home Square賽車</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LittleBigPlanet™ Karting Home Square Races [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Courses LittleBigPlanet™ Karting du Square Home [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"LittleBigPlanet™ Karting"-Rennen für den Home-Platz [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gare di LittleBigPlanet™ Karting nella Piazza Home [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Carreras de LittleBigPlanet™ Karting en la Plaza Home [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">LittleBigPlanet™ Karting 홈 스퀘어 레이스 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">LittleBigPlanet™ Karting Home Square Races [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「小小大星球™ 布娃娃也賽車」Home Square賽車 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「小小大星球™ 布娃娃也賽車」Home Square賽車 [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">LittleBigPlanetKarting</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Vroom vroom! It's time to put the pedal to the metal. Choose between a cute cupcake kart or a snappy sardine tin kart and race round the LittleBigPlanet™ Karting track with your friends. The choice is yours: you can have a head-to-head race with just one other, or if you're feeling daring, why not grab as many people as you can and compete en masse! Now start your engines, pick your favourite helmet and get to the starting grid. Three, two, one, RACE!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vroum ! Vroum ! Il est temps de mettre le pied au plancher. Choisis un mignon cupcake-kart  ou encore une rapide boîte de sardines et fais la course contre tes amis sur la piste de LittleBigPlanet™ Karting. Le choix t'appartient : une course en un contre un avec un de tes amis ou, si tu te sens audacieux, pourquoi ne pas rameuter autant de joueurs que tu peux et c'est parti pour une monstrueuse course. Allez, fais tourner le moteur, enfile ton casque préféré et rends-toi sur la ligne de départ. 3 - 2 - 1, PARTEZ !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Brumm-brumm! Es ist Zeit, in die Eisen zu treten. Wähle zwischen einem süßen Cupcake-Kart und einem schnittigen Sardinendosen-Kart und fahre auf der Kartingstrecke von LittleBigPlanet™ Karting Rennen mit deinen Freunden. Du hast die Wahl: Trete im Kopf-an-Kopf-Rennen gegen nur einen anderen Spieler an, oder  sei mutig, trommle so viele Leute wie möglich zusammen und ihr liefert euch ein Massenrennen! Wirf die Maschine an, schnapp dir deinen Lieblingshelm und auf in die Startposition. Drei, zwei, eins, RENNEN!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Broom, broom! È il momento di premere sull'acceleratore! Scegli per kart un delizioso dolcetto o un'accattivante scatola di sardine e gareggia con i tuoi amici sulla pista LittleBigPlanet™ Karting. La scelta è solo tua: puoi lanciarti in un testa a testa con un solo avversario o, se ti senti particolarmente coraggioso, sfidare più persone possibile in una competizione di massa. Scalda il motore, indossa il tuo casco preferito e precipitati alla griglia di partenza. Tre, due, uno, VIA!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Brum, brum! Es hora de pisar el acelerador. Elige entre un kart magdalena precioso o un kart lata de sardinas veloz y corre en la pista de LittleBigPlanet™ Karting con tus amigos. La elección es tuya: puedes correr cara a cara contra un solo adversario o, si te atreves, ¡competir contra un mogollón de gente! Arranca tus motores, escoge tu casco favorito y ve a la parrilla de salida. Tres, dos, uno, ¡A CORRER!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">부릉부릉! 악셀 페달을 밟을 시간입니다. 컵케이크 카트와 날렵한 통조림 카트 중 하나를 골라서 친구들과 함께 LittleBigPlanet™ 트랙을 달려보세요. 여러분은 친구와 1 대 1 경주를 진행할 수도 있고, 도전 정신을 살려 최대한 많은 사람을 모아 대규모 레이스를 완료할 수도 있습니다. 선택은 여러분의 몫입니다! 자 이제 시동을 거세요. 좋아하는 헬멧을 고르고 준비 선에 대기하세요. 3, 2, 1, 시작!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Vroom vroom! It's time to put the pedal to the metal. Choose between a cute cupcake kart or a snappy sardine tin kart and race round the LittleBigPlanet™ Karting track with your friends. The choice is yours: you can have a head-to-head race with just one other, or if you're feeling daring, why not grab as many people as you can and compete en masse! Now start your engines, pick your favourite helmet and get to the starting grid. Three, two, one, RACE!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">此時正是踩油門踩到底的時刻！從可愛的杯型蛋糕造型車或時髦的沙丁魚罐頭造型車選擇一台適合您的車，並在「小小大星球™ 布娃娃也賽車」的車道上跟您的朋友賽車！您可選擇1對1單挑，或者如果您夠勇敢的話，邀請大家來進行大混戰！所以趕快去發動引擎，選個您喜歡的安全帽，並在起跑線上排隊吧！三、二、一、賽車！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">此時正是踩油門踩到底的時刻！從可愛的杯型蛋糕造型車或時髦的沙丁魚罐頭造型車選擇一台適合您的車，並在「小小大星球™ 布娃娃也賽車」的車道上跟您的朋友賽車！您可選擇1對1單挑，或者如果您夠勇敢的話，邀請大家來進行大混戰！所以趕快去發動引擎，選個您喜歡的安全帽，並在起跑線上排隊吧！三、二、一、賽車！</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CIRCLE] Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CIRCLE] Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CIRCLE] Beenden</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CIRCLE] Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CIRCLE] Salir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[DECLINE] 종료</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[DECLINE] Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[DECLINE] 離開</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[DECLINE] 離開</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>