<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Indian, 1967</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Indian, 1967</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Indian, 1967</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Indian, 1967</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Indian, 1967</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Indian, 1967</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Indian, 1967</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Indian, 1967</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Indian, 1967</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Indian, 1967</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Indian, 1967</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Van Hamersveld recalls “I found the Indian image there on 7th Street and Coronado Avenue in  a "Junk Store" along the sidewalk, a few doors down from  McManus and Morgan, where I bought exotic papers for my art classes. Honeya my art school girlfriend pointed to the pile of photos, suggesting I should take a look. As I shuffled throughout the images, I found four Indian pictures; There was one I liked of a young Native American man. He seemed to be looking at me, there was something good about him and felt a connection between us. That was 1967”. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Van Hamersveld se souvient : "C'est ici que j'ai trouvé le portrait de cet Indien, entre 7th Street et Coronado Avenue, dans un bazar installé sur le trottoir, à quelques enjambées de chez Mc Manus et Morgan où je venais d'acheter du papier à dessin pour mes cours. Honeya, une amie de l'école, me montra la pile de photos en me disant d'y jeter un coup d'œil. En fouillant un peu, j'ai trouvé quatre portraits d'Indiens et l'image de ce jeune homme m'a plu. J'avais l'impression qu'il me regardait. Il dégageait une aura positive et le courant est bien passé entre nous. C'était en 1967". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Van Hamersveld erinnert sich: „Auf das Indianer-Motiv stieß ich auf der 7th Street, Ecke Coronado Avenue in einem Ramschladen, nur ein paar Schritte von McManus and Morgan entfernt, wo ich ausgefallenes Papier für meinen Kunstunterricht kaufte. Honeya, meine Freundin an der Kunstschule, zeigte auf den Stapel Fotos und schlug vor, ich sollte doch mal einen Blick darauf werfen. Beim Durchschauen der Bilder fand ich vier Indianerfotos. Eines, das mir gut gefiel, zeigte einen jungen indianischen Mann. Er schien mich anzuschauen, er hatte eine gute Ausstrahlung und ich fühlte eine Verbindung zwischen uns. Das war 1967.“ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Van Hamersveld racconta: "ricordo di aver trovato l'immagine dell'indiano tra la 7th Street e Coronado Avenue, in un negozio di cianfrusaglie lungo la strada, a pochi passi da McManus and Morgan dove avevo acquistato carta esotica per i miei corsi di arte. Honeya, la mia fidanzata di allora, mi indicò un mucchio di foto, consigliandomi di dare un'occhiata. Mentre le sfogliavo, trovai quattro foto di indiani e una mi colpì particolarmente: si trattava dell'immagine di un giovane. Sembrava che mi stesse guardando, c'era qualcosa di bello in lui e avvertii immediatamente una sorta di legame fra noi. Era il 1967". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Van Hamersveld declaró: "Encontré la imagen del indio en el cruce de la calle 7 con Coronado Avenue en un puesto en la acera, a unas pocas casas de McManus and Morgan, donde compraba papel especial para mis clases de arte. Honeya, mi novia de la época de Bellas Artes, me señaló un montón de fotos y dijo que debería echarles un vistazo. Mientras miraba las fotos, encontré cuatro imágenes de indios. Había una que me gustó en la que se veía a un indio americano joven. Parecía estar mirándome, tenía algo bueno y sentí una conexión entre nosotros. Corría el año 1967”. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Van Hamersveld recalls “I found the Indian image there on 7th Street and Coronado Avenue in  a "Junk Store" along the sidewalk, a few doors down from  McManus and Morgan, where I bought exotic papers for my art classes. Honeya my art school girlfriend pointed to the pile of photos, suggesting I should take a look. As I shuffled throughout the images, I found four Indian pictures; There was one I liked of a young Native American man. He seemed to be looking at me, there was something good about him and felt a connection between us. That was 1967”. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Van Hamersveld recalls “I found the Indian image there on 7th Street and Coronado Avenue in  a "Junk Store" along the sidewalk, a few doors down from  McManus and Morgan, where I bought exotic papers for my art classes. Honeya my art school girlfriend pointed to the pile of photos, suggesting I should take a look. As I shuffled throughout the images, I found four Indian pictures; There was one I liked of a young Native American man. He seemed to be looking at me, there was something good about him and felt a connection between us. That was 1967”. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Van Hamersveld recalls “I found the Indian image there on 7th Street and Coronado Avenue in  a "Junk Store" along the sidewalk, a few doors down from  McManus and Morgan, where I bought exotic papers for my art classes. Honeya my art school girlfriend pointed to the pile of photos, suggesting I should take a look. As I shuffled throughout the images, I found four Indian pictures; There was one I liked of a young Native American man. He seemed to be looking at me, there was something good about him and felt a connection between us. That was 1967”. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Van Hamersveld recalls “I found the Indian image there on 7th Street and Coronado Avenue in  a "Junk Store" along the sidewalk, a few doors down from  McManus and Morgan, where I bought exotic papers for my art classes. Honeya my art school girlfriend pointed to the pile of photos, suggesting I should take a look. As I shuffled throughout the images, I found four Indian pictures; There was one I liked of a young Native American man. He seemed to be looking at me, there was something good about him and felt a connection between us. That was 1967”. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Van Hamersveld recalls “I found the Indian image there on 7th Street and Coronado Avenue in  a "Junk Store" along the sidewalk, a few doors down from  McManus and Morgan, where I bought exotic papers for my art classes. Honeya my art school girlfriend pointed to the pile of photos, suggesting I should take a look. As I shuffled throughout the images, I found four Indian pictures; There was one I liked of a young Native American man. He seemed to be looking at me, there was something good about him and felt a connection between us. That was 1967”. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Worn Free" T-Shirt male. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>