<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Crystal Seashores Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cristal bords de mer clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kristallküste: Clubhaus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sede del club Spiagge cristalline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sede del club Orillas de cristal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Crystal Seashores Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">수정 해안 클럽하우스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Crystal Seashores Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">水晶海岸聯盟俱樂部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">水晶海岸聯盟俱樂部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Crystal Seashores Clubhouse</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Crystal Seashores is a lavish waterfront home meant for those with extravagant lifestyles. A split staircase, open foyer, and backyard swimming pool are just footnotes when compared to the ocean view this home has to offer. The Crystal Seashores space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cristal bords de mer est une maison front de mer somptueux signifiait pour ceux qui ont un mode de vie extravagant. Un escalier divisé, foyer ouvert, et la piscine sont juste cour notes par rapport à la vue sur l'océan de cette maison a à offrir. Cristal bords de mer clubhouse est un espace où chacun est invité à se joindre. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Kristallküste ist ein großzügiges Zuhause in Küstenlage für Menschen mit einem extravaganten Lebensstil. Eine geteilte Treppe, ein offenes Foyer und ein Swimmingpool im Garten sind nur Fußnoten, wenn man den Ozeanblick in Betracht zieht, den dieses Haus bietet. Die Kristallküste ist ein Clubhaus, in dem jeder Gast willkommen ist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lo spazio Spiagge cristalline è una casa lussuosa sull'acqua ideata per tutte le persone dallo stile di vita dispendioso. Una doppia scalinata, un atrio all'aperto, e una piscina sul retro sono semplici dettagli se paragonati alla vista dell'oceano che questa casa può offrire. Lo spazio Spiagge cristalline è una sede del club dove chiunque è il benvenuto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Orillas de cristal es una casa costera muy lujosa para todos aquellos que disfruten con los estilos de vida extravagantes. La escalera dividida, el recibidor abierto y la piscina en el patio trasero no parecen nada en comparación con la vista al océano de esta casa. El espacio Orillas de cristal es una sede del club a la que todos están invitados. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Crystal Seashores is a lavish waterfront home meant for those with extravagant lifestyles. A split staircase, open foyer, and backyard swimming pool are just footnotes when compared to the ocean view this home has to offer. The Crystal Seashores space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">수정 해안은 화려한 삶을 즐기는 사람들을 위한 해안가의 집입니다. 화려한 계단과 탁 트인 현관과 뒤뜰에 있는 수영장은, 집안에서 볼 수 있는 해변의 경치에 비교하면 아무것도 아닙니다. 수정 해안 스페이스는 누구나 환영받는 클럽하우스입니다.*수정 해안 클럽하우스 에 입장하려면 먼저 클럽을 구매해야 합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Crystal Seashores is a lavish waterfront home meant for those with extravagant lifestyles. A split staircase, open foyer, and backyard swimming pool are just footnotes when compared to the ocean view this home has to offer. The Crystal Seashores space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. *Please note, in order to access the Crystal Seashores Clubhouse, you will need to have purchased the Club Slot. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">水晶海岸具備極盡奢華的氣派，最適合懂得享受的您。兩排的開放樓梯、開揚的庭院及後花園的游泳池也比不上此屋座擁的無敵海景。和大家一起在水晶海岸聯盟俱樂部內相聚吧。※請注意，要使用水晶海岸聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">水晶海岸具備極盡奢華的氣派，最適合懂得享受的您。兩排的開放樓梯、開揚的庭院及後花園的游泳池也比不上此屋座擁的無敵海景。和大家一起在水晶海岸聯盟俱樂部內相聚吧。※請注意，要使用水晶海岸聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Crystal Seashores is a lavish waterfront home meant for those with extravagant lifestyles. A split staircase, open foyer, and backyard swimming pool are just footnotes when compared to the ocean view this home has to offer. The Crystal Seashores space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>