<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Hazard" Battle Scarred Sneakers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Basketsde combat abîmées "Danger"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schuhe „Gefahr“ mit Kampfschaden</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scarpe sfregiate "Hazard"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Zapatillas desgastadas "Hazard"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ダメージドスニーカー ”ハザード”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">전투의 흔적이 남은 운동화 - "위협"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Hazard" Battle Scarred Sneakers</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">留有戰鬥痕跡的「Hazard」運動鞋</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">留有戰鬥痕跡的「Hazard」運動鞋</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Hazard" Battle Scarred Sneakers</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">S.V.E.R. battle gear offers durable and extensible armour solutions for all battle environments under all conditions. Reflecting S.V.E.R.'s general battle philosophy, S.V.E.R.'s uniforms prioritise performance over aesthetics. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'équipement de combat S.V.E.R. offre des solutions de protection résistantes et confortables pour tous les environnements possibles, dans toutes les conditions. Reflétant la philosophie générale de S.V.E.R., les uniformes privilégient la performance et non l'esthétisme. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">S.V.E.R.-Kampfausrüstung zeichnet sich durch eine hohe Beständigkeit und umfassende Lösungen für jeden Kriegsschauplatz und alle Bedingungen aus. Wie es auch der Kampfphilosophie von S.V.E.R. entspricht, gab man hier der Leistung den Vorzug gegenüber der Ästhetik. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'equipaggiamento della S.V.E.R. offre delle soluzioni durevoli e adattabili ad ogni tipo e condizione di battaglia. In conformità con la filosofia bellica della S.V.E.R., l'estetica delle uniformi passa in secondo piano rispetto alle prestazioni. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El equipo de combate de S.V.E.R. incluye soluciones de blindaje resistentes y extensibles para adaptarse a todo tipo de entornos y condiciones de combate. Muy en línea con la filosofía general de S.V.E.R., sus uniformes sacrifican la estética en favor del rendimiento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このセイバー用の戦闘ギアは伸縮性素材で作られたアーマーで、あらゆる環境に適している。セイバーの信念を反映して、見た目より機能を重視している。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">S.V.E.R.의 전투 장비는 내구력이 강하며 어떠한 상황에도 적응할 수 있는 다양한 형태의 제작이 가능합니다. 조직 자체의 신념을 담았기 때문에 외관 보다는 성능을 우선으로 여깁니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">SVER battle gear offers durable and extensible armor solutions for all battle environments under all conditions. Reflecting SVER's general battle philosophy, SVER's uniforms prioritize performance over aesthetics. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">SVER戰鬥裝備，為所有戰鬥環境狀況提供耐用而可擴充的武裝解決方案。反映SVER總體戰鬥哲學的SVER制服，其實際效能完全凌駕於美學之上。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">SVER戰鬥裝備，為所有戰鬥環境狀況提供耐用而可擴充的武裝解決方案。反映SVER總體戰鬥哲學的SVER制服，其實際效能完全凌駕於美學之上。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">SVER battle gear offers durable and extensible armor solutions for all battle environments under all conditions. Reflecting SVER's general battle philosophy, SVER's uniforms prioritize performance over aesthetics. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>