<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MotorStorm® Carrier Treasure Hunt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MotorStorm® Carrier Treasure Hunt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chasse au trésor du transporteur MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MotorStorm®-Flugzeug- träger-Schatzsuche</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caccia al tesoro Portaerei MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Portaaviones MotorStorm® En busca del tesoro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">MotorStorm®  トレジャーハント</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">MotorStorm®  모함 속의 보물 찾기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">MotorStorm™  Carrier Treasure Hunt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">MotorStorm™ 航空母艦尋寶</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">MotorStorm™ 航空母艦尋寶</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MotorStorm® Carrier Treasure Hunt</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">LEGEND EXIT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CIRCLE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CIRCLE] Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CIRCLE] Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CIRCLE] Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CIRCLE] Salir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[CIRCLE] 終了</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[CIRCLE] 나가기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[CIRCLE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[CIRCLE] 退出</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[CIRCLE] 退出</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[CIRCLE] Exit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">LEGEND PICKUP</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] Pickup</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] Ramasser</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] Nehmen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] Raccogli</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] Recoger</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[CROSS] 拾う</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[CROSS] 줍기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[CROSS] Pickup</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[CROSS] 拾起</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[CROSS] 拾起</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[CROSS] Pickup</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">LEGEND TALK</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] Talk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] Parler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] Sprechen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] Parla</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] Hablar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[CROSS] 話す</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[CROSS] 대화</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[CROSS] Talk</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[CROSS] 講話</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[CROSS] 講話</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[CROSS] Talk</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">LEGEND LISTEN</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS] Listen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[CROSS] Écouter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[CROSS] Hören</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[CROSS] Ascolta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[CROSS] Escuchar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[CROSS] 聴く</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[CROSS] 듣기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[CROSS] Listen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[CROSS] 聆聽</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[CROSS] 聆聽</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[CROSS] Listen</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MERCH_GIRL_TALK_1_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">“Hey, I’m Fidget, supplier of all your MotorStorm® gear needs. I’m almost out of MX helmets but I’ve, err, lost the key to the stock room. I can’t leave the store, could you help me find it? Maybe it's in my bag, up in the VIP section by the DJ box.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Salut, moi c'est Fidget, le fournisseur de tout  l'équipement MotorStorm® dont vous aurez besoin. Je  n'ai presque plus de casques MX mais j'ai heu, perdu la  clé du stock. Je peux pas quitter la magasin.  Pourriez-vous m'aider à la retrouver ? Elle doit être dans  mon sac, dans la zone VIP, vers la cabine du DJ."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Hallo! Ich bin Fidget, ich versorge dich mit jeglicher MotorStorm®-Ausrüstung. Im Augenblick brauche ich MX-Helme, aber ich ... ähh ... habe wohl den Schlüssel zum Vorratsraum verloren. Ich kann den Laden nicht verlassen, könntest du mir vielleicht helfen? Vielleicht befindet er sich in meiner Tasche, die im VIP-Bereich beim DJ-Platz sein sollte.“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Ehi, io sono Fidget e ho tutti i gadget MotorStorm® che  tu possa desiderare. Ho quasi finito le t-shirt, ma...  ehm... purtroppo ho perso la chiave del magazzino. Il fatto  è che non posso lasciare il negozio. Ti andrebbe di  aiutarmi a trovarla? Dovrebbe essere nella mia borsa che ho lasciato nel settore VIP, accanto ai CD del DJ."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Hola, me llamo Fidget, y soy tu proveedora de equipo de MotorStorm®. Casi no me quedan cascos de MX, y me temo que –ejem– he perdido la llave del almacén. No puedo salir de la tienda. ¿Podrías ayudarme a encontrarla? Tal vez esté en mi bolso, en la zona VIP, al lado de la cabina del DJ".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「ヘイ！MotorStormグッズを扱ってるフィジェットよ。モトクロスヘルメットの在庫を補充したいんだけど、倉庫の鍵をどこかで落としちゃって・・・。今店を抜けることが出来ないんで、悪いけど代わりに鍵を探してきてくれない？VIPエリアのDJボックスに私の鞄があるんだけど、その中にあると思うの。マジ助かるわ！！」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"이봐, 난 피젯이라고 해. 여기서 필요한 모든 걸 담당하는 사람이지. 지금은 MX 헬멧이 상당히 부족하지만, 음, 사실은 창고의 열쇠를 잃어버렸지 뭐야. 가게를 비울 순 없으니까 자네가 좀 가서 찾아주겠나? 아마 내 가방에 있을 거야. DJ 부스 옆의 VIP 실에."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">“Hey, I’m Fidget, supplier of all your MotorStorm™ gear needs. I’m almost out of MX helmets but I’ve, err, lost the key to the stock room. I can’t leave the store, could you help me find it? Maybe it's in my bag, up in the VIP section by the DJ box.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">『嗨，我是Fidget，MotorStorm™裝備的供應商。MX頭盔的存貨已經很少了，但是我好像把倉庫的鑰匙給弄丟了。我現在沒法離開店裡，你能幫我找一下嗎？我想應該放在我的包包裡了，我的包包在DJ包廂旁邊的VIP區。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">『嗨，我是Fidget，MotorStorm™裝備的供應商。MX頭盔的存貨已經很少了，但是我好像把倉庫的鑰匙給弄丟了。我現在沒法離開店裡，你能幫我找一下嗎？我想應該放在我的包包裡了，我的包包在DJ包廂旁邊的VIP區。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">“Hey, I’m Fidget, supplier of all your MotorStorm® gear needs. I’m almost out of MX helmets but I’ve, err, lost the key to the stock room. I can’t leave the store, could you help me find it? Maybe it's in my bag, up in the VIP section by the DJ box.”</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MERCH_GIRL_TALK_1_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">“Damn, they’re not in here... Erm, err... I dunno, maybe I left them in my buggy, would you mind having a look?”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Zut, c'est pas là... Hum, euh... Je sais pas, je l'ai peut-être laissée dans mon buggy. Vous voulez bien aller jeter un coup d'œil ?"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Mist, hier ist er nicht ... Ähh, hmm ... Keine Ahnung ... Vielleicht ist er in meinem Buggy. Könntest du dort mal nachschauen?“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">“Diamine, qui non c'è... ehm... chissà, forse l'ho lasciata nella mia buggy. Ti dispiace andare a vedere?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“Maldita sea, no están aquí... Erm, err... No sé, a lo mejor me las dejé en el buggy. ¿Te importaría echar un vistazo?”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「うそ。絶対バッグの中だと思ったのに・・・う～ん、じゃあもしかしたら私のバギーの中にあるかも・・・。ちょっとバギーの中をチェックしてくれない？」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이런, 여기에는 없네… 아니면 내 버기에 두고 내렸나?  가서 한 번만 봐 줘.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">“Damn, they’re not in here... Erm, err... I dunno, maybe I left them in my buggy, would you mind having a look?”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">『該死，沒在這兒…唔…不知道會不會是放在我的車上了，能幫我去看一下嗎？』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">『該死，沒在這兒…唔…不知道會不會是放在我的車上了，能幫我去看一下嗎？』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">“Damn, they’re not in here... Erm, err... I dunno, maybe I left them in my buggy, would you mind having a look?”</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MERCH_GIRL_TALK_2_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">“Did you speak to Bones? He was looking for the DJ earlier, maybe you should go see if you can help out. We can’t leave this CD on repeat forever!”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Vous avez parlé à Bones ? Il cherchait le DJ, tout à l'heure. Vous devriez peut-être aller lui proposer un coup de main. On peut pas laisser ce CD en boucle éternellement !"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Hast du mit Bones gesprochen? Er hat vorhin nach dem DJ gesucht. Vielleicht könntest du ihm helfen. Es wäre ärgerlich, wenn wir die ganze Zeit nur diese eine CD hören müssten!“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">“Hai parlato con Bones? Prima stava cercando il DJ: forse dovresti andare a vedere se puoi dare una mano. Non possiamo lasciare questo CD in eterno!”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“¿Has hablado con Bones? Antes estaba buscando al DJ. A lo mejor deberías ir a ver si puedes echar una mano. ¡No podemos dejar que este CD se repita una y otra vez!”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「ボーンズとは話した？DJがどこかへいなくなったから今探しに行ってるんだけど、彼を助けてあげて。さっきからずっと同じCDが流れてるから早くなんとかしないと！」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"본즈한테 이야기를 해 보는 게 어때? 조금 전에 DJ를 찾고 있던데, 가서 좀 도와줄 수 있겠나 봐줘. 이 CD만 계속 틀어줄 순 없다구!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">“Did you speak to Bones? He was looking for the DJ earlier, maybe you should go see if you can help out. We can’t leave this CD on repeat forever!”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">『你和Bones聊過了嗎？他之前正在尋找DJ，也許你可以過去看看可不可以幫上什麼忙。我們不能永遠重複播放同一張CD！』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">『你和Bones聊過了嗎？他之前正在尋找DJ，也許你可以過去看看可不可以幫上什麼忙。我們不能永遠重複播放同一張CD！』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">“Did you speak to Bones? He was looking for the DJ earlier, maybe you should go see if you can help out. We can’t leave this CD on repeat forever!”</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MERCH_GIRL_TALK_2_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">“Found him... Go stand over there by the portable toilets, I’d take a deep breath first... I don’t think he’ll be out for a while, see what Bones wants to do...”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Trouvé... Allez voir du côté des toilettes de chantier. Je serais vous, je prendrais une grande respiration d'abord... Je pense pas qu'il sortira avant un moment. Allez voir ce que Bones veut faire..."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Er ist gefunden ... Geh hinüber zum Toilettencontainer, halte dort aber lieber die Luft an ... Ich glaube, er könnte dort etwas länger brauchen. Bring in Erfahrung, was Bones vorhat ...“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">“Trovato! Mettiti là, fuori dai bagni chimici. Fossi in te, prenderei prima un bel respiro... non credo che uscirà presto. Vediamo che dice Bones...”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“Lo encontré... Ve adonde los baños portátiles. Si fuera tú, antes respiraría bien hondo... Creo que tardará un rato en salir. Mira a ver lo que quiere hacer Bones…”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「あっ、いた！鼻つまんであの簡易トイレのそばで待ってればDJがいつか出てくるはず・・・うっ、まだ出てきそうもないからボーンズにどうすればいいか確認してみよう。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"그를 봤어… 저기 간이 화장실 앞에 서 있어봐. 아마 숨을 들이마시지 않는 게 좋을 거야. 한참은 기다려야 할 테니 본즈가 뭘 원하는지 보는 게 어때…"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">“Found him... Go stand over there by the portable toilets, I’d take a deep breath first... I don’t think he’ll be out for a while, see what Bones wants to do...”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">『找到他了…。先去那邊的簡易廁所一下，過去之前我得先深深地吸口氣…。我想他暫時不會出來了，看看Bones想要做些什麼吧…。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">『找到他了…。先去那邊的簡易廁所一下，過去之前我得先深深地吸口氣…。我想他暫時不會出來了，看看Bones想要做些什麼吧…。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">“Found him... Go stand over there by the portable toilets, I’d take a deep breath first... I don’t think he’ll be out for a while, see what Bones wants to do...”</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BOUNCER_TALK_1_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">“Hey buddy – don’t tell me, you’re looking for Fidget’s bag? I’ve already told her and everyone else she’s sent looking for it - it’s not here. I sent her to go have a lie down, try looking around the chill-out lounge under the deck ramp. If you’re into finding things, head back over here in a while, I might have another mission for you.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Eh, là-bas. Laissez-moi deviner, vous cherchez le sac de Fidget ? Je lui ai déjà dit, ainsi qu'à tous ceux qu'elle a envoyés, qu'il était pas là. Je lui ai dit d'aller se reposer. Allez voir dans la salle de détente, sous la rampe. Si votre truc c'est de retrouver des choses, revenez plus tard, je pourrais avoir une autre mission pour vous."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Hey, Kumpel! Lass mich raten: Du suchst nach Fidgets Tasche! Ich habe es ihr gesagt, und ich habe es auch jedem anderen gesagt, den sie hierher geschickt hat: Sie ist nicht hier! Sie sollte eigentlich ein Nickerchen machen, sieh mal in der Chill-out-Lounge unter Deck nach. Komm wieder zu mir, wenn du gerne nach Dingen suchst ... Ich könnte einen anderen Auftrag für dich haben.“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">“Ehi, bello, non mi dire che cerchi la borsa di Fidget!? L'ho già detto a lei e a tutti quelli che ha mandato: qui non c'è. Ricordo di averle dato qualche minuto di pausa: prova a dare uno sguardo nella saletta relax, sotto la passerella. Ah, se ti piace così tanto trovare cose, torna qua più tardi: potrei avere una missione per te”.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“Eh, colega... No me digas que estás buscando el bolso de Fidget... Ya le he dicho a ella y a todos los que ha mandado a buscarlo que no está aquí. Le he dicho que fuera a tumbarse un rato. Mira por la zona del chill-out, bajo la rampa. Si te apetece buscar cosas, vuelve aquí dentro un rato. Puede que tenga otra misión para ti."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「おい、あんたもフィジェットのバッグを探してるのか？フィジェットに頼まれて探し回ってる他の奴等にも言ったけど、ここにはバッグ無いぜ。彼女にはラウンジにあるデッキの斜面の下とか調べてみるよう伝えといたぜ。また後でここへ戻ってきな。また他に手助けしてもらいたいことがあるかも。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"어이, 친구, 맞춰볼까? 피젯의 가방을 찾고 있는 거지? 이 이야기를 대체 몇 번째 하는 거야, 쳇. 가방은 여기에 없어. 갑판의 난간 아래에 있는 라운지를 한 번 봐. 아, 그리고 뭘 찾는 걸 좋아하는 사람이라면 조금 있다가 나한테 다시 와줘. 부탁할 일이 있을지도 모르니까."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">“Hey buddy – don’t tell me, you’re looking for Fidget’s bag? I’ve already told her and everyone else she’s sent looking for it - it’s not here. I sent her to go have a lie down, try looking around the chill-out lounge under the deck ramp. If you’re into finding things, head back over here in a while, I might have another mission for you.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">『嗨，兄弟。可別告訴我你在找Fidget的包包，我已經告訴她和所有其他幫她找包包的人了。包包不在這兒。我讓她仔細好好想想，看看甲板下面的休閒娛樂室有沒有。如果你喜歡找東西，過會兒可以再回來這裡，我可能會有新的任務給你。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">『嗨，兄弟。可別告訴我你在找Fidget的包包，我已經告訴她和所有其他幫她找包包的人了。包包不在這兒。我讓她仔細好好想想，看看甲板下面的休閒娛樂室有沒有。如果你喜歡找東西，過會兒可以再回來這裡，我可能會有新的任務給你。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">“Hey buddy – don’t tell me, you’re looking for Fidget’s bag? I’ve already told her and everyone else she’s sent looking for it - it’s not here. I sent her to go have a lie down, try looking around the chill-out lounge under the deck ramp. If you’re into finding things, head back over here in a while, I might have another mission for you.”</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BOUNCER_TALK_2_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">“Hey, thanks for coming back – see, we’ve kinda misplaced the DJ, he was last seen erm, how can I put this - reacting badly to a burger. Maybe check the toilets...?”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Eh, merci de revenir. Écoutez, on a comme qui dirait  égaré le DJ. La dernière fois qu'on l'a vu il... comment  dire ? Il digérait mal un burger. Peut-être aux  toilettes... ?"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Hey! Danke, dass du zurückgekommen bist! Wir scheinen den DJ verloren zu haben. Er wurde zuletzt gesehen, als er ... wie soll ich’s sagen ... schlecht auf einen Burger reagiert hat. Vielleicht solltest du in den Toiletten nach ihm sehen ...“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">“Ehi, sei qui! Bene! Ascolta, il DJ non se la sta passando bene. Ha avuto... come dire... una brutta esperienza con un hamburger. Prova a vedere se lo trovi nei bagni...”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“Eh, gracias por volver... Mira, no sabemos bien dónde está el DJ. La última vez que lo vimos estaba... cómo lo diré... reaccionando malamente a una hamburguesa. ¿Podrías, quizá, mirar en los baños...?”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「よお！戻ってきてくれてありがとう。実はDJが変なバーガーを食って腹を壊したらしいんだ。ちょっとトイレでもチェックしに行ってくれないか？」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"다시 와 줘서 고마워. 지금 DJ가 사라진 상태라서 당장 데려와 주면 고맙겠어. 아까는 햄버거를 먹고 배탈이 난 것 같던데. 화장실을 확인해 보는 게 어떨까."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">“Hey, thanks for coming back – see, we’ve kinda misplaced the DJ, he was last seen erm, how can I put this - reacting badly to a burger. Maybe check the toilets...?”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">『嗨，真高興你能回來。你看，我們到處也找不到DJ，他最後出現是在…。唔，這麼說吧，他好像吃了漢堡之後有點拉肚子。也許你可以去廁所看看…？』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">『嗨，真高興你能回來。你看，我們到處也找不到DJ，他最後出現是在…。唔，這麼說吧，他好像吃了漢堡之後有點拉肚子。也許你可以去廁所看看…？』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">“Hey, thanks for coming back – see, we’ve kinda misplaced the DJ, he was last seen erm, how can I put this - reacting badly to a burger. Maybe check the toilets...?”</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BOUNCER_TALK_2_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">“Oh, I forgot to say - no idea why but there’s another toilet over there, by the cargo containers.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Oh, j'ai oublié de préciser : je ne sais pas pourquoi, mais il y a d'autres toilettes là-bas, près des containers."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Oh, fast hätte ich es vergessen: Bei den Transportcontainern gibt es noch eine Toilette ... Warum auch immer sie da eine hinstellen.“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">“Oh, dimenticavo... non so perché, ma c'è un altro bagno laggiù, vicino ai container”.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Ah, me he olvidado de decirte que, no sé por qué, pero hay otros servicios allí, donde los contenedores de mercancías".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「おっと、言い忘れてた。あっちにある貨物にもコンテナトイレが設置されてるぜ。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"아, 내가 깜박하고 말을 안 했는데, 사실 카고 컨테이너 근처에도 화장실이 하나 더 있었어."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">“Oh, I forgot to say - no idea why but there’s another toilet over there, by the cargo containers.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">『哦，我忘了說一件事。在貨物集裝箱那邊還有一個廁所。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">『哦，我忘了說一件事。在貨物集裝箱那邊還有一個廁所。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">“Oh, I forgot to say - no idea why but there’s another toilet over there, by the cargo containers.”</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BOUNCER_TALK_2_3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">“Hmm, weird – you any good with a pair of decks? We’ll give him a few minutes but if he doesn’t turn up... Go check if Fidget’s seen him.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Hmm, bizarre... Vous savez vous servir de platines ? On va lui laisser quelques minutes, mais s'il ne revient pas... Allez voir si Fidget ne l'a pas vu."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Hmm, merkwürdig … Kannst du mit Turntables umgehen? Wir geben ihm noch ein paar Minuten. Aber wenn er nicht aufkreuzt ... Sieh bitte nach, ob Fidget ihn gesehen hat.“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">“Hmm, la vedo brutta, come te la cavi alla console? Gli diamo ancora qualche minuto ma se non torna... anzi, chiedi a Fidget se l'ha visto.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Hmm, qué raro... ¿Se te dan bien estas cosas? Vamos a darle unos minutos, pero si no aparece... Ve a ver si Fidget lo ha visto".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「こまったなぁ・・・あんたターンテーブル回せないのかい？とりあえずあいつが戻るのをもう少し待ってみるか。もし戻ってこなかったらフィジェットと話してきてくれ。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"이상하네… 혹시 DJ 할 줄 알아? 몇 분 더 기다려 보겠지만 그래도 안 오면…  피젯이 혹시 봤는지 가서 물어봐 줘."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">“Hmm, weird – you any good with a pair of decks? We’ll give him a few minutes but if he doesn’t turn up... Go check if Fidget’s seen him.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">『嗯…，真奇怪。你會用唱片機嗎？我們再給他幾分鐘，要是他還不露面…，你就去問問Fidget看到他沒有。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">『嗯…，真奇怪。你會用唱片機嗎？我們再給他幾分鐘，要是他還不露面…，你就去問問Fidget看到他沒有。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">“Hmm, weird – you any good with a pair of decks? We’ll give him a few minutes but if he doesn’t turn up... Go check if Fidget’s seen him.”</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BOUNCER_TALK_2_4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">“Yeah, sounds like he'll be busy for a while. You’ve got his records, the stage is yours if you want it.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Ouais, on dirait qu'il va en avoir pour un moment. Vous avez ses disques, la scène est à vous, si vous voulez."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Klingt so, als wäre er noch eine Weile beschäftigt. Du hast seine Platten, die Bühne gehört dir, wenn du willst.“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">“Mmh, credo che per un po' sarà fuori circolazione. Beh, qui ci sono i suoi dischi: il palco è tuo”.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“Sí, parece que va a estar ocupado un rato. Tienes sus discos: el escenario es tuyo si lo quieres.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「あいつは当分無理そうだな。あいつのレコード持ってるんだし、ステージはあんたに任せるよ。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"그래, 아마 곧 오기는 힘들 것 같네. 레코드 가방을 가지고 있으니 스테이지에서 원하는 대로 해 봐."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">“Yeah, sounds like he'll be busy for a while. You’ve got his records, the stage is yours if you want it.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">『這樣啊，聽起來他要忙上一陣子了。你就拿著他的唱片吧，只要你喜歡，這個舞台就交給你了。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">『這樣啊，聽起來他要忙上一陣子了。你就拿著他的唱片吧，只要你喜歡，這個舞台就交給你了。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">“Yeah, sounds like he'll be busy for a while. You’ve got his records, the stage is yours if you want it.”</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TREASURE_HUNT_COMPLETE_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Hey Thanks, you found my keys!  Here, have this old helmet for your trouble."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Hé, merci ! Vous avez retrouvé mes clés ! Tenez, prenez ce vieux casque pour le dérangement."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Hey! Danke, du hast meinen Schlüssel gefunden! Hier, nimm diesen Helm!“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Ehi, grazie! Hai trovato le mie chiavi! Ecco, prendi questo vecchio casco per il disturbo."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"Eh, gracias, ¡has encontrado las llaves! Toma, llévate este viejo casco por las molestias".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「ワオッ！鍵見つけてくれたのね！サンキュー！はい。お礼にヘルメットあげる！」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"와, 고마워! 내 가방을 찾았잖아! 이 낡은 헬멧이라도 받아 주길 바래!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Hey Thanks, you found my keys!  Here, have this old helmet for your trouble."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">『啊，太感謝了，你找到了我的鑰匙！送你這個頭盔當作謝禮。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">『啊，太感謝了，你找到了我的鑰匙！送你這個頭盔當作謝禮。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Hey Thanks, you found my keys!  Here, have this old helmet for your trouble."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TREASURE_HUNT_COMPLETE_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"You'll need this to look the part."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Vous aurez besoin de ça pour vous fondre dans le décor."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Dein Look muss passen!“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Indossala... se non vuoi sembrare fuori posto".</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“Necesitarás esto.”</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「ほら。これあれば完璧。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"이게 있어야 그럴듯하게 보일걸?"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"You'll need this to look the part."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">『你需要這個來讓自己看上去更像其中一份子。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">『你需要這個來讓自己看上去更像其中一份子。』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"You'll need this to look the part."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">TREASURE_HUNT_COMPLETE_3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Thanks for helping us out!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Merci pour votre aide !"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Vielen Dank für deine Hilfe!“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Grazie per il tuo aiuto!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“¡Gracias por ayudarnos!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「ほんと助かったわ！」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"도와줘서 정말 고마워!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Thanks for helping us out!"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">『非常感謝你的幫助！』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">『非常感謝你的幫助！』</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Thanks for helping us out!"</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">LISTENING</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LISTENING…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">ÉCOUTE...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">HÖRT ZU ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">IN ASCOLTO...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">ESCUCHANDO...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">傾聴中・・・</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">듣는 중…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">LISTENING…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">聆聽中…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">聆聽中…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LISTENING…</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BACK_TO_QUESTGIVER_1_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You found a bag! Take it back to Fidget.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez trouvé un sac ! Rapportez-le à Fidget.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast eine Tasche gefunden! Bringe sie zu Fidget.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai trovato una borsa! Riportala a Fidget.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has encontrado un bolso! Llévaselo a Fidget.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">バッグを発見！バッグをフィジェットに渡そう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">가방을 찾았다! 피젯에게 돌아가자.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">You found a bag! Take it back to Fidget.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">找到了一個包包！快拿去給Fidget吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">找到了一個包包！快拿去給Fidget吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You found a bag! Take it back to Fidget.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BACK_TO_QUESTGIVER_1_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You found a set of keys! Take them back to Fidget.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez trouvé un jeu de clés ! Rapportez-le à Fidget.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast einen Schlüsselbund gefunden! Bringe ihn zu Fidget.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai trovato delle chiavi! Portale a Fidget.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has encontrado unas llaves! Llévaselas a Fidget.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">鍵を発見！鍵をフィジェットに渡そう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">열쇠를 찾았다! 피젯에게 돌아가자.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">You found a set of keys! Take them back to Fidget.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">找到了一串鑰匙！快拿去給Fidget吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">找到了一串鑰匙！快拿去給Fidget吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You found a set of keys! Take them back to Fidget.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BACK_TO_QUESTGIVER_2_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You didn't find the DJ, but found his record bag.  Report back to Bones.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous n'avez pas trouvé le DJ, mais vous avez son sac de disques. Dites-le à Bones.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du hast den DJ nicht gefunden, aber seine Plattentasche gefunden. Berichte Bones davon.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non hai trovato il DJ, ma hai trovato i suoi dischi. Dillo a Bones.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No has encontrado al DJ, pero sí su bolsa de discos.  Vuelve a donde Bones.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">DJを見つけることは出来なかったが、彼のレコードバッグを見つけた。ボーンズのところへ戻ろう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">DJ를 찾지는 못했지만 레코드 가방을 찾았다. 본즈에게 돌아가자.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">You didn't find the DJ, but found his record bag.  Report back to Bones.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">沒有找到DJ，但是找到了他的唱片包。快去向Bones報告吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">沒有找到DJ，但是找到了他的唱片包。快去向Bones報告吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You didn't find the DJ, but found his record bag.  Report back to Bones.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">BACK_TO_QUESTGIVER_2_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You think you heard the DJ in the toilet.  Go and tell Bones.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous pensez avoir entendu le DJ dans les toilettes ? Allez le dire à Bones.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du glaubst, den DJ in der Toilettenkabine gehört zu haben. Berichte Bones davon.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai sentito il DJ in bagno. Vai a dirlo a Bones.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Crees haber oído al DJ en el servicio. Ve a decírselo a Bones.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">DJの声がトイレの中から聞こえる。ボーンズに報告しよう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">DJ가 화장실에 있는 소리를 들었다. 본즈에게 돌아가자.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">You think you heard the DJ in the toilet.  Go and tell Bones.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">好像聽到DJ在廁所裡。快去告訴Bones吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">好像聽到DJ在廁所裡。快去告訴Bones吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You think you heard the DJ in the toilet.  Go and tell Bones.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>