<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Stole Cardigan Outfit Set (Green &amp; Black, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de Cardigan en laine (vert et noir, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Stola-Cardigan Outfit-Set (grün &amp; schwarz, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set abito e soprabito in coordinato (verde e nero, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de traje de cárdigan tipo estola (verde y negro, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ストールカーディガン着こなしセット（グリーン＆ブラック・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Stole Cardigan Outfit Set (Green &amp; Black, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 4-piece set, including a stole cardigan &amp; one piece, vertical belted long boots, and 2 sizes of knit cat ear caps.\nCuteness: ★★\nDefensive Strength: None~★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Knit Cat Ear Cap (Black, Women) (Accessories)\n- Knit Cat Ear Cap, Large (Black, Women) (Accessories)\n- Stole Cardigan &amp; One Piece (Green &amp; Black, Women) (Outfits)\n- Vertical Belted Long Boots (Brown, Women) (Feet)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 4 pièces incluant un cardigan en laine et une robe, de longues bottes avec boucles verticales et 2 tailles de bonnets oreilles de chat.\nCharme : ★★\nDéfense : (Sans)~★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Bonnet oreilles de chat (noir, femme) (Accessoires)\n- Bonnet oreilles de chat, grand (noir, femme) (Accessoires)\n- Cardigan en laine et robe (vert et noire, femme) (Tenues)\n- Bottes longues avec boucles verticales (marron, femme) (Pieds)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 4-teiliges Set, das einen Stola-Cardigan &amp; Kleid, Schaftstiefel mit vertikal angebrachten Schnallen und zwei verschieden große Strickmützen mit Katzenohren enthält.\nNiedlichkeit: ★★\nVerteidigung: Keine~★\nDieses Set enthält die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Strickmütze mit Katzenohren (schwarz, für Frauen) (Accessoires)\n- Strickmütze mit Katzenohren, groß (schwarz, für Frauen) (Accessoires)\n- Stola-Cardigan &amp; Einteiler (grün &amp; schwarz, für Frauen) (Outfits)\n- Schaftstiefel mit vertikal angebrachten Schnallen (braun, für Frauen) (Füße)\n\n* Beim Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set di 4 elementi comprendente un abito e soprabito in coordinato, stivali con cinturini verticali, e 2 berretti di maglia con orecchie da gatto di diverse dimensioni.\nRicercatezza: ★★\nDifesa: (nulla)~★\nQuesto set include i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Berretto di maglia con orecchie da gatto (nero, da donna) (accessori)\n- Berretto di maglia con orecchie da gatto, grande (nero, da donna) (accessori)\n- Abito e soprabito in coordinato (verde e nero, da donna) (aspetti)\n- Stivali con cinturini verticali (marroni, da donna) (piedi)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de 4 piezas que incluye un cárdigan tipo estola y un vestido de una pieza, botas largas con correa vertical y 2 tallas de gorros de punto con orejas de gato.\nEncanto: ★★\nDefensa: (ninguna)~★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\nGorro de punto con orejas de gato (negro, mujer) (complemento)\n- Gorro de punto con orejas de gato, grande (negro, mujer) (complemento)\n- Cardigán tipo estola y un vestido de una pieza (verde y negro, mujer) (trajes)\n- Botas largas con correa vertical (marrón, mujer) (pies)\n\n* Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ストールカーディガン＆ワンピース、縦ベルトロングブーツ、猫耳ニット帽（大きさ違い２点）を含む、計４点セット。\nかわいさ：　★★\n防御力：　（なし）～★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・猫耳ニット帽（ブラック・女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n・猫耳ニット帽・大（ブラック・女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n・ストールカーディガン＆ワンピース（グリーン＆ブラック・女性）/組み合わせ\n・縦ベルトロングブーツ（ブラウン・女性）/靴\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 4-piece set, including a stole cardigan &amp; one piece, vertical belted long boots, and 2 sizes of knit cat ear caps.\nCuteness: ★★\nDefensive Strength: None~★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Knit Cat Ear Cap (Black, Women) (Accessories)\n- Knit Cat Ear Cap, Large (Black, Women) (Accessories)\n- Stole Cardigan &amp; One Piece (Green &amp; Black, Women) (Outfits)\n- Vertical Belted Long Boots (Brown, Women) (Feet)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
