<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Treasure Earring (Pink Coral, Right Ear, Men)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Boucle d'oreille trésor (corail, oreille droite, homme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ohrring aus einem Schatz (rosa Koralle, rechtes Ohr, Herren)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Orecchino prezioso (corallo rosa, orecchio destro, uomo)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Pendiente del tesoro (coral rosa, oreja derecha, hombre)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">宝のイヤリング（ピンク珊瑚・右耳・男性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">보석 귀걸이(분홍 산호, 오른쪽 귀, 남성)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Treasure Earring (Pink Coral, Right Ear, Men)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">寶物耳環（粉紅珊瑚/右耳/男用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">寶物耳環（粉紅珊瑚/右耳/男用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Treasure Earring (Pink Coral, Right Ear, Men)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A precious stone created from burnishing pink coral until it shines with a soft luster.  For the right ear. (Mohs hardness: 4)[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Une pierre précieuse créée en brunissant du corail rose jusqu'à ce qu'il brille légèrement. Pour l'oreille droite. (Échelle de dureté de Mohs : 4) [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein kostbarer Stein, der aus rosafarbener Koralle hergestellt wird, die so lange poliert wird, bis sie zart glänzt. Für das rechte Ohr. (Mohssche Härte: 4) [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Una pietra preziosa ottenuta lucidando il corallo rosa finché non risplende di un delicato lucore. Orecchio destro. (Durezza in scala Mohs: 4) [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Una piedra preciosa creada puliendo el coral rosa hasta que adquiere un suave lustre. Para la oreja derecha. (Dureza en la escala de Mohs: 4) [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">優しく淡いピンク色の珊瑚を磨いてできた宝石。 右耳用。（モース硬度４）[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">부드러운 옅은 분홍색의 산호를 연마하여 만든 보석. 오른쪽 귀 전용. (모스 경도4) [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">A precious stone created from burnishing pink coral until it shines with a soft luster.  For the right ear. (Mohs hardness: 4)[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">這種寶石是透過打磨淡粉紅色的珊瑚而製成。右耳用。（摩斯硬度4）[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">這種寶石是透過打磨淡粉紅色的珊瑚而製成。右耳用。（摩斯硬度4）[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A precious stone created from burnishing pink coral until it shines with a soft luster.  For the right ear. (Mohs hardness: 4)[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
