<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Musée PixelJunk™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">PixelJunk™-Ausstellung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Museo PixelJunk™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Exposición PixelJunk™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">PixelJunk™ Exhibition</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le musée PixelJunk™ est un temple virtuel de tout PixelJunk™ ! Rempli d'objets et de raretés de la série PixelJunk™, ce lieu vous permet de découvrir un géant de pierre plus vrai que nature, de mettre un coup de pied dans les pneus d'un bolide de PixelJunk™ Racer ou encore de vous ballader en écoutant la bande originale d'Eden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Die PixelJunk™-Ausstellung ist ein virtueller Schrein, gefüllt mit jeder Menge Artefakten und Seltenheiten zum Thema PixelJunk™! Gehen Sie mit einem überlebensgroßen Steinriesen auf Tuchfühlung, bewundern Sieeinen flotten PixelJunk™-Rennwagen oder entspannen Sie zum Eden-Soundtrack."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Il Museo PixelJunk™ è il tempio virtuale di tutte le cose PixelJunk™! Pieno di artefatti e rarità della serie PixelJunk™: avvicinati e familiarizza con un gigante di pietra in dimensioni reali, tira calci alle gomme di un'auto PixelJunk™ Racer, o semplicemente siediti e ascolta la colonna sonora di Eden."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"¡La exposición PixelJunk™ es el templo virtual de todo lo relacionado con PixelJunk™! Cargada de artefactos y rarezas de la serie PixelJunk™, podrás encontrarte cara a cara con un descomunal gigante de piedra, admirar los super bólidos PixelJunk™, o símplemente ponerte cómodo y desconectar con la banda sonora de Eden."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The PixelJunk™ Home Exhibition is a virtual shrine to all things PixelJunk™! Stocked with artifacts and rarities from the PixelJunk™ series, you can get up-close and personal with a larger than life stone giant, kick the tires of a super slick PixelJunk™ Racer, or just sit back and zone out to the Eden Soundtrack.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>