<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Torso_Nis_Tops_Musou_001</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">T-shirt Achèvement</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">「夢想灯籠」発売記念Ｔシャツ（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">「몽상등롱」판매 기념 Ｔ셔츠（남성）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Musou Toryuu" Commemorative Release T-shirt (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「夢想燈籠」記念T恤（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「夢想燈籠」記念T恤（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dream T-Shirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nis_Tops_musou_001_m</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Untitled</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un T-shirt pour commémorer la sortie d'un jeu Nippon Ichi Software sur PSP® system (PlayStation®Portable).[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">黄泉に落ちても　守りたい人がいる…このアイテムはPSP® (PlayStation®Portable) で2009年3月19日に発売された、本格伝奇アドベンチャーゲーム「夢想灯籠」の発売記念Tシャツです。現代と平安時代を舞台に、人々の輪廻をめぐるストーリーが展開していきます。笑いあり、涙あり、美少女あり、バトルありと、アドベンチャーファンにはたまらないゲームとなっています。このTシャツをアバターに着せながらゲームをプレイしましょう！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">죽어서도 지키고 싶은 사람이 있다… 이 아이템은 PSP® (PlayStation®Portable)에서 2009년 3월 19일에 발매된 본격 전기 어드벤처 게임「몽상등롱」의 판매 기념 T셔츠입니다. 현대와 헤이안 시대를 무대로, 사람들의 윤회를 둘러싼 스토리가 전개됩니다. 웃음과 눈물, 미소녀, 그리고 배틀이 있는, 어드벤처 게임의 팬이라면 참을 수 없는 게임입니다. 이 T셔츠를 아바타에게 입히고 게임을 플레이합시다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Even when falling into the underworld, there is someone he longs to protect... This T-shirt is to commemorate  "Musou Tourou," a serious, romantic adventure game released  for the PSP® system (PlayStation®Portable)  on March 19, 2009 in Japan. The story revolves around the reincarnation of certain people, taking place in both modern times and the Heian Era. It's sure to make you laugh and cry, with beautiful young girls and battles that no adventure fan can resist. Dress your avatar in this shirt and go play the game! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">即使是墜入黃泉也有想要保護的人…這個道具是PSP™ (PlayStation®Portable)於2009年3月19日在日本推出的正統傳奇冒險遊戲 「夢想燈籠」的記念T恤。以現代和平安時代做為舞台，環繞人世輪迴而展開故事發展。其中有笑有淚、有美少女、也有戰鬥，是冒險遊戲迷無法抗拒的一款遊戲。讓自己的角色穿著這件T恤一起進行遊戲吧！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">即使是墜入黃泉也有想要保護的人…這個道具是PSP™ (PlayStation®Portable)於2009年3月19日在日本推出的正統傳奇冒險遊戲 「夢想燈籠」的記念T恤。以現代和平安時代做為舞台，環繞人世輪迴而展開故事發展。其中有笑有淚、有美少女、也有戰鬥，是冒險遊戲迷無法抗拒的一款遊戲。讓自己的角色穿著這件T恤一起進行遊戲吧！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A T-shirt to commemorate the release of Musou Torou.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A T-shirt to commemorate the release of Musou Torou.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>