<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bot Bee Swarm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Essaim d'abeilles-droïdes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bot Bee Swarm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sciame robot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Enjambre robot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ボット蜂の群れ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">봇 벌떼</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Bot Bee Swarm</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">機械蜂群</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">機械蜂群</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Bot Bee Swarm</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Programmed to be your best friend, the Bot Bee Swarm will loyally follow its owner, providing the kind of affection that only a single-purpose AI can give. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Programmé pour être votre meilleur ami, l'essaim d'abeilles-droïdes vous suivra partout loyalement, vous fournissant le type d'affection que seule une intelligence artificielle à but unique peut prodiguer. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Darauf programmiert, dein bester Freund zu sein, wird der Bot Bee Swarm seinem Besitzer loyal folgen und ihm die Art von Zuneigung entgegenbringen, wie es nur solch eine KI kann. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Programmato per essere il tuo miglior amico, lo Sciame robot seguirà fedelmente il padrone, assicurando un tipo di attenzione che solo un'IA dedicata può assicurare. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Programados para ser tus mejores aliados, el enjambre robot seguirá fielmente a su dueño, creando todo tipo de efectos que sólo IA de propósito simple puede otorgar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ボット蜂の群れは君の親友となるようにプログラムされており、親愛を込めて飼い主の後を飛び回る。単一目的ＡＩならではの愛情をたっぷり味わわせてくれる。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">최고의 친구가 되도록 설계된 봇 벌떼는 주인을 충실하게 따르며, 단일 목적 AI만이 제공할 수 있는 일종의 애정을 선사합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Programmed to be your best friend, the Bot Bee Swarm will loyally follow its owner, providing the kind of affection that only a single-purpose AI can give. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">機械蜂群設定為你的最佳朋友，會忠心的跟隨主人，提供只有單一目的人功智能機械人才能提供的關愛。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">機械蜂群設定為你的最佳朋友，會忠心的跟隨主人，提供只有單一目的人功智能機械人才能提供的關愛。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Programmed to be your best friend, the Bot Bee Swarm will loyally follow its owner, providing the kind of affection that only a single-purpose AI can give. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>