<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Doctor Who TARDIS - Private Space and Clubhouse Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Doctor Who TARDIS - Lot Club-House et Espace Privé</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Doctor Who TARDIS – Paket „Private Space und Klubhaus“</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">TARDIS del Doctor Who - Pacchetto Ambiente privato e Circolo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Doctor Who TARDIS - Espacio privado y lote Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Doctor Who TARDIS - Private Space and Clubhouse Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Doctor Who TARDIS - Private Space and Clubhouse Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This Bundle comes with the Doctor Who TARDIS Clubhouse and Doctor Who TARDIS Private Space, including the BBC Active Camera and Active Light items. TARDIS™ stands for “Time And Relative Dimension In Space.” The TARDIS™ looks like a 1950s wooden Police Phone Box on the outside, but it’s far bigger on the inside. Amaze your friends when they discover the wonder of Time Lord technology. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce lot vient avec le club-house Doctor Who TARDIS et l'Espace Privé Doctor Who TARDIS, et comprend la Caméra Active et la Lumière Active de BBC articles. Le TARDIS signifie "Temps À Relativité Dimensionnelle Inter Spatiale”.  Le TARDIS ressemble de l'extérieur à une cabine téléphonique en bois de la police des années 1950, mais il est beaucoup plus grand à l'intérieur. Impressionnez vos amis en leur faisant découvrir la merveille de technologie du Seigneur du Temps. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Paket enthält das Doctor Who TARDIS Clubhaus und den Doctor Who TARDIS Private Space sowie die Gegenstände BBC Active Camera, Active Light. TARDIS steht für „Time And Relative Dimensions In Space“ oder „Trips aufgrund relativer Dimensionen im Sternenzelt“. Die TARDIS sieht von außen wie eine hölzerne Polizei-Notrufzelle aus den 50er-Jahren aus, ist aber im Innern viel größer. Bringe deine Freunde zum Staunen, wenn sie das Wunder der Technologie der  Timelords entdecken. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo pacchetto è disponibile insieme a TARDIS™ del Doctor Who - Circolo e a TARDIS™ del Doctor Who - Ambiente privato e include gli oggetti di LOOT Telecamera attiva e Illuminazione attiva. Il presente pacchetto contiene il Club House Doctor Who TARDIS e lo Spazio privato Doctor Who TARDIS, inclusa la BBC Active Camera e la BBC Active Light. Il termine TARDIS significa "Tempo e Relativa Dimensione nello Spazio" (Time And Relative Dimension In Space). L'esterno del TARDIS ha l'aspetto di una cabina telefonica della polizia degli anni cinquanta, ma l'interno è enorme. Stupisci i tuoi amici con le meraviglie della tecnologia dei Signori del Tempo.Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este lote incluye la Clubhouse de la TARDIS del Doctor Who y el espacio privado de la TARDIS del Doctor Who, incluyendo la cámara activa BBC y la luz activa. TARDIS son las siglas en inglés de “Time And Relative Dimension In Space” (tiempo y dimensión relativa en el espacio). Por fuera, la TARDIS parece una cabina de teléfonos policíaca de los años 50, pero por dentro cuenta con unas proporciones infinitas. Sorprende a tus amigos cuando descubran las maravillas de la tecnología del Time Lord. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This Bundle comes with the Doctor Who TARDIS Clubhouse and Doctor Who TARDIS Private Space, including the BBC Active Camera and Active Light items. TARDIS™ stands for “Time And Relative Dimension In Space.” The TARDIS™ looks like a 1950s wooden Police Phone Box on the outside, but it’s far bigger on the inside. Amaze your friends when they discover the wonder of Time Lord technology. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This Bundle comes with the Doctor Who TARDIS Clubhouse and Doctor Who TARDIS Private Space, including the BBC Active Camera and Active Light items. TARDIS™ stands for “Time And Relative Dimension In Space.” The TARDIS™ looks like a 1950s wooden Police Phone Box on the outside, but it’s far bigger on the inside. Amaze your friends when they discover the wonder of Time Lord technology. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>