<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Pen Draig's Warblade (Legendary Weapon)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Épée de guerre de Pen Draig (arme légendaire)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Pen Draigs Kriegsklinge (Legendäre Waffe)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Spada da guerra di Pen Draig (Arma leggendaria)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Espada de guerra de Pen Draig (Arma legendaria)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Pen Draig's Warblade (Legendary Weapon)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Belonging to one of the first Guardians of Mercia; this Legendary Warblade is said to have split the sky until the stars bled from the heavens and rained upon the enemies of Mercia.\n\nThis Warblade is  best suited to a Defender of Mercia against  enemies that tremble the earth with their walk.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ayant appartenu à l'un des premiers gardiens de Mercia, on dit que cette épée de guerre légendaire a fendu le ciel, fait couler le sang des étoiles jusqu'à ce qu'il pleuve sur les ennemis de Mercia.\n\nCette épée de guerre convient mieux à un défenseur de Mercia qui s'apprête à affronter les ennemis qui font trembler le sol de leurs pas.\n\nDÉBLOQUE DES ARTICLES DU JEU MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS – N'OFFRE PAS DE COMPOSANTS D'AVATAR POUR UN USAGE GÉNÉRAL SUR PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBLE POUR LES UTILISATEURS DU JAPON ET DE L'ASIE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese legendäre Kriegsklinge gehörte einem der ersten Wächter Mercias und soll der Sage nach den Himmel geteilt haben, woraufhin die Sterne auf die Feinde Mercias niederstürzten.\n\nDiese Kriegsklinge eignet sich am besten für Mercia-Beschützer im Kampf gegen Feinde, die mit ihren Schritten die Erde erzittern lassen.\n\nZUM FREISCHALTEN VON GEGENSTÄNDEN IN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS - NICHT ZUM ERHALT VON AVATAR-KOMPONENTEN ZUR ALLGEMEINEN NUTZUNG AUF PLAYSTATION®HOME. NICHT VERFÜGBAR FÜR BENUTZER IN JAPAN UND ASIEN [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Appartiene a uno dei primi guardiani di Mercia;  questa spada da guerra leggendaria pare abbia spaccato in due il cielo fino a far sanguinare le stelle che sono piovute sui nemici di Mercia.\n\nQuesta spada da guerra è perfetta per un difensore di Mercia per affrontare nemici che fanno tremare la terra solo camminando.\n\nSBLOCCA OGGETTI ALL'INTERNO DEL GIOCO MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS. NON REGALA COMPONENTI PER AVATAR PER USO GENERICO CON PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBILE PER GLI UTENTI IN ASIA E GIAPPONE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Propiedad de uno de los primeros guardianes de Mercia; se dice que esta legendaria espada de guerra dividió el cielo hasta que las estrellas sangraron desde las alturas y llovieron sobre los enemigos de Mercia.\n\nEsta espada de guerra está pensada para un defensor de Mercia que luche contra enemigos que hacen temblar la tierra al caminar.\n\nDESBLOQUEARÁ ELEMENTOS EN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS GAME. NO REGALARÁ COMPONENTES DE AVATAR PARA EL USO GENERAL EN CASA DE PLAYSTATION. NO DISPONIBLE PARA LOS USUARIOS DE JAPÓN Y ASIA. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Belonging to one of the first Guardians of Mercia; this Legendary Warblade is said to have split the sky until the stars bled from the heavens and rained upon the enemies of Mercia.\n\nThis Warblade is  best suited to a Defender of Mercia against  enemies that tremble the earth with their walk.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>