<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">TNT Time</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Opération explosion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sprengstunde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sorpresa TNT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hora del TNT</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">TNT Time</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A Sneak Attack Sound Bank! Blow the man down with these radical explosions. Set up the triggers and let the fun begin!  (This item adds sounds to the free Sneak Attack audio trigger system and includes the male and female TNT Time Plunger Hats.) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Piste pour le répertoire Attaque furtive ! Vos amis seront soufflés par ces explosions retentissantes. Installez les capteurs et profitez du spectacle !  Également inclus : les chapeaux ventouse Heure du TNT, modèles homme et femme. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Sounddatenbank für den perfekten Überraschungsangriff! Diese Explosionen hauen jeden um. Wenn die Auslöser eingestellt sind, kann der Spaß beginnen! Mit geschlechtsspezifischen Sprengstunden-Saugglockenhüten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una valanga di suoni per i tuoi attacchi furtivi! Sferra un attacco furtivo con potentissime esplosioni. Piazza i dispositivi audio e dai inizio al divertimento!  In più, include i cappelli sturalavandini Bomba a orologeria TNT per uomo e donna. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Una librería de sonidos para ataques sigilosos! Derríbalos con estas explosiones radicales. Instala los disparadores y... ¡qué comience la diversión! ... e incluye los cascos de protección para hombres y mujeres para la Hora del TNT. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A Sneak Attack Sound Bank! Blow the man down with these radical explosions. Set up the triggers and let the fun begin!  (This item adds sounds to the free Sneak Attack audio trigger system and includes the male and female TNT Time Plunger Hats.) [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>