<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tauntaun Taxidermy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Taxidermie Tauntaun</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tauntaun-Taxidermie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tassidermia Tauntaun</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tauntaun disecado</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Taun_Taun_Taxidermy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Taun_Taun_Taxidermy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Tauntaun Taxidermy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Taun_Taun_Taxidermy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Taun_Taun_Taxidermy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Tauntaun Taxidermy</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Decorate your home with this Tauntaun bust. These creatures were used by the Rebels as patrol mounts on Hoth because their own vehicles were unreliable in the extremely cold climate.  They evidently smell really bad.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Décorez votre intérieur avec ce buste Tauntaun. Ces créatures étaient utilisées par les Rebelles en tant que montures pour les patrouilles sur Hoth en raison du manque de fiabilité de leurs véhicules sous un climat extrêmement froid.  Leur odeur est évidemment atroce.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dekoriere dein Heim mit dieser Tauntaunbüste. Diese Kreaturen wurden auf Hoth von den Rebellen als Reittiere eingesetzt, weil deren eigene Transportmittel in dem extrem kalten Klima zu oft versagten. Sie riechen offenkundig recht streng.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Decora la tua casa con questo busto di Tauntaun. Queste creature venivano usate dai Ribelli per andare in pattuglia sul pianeta Hoth, dal momento che i loro veicoli erano poco affidabili in quel clima polare. A quanto pare, i Tauntaun puzzano molt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Decora tu hogar con este busto de Tauntaun. Estas criaturas fueron usadas por los Rebeldes como patrullas montadas en Hoth porque sus propios vehículos eran poco fiables en el clima extremamente frío. Evidentemente, huelen muy mal.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Taun_Taun_Taxidermy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Taun_Taun_Taxidermy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Decorate your home with this Tauntaun bust. These creatures were used by the Rebels as patrol mounts on Hoth because their own vehicles were unreliable in the extremely cold climate.  They evidently smell really bad.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Taun_Taun_Taxidermy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Taun_Taun_Taxidermy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Decorate your home with this Tauntaun bust. These creatures were used by the Rebels as patrol mounts on Hoth because their own vehicles were unreliable in the extremely cold climate.  They evidently smell really bad.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>