<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Smouldering Ember Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack Braise Incandescente</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">„Schwelende Glut“-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bundle Brace Ardente</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de Brasa Ardiente</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_166</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_166</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_166</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_166</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_166</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Smoldering Ember Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You're a smouldering creature from the underworld. This bundle includes Smouldering Ember Head, Smouldering Ember Torso, Smouldering Ember Legs, Smouldering Ember Hands and Smouldering Ember Feet.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous êtes une créature incandescente venue des profondeurs de la terre. Ce pack comprend la Tête Braise Incandescente, le Buste Braise Incandescente, les Jambes Braise Incandescente, les Mains Braise Incandescente et les Pieds Braise Incandescente.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit diesem Outfit verwandelt man sich in eine schwelende Kreatur der Unterwelt. Das Paket umfasst einen "Schwelende Glut"-Kopf, einen "Schwelende Glut"-Oberkörper, "Schwelende Glut"-Beine, "Schwelende Glut"-Hände und "Schwelende Glut"-Füße. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sei una creatura ardente del sottosuolo. Questo bundle include Testa Brace Ardente, Torso Brace Ardente, Gambe Brace Ardente, Mani Brace Ardente e Piedi Brace Ardente.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Eres una criatura ardiente del inframundo. El conjunto incluye: cabeza de brasa ardiente, torso de brasa ardiente, piernas de brasa ardiente, manos de brasa ardiente y pies de brasa ardiente.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_166 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_166 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_166 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_166 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_166 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You're a smoldering creature from the underworld. This bundle includes Smoldering Ember Head, Smoldering Ember Torso, Smoldering Ember Legs, Smoldering Ember Hands and Smoldering Ember Feet.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>