<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Personal Chef - French</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chef personnel - Français</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ihr persönlicher französischer Chefkoch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chef Personale - Francese</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chef personal - Francés</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Let the chef work his magic and whip you up a delicious crêpe. Gather your friends in your personal space, grab a plate and indulge on the chef's masterpiece. Once finished you will receive the consumed item as a reward.

\n\n※ Active items provide more functionality than normal items. You may only place limited numbers of the active items in your apartment or clubhouse at any time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Laissez ce chef donner libre cours à ses talents et vous préparer de délicieuses crêpes. Rassemblez vos amis dans votre espace personnel, attrapez une assiette et régalez-vous des chefs d'œuvre de ce chef. Une fois terminé, vous recevrez l'article consommé comme récompense.

\n\n※ Les articles actifs offrent davantage de fonctionnalités que les articles normaux. À tout moment, vous ne pouvez placer qu'un nombre limité d'articles actifs dans votre appartement ou votre club-house. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lassen Sie sich von Ihrem persönlichen Chefkoch ein sensationales Crêpe zubereiten. Laden Sie Ihre Freunde zu sich ein und lassen Sie sich das Meisterwerk Ihres Chefkochs gut schmecken. Nach dem Essen erhalten Sie die verzehrte Speise als Belohnung.

 \n\n※ Aktive Artikel bieten mehr Funktionalität als normale Artikel. Sie dürfen nur eine begrenzte Anzahl aktiver Artikel jeweils in Ihrem Apartment oder Clubhaus aufstellen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lascia che lo chef faccia le sue magie e ti prepari una deliziosa crêpe. Invita gli amici nel tuo spazio personale, prendi un piatto e gusta il capolavoro dello chef. Una volta finito, riceverai l'articolo consumato come premio.

\n\n※ Gli articoli attivi offrono maggiori funzionalità rispetto a quelli normali. Puoi posizionare solo un numero limitato di articoli attivi alla volta nel tuo appartamento o circolo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Deja que el chef obre su magia y te haga un crepe delicioso. Reúne a tus amigos en tu espacio exclusivo, coge un plato y date el gusto con esta obra maestra del chef. Cuando termines, recibirás el artículo que hayas consumido de premio.

\n\n※ Los artículos activos ofrecen más funcionalidad que los normales. Así, en todo momento, podrás ubicar sólo un número limitado de artículos activos en tu apartamento o tu club. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">But_Accept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">But_Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">AcceptFood</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Consume</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Consommer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verzehren Sie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Consuma</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Consumir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Abbrechen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>