<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sodium Cutaway Halter Top - Stars And Stripes (for Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Haut Sodium à dos nu et découpes - Bannière étoilée (pour Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sodium-Trägeroberteil - Stars and Stripes (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Top Cutaway Halter Sodium - Stelle e strisce (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta recortada con dogal Sodium; barras y estrellas (para mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Sodiumカッタウェイホルタートップ - アメリカ（女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium 컷어웨이 홀터 탑 - 스타 스트라이프 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sodium Cutaway Halter Top - Stars And Stripes (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sodium挖空繞頸上衣：星條旗(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sodium挖空繞頸上衣：星條旗(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sodium Cutaway Halter Top - Stars And Stripes (for Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Who says the racers should get all the attention? Grab some of the glory for yourself in a head-turning cutaway top. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Qui a dit que les champions auraient toute l'attention ? Récoltez un peu de gloire aussi avec ce haut qui fera tourner les têtes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer sagt, dass die Rennfahrer die ganze Aufmerksamkeit bekommen sollen? Versetz dich mit diesem Hingucker von Oberteil selbst ins Rampenlicht. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chi dice che solo i migliori devono essere al centro dell'attenzione? Indossa questo top mozzafiato e assaggia un po' di gloria. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Quién dice que los corredores deberían llevarse toda la atención? Hazte con un poco de la gloria para ti misma con esta camiseta de lo más sexy. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">注目を集めるのはハイスコアラーだけではありません。カッタウェイトップでみんなの注目を集めましょう。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">높은 점수를 기록한 플레이어만이 눈길을 끄는 건 아닙니다. 컷 홀터 탑을 입고 영광을 조금은 빼앗아 오세요.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Who says the racers should get all the attention? Grab some of the glory for yourself in a head-turning cutaway top. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">誰說參賽者才有人看？穿上這件眾人矚目的挖空上衣，你也可以是焦點。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">誰說參賽者才有人看？穿上這件眾人矚目的挖空上衣，你也可以是焦點。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Who says the racers should get all the attention? Grab some of the glory for yourself in a head-turning cutaway top. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>