<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Snow Globe Mega Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">le globe de neige méga Paquet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schneekugel Mega Bündeln</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Globo di neve mega del impacchettare</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Globo de la nieve mega del paquete</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Snow Globe Mega Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">including Snow Globe Apartment, Snow-man, Snow-woman, snow-boy, snow-girl, 2 x neon ice chair, 2 x neon ice sofa, 2 x neon ice table (purple and green) and exclusive clothing Mrs Frost and Mrs Frost Hat and Mr Frost, Mr Frost Shoes and Mr Frost Hat. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">compris le globe de neige appartement, Neige-homme, Neige-femme, Neige-garçon, Neige-fille, 2 x Chaise glacée néon, 2 x Canapé glacée néon, 2 x Tableau glacée néon (Pourpre et Vert) et vêtements exclusifs  Madam Givre et Madam Givre chapeau et Monsieur Givre, Monsieur Givre chaussures et Monsieur Givre chapeau. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">einschließlich, Schnee-Mann, Schnee-Frau, Schnee-Junge, Schnee-Mädchen, 2 x Neon Eis Stuhl, 2 x Neon Eis Schlafsofa, 2 x Neon Eis Tisch (lila und grün) und exklusive Kleidung Frau Frost und Frau Frost Hut und Herr Frost, Herr Frost Schuhe und Herr Frost Hut [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">compresi Nevicata-uomo, Nevicata-donna, Nevicata-ragazzo, Nevicata-ragazza, 2 x Sedia ghiaccio neon, 2 x Divano ghiaccio neon, 2x Tavolo di ghiaccio neon (Viola e verde) e abiti esclusivi Signora Gelo e Signora Gelo cappello e Signor Gelo, Signor Gelo scarpe e Signor Gelo cappello [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">incluso Nieve-hombre,  Nieve-mujer, Nieve-chico, Nieve-chica, 2 x Silla hielo neón, 2 x Sofá hielo neón 2 x Mesa hielo neón (Púrpura y verde) y ropa exclusiva Señora Helada y Señora Helada sombrero y Señor Helada, Señor Helada zapatos y Señor Helada sombrero [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">including Snow Globe Apartment, Snow-man, Snow-woman, snow-boy, snow-girl, 2 x neon ice chair, 2 x neon ice sofa, 2 x neon ice table (purple and green) and exclusive clothing Mrs Frost and Mrs Frost Hat and Mr Frost, Mr Frost Shoes and Mr Frost Hat. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>