<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gothic Manor Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack de meubles de Manoir gothique</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gotik-Villa: Möbelset</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto arredamento Maniero gotico</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de muebles mansión gótica</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴシックマンション家具セット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">고딕풍 영지 가구 번들</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Gothic Manor Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">哥德式莊園家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">哥德式莊園家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gothic Manor Furniture Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Place these shadowy furniture items all over your Gothic Manor. Bundle includes a bed, lamp, couch, shelf, and table. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Meublez votre Manoir gothique avec ces sombres objets. Le pack comprend un lit, une lampe, un canapé, une étagère et une table. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Platziere diese düsteren Möbelstücke in deiner Gotik-Villa. Das Set enthält ein Bett, eine Lampe, eine Couch, ein Regal und einen Tisch. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Disponi questi articoli di arredamento scuri nel tuo Maniero gotico. Il pacchetto include letto, lampada, divano, libreria e tavolo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pon estos oscuros objetos de decoración por toda tu mansión gótica. El conjunto incluye cama, lámpara, sofá, estantería y mesa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴシックマンションにぴったりな謎に包まれた家具のセットです。\n\n本セットには以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n・「テーブル（ゴシックマンション）」（テーブル）\n・「シェルフ（ゴシックマンション）」（収納家具）\n・「ランプ（ゴシックマンション）」（照明器具）\n・「カウチ（ゴシックマンション）」（ソファー）\n・「ベッド（ゴシックマンション）」（アドバンスド家具）\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。\n\n※本セットには、アニメーションや機能が追加されているアドバンスド家具が含まれています。この種類のアイテムは配置できる数に制限があります。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">어둠 속에서 일렁이는 그림자 처럼 거실을 지키는 가구를 만나 보십시오.\n 본 번들에는 다음 아이템이 포함되어 있습니다.\n\n  ●고딕풍 영지 침대\n ●고딕풍 영지 램프\n ●고딕풍 영지 소파\n ●고딕풍 영지 선반\n ●고딕풍 영지 탁자\n\n  *구입하면 해당 카테고리에 각 아이템이 추가됩니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Place these shadowy furniture items all over your Gothic Manor.\n This bundle includes the following items.\n\n  ・Gothic Manor Bed\n ・Gothic Manor Lamp\n ・Gothic Manor Couch\n ・Gothic Manor Shelf\n ・Gothic Manor Table\n\n  *When purchased, each item is added to its respective category.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在你的哥德式莊園內放置這些陰暗的家具道具。\n 本組合包包括：\n\n  ●哥德式莊園床\n ●哥德式莊園電燈\n ●哥德式莊園長沙發\n ●哥德式莊園架\n ●哥德式莊園桌\n\n  ※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別內。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在你的哥德式莊園內放置這些陰暗的家具道具。\n 本組合包包括：\n\n  ●哥德式莊園床\n ●哥德式莊園電燈\n  ●哥德式莊園長沙發\n ●哥德式莊園架\n ●哥德式莊園桌\n\n  ※購買後，各道具將被置於對應的類別內。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Place these shadowy furniture items all over your Gothic Manor. Bundle includes a bed, lamp, Couch, Shelf, and Table. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>