<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MotorStorm® Burnt Out BBQ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">MotorStorm® Burnt Out BBQ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Barbecue "burn" MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">MotorStorm®: Ausgebrannter Grill</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Barbecue disastrato MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Barbacoa carbonizada de MotorStorm®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">MotorStorm® がらくたグリル</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">MotorStorm® 타버린 BBQ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">MotorStorm™ Burnt Out BBQ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">MotorStorm™ 燒壞了的BBQ烤爐</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">MotorStorm™ 燒壞了的BBQ烤爐</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">MotorStorm® Burnt Out BBQ</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Don’t let that roadkill go to waste – skewer it up and chargrill the little critter on this impromptu BBQ, cunningly fashioned from an oil drum and other non-descript pieces of post-race junk. If only it actually worked! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Don’t let that roadkill go to waste – skewer it up and chargrill the little critter on this impromptu BBQ, cunningly fashioned from an oil drum and other non-descript pieces of post-race junk. If only it actually worked! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ne laissez pas cet animal renversé se perdre. Embrochez-le et faites-le griller sur ce barbecue de fortune, fabriqué à partir d'un vieux bidon d'huile et d'autres pièces détachées de compétition non-identifiées. Si seulement il fonctionnait ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lass die überfahrenen Tiere nicht einfach liegen – spieße sie auf und röste die kleinen Viecher über diesem improvisierten Grill, geschickt aus einem Ölfass und einigem anderen undefinierbaren Rennmüll zusammengeschustert. Wenn er jetzt nur noch funktionieren würde![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non lasciare che quella creaturina sia stata travolta invano, infilzala con lo spiedo e arrostiscila su questo barbecue improvvisato, ingegnosamente costruito con un vecchio barile d'olio e altri rottami di veicoli non meglio identificati. Se solo funzionasse davvero![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si murió atropellado, es una pena tirarlo: prepara el espetón y prepara al bichejo a la parrilla en esta barbacoa improvisada, hecha con un bidón de aceite y otros restos de chatarra de las carreras. ¡Ay, si funcionase! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">砂漠をさまようどんな動物でも炭焼きにすれば絶対に美味しい！しかし、ドラム缶とがらくたで作られた自家製バーベキューグリルでは、肉がちゃんと焼けるのか不安・・・[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">길에서 실수로 친 동물이 있습니까? 그럼 지나치지 말고 이 BBQ에서 구워보세요. 기름통과 기타 잡동사니 부품들로 만든 그릴입니다. 작동만 한다면 참 좋을텐데.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Don’t let that roadkill go to waste – skewer it up and chargrill the little critter on this impromptu BBQ, cunningly fashioned from an oil drum and other non-descript pieces of post-race junk. If only it actually worked! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">不要白白浪費在路上被車子撞死的小動物－將牠們串起來再用這個烤爐烤熟吧。假若這個用油桶和賽車後剩下的無聊物資拼湊出來的烤爐真的可以用的話。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">不要白白浪費在路上被車子撞死的小動物－將牠們串起來再用這個烤爐烤熟吧。假若這個用油桶和賽車後剩下的無聊物資拼湊出來的烤爐真的可以用的話。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Don’t let that roadkill go to waste – skewer it up and chargrill the little critter on this impromptu BBQ, cunningly fashioned from an oil drum and other non-descript pieces of post-race junk. If only it actually worked! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>