<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Personal Chef - BBQ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chef personnel - Barbecue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ihr persönlicher Grill-Chefkoch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chef Personale - Barbecue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chef personal - Parrilla</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Get the personal chef to grill up some tasty steak! Invite friends over to your apartment for an entertaining evening and get your taste buds going with a selection of mouth-watering barbecued food. Once finished you will receive the consumed item as a reward.

\n\n※ Active items provide more functionality than normal items. You may only place limited numbers of the active items in your apartment or clubhouse at any time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bénéficiez de votre propre chef à domicile pour vous griller de délicieux steaks ! Invitez des amis à votre appartement pour une fête en soirée et régalez-vous grâce à une sélection d'aliments savoureux, cuits au barbecue. Une fois terminé, vous recevrez l'article consommé comme récompense.

\n\n※ Les articles actifs offrent davantage de fonctionnalités que les articles normaux. À tout moment, vous ne pouvez placer qu'un nombre limité d'articles actifs dans votre appartement ou votre club-house. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lassen Sie sich von Ihrem persönlichen Chefkoch ein schmackhaftes Steak grillen! Laden Sie Freunde zu einem Grillfest in Ihr Apartment ein und lassen Sie sich die appetitanregenden Kreationen Ihres Chefkochs gut schmecken. Nach dem Essen erhalten Sie die verzehrte Speise als Belohnung.

 \n\n※ Aktive Artikel bieten mehr Funktionalität als normale Artikel. Sie dürfen nur eine begrenzte Anzahl aktiver Artikel jeweils in Ihrem Apartment oder Clubhaus aufstellen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un cuoco personale per cuocere delle deliziose bistecche alla griglia! Invita gli amici nel tuo appartamento per una serata divertente e assapora una selezione di squisiti cibi cotti al barbecue. Una volta finito, riceverai l'articolo consumato come premio.

\n\n※ Gli articoli attivi offrono maggiori funzionalità rispetto a quelli normali. Puoi posizionare solo un numero limitato di articoli attivi alla volta nel tuo appartamento o circolo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Consigue que el chef personal haga un rico bistec a la parrilla! Invita a tus amigos a tu piso para pasar una entretenida velada y deleita tus papilas gustativas con una selección de platos a la parrilla que te harán la boca agua. Cuando termines, recibirás el artículo que hayas consumido de premio.

\n\n※ Los artículos activos ofrecen más funcionalidad que los normales. Así, en todo momento, podrás ubicar sólo un número limitado de artículos activos en tu apartamento o tu club. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">But_Accept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">But_Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">AcceptFood</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Consume</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Consommer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verzehren Sie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Consuma</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Consumir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Abbrechen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>