<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Cute Goth Loli Set (Navy, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set mignon de Gothic Lolita (marine, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Niedliches Goth Loli-Set (marineblau, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set carino da gothic lolita (blu scuro, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego lindo de lolita gótica (azul marino, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">キュートなゴスロリセット（ネイビー・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Cute Goth Loli Set (Navy, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 6-piece Gothic Lolita fashion set, consisting of a hairstyle, dresses (with and without tights), 2 sets of pumps (with and without tights), and a headdress.\nDefensive Strength: None~★\nCuteness: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Curly Pigtails Hairstyle (Women) (Head)\n- Ribbon Headdress (Navy, Women) (Head Accessory)\n- Cute Goth Loli Dress (Navy, Women) (Outfits)\n- Cute Goth Loli Dress &amp; Tights (Navy, Women) (Outfits)\n- Ribbon High Heel Pumps (Navy, Women) (Feet)\n- Ribbon High Heel Pumps &amp; Tights (Navy, Women) (Feet)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 6 pièces à la mode Gothic Lolita comprenant une coupe de cheveux, des robes (avec et sans collants), 2 jeux d'escarpins (avec et sans collants) et une coiffe.\nDéfense : Aucun(e)~★\nCharme : ★★★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Coupe de cheveux à nattes bouclées (femme) (Tête)\n- Coiffe ruban (marine, femme) (Accessoire de tête)\n- Robe mignonne de Gothic Lolita (marine, femme) (Tenues)\n- Robe mignonne de Gothic Lolita et collants (marine, femme) (Tenues)\n- Escarpins à rubans sur talons hauts (marine, femme) (Pieds)\n- Escarpins à rubans sur talons hauts et collants (marine, femme) (Pieds)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 6-teiliges Set von Gegenständen im Stil der Gothic Lolita-Mode. Es enthält eine Frisur, Kleider (mit und ohne Strumpfhose), 2 Paar Pumps (mit und ohne Strumpfhose) und ein Headdress.\nVerteidigung: keine~★\nNiedlichkeit: ★★★\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Lockige Zöpfe (für Frauen) (Kopf)\n- Headdress mit Schleife (marineblau, für Frauen) (Kopfbedeckung)\n- Niedliches Goth Loli-Kleid (marineblau, für Frauen) (Outfits)\n- Niedliches Goth Loli-Kleid &amp; Strumpfhose (marineblau, für Frauen) (Outfits)\n- Plateau-Pumps mit Schleifen (marineblau, für Frauen) (Füße)\n- Plateau-Pumps mit Schleifen &amp; Strumpfhose (marineblau, für Frauen) (Füße)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set composto da 6 elementi in stile gothic lolita, che include un'acconciatura, vestiti (con e senza calze), 2 paia di scarpe (con e senza collant) e un copricapo.\nDifesa: nulla~★\nBellezza: ★★★\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Acconciatura codine arricciate (da donna) (testa)\n- Copricapo con fiocco (blu scuro, da donna) (accessorio per la testa)\n- Vestito carino da gothic lolita (blu scuro, da donna) (aspetti)\n- Vestito carino da gothic lolita e collant (blu scuro, da donna) (aspetti)\n- Scarpe scollate con tacchi alti e fiocco (blu scuro, da donna) (piedi)\n- Scarpe scollate con tacchi alti e fiocco abbinate a collant (blu scuro, da donna) (piedi)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettiva categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de seis artículos estilo lolita gótica, con peinado, vestidos (con y sin leotardos), dos pares de zapatos (con y sin leotardos), y un tocado.\nDefensa: ninguna~★\nEncanto: ★★★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Peinado con coletas en tirabuzón (mujer) (cabeza)\n- Tocado con lazo (azul marino, mujer) (accesorio de cabeza)\n- Vestido lindo de lolita gótica (azul marino, mujer) (trajes)\n- Vestido lindo de lolita gótica y leotardos (azul marino, mujer) (trajes)\n- Zapatos de tacón con lazos (azul marino, mujer) (pies)\n- Zapatos de tacón con lazos y leotardos (azul marino, mujer) (pies)\n\n* Adquiriendo este conjunto, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ヘアスタイル、ドレス（タイツあり／なし）、パンプス２点（タイツあり／なし）、ヘッドドレスを含む、ゴシック＆ロリータファッション６点セット。\n防御力：　（なし）～★\nかわいさ：　★★★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・ツインロールヘアスタイル（女性）/頭\n・リボンヘッドドレス（ネイビー・女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n・キュートなゴスロリドレス（ネイビー・女性）/組み合わせ\n・キュートなゴスロリドレス＆タイツ（ネイビー・女性）/組み合わせ\n・リボンハイソールパンプス（ネイビー・女性）/靴\n・リボンハイソールパンプス＆タイツ（ネイビー・女性）/靴\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 6-piece Gothic Lolita fashion set, consisting of a hairstyle, dresses (with and without tights), 2 sets of pumps (with and without tights), and a headdress.\nDefensive Strength: None~★\nCuteness: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Curly Pigtails Hairstyle (Women) (Head)\n- Ribbon Headdress (Navy, Women) (Head Accessory)\n- Cute Goth Loli Dress (Navy, Women) (Outfits)\n- Cute Goth Loli Dress &amp; Tights (Navy, Women) (Outfits)\n- Ribbon High Heel Pumps (Navy, Women) (Feet)\n- Ribbon High Heel Pumps &amp; Tights (Navy, Women) (Feet)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
