<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Barbarian Armor Set (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble d’armure de barbare (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rüstungssatz Barbar (Männer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set di armatura da barbaro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de armadura del bárbaro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Barbarian Armor Set (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Heed the Call of Arreat with this complete set of iconic Barbarian armor from Diablo III! The set includes the Barbarian Helm, Barbarian Plate Mail, Barbarian Plate Leggings, Barbarian Greaves, and Barbarian Plated Gauntlets.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Répondez à l’appel d’Arreat grâce à cet ensemble complet d’armure emblématique du barbare de Diablo III ! Il comprend : heaume de barbare, armure de barbare en plaques, jambards de barbare en plaques, grèves de barbare, gantelets de barbare en plaques.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Folgen Sie dem Ruf des Arreat mit diesem vollständigen Satz einer unverwechselbaren Barbarenrüstung aus Diablo III! Der Rüstungssatz umfasst Barbaren-Kopfschutz, Barbaren-Plattenharnisch, Barbaren-Plattenhose, Barbaren-Beinschienen und Barbaren-Panzerhandschuhe.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Rispondi al richiamo di Arreat con questo set di armatura da barbaro tratto da Diablo III! Il set include Elmo da barbaro, Corazza da barbaro, Gambali da barbaro, Schinieri da barbaro e Guanti a piastre da barbaro.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Prepárate para acudir a la Llamada de Arreat con este conjunto completo de armadura del bárbaro de Diablo III! El equipo incluye el yelmo, la cota de placas, los leotardos de placas, las grebas y los guanteletes de placas del bárbaro.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_6 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_6 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_6 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_6 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_6 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Heed the Call of Arreat with this complete set of iconic Barbarian armor from Diablo III! The set includes the Barbarian Helm, Barbarian Plate Mail, Barbarian Plate Leggings, Barbarian Greaves, and Barbarian Plated Gauntlets.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>