<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Old West Saloon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Saloon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Saloons</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Saloon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Salón</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Old West Saloon</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take pride as the new owner of The Old West Saloon today! You've worked hard moving westward to explore the new frontier, and it's time to take pride in your latest acquisition. The Saloon is the perfect place to host friends with included games of Blackjack, Liar's Dice and even Darts. But no new piece of real estate would be complete without a wardrobe so included is Old West attire and furniture to truly give your new home an authentic look and feel. This Saloon is so jammed packed with items and minigames you'll be the talk of the town!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous êtes le fier nouveau patron du Saloon aujourd'hui! Vous avez difficilement gagné l'Ouest afin d'explorer la nouvelle frontière, et il est temps de profiter de votre tout dernier achat. Le Saloon est l'endroit idéal pour acceuillir des amis avec des jeux comme le Blackjack, le Liars Dice et même les Fléchettes. Mais aucun nouveaux endroits immobilier ne serait complet sans une garde-robe, alors inclus se trouve une tenue et un mobilier de l'Ouest Ancien, pour donner vraiment à votre nouvelle maison un aspect et une ambiance authentique. Ce Saloon est tellement bourré d'objets et de mini-jeux, que toute la ville parlera de vous! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Glückwunsch, Sie sind der neue Eigentümer des Saloons. Sie haben viel gewagt und mutigen Schrittes das neue Land im Westen erkundet. Es ist Zeit zu feiern und stolz auf Ihre neueste Errungenschaft zu sein. Der Saloon ist der perfekte Ort um mit Freunden zu feiern. Am Pokertisch, beim Würfelspiel “Liar's Dice”, oder bei ein paar Runden Darts. Aber kein Zuhause ist komplett, solange es nicht passend ausgestattet ist. Also liefern wir eine passende Garderobe bestehend aus authentischen Wild-West Kleidern, Anzügen und Möbeln. Dieser Saloon steckt voller Spiele und Sehenswürdigkeiten, dass Sie sich vor Freunden und Besuchern nicht mehr retten werden können. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Siate orgogliosi del vostro nuovo Saloon! Avete lavorato duro per esplorare nuove frontiere e cercare opportunità nel vecchio West, ora è tempo per voi di godervi i frutti del vostro acquisto. Il Saloon è il luogo perfetto per divertirsi con gli amici giocando a Blackjack, Dadi bugiardi o Freccette. Ma nessun nuovo acquisto immobiliare è completo senza un guardaroba all'altezza, perciò troverete inclusi anche abiti e mobili in puro stile Old West per dare alla vostra nuova casa un autentico look d'epoca. Il vostro Saloon è così pieno di mini-giochi e accessori che sarà presto sulla bocca di tutti! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Enorgullécete de ser el nuevo propietario de El Salón, hoy! Usted ha trabajado duro hacia el oeste para explorar la nueva frontera, y es hora de que se enorgullezca de su última adquisición. El salón es el lugar perfecto para amigos, con juegos incluidos de Blackjack, Liar´s Dice e incluso Dardos. Pero ninguna nueva pieza de bienes raíces no estaría completa sin un armario de ropa, se incluye ropa del antiguo Oeste y muebles para darle verdaderamente estilo a su nuevo hogar y una mirada auténtica. Este salón es tan lleno de objetos y minijuegos que estará en la plática de todos en la ciudad! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Take pride as the new owner of The Old West Saloon today! You've worked hard moving westward to explore the new frontier, and it's time to take pride in your latest acquisition. The Saloon is the perfect place to host friends with included games of Blackjack, Liar's Dice and even Darts. But no new piece of real estate would be complete without a wardrobe so included is Old West attire and furniture to truly give your new home an authentic look and feel. This Saloon is so jammed packed with items and minigames you'll be the talk of the town!  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>