<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Neptune Suite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Suite Neptune</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Neptune-Suite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Suite di Nettuno</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Suite de Neptuno</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Neptune Suite</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The "Neptune Suite" offers a virtual life of luxury in this opulent underwater paradise. Enjoy this action-packed personal space featuring an 8-player picture scramble game, a 4-player action game, an interactive robotic pet, and a sweeping underwater glass wall vista. Buy now! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La Suite Neptune offre une vie virtuelle de luxe dans ce paradis sous-marin opulent. Profitez de cet espace personnel rempli d'action avec un jeu d'images mélangées accueillant jusqu'à 8 joueurs, un jeu d'action à quatre joueurs, un animal-robot interactif, et un panorama époustouflant derrière la paroi de verre. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Neptun-Suite bietet ein virtuelles Leben im Luxus in diesem opulenten Unterwasser-Paradies. Genießen Sie dieses vielfältige persönliche Apartment mit einem 8-Spieler-Bildpuzzlespiel, einem 4-Spieler-Actionspiel, einem interaktiven Roboter-Haustier und einer ausgedehnten Unterwasser-Aussichtsglaswand. Jetzt kaufen! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La "Suite di Nettuno" propone una vita virtuale in questo opulento paradiso sottomarino. Godetevi questo spazio personale pieno d’azione con un puzzle di immagini per 8 giocatori, un gioco d'azione per 4 giocatori, un animale domestico interattivo e una vista mozzafiato del fondale marino. Acquistalo ora! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La "suite de Neptuno" te ofrece una vida virtual de lujo en este opulento paraíso submarino. Disfruta de este espacio personal cargado de acción con: un puzle de imágenes para 8 jugadores, un juego de acción para 4 jugadores, una mascota robótica interactiva y un cristal con vistas al fondo marino. ¡Cómpralo ya! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The "Neptune Suite" offers a virtual life of luxury in this opulent underwater paradise. Enjoy this action-packed personal space featuring an 8-player picture scramble game, a 4-player action game, an interactive robotic pet, and a sweeping underwater glass wall vista. Buy now! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>