<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Genie-less Lamp</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lampe sans génie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unmagische Lampe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lampada senza genio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lámpara del genio desaparecido</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ジーニーが出てこないランプ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">지니가 없는 램프</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Genie-less Lamp</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">無精靈神燈</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">無精靈神燈</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Genie-less Lamp</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This one doesn't contain a Genie. Because if a Genie granted you a wish that was a lamp that contained a Genie that could grant you a wish…. Well, you can see the problem! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette lampe ne contient pas de génie. Car si un génie vous accordait un vœu qui était une lampe contenant un génie qui pourrait vous accorder un vœu… Bref, vous voyez le problème ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hier drin steckt kein Flaschengeist. Denn wenn ein Flaschengeist deinen Wunsch einer magischen Lampe erfüllen würde, so dass der Geist darin dir einen Wunsch erfüllen kann ... Na ja, du siehst schon, wie problematisch das wäre. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa non contiene nessun genio. Perché se un genio ti concedesse un desiderio, quella sarebbe una lampada che contiene un genio che realizza i desideri... Beh, è chiaro il problema! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta lámpara fue antaño la morada de un antiguo genio. ¡Para que luego nos quejemos de los pisos de 30 metros cuadrados! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">注意：このランプにはあなたの願いを叶えてくれそうなジーニーは含まれていません。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">여기에는 지니가 살지 않아요. 만일 지니가 당신의 소원을 들어 주었다면 거기에 지니가 있었을 것이고, 그래서 당신의 소원을 들어 주었을 것이고… 흠, 이제 무엇이 문제인지 알겠지요! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This one doesn't contain a Genie. Because if a Genie granted you a wish that was a lamp that contained a Genie that could grant you a wish…. Well, you can see the problem! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">裡面沒有精靈。因為如果精靈讓你許願，這個願望又是來自裡面有精靈而且能讓你許願的神燈……這樣你知道問題在哪了嗎？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">裡面沒有精靈。因為如果精靈讓你許願，這個願望又是來自裡面有精靈而且能讓你許願的神燈……這樣你知道問題在哪了嗎？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This one doesn't contain a Genie. Because if a Genie granted you a wish that was a lamp that contained a Genie that could grant you a wish…. Well, you can see the problem! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>