<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Dragon Year Toxic Doll Full Body Suit (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dragon Year Toxic Doll Full Body Suit (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Costume de Poupée Toxique de l'année du Dragon (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Anzug der Giftigen Puppe für Jahr des Drachen (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Abito Bambola Tossica dell’Anno del Drago (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de muñeco tóxico año dragón (Hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_ToxicDoll</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">용의해 맹독인형 의상 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Dragon Year Toxic Doll Full Body Suit (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">龍年毒娃娃套裝(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">龍年毒娃娃套裝(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dragon Year Toxic Doll Full Body Suit (Men)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">This is the special edition of Toxic Doll Full Body Suit for Dragon Year. There are dragon lines and scales covered on deep red cloth with golden dragon design. Also there are glowing sharp eyes on the face decorated with dragon claws. These are full of secret eastern legend of dragon.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is the special edition of Toxic Doll Full Body Suit for Dragon Year. There are dragon lines and scales covered on deep red cloth with golden dragon design. Also there are glowing sharp eyes on the face decorated with dragon claws. These are full of secret eastern legend of dragon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Costume de Poupée Toxique est une collection sépciale de l'année du Dragon. La peau est avec la tatouage et des écailles du Dragon. Le vêtement est en forme du dragon doré avec un chiffon rouge foncé. Dans le visage, les yeux sont bleus et brillants, un déco des griffes du Dragon autour. ça remplit la légende mystérieuse orientale du Dragon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sonderausgabe von Anzug der Giftigen Puppe für Jahr des Drachen, darauf wird es mit Pattern und Schuppen von Drachen bedeckt. Die Kleidung hat goldenen Drachen Muster auf deren dunkelroten Stoffe, und auf das Gesicht ist mit glänzenden blauen scharfen Augen und Drachenkralle geschmückt. Dieser ganze Anzug ist erfüllt von geheimnisvoller Atmosphäre der orientalischen Drachenlegenden. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L’edizione speciale dell’abito Bambola Tossica per l’anno del Drago. Ricoperta di grane e squame, la Bambola Tossica indossa un abito color violaceo con il disegno di un drago dorato, sul suo viso decorato con disegni di zampe di drago spicca lo sguardo tagliente dei suoi occhi bluastri. Una leggenda del Drago circondata dalla misteriosità orientale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de muñeco tóxico versión especial  del año dragón, el cuerpo está cubierto de patrón y escalas del dragón, el vestido es color rojo con diseño de la imagen del dragón dorado, ojos verdes agudos y con la decoración de garras. Lleno de leyenda misteriosa del dragón oriental. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_FullBodySuit_ToxicDoll [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">맹독인형 의상 용의해 스페셜 버전으로 몸은 온통 용 무늬와 비늘 조각이 새겨져 있고 붉은 색 옷감과  금색 용 그림이 어우러져있으며 푸른 빛의 날카로운 눈과 용 갈퀴 데코레이션으로 동방의 신비로운 용의 전설 느낌을 풍깁니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This is the special edition of Toxic Doll Full Body Suit for Dragon Year. There are dragon lines and scales covered on deep red cloth with golden dragon design. Also there are glowing sharp eyes on the face decorated with dragon claws. These are full of secret eastern legend of dragon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">毒娃娃套裝的龍年特別版，身上覆蓋著龍紋及鱗片，衣服上以金色龍形圖案搭配深紅色的布料，臉上則有發光的青色銳利眼睛以及龍爪裝飾，充滿著神秘東方的龍的傳說。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">毒娃娃套裝的龍年特別版，身上覆蓋著龍紋及鱗片，衣服上以金色龍形圖案搭配深紅色的布料，臉上則有發光的青色銳利眼睛以及龍爪裝飾，充滿著神秘東方的龍的傳說。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This is the special edition of Toxic Doll Full Body Suit for Dragon Year. There are dragon lines and scales covered on deep red cloth with golden dragon design. Also there are glowing sharp eyes on the face decorated with dragon claws. These are full of secret eastern legend of dragon. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>