<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Electromagnetic Bomb</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bombe électromagnétique</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Elektromagnetische Bombe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bomba elettromagnetica</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bomba electromagnética</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">電磁爆弾</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">전자기 폭탄</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Electromagnetic Bomb</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">電磁炸彈</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">電磁炸彈</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Electromagnetic Bomb</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Shut down enemy ships with the Electromagnetic Bomb!  You control when this bomb detonates, unleashing a disruptive electromagnetic pulse that shuts down enemy weapons systems. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Neutralisez les vaisseaux ennemis grâce à la Bombe électromagnétique ! Vous contrôlez la détonation de la bombe dont l'explosion relâchera une impulsion électromagnétique perturbatrice qui neutralisera les systèmes d'armement ennemis. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schalte feindliche Schiffe mit der Elektromagnetischen Bombe aus! Du kontrollierst selber, wann die Bombe ausgelöst wird, wodurch ein elektromagnetischer Störimpuls ausgelöst wird, der feindliche Waffensysteme abschaltet. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Paralizza le navi nemiche con la bomba elettromagnetica! Sarai tu a comandare l'esplosione dell'ordigno, creando una potente onda magnetica che paralizzerà i sistemi di armi dei nemici. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Destruye las naves enemigas con la bomba electromagnética. Controlarás el momento de detonación de la bomba, liberando un pulso electromagnético que anula los sistemas de armas del enemigo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">電磁爆弾で敵の船をシャットダウン！このボムは敵の武器システムをシャットダウンする電磁パルスを放つ。爆発するタイミングをコントロールすることができる。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">전자기 폭탄으로 적 함선을 무력화시키십시오! 폭탄이 터질 때를 직접 조절할 수 있으며, 폭발 시 위협적인 전자기장을 뿜어내 적의 무기 체계를 무력화시킵니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Shut down enemy ships with the Electromagnetic Bomb!  You control when this bomb detonates, unleashing a disruptive electromagnetic pulse that shuts down enemy weapons systems. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用電磁炸彈將敵方的戰鬥機炸得不能動弹！你可引爆炸彈，發散一道干擾性的電磁脈衝，令敵方武器系統停止運作。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用電磁炸彈將敵方的戰鬥機炸得不能動弹！你可引爆炸彈，發散一道干擾性的電磁脈衝，令敵方武器系統停止運作。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Shut down enemy ships with the Electromagnetic Bomb!  You control when this bomb detonates, unleashing a disruptive electromagnetic pulse that shuts down enemy weapons systems. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>