<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Resistance 3™  Magnum</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Magnum Resistance 3™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Resistance 3™"-Magnum</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Magnum di Resistance 3™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Magnum de Resistance 3™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Resistance 3™  Magnum</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It might not be as advanced as the Chimera weapons, but this trusty hand gun could be all that stands between you and your doom. This item was won from playing the Resistance 3™ Scavenger mini game. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Même s'il n'est pas aussi évolué que les armes chimériennes, ce fidèle pistolet pourrait bien être le dernier rempart entre vous et votre perte. Objet gagné en jouant au mini-jeu Chasse au trésor Resistance 3™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese Handwaffe ist vielleicht nicht so fortschrittlich wie die Waffen der Bestien, könnte aber alles sein, das zwischen Ihnen und dem Untergang steht. Dieser Gegenstand wurde durch Spielen des Minispiels "Resistance 3™"-Plünderer gewonnen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nonostante non sia avanzata come le armi Chimera, questa pistola è in grado di volgere l'ago della bilancia a tuo favore, in caso di pericolo. Questo oggetto è stato vinto giocando al minigioco Ricerca di Resistance 3™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Puede que no sea tan avanzada como las armas quimeras, pero este fiable revólver puede ser tu única defensa ante la muerte. Has conseguido este objeto jugando al minijuego de búsqueda de recursos de Resistance 3™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">It might not be as advanced as the Chimera weapons, but this trusty hand gun could be all that stands between you and your doom. This item was won from playing the Resistance 3™ Scavenger mini game. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>