<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sith Banner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bannière Sith</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sith-Banner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Stendardo Sith</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estandarte Sith</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sith Banner</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">As I wandered the corridors of Coruscant, seeking out my Jedi prey, I furtively searched for any sign of where he may have been. Charging down the halls, I glanced to my left and my right. Then I stopped. My eyes had landed upon a cloth which struck a chord deep within my dark soul. Emblazoned upon this tapestry was the symbol of my order. It was, the Sith Banner. Behind it was the Jedi. The dark side, once again, proves fortuitous. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tandis que je parcourais les couloirs de Coruscant, à la recherche de ma proie jedi, je cherchais furtivement tout signe m'indiquant où il avait pu se trouver. Arpentant les halls, je regardais à gauche et à droite. Je m'arrêtai. Mes yeux étaient tombés sur une toile qui fit vibrer une corde au fond de mon âme noire. Brodé dans la tapisserie, on pouvait voir le symbole de mon ordre. La bannière Sith. Et derrière, il y avait le Jedi. Le côté obscur, une fois encore, s'était révélé de manière imprévue. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Während ich durch die Gänge von Coruscant wanderte und meine Jedi-Beute aufspürte, suchte ich heimlich nach einem Zeichen, wo er gewesen sein konnte. Ich stürmte durch die Gänge und blickte nach links und rechts. Dann hielt ich an. Mein Blick landete auf einem Stück Stoff, der tief in meiner dunklen Seele etwas traf. Das Symbol meines Ordens schmückte diesen Wandteppich. Es war das Banner der Sith. Dahinter war der Jedi. Wieder einmal half der Dunklen Seite der Zufall. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mentre vagavo per i corridoi di Coruscant alla ricerca della mia preda Jedi, furtivamente cercavo qualsiasi traccia della sua presenza. Correndo lungo i corridoi, guardavo alla mia destra e alla mia sinistra. Poi mi sono fermato. I miei occhi si erano fermati su un pezzo di stoffa la cui vista stava penetrando nel profondo della mia anima oscura. Sulla stoffa appariva infatti il simbolo del mio ordine. Si trattava dello Stendardo Sith. Dietro c'era lo Jedi. Il lato oscuro si dimostra ancora una volta fortunato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Recorriendo los pasillos de Coruscant en busca de mi víctima Jedi, busqué furtivamente cualquier señal que me indicara dónde podía haber estado. Atravesando los pasajes a toda velocidad, miré a mi izquierda y a mi derecha. Entonces me detuve. Mis ojos se posaron en una tela que hizo vibrar mi oscura alma. Decorando dicha tela estaba el símbolo de mi orden. Era el Estandarte Sith. Detrás de él estaba el Jedi. El lado oscuro, una vez más, se demuestra fortuito. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">As I wandered the corridors of Coruscant, seeking out my Jedi prey, I furtively searched for any sign of where he may have been. Charging down the halls, I glanced to my left and my right. Then I stopped. My eyes had landed upon a cloth which struck a chord deep within my dark soul. Emblazoned upon this tapestry was the symbol of my order. It was, the Sith Banner. Behind it was the Jedi. The dark side, once again, proves fortuitous. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>