<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wide Load and Baby Girl Diaper Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Couche de Charge Vaste et Petite-Fille Ensemble</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weiten Last und Baby Mädchen Windel Bündel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Carico Pannolino Ampio i Pannolino del Bambino Ragazza Raccolta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Carga Ancha y Baby Girl Pañales Carga Ancha Paquete</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Wide Load and Baby Girl Diaper Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Now, this is a bundle of joy!  Boy and Girl diapers and tops . . .Now with pacifiers. When you wear this around Home, you'll prove that you're the Sh**!  Bundle comes with Male and Female diapers and tops.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Alors ca, c'est un paquet de joie! Couches Garçon et Fille et des couvertures . . . Maintenant, avec les sucettes. Lorsque vous portez ce autour de Home, vous prouvez que vous êtes le Sh **! Bundle est livré avec des couches pour les Hommes et les Femmes et des couvertures. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nun, dies ist ein bündel von freude! Boy und Girl Windeln und Topen  . . . jetzt mit schnuller. Wenn Sie diese tragen um Home, Sie beweisen, dass Sie die Sh***** sind! Bündel kommt mit männlichen und weiblichen windeln und topen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ora, questo è un fascio di gioia! Pannolini Boy e Girl e piani  . . . Ora, con ciucci. Quando indossi questo giro per la casa, si dimostra che tu sei l'Me***! Raccolta viene fornito con Maschio e Femmina pannolini e top. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ahora, se trata de un paquete de alegría! Chico y Chica pañales y las tapas  . . . Ahora, con el chupete. Cuando usted usa este alrededor de la casa, usted demuestra que usted es el Mi***! Paquete viene con pañales masculina y femenina y las tapas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Now, this is a bundle of joy!  Boy and Girl diapers and tops . . .Now with pacifiers. When you wear this around Home, you'll prove that you're the Sh**!  Bundle comes with Male and Female diapers and tops.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>