<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Rank Trophy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">WipEout® Rank Trophy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Trophée de rang WipEout®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">WipEout®-Rang-Trophäe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Trofeo rango WipEout®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Trofeo de clasificación de WipEout®</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Rank Trophy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">WipEout® 랭크 트로피</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">WipEout® Rank Trophy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">WipEout® 排名獎盃</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">WipEout® 排名獎盃</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rank Trophy</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Were you ever good enough to make the “Immortal” rank? No me neither. But now it matters not one iota! Fake it! Bring this beautiful replica trophy to your home for a price that surely has to be a misprint! Bargain!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Were you ever good enough to make the “Immortal” rank? No, me neither. But now it matters not one iota! Fake it! Bring this beautiful replica trophy to your home for a price that surely has to be a misprint! Bargain! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avez-vous jamais été assez fort pour atteindre le rang "Immortel" ? Non ? Moi non plus, mais désormais, cela n'a plus d'importance ! Faites semblant : installez cette superbe réplique du trophée chez vous pour un prix qui ressemble étrangement à une erreur d'impression ! C'est cadeau ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer hat es jemals geschafft, den Rang „Unsterblicher“ zu erreichen? Wir nicht! Aber das ist auch egal! Man kann ja so tun, als ob, mit dieser wunderschönen Trophäen-Replik, deren Preis ein Druckfehler sein muss! Gekauft! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Siete mai arrivati al rango di “Immortale”? No? Beh, nemmeno io, ma ormai non ha più importanza! Potrete far finta di averlo raggiunto acquistando questa bellissima replica del trofeo a un prezzo ridicolo! È un affare da non perdere! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Has demostrado tener la destreza suficiente para conseguir el rango “Inmortal”? Yo tampoco. ¡Pero no importa en absoluto! Tú di que sí y llévate esta preciosa réplica a casa por un precio que se te antojará irrisorio. ¡Toda una ganga! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Were you ever good enough to make the “Immortal” rank? No me neither. But now it matters not one iota! Fake it! Bring this beautiful replica trophy to your home for a price that surely has to be a misprint! Bargain! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">게임을 플레이하면서 가장 높은 랭크를 획득하실 수 있었나요? 물론 저도 실패했지요. 하지만 이제는 상관 없습니다. 모델 트로피를 구입하면 되니까요! 아무도 눈치채지 못할 엄청난 디테일이, 놀라운 가격에 제공됩니다. 가격표는 오타가 아니에요, 정말 이렇게 싼 겁니다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Were you ever good enough to make the “Immortal” rank? No me neither. But now it matters not one iota! Fake it- bring this beautiful replica trophy to your home for a price that surely has to be a misprint! Bargain! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">您是否有能耐成為「Immortal（神人）」級的車手？我沒有。但這些現在已毫不重要了！有了這個美不勝收的複製獎盃，您可以裝成是神人級車手了，只是要付出的代價高得令人難以置信。要求減價！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">您是否有能耐成為「Immortal（神人）」級的車手？我沒有。但這些現在已毫不重要了！有了這個美不勝收的複製獎盃，您可以裝成是神人級車手了，只是要付出的代價高得令人難以置信。要求減價！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Were you ever good enough to make the “Immortal” rank? No, me neither. But now it matters not one iota! Fake it! Bring this beautiful replica trophy to your home for a price that surely has to be a misprint! Bargain! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>