<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cupcake Dress Bundle (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack robe gâteau (pour Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Cupcake-Kostümpaket (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Abito pasticcino (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de vestido de pastelito (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">컵케이크 번들 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Cupcake Dress Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">紙杯蛋糕服裝組(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">紙杯蛋糕服裝組(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cupcake Dress Bundle (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take centre stage in your riveting new dress. Bundle includes top, bottom, bracelet, and heels. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Attirez tous les regards dans cette robe fascinante. Le pack comprend un haut, un bas, un bracelet et des chaussures à talons. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stell dich mit deinem fesselnden neuen Kleid in den Mittelpunkt. Im Paket enthalten sind Ober- und Unterteil, Armband sowie Schuhe mit Absatz. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Attira tutti gli sguardi su di te con questo strabiliante completo. Il pacchetto include corpetto, gonna, bracciale e scarpe con tacco. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Toma el centro del escenario con tu fascinante vestido nuevo. El conjunto incluye las partes superior e inferior del vestido, pulsera y zapatos de tacón. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">시선을 끄는 새 드레스를 입고 센터 스테이지를 차지하세요. 이 번들은 컵케이크 상의, 하의, 팔찌, 그리고 구두를 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Take center stage in your riveting new dress. Bundle includes Cupcake Top, Cupcake Bottom, Cupcake Bracelet, and Cupcake Heels. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">穿上這件迷人的新連身裙，成為焦點。服裝組包括紙杯蛋糕服裝-上身、紙杯蛋糕服裝-下身、紙杯蛋糕手鐲及紙杯蛋糕高跟鞋。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">穿上這件迷人的新連身裙，成為焦點。服裝組包括紙杯蛋糕服裝-上半身、紙杯蛋糕服裝-下半身、紙杯蛋糕手鐲及紙杯蛋糕高跟鞋。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Take center stage in your riveting new dress. Bundle includes top, bottom, bracelet, and heels. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>