<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Shed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Shed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Shed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Shed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cartas fuera</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is a 4 player card game. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il s'agit d'un jeu de cartes à 4 joueurs. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dies ist ein Kartenspiel für 4 Spieler. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gioco di carte per 4 giocatori. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de cartas para cuatro personas. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Shed Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Instructions Shed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Shed-Anleitung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Istruzioni di Shed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Instrucciones de Cartas fuera</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions SubTitle 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">How To Play</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Comment jouer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spielanleitung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Come si gioca</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cómo jugar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The aim of the game is to lose all of your cards before your opponents.  To put a card down you must have a card which is of higher or equal value to the card played last. Each player must have at least three cards in their hand at any one time while there are cards in the unused deck to be drawn.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'objectif de ce jeu est de perdre toutes vos cartes avant vos adversaires. Pour jouer une carte, elle doit avoir une valeur supérieure ou égale à celle qui a été jouée en dernier. Chaque joueur doit avoir au moins trois cartes en main au même moment tant qu'il reste des cartes à tirer dans le talon.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ziel des Spiels ist es, als erster Spieler alle Karten abzulegen. Um eine Karte ablegen zu können, muss sie mindestens so hoch sein wie die oberste, zuletzt gespielte Karte. Während noch unbenutzte Karten zum Ziehen im Stapel vorhanden sind, muss jeder Spieler zu jeder Zeit mindestens drei Karten auf der Hand haben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lo scopo del gioco è di finire tutte le carte prima degli altri giocatori. Per scartare devi avere una carta di valore pari o superiore all'ultima giocata. Ogni giocatore deve avere in mano almeno tre carte nello stesso momento quando ci sono carte nel mazzo dove si pesca.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El objetivo del juego es quedarse sin cartas antes que nadie. Para jugar una carta, debes tener una de igual o mayor valor que la última carta jugada. Los jugadores deben tener al menos tres cartas en todo momento mientras haya cartas que robar en la baraja.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">When it is your turn, you must play a valid card if you have one. If you cannot play a card, you must pick up all of the cards that have been played in the middle so far (the Live cards). After picking up the Live cards, your turn will end and the next player must place a new card to continue the game, this is known as the Seed Card.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lorsque c'est votre tour, vous devez jouer une carte valide si vous en avez une. Si vous ne pouvez pas jouer, vous devez ramasser toutes les cartes qui ont été jouées jusqu'à présent (les cartes de la pile). Une fois que vous avez ramassé les cartes de la pile, votre tour se termine et le joueur suivant doit jouer une nouvelle carte pour continuer la partie ; cette carte s'appelle la Carte Initiale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn Sie am Zug sind, müssen Sie eine gültige Karte spielen, sofern Sie eine haben. Können Sie keine Karte spielen, müssen Sie alle Karten aufnehmen, die bisher in der Mitte ausgespielt wurden (den Ablegestapel). Danach endet Ihr Zug und der nächste Spieler legt eine neue Karte ab, um das Spiel fortzusetzen. Diese Karte nennt man Saatkarte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Durante il tuo turno, devi giocare una carta valida, se ce l'hai. Se non puoi giocare una carta, devi prendere tutte le carte che sono state scartate fino a quel momento (carte attive). Dopo aver preso le carte attive, il turno passa al giocatore successivo che, per continuare la partita, deve mettere sul tavolo una nuova carta, che prende il nome di carta seme.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Al llegar tu turno, debes jugar una carta válida si tienes. Si no, deberás coger todas las cartas que se hayan jugado hasta el momento (las cartas vivas). Después de recoger las cartas vivas, acaba tu turno y el siguiente jugador pone en juego una nueva carta, que se conoce como la carta presa.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Once the cards in the deck have been exhausted, players must use the three cards sitting face up in front of them and finally the three cards sitting face down beneath those. Once a player has successfully used all of the cards in their hand and on the table in front of them they are out. The game ends when there is only one player left in the game.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une fois qu'il n'y a plus de cartes dans le talon, les joueurs doivent utiliser les trois cartes disposées face visible devant eux et enfin les trois cartes disposées face non-visible sous ces dernières. Une fois qu'un joueur a utilisé toutes ses cartes en main et celles qui se trouvent devant lui sur la table, il sort du jeu. La partie se termine lorsqu'il ne reste plus qu'un joueur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sind keine Karten mehr im Stapel vorhanden, müssen die Spieler die drei Karten benutzen, die aufgedeckt vor ihnen liegen, und schließlich die drei verdeckten Karten daneben. Hat ein Spieler alle Karten auf seiner Hand und vor sich auf dem Tisch abgelegt, scheidet er aus. Das Spiel endet, wenn nur noch ein Spieler übrig ist.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una volta terminate le carte del mazzo, i giocatori devono usare le tre carte scoperte davanti a loro e, solo in seguito, le tre carte coperte che si trovano sotto. Quando un giocatore ha usato tutte le sue carte e quelle sul tavolo, esce dal gioco. La partita finisce quando resta in gioco un solo giocatore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuando se acaban las cartas de la baraja, los jugadores deben usar las tres cartas colocadas boca arriba que tienen enfrente y, por último, las tres cartas que están boca abajo de al lado. Cuando un jugador ha usado todas sus cartas, las de la mano y las de la mesa, está fuera. El juego acaba cuando solo queda un jugador.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions SubTitle 2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Standard and Power Cards</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cartes Standard et cartes Puissance</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Standard- und Spezial-Karten</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Carte normali e speciali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cartas estándar y especiales</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The majority of the cards are known as ‘Standard Cards’, which means that they have no special abilities. The cards that do have special abilities are as follows:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La majorité des cartes sont des "Cartes Standard", ce qui signifie qu'elles n'ont pas de caractéristiques particulières. Les cartes qui ont des caractéristiques particulières sont les suivantes :</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die meisten Karten sind Standardkarten, die keine besonderen Attribute besitzen. Folgende Karten haben besonderen Eigenschaften:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La maggior parte delle carte sono "carte normali", ossia non hanno particolari proprietà. Le carte speciali sono le seguenti:</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La mayoría de las cartas son “cartas estándar”, sin ningún tipo de capacidades. Las especiales son las siguientes:</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Star Card</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La carte Étoile</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Stern-Karte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La carta Stella</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La carta estrella</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">When the Star Card has been placed, the deck is reset and any card can now be played on the next players turn.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quand la carte Étoile est jouée, le talon est remis à zéro, ce qui permet au joueur suivant de jouer n'importe quelle carte lors de son tour.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn die Stern-Karte abgelegt wird, wird der Stapel zurückgesetzt und der nächste Spieler kann eine beliebige Karte ablegen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quando viene usata la carta Stella, il mazzo viene rimescolato e qualsiasi carta può essere giocata al turno successivo del giocatore.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuando la carta estrella se haya colocado, la baraja se reiniciará y los jugadores podrán jugar cualquier carta en su turno.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Five</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Cinq</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Fünf</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Cinque</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El cinco</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Five must be played in order just like any other card (i.e. on a five or lower, or as a Seed card). However, when placed on the Live Cards, the next player must place a card that is equal to or lower than a five. Once a lower card is placed on the five, play returns to normal and the next card played must be higher than the last Live card.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Cinq doit être joué comme toutes les autres cartes (c'est-à-dire sur une carte cinq ou inférieure, ou comme Carte Initiale). Cependant, lorsqu'il est placé sur la pile, le joueur suivant doit jouer une carte égale ou inférieure à cinq. Lorsqu'une carte inférieure est jouée sur le cinq, le jeu reprend son cours normal et la carte suivante devra être d'une valeur supérieure à la dernière carte de la pile.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Fünf muss wie jede andere Karte in der richtigen Reihenfolge gespielt werden (d. h. auf eine andere Fünf bzw. eine niedrigere Zahl oder als Saatkarte). Wird sie aber auf den Ablegestapel gelegt, muss der nächste Spieler eine Karte mit gleichem oder niedrigerem Wert ablegen. Sobald eine niedrigere Karte auf die Fünf gelegt wurde, gelten wieder die ursprünglichen Regeln und die nächste Karte muss höher als die oberste Karte auf dem Ablegestapel sein.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il cinque deve essere giocato in ordine come qualsiasi altra carta (ad esempio su un altro cinque o una carta di valore inferiore, o su una carta seme). In ogni caso, quando posizionato su una carta attiva, il giocatore successivo deve giocare una carta che sia di valore uguale o inferiore al cinque. Una volta posizionata una carta inferiore al cinque su di esso, il gioco ritorna normale e la prossima carta ad essere giocata deve essere di valore maggiore all'ultima carta attiva.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El cinco debe jugarse en orden, como las demás cartas (es decir, con un cinco o una carta de menor valor, o como carta presa). Sin embargo, una vez colocado en las cartas vivas, el siguiente jugador deberá soltar una carta de igual o menor valor que cinco. Al colocarse una carta inferior sobre el cinco, el juego vuelve a la normalidad y la siguiente carta que se juegue debe ser superior a la última carta viva.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 9</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Six</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Six</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Sechs</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Sei</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El seis</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 10</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Six must also be played in order (i.e. on a six or lower, or as a Seed card). When placed on the Live Cards, the next player misses their turn. This card is cumulative, so if a player puts down two 6’s it will skip two players’ turns.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Six doit également être joué comme les autres cartes (c'est-à-dire sur une carte six ou inférieure, ou comme Carte Initiale). Lorsqu'elle est placée sur la pile, le joueur suivant doit passer son tour. Cette carte est cumulable, ce qui signifie que si un joueur place deux 6, deux joueurs doivent passer leur tour.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Sechs muss ebenfalls in der richtigen Reihenfolge gespielt werden (d. h. auf eine Sechs bzw. eine niedrigere Zahl oder als Saatkarte). Wird sie auf den Ablegestapel gelegt, muss der nächste Spieler einmal aussetzen. Die Karte ist kumulativ. Wenn also ein Spieler zwei Sechsen ablegt, müssen die nächsten beiden Spieler einmal aussetzen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Anche il sei deve essere giocato in ordine (ad esempio su un altro sei o una carta di valore inferiore, o su una carta seme). Quando posizionato sulle carte attive, il prossimo giocatore salta il turno. Questa carta è cumulativa, quindi se un giocatore gioca due sei farà saltare il turno a due giocatori.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El seis también debe jugarse en orden (es decir, con un seis o una carta de menor valor, o como carta presa). Una vez colocado en las cartas vivas, se salta el turno del siguiente jugador. La carta se acumula, de modo que, si un jugador se saca dos seis, se saltará el turno de dos jugadores.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Burn Card</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La carte Feu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Feuerkarte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La carta Brucia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La carta de fuego</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 12</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">When this card is used, all of the Live Cards are destroyed. The player gets to take another turn straight after using the Burn Card.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lorsque cette carte est jouée, toutes les cartes de la pile sont détruites. Le joueur obtient un tour supplémentaire juste après l'utilisation d'une carte Feu..</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wird diese Karte benutzt, werden alle Karten des Ablegestapels vernichtet. Der Spieler kann nach Ablegen der Feuerkarte sofort eine weitere Karte ablegen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quando viene usata questa carta, tutte le carte attive vengono distrutte. Il giocatore che ha usato la carta Brucia ottiene un altro turno.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una vez usada esta carta, se eliminan todas las cartas vivas; además, el jugador tendrá otro turno tras usarla.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Four of a Kind</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quatre cartes de la même valeur :</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vierling</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quattro carte uguali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuatro iguales</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Instructions 14</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Any time four of the same card are placed directly on top of each other, the Live Cards are destroyed.  This counts whether placing four cards at once or completing four of a kind with cards played in the previous turn.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lorsque quatre cartes de la même valeur sont jouées à la suite, les cartes de la pile sont détruites. Ceci est valable lorsque quatre cartes sont jouées d'un coup ou qu'une quatrième carte de la même valeur que celles des tours précédents est placée.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Karten des Ablegestapels werden immer dann vernichtet, wenn vier gleiche Karten direkt aufeinander abgelegt wurden. Dies gilt, wenn vier Karten gleichzeitig abgelegt werden, oder wenn der Vierling mit Karten aus dem vorherigen Zug abgeschlossen wird.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quando vengono scartate quattro carte uguali di seguito, le carte attive vengono distrutte. Le quattro carte sono conteggiate sia che vengano scartate tutte insieme, sia in due turni diversi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si se juegan cuatro cartas iguales de forma sucesiva, las cartas vivas se eliminan. No importa si es el mismo jugador el que coloca las cuatro cartas, o si solo coloca la cuarta carta al comenzar su turno.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Continue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Continuer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Fortfahren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Continua</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Continuar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Win Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Congratulations</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Félicitations !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Glückwunsch!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Complimenti!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Enhorabuena!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Win Text</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You have won the game.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez remporté la partie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben das Spiel gewonnen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai vinto la partita</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Has ganado la partida.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Lose Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Unlucky!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pas de chance !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Pech gehabt!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Peccato!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Mala suerte!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Lose Text</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You did not manage to get rid of all your cards before the other players. Why not try again?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous n'avez pas réussi à vous débarrasser de vos cartes avant les autres joueurs. Réessayer ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie konnten nicht alle Ihre Karten vor den anderen Spielern ablegen. Versuchen Sie es ruhig noch einmal!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non hai scartato tutte le tue carte prima degli altri giocatori. Riprova!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No has conseguido deshacerte de todas tus cartas antes que el resto de jugadores. ¿Quieres volver a intentarlo?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Salir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Waiting</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Waiting For Players</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En attente de joueurs</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wartet auf Spieler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">In attesa di altri giocatori</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esperando a los jugadores...</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Play Card</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Play Card</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Jouer carte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Karte spielen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Gioca una carta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Jugar carta</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Play Cards</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Play Cards</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Jouer cartes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Karten spielen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Gioca carte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Jugar cartas</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Back</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Back</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE] Retour</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE] Zurück</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE] Indietro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE] Atrás</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Change Cards</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[RIGHT]/[LEFT] to add / remove selected cards</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[RIGHT]/[LEFT] pour ajouter / supprimer les cartes sélectionnées</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[RIGHT]/[LEFT] Ausgewählte Karten hinzufügen/entfernen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[RIGHT]/[LEFT] per aggiungere / rimuovere le carte selezionate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[RIGHT]/[LEFT] para agregar / quitar cartas seleccionadas</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PickUp</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT] Pick up cards</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT] Ramasser cartes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT] Karten aufnehmen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT] Pesca delle carte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT] Recoger cartas</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">NotYourTurn</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Opponent’s turn</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tour de l'adversaire</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zug des Gegners</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tocca all'avversario</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Turno del rival</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">YourTurn</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Your turn</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Votre tour</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ihr Zug</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tocca a te</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tu turno</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Next</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Next opponent misses turn</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'adversaire suivant passe son tour</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der nächste Gegner setzt aus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il prossimo avversario salta il turno</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Se salta el turno del siguiente rival.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Destroy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Destroy the deck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Détruire le talon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapel zerstören</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Distruggi il mazzo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Destruir la baraja</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Reset</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Reset the deck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Rétablir le talon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stapel zurücksetzen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Azzera il mazzo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Restablecer la baraja</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Lower</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Opponent must play a 5 or lower</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'adversaire doit jouer un 5 ou inférieur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gegner muss eine 5 oder niedriger spielen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'avversario deve giocare un 5 o una carta più bassa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El rival debe jugar un 5 o inferior.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameStart</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The game will begin in $sec seconds.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le jeu débutera dans $sec seconde(s).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Spiel beginnt in $sec  Sekunde(n).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La partita comincerà tra $sec secondo/i.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La partida comenzará en $sec segundo(s).</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Thinking</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Thinking</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Réfléchit...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Denkt nach.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pensando…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pensando...</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PlayOrMore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFT][RIGHT] Change Number of Cards to play</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[LEFT][RIGHT] Changer le nombre de cartes à jouer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[LEFT][RIGHT] Anzahl der zu spielenden Karten ändern</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[LEFT][RIGHT] Cambia il numero di carte da giocare</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[LEFT][RIGHT] Cambiar el número de cartas a jugar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Auto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">AUTO EXIT in $s seconds</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quitte automatiquement dans $sec seconde(s)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verlässt automatisch in $s Sekunde(n).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Uscita automatica in $s secondo/i.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salida automática en $s segundo(s)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>