<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">High Rollers Vest (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Veste de Flambeur (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">High-Roller-Weste (Weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Gilè dei Grandi Giocatori (Femmina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chaleco para Jugadores de Alto Calibre (Mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">High Rollers Vest (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our high rollers lounge is where the top casino gamers come to play. This High Rollers Vest  will provide you with unlimited access to the highest stakes tables in our High Rollers Lounge. You'll be able to earn some serious rewards, and chips fast! Prove you're one of the best without delay! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Notre salon des flambeurs est l'enroit où se réunissent les meilleurs joueurs du casino. Cette Veste de Flambeur vous garantira l'accès illimité aux tables aux mises les plus élevées dans notre Salon des Flambeurs. Vous pourrez accumuler très rapidement jetons et récompenses ! Prouvez que vous appartenez aux meilleurs sans plus attendre ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unsere high-roller-lounge ist der ort, an den die besten kasino-spieler kommen, um zu spielen. Diese High-Roller-Weste gibt Ihnen in unserer High-Roller-Lounge unbegrenzten zugang zu den tischen mit den höchsten einsätzen. Dies gibt Ihnen die möglichkeit, großartige preise und chips auf schnelle weise zu verdienen! Zögern sie nicht und beweisen sie, daß sie einer der besten sind! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La nostra sala per grandi giocatori è il luogo dove il top dei giocatori viene a giocare. Il nostro gilè per Grandi Giocatori vi consentirà l'accesso illimitato ai tavoli della Sala dei Grandi Giocatori, dove le puntate sono le più alte. Potrete guadagnarvi dei bei premi, e tante fiche, molto rapidamente! Dimostrate a tutti di essere uno dei migliori senza indugio!   [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nuestro salón para jugadores de alto calibre es el lugar donde los mejores jugadores del casino vienen a jugar. Este chaleco para jugadores de alto calibre te ofrecerá un acceso ilimitado a las mesas de las apuestas más altas en el salón para jugadores de alto calibre. ¡Podrás ganar premios importantes y fichas muy rápido! ¡Demuestra que eres uno de los mejores sin demora! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Female01_Torso_SheriffJacket [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Our high rollers lounge is where the top casino gamers come to play. This High Rollers Vest  will provide you with unlimited access to the highest stakes tables in our High Rollers Lounge. You'll be able to earn some serious rewards, and chips fast! Prove you're one of the best without delay! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>