<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Zeus Costume Bundle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack Zeus (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Zeus-Kostümpaket (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto costume da Zeus (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de Zeus (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">제우스 의상 세트 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Zeus Costume Bundle (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">宙斯服裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">宙斯服裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Zeus Costume Bundle (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take on the look of the Greek god of thunder and lightning, Zeus. Bundle includes helmet, top, bottom, sandals and a bolt in your hands. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Enfilez le costume de Zeus, dieu grec du tonnerre et de la foudre. Ce pack comprend un casque, un plastron, un pagne, des sandales et un éclair dans vos mains. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kleiden Sie sich wie der griechische Gott des Donners und des Blitzes, Zeus. Im Paket enthalten sind Helm, Ober- und Unterteil, Sandalen und ein Blitz für die Hände. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Assumi l'aspetto di Zeus, il dio greco dei tuoni e dei fulmini. Il pacchetto include elmo, corazza, drappo, sandali e saetta da tenere in mano. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Adopta el aspecto del dios griego del trueno y el relámpago, Zeus. El conjunto comprende casco, parte superior, parte inferior, calzado y un rayo en las manos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">그리스 번개의 신, 제우스의 모습이 되어 보십시오. 이 세트는 헬멧, 상의, 하의, 샌들, 그리고 손에 쥘 수 있는 번개를 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Take on the look of the Greek god of thunder, Zeus. Bundle includes helmet, top, bottom, sandals and a bolt in your hands. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">裝扮成希臘神話的雷神宙斯。本服裝組包括頭盔、上身、下身、涼鞋及手中的閃電。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">裝扮成希臘神話的雷神宙斯。本服裝組包括頭盔、上半身、下半身、涼鞋及手中的閃電。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Take on the look of the Greek god of thunder, Zeus. Bundle includes helmet, top, bottom, sandals and a bolt in your hands. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>