<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - All Day-Mix Sandals - Green (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Sandales All Day-Mix - Vert (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - All Day-Mix Sandalen - Grün (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - All Day-Mix Ciabatte - Verde (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - All Day-Mix Sandalias - Verde (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our All Day-Mix sandal features a variety of footbed art in pop prints and colours to help you individualize your style. Additional details include a wave logo molded outsole, and an arch cookie with a tapered heel wedge. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nos sandales All Day-Mix proposent un éventail de semelles artistiques dans des couleurs et des imprimés pop pour vous permettre de personnaliser votre style. Parmi les autres détails, on peut citer une semelle extérieure moulée en logo et une voûte plantaire compensée avec un talon compensé. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unsere All Day-Mix Sandalen sind in einer Reihe von verschiedenen Pop-Farben, Mustern und Fußbetten erhältlich, um Ihrem Stil die individuelle Note zu verleihen. Zu weiteren Details zählen das Billabong Wellenlogo auf der Sohle und die integrierte Senkfußeinlage mit abgeflachtem Absatzkeil. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le ciabatte All Day-Mix presentano una serie di disegni sulla pianta del piede in stampe e colori diversi per adattarsi al tuo stile. Tra i dettagli aggiuntivi vi sono la soletta esterna sagomata con logo dell'onda e un cuscinetto per l'arco plantare con zeppa sagomata sul tallone. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nuestra sandalia All Day-Mix presenta una variedad de estampados pop y de colores en las plantillas que ayudarán a personalizar tu estilo. Los detalles adicionales incluyen la suela moldeada, con el logotipo de la ola y arco de empeine con cuña ajustada. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Our All Day-Mix sandal features a variety of footbed art in pop prints and colors to help you individualize your style. Additional details include a wave logo molded outsole, and an arch cookie with a tapered heel wedge. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>