<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tumbleweed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tumbleweed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Steppenläufer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Rotolo di Cespuglio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Planta Rodadora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Tumbleweed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Tumbleweed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Tumbleweed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Tumbleweed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Tumbleweed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Tumbleweed</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You always know when a duel is about to begin when the tumbleweed blows across the road. The tumbleweed has been a key part to every western showdown ever. Make your presence known with this bad boy always available for your dueling pleasure. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tu peux toujours savoir qu'un duel se prépare quand, poussé par le vent, le tumbleweed traverse la route. Le tumbleweed est un élèment clé dans l'histoire du duel de western. Fais savoir que t'es là avec ce polisson toujours disponible pour ton pur plaisir de duelliste. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du weißt, daß das Duell beginnt, wenn der Steppenläufer über die Straße fegt. Der Steppenläufer ist ein Stilelement in jedem Western-Showdown. Dieses Accessoire kündigt stilsicher Dein Auftreten beim Duell an. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Saprai sempre quando un duello sta per iniziare quando il rotolo di cespuglio soffia attraverso la strada. Il rotolo di cespuglio è stato un componente chiave in ogni resa dei conti del west. Rendi nota la tua presenza con questo cattivo ragazzo sempre disponibile per il tuo piacere di duellare. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tu siempre sabes cuando un duelo está cerca de su comienzo cuando una Planta Rodadora cruza el camino. La Planta Rodadora es una parte clave en cualquier encuentro del viejo oeste. Haz sentir tu presencia a placer con ellas en cada duelo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Fast Draw Tumble Weed [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Fast Draw Tumble Weed [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Fast Draw Tumble Weed [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Fast Draw Tumble Weed [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Fast Draw Tumble Weed [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You always know when a duel is about to begin when the tumbleweed blows across the road. The tumbleweed has been a key part to every western showdown ever. Make your presence known with this bad boy always available for your dueling pleasure. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>