<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Sunset Ramble Pants - Off Black (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Pantalon Sunset Ramble - Noir mat (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Sunset Ramble Hose - Dunkelgrau (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Pantaloni Sunset Ramble - Nero slavato (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Sunset Ramble Pantalón - Negro apagado (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Lightweight and breezy beach pants bring an exotic look to your beach style with a tribal print. Designed with a smocked waistband and a rope drawcord that lets you adjust the rise and comfort. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce pantalon de plage léger et décontracté confère une touche d'exotisme à votre style plage avec son imprimé tribal. Conçu avec une ceinture smockée et un cordon de serrage qui vous permet d'ajuster sa taille et son confort. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese leichte weite Strandhose mit Folkloremuster sorgt für einen exotischen Look am Strand. Mit gesmoktem Bund und Tunnelzug für optimalen Sitz und höchsten Komfort. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pantaloni da spiaggia freschi e leggeri che danno un tocco esotico all'abbigliamento balneare grazie al motivo tribale. Hanno la cintura lavorata a nido d'ape e un cordoncino in vita per regolarne l'altezza e la comodità. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este pantalón playero, fresco y ligero, con un estampado tribal, le dará un toque exótico a tu estilo cuando vayas en modo "playa". Diseñado con una banda fruncida en la cintura y cordones ajustables para que decidas a qué altura llevarlo más cómodo. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>