<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S3L8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Aurora was invincible, Aurora was resolute...  and would remain thus for another 100 years.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aurora était invincible, Aurora était déterminée... et le resterait par conséquent pour le prochain siècle.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aurora war unbesiegbar, Aurora war entschlossen ... und blieb es für weitere 100 Jahre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aurora era invincibile, Aurora era decisa... e rimarrà tale per altri 100 anni.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aurora era invencible. Aurora era decidida… Y así permanecería durante otros 100 años.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラは無敵で断固たる存在価値を示し、100年後もその姿を変えることはない。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Aurora는 천하무적이며, Aurora는 단호하고... 다음 100년도 똑같이 존재할 것입니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Aurora was invincible, Aurora was resolute...  and would remain thus for another 100 years.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">極光是不可戰勝的、極光是堅定不移的…  並會在今後百年中保持如此。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">極光是不可戰勝的、極光是堅定不移的…  並會在今後百年中保持如此。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Aurora was invincible, Aurora was resolute...  and would remain thus for another 100 years.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S3L7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">So much for the ego. A thousand more foolhardy souls were to follow Sir Roger and all would meet the same humbling fate.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tu parles d'un égo. Mille âmes téméraires suivirent Sir Roger, et toutes connurent le même destin, avec la même humilité.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">So viel zum Thema Ego. Tausend weitere Narren folgten Sir Roger und erlitten das gleiche demütigende Schicksal.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tu parli di ego. Un migliaio di altre anime temerarie seguirono Sir Roger e tutte conobbero lo stesso umiliante destino.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Demasiado para su ego. Y a Sir Roger le siguieron más almas insensatas que acabarían encontrando la misma suerte humillante.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ロジャー卿の挑戦後も、我こそはと、数知れずの無謀なハンターたちが後を絶たなかった。そしてそのすべては同じ運命を辿った。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">대단한 자존심이군요. 수천 명의 무모한 영혼들이 로저 경을 따라갔으며 모두 똑같이 비참한 운명을 맞이했습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">So much for the ego. A thousand more foolhardy souls were to follow Sir Roger and all would meet the same humbling fate.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">有關自負的討論到此為止。一千個更有勇無謀的靈魂跟隨著羅傑爵士的腳步，而且所有人都遭遇同樣丟人的命運。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">有關自負的討論到此為止。一千個更有勇無謀的靈魂跟隨著羅傑爵士的腳步，而且所有人都遭遇同樣丟人的命運。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">So much for the ego. A thousand more foolhardy souls were to follow Sir Roger and all would meet the same humbling fate.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S3L6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Armed with a mighty harpoon and the hopes of a nation, Sir Roger climbed into the clouds of the Hindu Kush and was never heard from again.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Armé d'un puissant harpon et des espoirs d'une nation, Sir Roger escalada les nuages de l'Hindou Kouch et disparut à tout jamais.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit einer mächtigen Harpune bewaffnet und von den Hoffnungen einer ganzen Nation begleitet, kletterte Sir Roger in die Wolken des Hindukusch und ward nie mehr gesehen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Armato di un enorme arpione e delle speranze di una nazione, Sir Roger salì fino alle nuvole di Hindu Kush, ma non si seppe più nulla di lui.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Armado con un arpón poderoso y las esperanzas de una nación, Sir Roger subió a las nubes de Hindu Kush y nadie volvió a saber de él.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ロジャー卿は、巨大な銛で武装し国家の希望を背負って、ヒンドゥークシュ山を登りその雲の中へと消えていった。しかし彼が再び戻ってくることはなかった。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">강력한 작살과 국가의 희망으로 무장한 로저 경은 힌두 쿠시의 구름 위로 기어올라가 사라져버렸습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Armed with a mighty harpoon and the hopes of a nation, Sir Roger climbed into the clouds of the Hindu Kush and was never heard from again.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">手持一柄強力魚叉，帶著一個民族的期望，羅傑爵士攀登上雲霧繚繞的庫什山脈之巔，然後再無音訊。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">手持一柄強力魚叉，帶著一個民族的期望，羅傑爵士攀登上雲霧繚繞的庫什山脈之巔，然後再無音訊。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Armed with a mighty harpoon and the hopes of a nation, Sir Roger climbed into the clouds of the Hindu Kush and was never heard from again.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S3L5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">None were more wilful than the Queen’s man, Sir Roger de Monmouth, who declared he would intercept Aurora as it passed a high mountain range.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nul n'était plus obstiné que l'homme de la Reine, Sir Roger  de Monmouth, qui déclara qu'il intercepterait Aurora alors qu'elle survolait une chaîne de montagnes élevée.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Niemand war starrsinniger als der treueste Mann der Königin, Sir Roger de Monmouth, der erklärte, dass er Aurora abfangen würde, wenn sie eine hohe Bergkette passierte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nessuno fu più caparbio del marito della regina, Sir Roger de Monmouth, che dichiarò che avrebbe intercettato Aurora non appena fosse passata su una catena montuosa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nadie era más terco que el esposo de la Reina, Sir Roger de Monmouth, que declaró que invadiría Aurora cuando pasase cerca de una cadena montañosa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">女王の使いロジャー・デ・モンマス卿は、誰よりも意志が固く、高い山を通過するオーロラを攻撃すると宣言した。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">높은 산악 지대를 지나면서 Aurora를 가로채겠다고 선언했던 여왕의 남자인 로저 드 몬마우스 경보다 고집이 센 이는 없었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">None were more wilful than the Queen’s man, Sir Roger de Monmouth, who declared he would intercept Aurora as it passed a high mountain range.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">任何人都沒有女王的丈夫羅傑·萬茂爵士更任性，他宣佈將於極光經過山脈時攔截它。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">任何人都沒有女王的丈夫羅傑·萬茂爵士更任性，他宣佈將於極光經過山脈時攔截它。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">None were more wilful than the Queen’s man, Sir Roger de Monmouth, who declared he would intercept Aurora as it passed a high mountain range.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S3L4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Today these men have balloons and engines but once all they had was the will of man.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aujourd'hui ces hommes ont des ballons et des moteurs, mais il fut un temps où ils n'avaient que leur volonté.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Heute haben diese Männer, die einst nur eine feste Entschlossenheit besaßen, Ballons und Motoren.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Oggi questi uomini hanno mongolfiere e motori, ma una volta tutto ciò che avevano era la volontà umana.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estos hombres, que en su día solo tenían su propia voluntad, hoy tienen globos y motores.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">かつて、全てのハンターは彼が持つ強い意志だけで戦ったが、今ではバルーンとエンジンを備えている。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">오늘날 이들은 풍선과 엔진을 갖게 되었지만 한 때 이들이 가진 것은 의지 하나뿐이었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Today these men have balloons and engines but once all they had was the will of man.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">如今人們有熱氣球和發動機，但是以前只有意志。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">如今人們有熱氣球和發動機，但是以前只有意志。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Today these men have balloons and engines but once all they had was the will of man.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S3L3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Aurora was the mother of all undiscovered lands and fortune-hunters far and wide were moonstruck by the prospect of being the first to breach her shores.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aurora était la mère de toutes les terres inconnues, et les coureurs de dot de tous horizons étaient rêveurs à l'idée d'être les premiers à y accoster.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aurora war die Mutter aller Länder, die es noch zu entdecken galt, und Glücksritter von überall her waren begeistert von der Aussicht, die ersten zu sein, die ihre Küsten betraten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aurora era la madre di tutte le terre inesplorate e i cacciatori di fortuna di ogni parte erano stregati dall'idea di essere i primi a metter piede sulle sue coste.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aurora era la madre de todas las tierras por descubrir y los cazadores de destinos que llegaron de todos los lugares estaban chiflados por el prospecto de ser los primeros que invadan sus costas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラはあらゆる未知の場所をうみだす根源だった。世界中のフォーチューン ハンターが、最初にそこへ上陸することを夢見ていた。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Aurora는 모든 미개척지의 어머니이며 포춘 헌터들은 그 해안을 처음으로 범할 수 있다는 기대로 미쳐버렸습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Aurora was the mother of all undiscovered lands and fortune-hunters far and wide were moonstruck by the prospect of being the first to breach her shores.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">極光是所有未探索土地之母，天涯海角的尋寶獵人都瘋狂地想成為第一個踏上其岸的人。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">極光是所有未探索土地之母，天涯海角的尋寶獵人都瘋狂地想成為第一個踏上其岸的人。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Aurora was the mother of all undiscovered lands and fortune-hunters far and wide were moonstruck by the prospect of being the first to breach her shores.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S3L2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The North pole? The Earth’s core? These were naught by comparison!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le pôle Nord et le centre de la Terre ne sont rien à côté de ceci !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Nordpol? Der Erdkern? Im Vergleich dazu waren sie nichts.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il polo nord? Il centro della Terra? Questi erano nulla in paragone!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿El polo norte? ¿El centro de la Tierra? En comparación, no eran nada.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">北極点も地軸も、たいして役にたたない！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">북극이요? 지구의 중심? 이것들은 그와 비교하면 아무것도 아니에요!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The North pole? The Earth’s core? These were naught by comparison!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">北極？地心？相比之下，這些靈魂十分淘氣！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">北極？地心？相比之下，這些靈魂十分淘氣！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The North pole? The Earth’s core? These were naught by comparison!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S3L1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Aurora. Aurora! No sooner than it was discovered, Aurora infected the minds of man.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aurora. Aurora ! Sitôt découverte, Aurora a infecté l'esprit des hommes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aurora. Aurora! Kaum entdeckt, infizierte Aurora bereits die Gedanken der Menschen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aurora! Aurora! Non appena fu scoperta, Aurora pervase la mente degli uomini.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aurora. ¡Aurora! En cuanto fue descubierta, Aurora infectó el pensamiento del hombre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラ、オーロラ ! 発見するや否やオーロラは人間の心を感染させてしまった。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Aurora, Aurora! 그곳이 발견되면서, Aurora는 인간의 정신을 감염시켰습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Aurora. Aurora! No sooner than it was discovered, Aurora infected the minds of man.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">極光。極光！就在極光被發現的同時，極光就感染了人們的思維。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">極光。極光！就在極光被發現的同時，極光就感染了人們的思維。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Aurora. Aurora! No sooner than it was discovered, Aurora infected the minds of man.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MENU_ITEM_3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Fortune Hunters</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les coureurs de dot</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Glücksritter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I Cacciatori della fortuna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los cazadores del destino</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">フォーチューン ハンター</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">포춘 헌터</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Fortune Hunters</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">財富獵人</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">財富獵人</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Fortune Hunters</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S2L9</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A colossus, we ask?\n"Why not? Why not. All you have to do is believe."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un colosse ? \n"Pourquoi pas ? Pourquoi pas. Il n'y a qu'à demander."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Ein Koloss?", fragen wir.\n"Warum nicht? Warum nicht. Du musst nur daran glauben."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un colosso, chiedemmo?\n"Perché no? Perché no. Bisogna soltanto credere."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Un coloso? \n“¿Por qué no? ¿Eh? Solo hay que creerlo”.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コロッサス、ですか？\n"いえいえ、いいじゃないですか。要は信じることですよ。"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">거인이라고요?\n"안 될 것 없죠. 안 될 것 없어요. 믿기만 하면 됩니다."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A colossus, we ask?\n"Why not? Why not. All you have to do is believe."</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">我們問道，巨人？\n「為什麼不？為什麼不。你所需要的就是相信。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">我們問道，巨人？\n「為什麼不？為什麼不。你所需要的就是相信。」</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A colossus, we ask?\n"Why not? Why not. All you have to do is believe."</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S2L8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The fishermen believe there are creatures out there that would turn your hair white. And all you have to do to catch them is have nerve enough and know where and when to look.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les pêcheurs croient en l'existence de créatures  là-bas qui vous glaceraient jusqu'au sang. Et pour les attraper, il n'y a qu'à prendre son courage à deux mains, et savoir où et quand chercher.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Fischer glauben, dass es Kreaturen gibt, bei deren Anblick deine Haare weiß werden. Und um sie zu fangen, musst du nur genug Mut haben und wissen, wo und wann du sie suchen musst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I pescatori credono che ci siano creature che farebbero venire i capelli bianchi. E tutto ciò che bisogna fare per acchiapparle è restare calmi e sapere quando e dove guardare.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los pescadores creen que hay criaturas por ahí que te congelarían la sangre. Todo lo que hay que hacer para atraparlos es tener valor y saber dónde buscar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">またフィッシャーの間には、こちらの髪の毛を白くしてしまう生き物がいるという言い伝えがあります。言い伝えによれば、捕まえるには度胸がいるのはもちろん、現れる時と場所も知らなければならないそうです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">낚시꾼들은 당신의 머리카락을 하얗게 만들어 버릴 생물체가 존재한다고 믿습니다. 그들을 잡기 위해 필요한 것은 용기와 언제 어디를 봐야 할지 아는 것입니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The fishermen believe there are creatures out there that would turn your hair white. And all you have to do to catch them is have nerve enough and know where and when to look.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">釣魚者相信有會讓你的頭髮變白的生物存在。要釣到這些生物，你需要足夠的敏覺，並知道何時會有收穫。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">釣魚者相信有會讓你的頭髮變白的生物存在。要釣到這些生物，你需要足夠的敏覺，並知道何時會有收穫。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The fishermen believe there are creatures out there that would turn your hair white. And all you have to do to catch them is have nerve enough and know where and when to look.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S2L7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The fishermen believe these creatures – one hundred leagues from the nearest ocean - are enticed here by mighty vortices created by Aurora's strange electricity.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les pêcheurs pensent que ces créatures - à cent lieues de l'océan le plus proche - sont attirées ici par d'énormes vortex créés par l'électricité étrange d'Aurora.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Fischer glauben, dass diese Wesen - 100 Meilen vom nächsten Ozean entfernt - von mächtigen Strudeln angezogen werden, die von Auroras seltsamer Elektrizität erzeugt werden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I pescatori credono che queste creature (cento leghe dall'oceano più vicino) sono attirate qui da potenti vortici creati dalla strana elettricità di Aurora.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los pescadores creen que estas criaturas, que se encuentran a más de 100 leguas del océano más cercano, llegan hasta aquí atraídas por poderosos vórtices creados por la atípica electricidad de Aurora.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">フィッシャーたちは、あれらの生き物はオーロラ の謎の電気が生み出した全能の渦が連れてきたのだと信じています。もちろん、海と百里も離れていることを承知した上で。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">낚시꾼들은 이들 생물체들이 - 가장 가까운 바다로부터 100 리그 거리 - Aurora의 수상한 전기로 생성된 강력한 볼텍스로 인해 이곳으로 유인되어 왔다고 믿고 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The fishermen believe these creatures – one hundred leagues from the nearest ocean - are enticed here by mighty vortices created by Aurora's strange electricity.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">釣魚者相信這些生物（來自近千公里以外最近的海）被極光群島的怪異電流所產生的強大旋渦吸引至此。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">釣魚者相信這些生物（來自近千公里以外最近的海）被極光群島的怪異電流所產生的強大旋渦吸引至此。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The fishermen believe these creatures – one hundred leagues from the nearest ocean - are enticed here by mighty vortices created by Aurora's strange electricity.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S2L6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Recently it has become something of a sport here on Aurora to cast fishing lines and attempt to catch these odd sea creatures.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C'est devenu comme une sorte de mode ici sur Aurora, de jeter ses lignes de pêche en espérant attraper l'une de ces étranges créatures aquatiques.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In letzter Zeit ist es hier auf Aurora zu einem Sport geworden, die Angelruten auszuwerfen und zu versuchen, diese seltsamen Meereswesen zu fangen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Di recente, qui su Aurora è diventato quasi uno sport gettare lenze e tentare di pescare queste strane creature marine.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hace poco se ha puesto de moda en Aurora intentar pescar esas criaturas marinas tan extrañas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラ  では近年、これらの不思議な生き物を捕らえる行為はスポーツとして捉えられています。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">최근 Aurora에서는 낚시줄을 던져 이 이상한 해양 생물체를 잡는 것이 유행이 되었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Recently it has become something of a sport here on Aurora to cast fishing lines and attempt to catch these odd sea creatures.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">近來，拋魚線已成為極光群島上嘗試釣到那些古怪海洋生物的一項體育運動。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">近來，拋魚線已成為極光群島上嘗試釣到那些古怪海洋生物的一項體育運動。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Recently it has become something of a sport here on Aurora to cast fishing lines and attempt to catch these odd sea creatures.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S2L5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">But with the discovery of Aurora the yoke was broken, our minds freed!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mais avec la découverte d'Aurora, le joug fut brisé, et nos esprits libérés !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Doch mit der Entdeckung von Aurora wurde das Joch gebrochen, wurde unser Geist befreit!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ma con la scoperta di Aurora s'interruppe la schiavitù e le nostre menti furono libere!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pero el descubrimiento de Aurora truncó esa esclavitud. ¡Nuestras mentes eran libres!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">しかし オーロラ の発見によりくびきは解かれ、我らの精神は解き放たれたのです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">하지만 Aurora의 발견으로 멍에는 부숴졌고, 우리의 정신은 자유로워졌습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">But with the discovery of Aurora the yoke was broken, our minds freed!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">但是，極光群島的發現打破了枷鎖，解放了我們的思想！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">但是，極光群島的發現打破了枷鎖，解放了我們的思想！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">But with the discovery of Aurora the yoke was broken, our minds freed!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S2L4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">For many years we were pinned by gravity to the earth, our minds trapped in the yoke of the toil.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Durant des années, nous fûmes cloués au sol par la gravité, nos esprits prisonniers du joug du labeur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Viele Jahre lang hatte die Schwerkraft uns auf den Boden gezwungen, steckte unser Geist im Joch der Schufterei fest.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per molti anni siamo stati bloccati sulla terra dalla gravità, con le menti intrappolate nella schiavitù della fatica.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Durante muchos años nos quedamos atrapados a la tierra por la gravedad, con nuestras mentes atrapadas por la esclavitud del trabajo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">重力の手に掴まれ、我らは、その精神と共に長い間大地に縛り付けられてきました。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">오랫동안 우리는 중력으로 인해 지구에 묶여 있었고, 우리의 정신은 노역의 멍에에 갇혀 있었습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">For many years we were pinned by gravity to the earth, our minds trapped in the yoke of the toil.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">許多年來，我們一直被重力壓在地球上，我們的思想受到土地枷鎖的束縛。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">許多年來，我們一直被重力壓在地球上，我們的思想受到土地枷鎖的束縛。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">For many years we were pinned by gravity to the earth, our minds trapped in the yoke of the toil.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S2L3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">And what creatures swam in this aether?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Et quelles créatures nageaient dans cet masse étherique ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Und was für Kreaturen schwammen in diesem Äther?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">E quali creature nuotavano in quest'etere?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Qué criaturas vagaban por este éter?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この空を悠然と泳ぐ生物とは一体？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">그리고 이 창공에는 어떤 생물체들이 헤엄치고 있는가?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">And what creatures swam in this aether?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">那麼哪些動物在眾神呼吸的空氣中游泳？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">那麼哪些動物在眾神呼吸的空氣中游泳？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">And what creatures swam in this aether?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S2L2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Was space the rarefied air breathed by the gods?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'espace était-il fait d'air raréfié respiré par les Dieux ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Besteht er aus der Luft, die den Göttern zum Atmen vorbehalten war?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lo spazio era l'aria rarefatta respirata dagli dei?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Fue el espacio el aire enrarecido que respiraban los dioses?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">空気が薄いのは、神が呼吸をしたからでしょうか？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">우주는 신이 숨쉬는 정화된 공기인가?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Was space the rarefied air breathed by the gods?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">天空是眾神呼吸的稀薄空氣嗎？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">天空是眾神呼吸的稀薄空氣嗎？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Was space the rarefied air breathed by the gods?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S2L1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">What is space? This has been a question firmly on man's mind since the first moment he looked skyward.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Qu'est-ce que l'espace ? Cette question obsède l'homme depuis qu'il a levé les yeux vers le ciel la première fois.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Was ist der Weltraum? Diese Frage beschäftigt die Menschheit, seit der erste Mensch seine Augen gen Himmel richtete.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cos'è lo spazio? È una domanda costante nella mente dell'uomo dal primo momento in cui ha osservato il cielo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Qué es el espacio? La pregunta que se ha hecho siempre la humanidad desde el primer momento en que miraron al cielo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">空とは何なのか？それは最初の人類が空を見上げた瞬間から抱き続けてきた疑問です。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">우주란 무엇인가? 이 질문은 인간이 처음 하늘을 바라본 순간부터 계속되어 왔습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">What is space? This has been a question firmly on man's mind since the first moment he looked skyward.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">天空是什麼？從第一刻仰望天空以來，人類的心中就有這個揮之不去的問題。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">天空是什麼？從第一刻仰望天空以來，人類的心中就有這個揮之不去的問題。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">What is space? This has been a question firmly on man's mind since the first moment he looked skyward.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S1L8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Aurora was once a myth. Now it is a reality its fate lies in our hands. So mind this place, the Teller of Tales. Return here once in a while and let us find strength through knowledge!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aurora était autrefois une légende. À présent, son sort est réellement entre nos mains. Alors n'oublie pas cet endroit, le raconteur. Reviens donc ici de temps en temps et enrichis nous !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aurora war einst ein Mythos. Jetzt ist es Wirklichkeit, sein Schicksal liegt in unseren Händen. Besuche also manchmal diesen Ort, den Geschichtenerzähler. Lass uns hier Stärke durch Wissen finden!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un tempo Aurora fu un mito. Ora è realtà e il suo destino giace nelle nostre mani. Stai attento a questo luogo: il Cantastorie. Tornaci di tanto in tanto e trova la forza attraverso la conoscenza.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hubo un tiempo en que Aurora fue un mito. Ahora, es una realidad cuyo destino yace en nuestras manos. Estad atentos a este lugar: el Cuentacuentos. Volved de vez en cuando y encontrad la fuerza gracias al conocimiento.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">かつて オーロラ は神話でした。しかし今やそれは現実として、我々に運命を委ねています。語り部は時折この場所にやって来ますから、覚えておいてください。語られる物語は、きっと我らに勇気と力を与えてくれるはずです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Aurora는 한 때 신화였습니다. 그 운명이 우리의 손 안에 있는 현실입니다. 그러니 이 곳을 조심하십시오, 텔러 오브 테일즈. 가끔 한 번씩 이곳에 돌아와서 지식을 통해 힘을 찾읍시다!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Aurora was once a myth. Now it is a reality its fate lies in our hands. So mind this place, the Teller of Tales. Return here once in a while and let us find strength through knowledge!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">極光群島曾經是個謎。現在卻已成為一個現實，並且其命運掌握在我們的手中。因此請留意這個地方，故事講堂。不時地回來看看，讓我們用知識創造力量！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">極光群島曾經是個謎。現在卻已成為一個現實，並且其命運掌握在我們的手中。因此請留意這個地方，故事講堂。不時地回來看看，讓我們用知識創造力量！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Aurora was once a myth. Now it is a reality its fate lies in our hands. So mind this place, the Teller of Tales. Return here once in a while and let us find strength through knowledge!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S1L7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">We will tell you of the great clamour to claim Aurora, the lives it ruined and the bizarre circumstances of how it came to be conquered.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nous vous raconterons l'immense quête d'Aurora, les vies qui furent brisées et les circonstances étranges entourant sa conquête.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wir werden dir von dem großen Streit um Aurora erzählen, von den Leben, die er ruinierte und die bizarren Umstände, unter denen es erobert wurde.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Racconteremo della grande protesta per riscattare Aurora, delle vite rovinate e delle strane circostanze con le quali fu conquistata.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Relataremos sobre el gran clamor por rescatar a Aurora, las vidas que arruinó y las circunstancias estrafalarias de su conquista.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラ にこだまする声、失われた命たち、そして征服されるに至った顛末などが語られていきます。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">우리는 Aurora를 요구하는 엄청나게 큰 소리, 그것이 파괴한 생명들, 그리고 그것이 어떻게 정복되었는지에 대한 기이한 상황들에 대해 얘기하겠습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">We will tell you of the great clamour to claim Aurora, the lives it ruined and the bizarre circumstances of how it came to be conquered.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">我們將告訴你那些在極光群島滯留的過去聲音、被奪走的生命，以及被征服時的經過。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">我們將告訴你那些在極光群島滯留的過去聲音、被奪走的生命，以及被征服時的經過。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">We will tell you of the great clamour to claim Aurora, the lives it ruined and the bizarre circumstances of how it came to be conquered.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S1L6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">What we have learnt of the mysterious technologies found without and its dark secrets hidden within...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nous avons appris bien des choses des technologies découvertes à l'extérieur, et des secrets cachés à l'intérieur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Was wir von den rätselhaften Technologien von draußen und den dunklen Geheimnissen hier erfahren haben ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cosa abbiamo imparato delle misteriose tecnologie scoperte all'esterno e dei misteriosi segreti nascosti all'interno...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hemos aprendido mucho de las tecnologías descubiertas fuera y los secretos escondidos dentro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ここで発見された謎のテクノロジー、その内に込められた暗き秘密の数々...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">우리가 알아낸 것은 신비의 기술은 밖에서 발견되었고 어두운 비밀은 안에 감춰져 있다는 것입니다...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">What we have learnt of the mysterious technologies found without and its dark secrets hidden within...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">我們已經學到了神秘科技以及其黑暗的秘密...。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">我們已經學到了神秘科技以及其黑暗的秘密...。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">What we have learnt of the mysterious technologies found without and its dark secrets hidden within...</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S1L5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Therefore we have built this Teller of Tales. Here we will pass on to you all we have learnt of Aurora these past months...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nous avons par conséquent mis au point ce raconteur. Nous allons vous transmettre tout ce que nous avons appris d'Aurora ces derniers mois…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Deswegen haben wir diesen Geschichtenerzähler gebaut. Hier werden wir dir alles übermitteln, was wir in den letzten Monaten über Aurora gelernt haben ...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Perciò abbiamo costruito questo Cantastorie, dove potremo trasmetterti tutto ciò che abbiamo imparato su Aurora in questi mesi...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Y es por eso que hemos construido este Cuentacuentos, para que os cuente lo que hemos aprendido de Aurora en los últimos meses…</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">と、これが語り部を作った理由です。この中には、過去数ヶ月で オーロラ について分かったことを全部まとめておきました。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">그런 이유로 우리는 이 텔러 오브 테일즈를 만들었습니다. 이제 지난 몇 달 간 우리가 Aurora에 대해 알게 된 모든 것을 당신에게 전달할 것입니다...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Therefore we have built this Teller of Tales. Here we will pass on to you all we have learnt of Aurora these past months...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">因此，我們建造了這個故事講堂。在這裡，我們會將過去數個月內聽到的極光群島相關知識傳授給你...。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">因此，我們建造了這個故事講堂。在這裡，我們會將過去數個月內聽到的極光群島相關知識傳授給你...。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Therefore we have built this Teller of Tales. Here we will pass on to you all we have learnt of Aurora these past months...</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S1L4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Enchanting as it may be, it burdens us with a strange sense of foreboding. If we are to comprehend Aurora's fate - our fate - the better we should know its past.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aussi agréable que cela puisse paraître, nous ne pouvons réprimer un étrange sentiment de malédiction. Si nous devons comprendre la destinée d'Aurora - notre destinée - nous devons d'abord comprendre son passé.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es ist zwar sehr betörend, erweckt in uns aber auch das seltsame Gefühl einer Vorahnung. Wenn wir Auroras Schicksal verstehen wollen (und damit auch unseres), müssen wir mehr über seine Vergangenheit lernen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Incantevole com'è, ci affligge con uno strano senso di inquietudine. Per comprendere il destino di Aurora, il nostro destino, dovremmo conoscere meglio il suo passato.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Por muy encantador que nos pueda parecer, nos ata con una extraña sensación de aprensión. Si hemos de comprender el destino de Aurora, nuestro destino, mejor que empecemos por conocer el pasado.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">確かにここは魅力的かもしれません。でもそれと同じように、何か不吉な予感も漂っているのです。オーロラ の – あるいは私たちの – 運命を理解するには、その過去を知らねばならないでしょう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">매혹적이기도 하지만, 불길한 느낌으로 부담을 주기도 합니다. Aurora의 운명 - 우리의 운명 - 을 이해하고자 한다면, 그 과거를 먼저 알아야 합니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Enchanting as it may be, it burdens us with a strange sense of foreboding. If we are to comprehend Aurora's fate - our fate - the better we should know its past.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">儘管極光群島如此迷人，但是它讓我們擔負著一種不祥的預感。若我們要理解極光群島命運、自己的命運，那麼我們最好知道它的過去。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">儘管極光群島如此迷人，但是它讓我們擔負著一種不祥的預感。若我們要理解極光群島命運、自己的命運，那麼我們最好知道它的過去。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Enchanting as it may be, it burdens us with a strange sense of foreboding. If we are to comprehend Aurora's fate - our fate - the better we should know its past.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S1L3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">But much about Aurora remains unknown to us. Where did it come from? What is its purpose?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mais une large partie d'Aurora nous est toujours inconnue. D'où vient-elle ? À quoi sert-elle ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aber vieles über Aurora ist uns noch ein Rätsel. Woher kommt es? Was ist sein Zweck?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ma tante cose di Aurora restano sconosciute. Da dove arriva? Qual è il suo scopo?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pero aún desconocemos mucho sobre Aurora. ¿De dónde viene? ¿Adónde va?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">でも オーロラ にはまだ謎がたくさん残っています。どのようにしてできたのか？その目的とは？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">하지만 Aurora의 많은 부분은 알려지지 않았습니다. 어디서 왔을까? 그 목적은 무엇일까?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">But much about Aurora remains unknown to us. Where did it come from? What is its purpose?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">但是 極光群島還有許多未解開的謎。它從哪裡來？有何目的？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">但是 極光群島還有許多未解開的謎。它從哪裡來？有何目的？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">But much about Aurora remains unknown to us. Where did it come from? What is its purpose?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S1L2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Yes, it's fun chatting to friends and running after orbs - go get 'em!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En effet, il est très amusant de discuter entre amis et de pourchasser des orbes - attrapez-les !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ja, es macht Spaß, mit Freunden zu chatten und Orbs hinterherzujagen. Los!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sì, è divertente chiacchierare con gli amici e correre dietro alle sfere... acchiappale!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Es divertido charlar con amigos mientras acechas Orbs. ¡A por ellos!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">友達とのチャットで盛り上がるのもいいですし、オーブを捕まえるのも楽しいものです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">네, 친구들과 얘기하고 오브를 찾으러 다니는 것은 재미있습니다 - 가서 찾으세요!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Yes, it's fun chatting to friends and running after orbs - go get 'em!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">確實，與好友交談以及搜尋能量球都有很多樂趣，大家一起來玩吧！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">確實，與好友交談以及搜尋能量球都有很多樂趣，大家一起來玩吧！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Yes, it's fun chatting to friends and running after orbs - go get 'em!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S1L1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Aurora – Jewel of the sky, playground of the enlightened!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Aurora - joyau du ciel, cour de récréation des illuminés !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aurora: Juwel des Himmels, Spielplatz der Erleuchteten!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aurora: gioello del cielo, divertimento per gli eletti!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aurora: la joya del cielo, ¡juego de los iluminados.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラ – それは空の宝石、極めし者たちの遊技場</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Aurora - 하늘의 보석, 깨우친 자들의 놀이터!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Aurora – Jewel of the sky, playground of the enlightened!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">極光群島 – 天空的寶石，智者的遊樂場！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">極光群島 – 天空的寶石，智者的遊樂場！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Aurora – Jewel of the sky, playground of the enlightened!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">PRESSX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyer sur [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücke [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premi [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulsa [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[ACCEPT] を押してください</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[ACCEPT]을 누르십시오</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Press [ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">按下[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">按下[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Press [ACCEPT]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MENU_HELP</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[UP][DOWN] Choose Tale, [ACCEPT] Select</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[UP][DOWN] Choisir le récit, [ACCEPT] sélectionner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[UP][DOWN] Geschichte aussuchen, [ACCEPT] Auswählen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[UP][DOWN] Scegli storia, [ACCEPT] Seleziona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[UP][DOWN] Elegir cuento; [ACCEPT] Seleccionar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[UP][DOWN] 物語を選択 [ACCEPT] 決定</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[UP][DOWN] 이야기 선택, [ACCEPT] 선택하기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[UP][DOWN] Choose Tale, [ACCEPT] Select</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[UP][DOWN]選擇故事，[ACCEPT]決定</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[UP][DOWN]選擇故事，[ACCEPT]決定</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[UP][DOWN] Choose Tale, [ACCEPT] Select</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MENU_ITEM_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Deep Sky Fishing</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pêche en haut ciel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Deep Sky Fishing</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pesca nel profondo del cielo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pesca de altura espacial</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ディープスカイフィッシング</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">딥 스카이 피싱</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Deep Sky Fishing</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">深空釣魚</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">深空釣魚</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Deep Sky Fishing</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MENU_ITEM_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Concerning Aurora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Concernant Aurora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über Aurora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Riguardo Aurora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sobre Aurora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラ について</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Aurora에 관하여</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Concerning Aurora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">關於極光群島</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">關於極光群島</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Concerning Aurora</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MENU_TITLE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">TELLER OF TALES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">RACONTEUR</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Geschichtenerzähler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">CANTASTORIE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">CUENTACUENTOS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">語り部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">텔러 오브 테일즈</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">TELLER OF TALES</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">故事講堂</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">故事講堂</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">TELLER OF TALES</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A place for stories [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Où les récits se racontent [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Ort für Geschichten [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un luogo da racconto [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Donde se cuentan las historias [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">物語が紡がれる場所 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이야기의 공간 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A place for stories [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">一個聽故事的地方[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">一個聽故事的地方[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A place for stories [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="Description">Do not translate content in Square brackets. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Teller of Tales</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Raconteur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Geschichtenerzähler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cantastorie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuentacuentos</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">語り部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">텔러 오브 테일즈</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Teller of Tales</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">故事講堂</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">故事講堂</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Teller of Tales</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">MENU_ITEM_4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Isles of Mystery</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les îles du mystère</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Inseln der Geheimnisse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le isole del mistero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las Islas del Misterio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ミステリー アイルズ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">신비의 섬</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Isles of Mystery</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">神秘島</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">神秘島</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Isles of Mystery</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S4L1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Islands that floated? Alchemistic emanations? No sooner had man stepped upon Aurora than he knew he was in a realm beyond. These were not technologies of man, these were the play things of the gods!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Des îles flottantes ? Des émanations alchimiques ? Une fois arrivé sur Aurora, les hommes savaient qu’ils se trouvaient dans un royaume dépassant toute imagination. Ces technologies n’étaient pas créées par l’homme, mais étaient bel et bien les joujoux des dieux !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Inseln, die schwebten? Alchemische Ausstrahlungen? Sobald die Menschheit Aurora entdeckt hatte, wusste sie, dass dies eine übernatürliche Welt ist. Dies waren nicht die Technologien der Menschen, sondern die die Spieldinge der Götter!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Isole che galleggiavano? Emanazioni alchemiche? Non appena l'uomo mise piede su Aurora capì di essere in un regno dell'aldilà. Queste non erano tecnologie umane, ma scherzi degli dei!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Islas flotantes? ¿Emanaciones alquímicas? En cuanto el hombre puso un pie en Aurora, supo que allí se encontraba otro reino. No eran tecnologías propias para el hombre, sino juguetes para los dioses.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">空中に浮かぶ島々...錬金術...オーロラに降り立つ者たちは、皆「未知の土地」へ来たことを肌で感じます。人知を超えたもの、神々のなせる技...。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">떠 있는 섬? 연금술의 발산? 인간이 Aurora에 첫 발을 내딛는 순간, 그들은 자신이 완전히 다른 세상에 있음을 깨닫게 됩니다. 이것은 인간의 기술이 아니라, 신의 장난감입니다!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Islands that floated? Alchemistic emanations? No sooner had man stepped upon Aurora than he knew he was in a realm beyond. These were not technologies of man, these were the play things of the gods!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">浮動的島嶼？煉金術化身？一旦進入極光群島，玩家將會發現走進了超出控制的領域。這些絕非人類的技術，而是神之玩物。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">浮動的島嶼？煉金術化身？一旦進入極光群島，玩家將會發現走進了超出控制的領域。這些絕非人類的技術，而是神之玩物。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Islands that floated? Alchemistic emanations? No sooner had man stepped upon Aurora than he knew he was in a realm beyond. These were not technologies of man, these were the play things of the gods!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S4L2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A tree that fed on energy drawn through our very bodies? A teleporting device that transported one instantaneously without molecule or mind being scrambled to broth? These were no mere inventions, these were dreams invocated.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un arbre puisant l’énergie de nos corps et s’en nourrissant ? Un appareil de téléportation pouvant transporter quelqu’un sans réduire en bouillie les molécules et l’esprit ? Il ne s’agissait plus d’inventions, mais de rêves devenus réalité.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Baum, der sich von Energie ernährt, die durch unsere Körper fließt? Eine teleportierende Vorrichtung, die einen unverzüglich transportiert, ohne Molekülen oder Gehirnen zu schaden? Dies waren nicht nur Erfindungen, es waren wahr gewordene Träume.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un albero che assorbe energia dai nostri corpi? Un dispositivo di teletrasporto che ha istantaneamente teletrasportato qualcuno senza polverizzarlo? Queste non erano invenzioni, ma sogni diventati realtà.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un árbol que se alimentaba de energía desprendida de nuestros cuerpos, un dispositivo de teletransporte que le llevaba a uno de forma instantánea sin que las moléculas o la mente acaben convirtiéndose en sopa... No eran simples invenciones; eran sueños invocados.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">人間の肉体からエネルギーを吸い出す木、分子も利用せず心身にも影響を及ぼさないまま一瞬でテレポートさせる機器、これらはもはや発明ではありません。具現化した夢そのものなのです。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">우리의 몸에서 가져간 에너지를 섭취한 나무? 분자 또는 정신 하나도 뒤범벅이 되지 않고 순식간에 순간이동을 시키는 순간이동 장치? 이것은 단순한 발명품이 아니라, 꿈의 실현입니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A tree that fed on energy drawn through our very bodies? A teleporting device that transported one instantaneously without molecule or mind being scrambled to broth? These were no mere inventions, these were dreams invocated.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">靠從我們體內吸收能量生長的樹木？將人瞬時轉移為肉湯而不會擾亂分子和思維的心靈傳輸裝置？這些不只是發明，它們更是激發的夢想。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">靠從我們體內吸收能量生長的樹木？將人瞬時轉移為肉湯而不會擾亂分子和思維的心靈傳輸裝置？這些不只是發明，它們更是激發的夢想。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A tree that fed on energy drawn through our very bodies? A teleporting device that transported one instantaneously without molecule or mind being scrambled to broth? These were no mere inventions, these were dreams invocated.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S4L3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">And might Aurora's greatest treasure have been denied us? Rumour has it the Illuminati beat us here and removed some devices for their own nefarious needs. Poppycock? So what then is the origin of these indentations?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Et le plus grand trésor d’Aurora nous a-t-il été dérobé ? La rumeur dit que les Illuminati sont arrivés ici avant nous et ont saisi des appareils pour satisfaire leurs vils desseins. Balivernes ? Alors d’où viennent ces marques ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Und wurde uns der größte Schatz von Aurora verweigert? Es geht das Gerücht um, dass die Illuminati vor uns hier waren und einige Geräte für ihre eigenen ruchlosen Bedürfnisse entfernt haben. Unsinn? Woher kommen dann diese Abdrücke?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">E se il più grande tesoro di Aurora ci fosse stato tenuto nascosto? Delle voci dicono che gli Illuminati ci hanno battuto e rimosso alcuni dispositivi per i loro scopi criminali. Fesserie? Allora, come sono nate queste insenature?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Y por qué se nos han negado los mayores tesoros de Aurora? Cuenta la leyenda que los Iluminados nos vencieron y se quedaron con algunos dispositivos para sus propias necesidades. ¿Una locura? ¿Cuál es el origen de estas hendiduras?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">私たちはオーロラ最高の宝に拒まれたのでしょうか? 噂では「イルミナティ」は我々を出しぬいて一部の機器を取り去ったと言われています。信用するかしないかはアナタ次第ですが、この刻み目はそうでないと説明がつきませんね...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">그리고 Aurora 최고의 보물을 우리는 아직 보지 못한것이 사실일까요? 소문에 따르면 광명파가 우리보다 일찍 이 곳을 발견하고 그들의 사악한 욕심을 위해 일부 장치를 가지고 갔다고 합니다. 말도 안 되는 소리라고요? 그럼 이 자국의 근원은 무엇일까요?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">And might Aurora's greatest treasure have been denied us? Rumour has it the Illuminati beat us here and removed some devices for their own nefarious needs. Poppycock? So what then is the origin of these indentations?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">極光群島的豐富寶藏是否會將我們拒之門外？據說，光明幫將在此打敗我們，取走一些設備，以用於他們自己的邪惡目的。胡說？那麼這些痕跡的起源是什麽？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">極光群島的豐富寶藏是否會將我們拒之門外？據說，光明幫將在此打敗我們，取走一些設備，以用於他們自己的邪惡目的。胡說？那麼這些痕跡的起源是什麽？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">And might Aurora's greatest treasure have been denied us? Rumour has it the Illuminati beat us here and removed some devices for their own nefarious needs. Poppycock? So what then is the origin of these indentations?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S4L4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">And who or what removed them before we arrived?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Et qui ou qu'est-ce qui les a pris avant que nous n'arrivions ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Und wer oder was hat sie entfernt, bevor wir angekommen sind?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">E chi o cosa hanno rimosso prima del nostro arrivo?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Y quién o qué las retiró antes de que llegásemos?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">私たちの到着前に誰が、何を持ち出したのでしょう...?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">그리고 우리가 도착하기 전에 누가 또는 무엇이 그것들을 제거했을까요?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">And who or what removed them before we arrived?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">那麼是誰或什麽物體在我們到達之前取走了這些設備？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">那麼是誰或什麽物體在我們到達之前取走了這些設備？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">And who or what removed them before we arrived?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S4L5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">On Aurora one is never far from mystery.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sur Aurora, le mystère n'est jamais loin.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Auf Aurora ist man nie weit von Geheimnissen entfernt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Su Aurora il mistero è sempre dietro l'angolo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">En Aurora todo es misterioso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラの謎は尽きることがありません。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Aurora에서는 모두가 미스테리에 연루되어 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">On Aurora one is never far from mystery.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在極光群島，您始終包裹在神秘之中。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在極光群島，您始終包裹在神秘之中。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">On Aurora one is never far from mystery.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S4L6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A sea monster, frozen by a glimpse of the Gorgon perhaps?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Peut-être un monstre maritime, paralysé après avoir aperçu le Gorgon ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Seeungeheuer, das vielleicht beim Anblick des Gorgon erstarrte?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un mostro marino, forse congelato da un'occhiata di Gorgone?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Un monstruo marino, tal vez congelado por la mirada del Gorgon?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴーゴンにひとにらみされた水棲モンスターでしょうか?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">고르곤의 일견으로 인해 얼어붙은 바다 괴물?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A sea monster, frozen by a glimpse of the Gorgon perhaps?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">或許，還有一見到蛇髮女怪立即石化的海怪？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">或許，還有一見到蛇髮女怪立即石化的海怪？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A sea monster, frozen by a glimpse of the Gorgon perhaps?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S4L7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Floating machines of industry.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Machines industrielles volantes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schwebende Industriemaschinen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Macchinari industriali galleggianti.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Las máquinas industriales flotantes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">電話ボックスと業務用浮遊機器</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">전화 박스와 떠다니는 산업 기계들.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Floating machines of industry.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">電話室和浮動機器。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">電話室和浮動機器。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Floating machines of industry.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S4L8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Are we being toyed with or is their purpose yet to be uncovered?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Est-ce qu'ils jouent avec nous, ou leur but est-il toujours secret ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wird mit uns gespielt oder wird ihr Zweck noch gefunden werden?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ci stanno prendendo in giro o la loro intenzione è ancora ignota?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Están jugando con nosotros o aún no han revelado su auténtico propósito?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このまま振り回されるのか、狙いを解き明かすか － 今はまだ分かりません。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">우리는 놀이감이 되는 것일까요 아니면 아직 밝혀지지 않은 목적이 있는 것일까요?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Are we being toyed with or is their purpose yet to be uncovered?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">是我們被人耍弄還是我們尚未知曉他們的目的？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">是我們被人耍弄還是我們尚未知曉他們的目的？</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Are we being toyed with or is their purpose yet to be uncovered?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S4L9</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Even the aether that surrounds Aurora is a broth of mystery and wonder. Aurorans, ever inventive, are now discovering ways of trapping these curios. What rare and priceless things they will find? We are yet to see! All we can be sure of is Aurora remains stubbornly a riddle, wrapped in a mystery, inside an enigma.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Même l’éther entourant Aurora est une énigme teintée de mystère. Les Auroriens, toujours inventifs, ont découvert des moyens de capturer ces bibelots. Quelles trouvailles rares et inestimables vont-ils débusquer ? Nous verrons bien !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sogar der Äther, der Aurora umgibt, ist eine Suppenbrühe aus Geheimnissen und Wundern. Auroraner, erfinderisch wie sie sind, finden jetzt Wege, um diese Kuriositäten zu fangen. Welche seltenen und unbezahlbaren Dinge werden sie finden? Das werden wir noch sehen!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Persino l'etere che circonda Aurora è un insieme di mistero e meraviglia. Gli abitanti di Aurora, da sempre ingegnosi, stanno scoprendo dei modi per catturare queste rarità. Che cosa troveranno di tanto raro e di inestimabile valore? Lo scopriremo!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hasta el éter que envuelve Aurora es un caldo de misterio y asombro. Los ingeniosos habitantes de Aurora están descubriendo formas de atrapar todos esos Curios. ¿Qué rarezas de valor incalculable encontrarán? ¡Ya veremos!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラでは、すべてを覆う天空ですらも、謎と不思議に満ちています。創意あふれるオーロラ人は、この天空ですら捕らえる術を身につけつつあります。果たして見つかるのは、どれほど貴重なものなのでしょう?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Aurora를 둘러싸고 있는 창공은 신비와 경이의 장입니다. 창의적인 Aurora인들은 이 수집품들을 가두는 방법을 찾아내고 있습니다. 그들은 어떤 귀하고 값진 것들을 찾아내게 될까요?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Even the aether that surrounds Aurora is a broth of mystery and wonder. Aurorans, ever inventive, are now discovering ways of trapping these curios. What rare and priceless things they will find? We are yet to see! All we can be sure of is Aurora remains stubbornly a riddle, wrapped in a mystery, inside an enigma.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">甚至環繞極光群島的天空也充滿神秘和離奇。曾經精通發明的Auroran現在正在尋找捕獲這些古董的陷阱。他們會發現什麽無價之寶？我們拭目以待！我們能夠確定的是極光群島仍將是一個謎團，包裹在層層神秘之中，充滿著撲朔迷離的謎題。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">甚至環繞極光群島的天空也充滿神秘和離奇。曾經精通發明的Auroran現在正在尋找捕獲這些古董的陷阱。他們會發現什麽無價之寶？我們拭目以待！我們能夠確定的是極光群島仍將是一個謎團，包裹在層層神秘之中，充滿著撲朔迷離的謎題。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Even the aether that surrounds Aurora is a broth of mystery and wonder. Aurorans, ever inventive, are now discovering ways of trapping these curios. What rare and priceless things they will find? We are yet to see! All we can be sure of is Aurora remains stubbornly a riddle, wrapped in a mystery, inside an enigma.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S4L10</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A final mystery looms darker still over Aurora. No autochthonous devices these, the twitcher craft arrived alongside us like pestilence delivered to the New World. Who controls them and what purpose they serve we do not yet know but we may surmise.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un ultime et sombre mystère plane toujours sur Aurora. L’appareil de type Twitcher, tout sauf une invention autochtone, arriva à nos côtés telle la misère sur le Nouveau Monde. Aucune idée d’où ils viennent ni à quoi ils servent, mais nous pouvons toujours spéculer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein letztes Geheimnis schwebt noch dunkler über Aurora. Die Twitcher-Flugzeuge stammen nicht vor Aurora und kamen mit uns wie die Pest zur Neuen Welt. Wir wissen noch nicht, wer sie kontrolliert und zu welchem Zweck, aber wir haben Vermutungen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un ultimo mistero cala ancora più oscuro su Aurora. Lo Spasmoditron volante, un'invenzione non autoctona, è arrivato insieme a noi come una pestilenza abbattutasi sul Nuovo Mondo. Chi li controlla e a cosa servano non lo sappiamo ancora, ma possiamo solo supporre.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un último misterio aún más oscuro se avecina a Aurora. Esos artefactos no son autóctonos: el Twitcher llegó con nosotros como una pestilencia traída al Nuevo Mundo. Aún no sabemos quién los controla y cuál es su propósito, pero podemos hacer conjeturas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラ最後の謎が薄暗くオーロラを照らします。この地には似つかわしくない機械...不時着した戦闘機は、New World に舞い込んだ疫病のようにも見えます。誰が、何の目的で...? 答えはわかりませんが、きっと驚きが待っていることでしょう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">최후의 미스터리는 Aurora에서 아직 어둡고 흐릿하게 보입니다. 토착민의 장치가 아닌 트위처 비행선은 신세계에 전달된 역병처럼 우리와 나란히 도착했습니다. 누가 조종하며 어떤 목적을 가지고 있는지는 우리도 알 수 없고 짐작만이 가능할 뿐입니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A final mystery looms darker still over Aurora. No autochthonous devices these, the twitcher craft arrived alongside us like pestilence delivered to the New World. Who controls them and what purpose they serve we do not yet know but we may surmise.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">最後的神秘仍隱藏在極光群島的深處。這些自生的觀測機如同瘟疫般纏繞我們，最終投向了新世界。誰在控制它們？它們有何意圖？我們尚不得而知，但我們可以猜測。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">最後的神秘仍隱藏在極光群島的深處。這些自生的觀測機如同瘟疫般纏繞我們，最終投向了新世界。誰在控制它們？它們有何意圖？我們尚不得而知，但我們可以猜測。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A final mystery looms darker still over Aurora. No autochthonous devices these, the twitcher craft arrived alongside us like pestilence delivered to the New World. Who controls them and what purpose they serve we do not yet know but we may surmise.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">S4L11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If they are controlled by men we only have to look to our own avaricious ways. They desire Aurora and it's all its mercurial wonders for themselves.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si des hommes ont pris le contrôle, il y a bien des chances qu’ils soient cupides, tout comme nous. Ils voudront s’approprier Aurora et ses merveilles.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn sie von Menschen kontrolliert werden, dann müssen wir nur unsere eigene Gier begutachten. Sie wollen Aurora und all seine Wunder für sich.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se degli uomini hanno preso il controllo, dobbiamo solo controllare la nostra avarizia. Loro vogliono che Aurora e tutte le sue meraviglie restino lì tutte per loro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si están controlados por hombres, tendremos que controlar nuestra avaricia. Quieren apropiarse de Aurora y de sus maravillas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">人類が操っていたのなら、注意が必要です。欲に流されてオーロラと謎に満ちた世界を手中に収めようとしてきたのでしょうから。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">만약 인간이 그것들을 조종하고 있다면, 우리는 우리 자신의 탐욕스러운 방법을 살펴봐야 할 것입니다. 그들은 Aurora를 원하고 있으며 그것은 그들을 위한 변덕스러운 경이일 뿐입니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">If they are controlled by men we only have to look to our own avaricious ways. They desire Aurora and it's all its mercurial wonders for themselves.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">如果它們由人類控制，那麼我們必需採用自己的貪婪方式應對。他們希望得到極光群島，這是他們狡詐的企圖。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">如果它們由人類控制，那麼我們必需採用自己的貪婪方式應對。他們希望得到極光群島，這是他們狡詐的企圖。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">If they are controlled by men we only have to look to our own avaricious ways. They desire Aurora and it's all its mercurial wonders for themselves.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>