<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Earth Fleet Hover Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaise Volante Flotte Terrienne</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erdflotte Schwebestuhl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sedia Hover della Flotta terrestre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sillón flotante de flota terreste</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Earth Fleet Hover Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Earth Fleet Hover Chair</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Novus Prime recruits can finally enjoy some rest between battles thanks to this latest breakthrough in Nebulon-powered hovering furniture. Simply activate the touchscreen on your armrest to float through PlayStation®Home in unparalleled comfort. The speed boost is engaged when the avatar is moving at its full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les recrues Novus Prime peuvent enfin apprécier un peu de repos entre les combats grâce à ce tout nouveau meuble volant à l'énergie Nébulon. Activez simplement l'écran tactile sur l'accoudoir pour flotter à travers PlayStation®Home dans un confort inégalé. L'amplificateur de vitesse est enclenché quand l'avatar se déplace à sa vitesse maximale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rekruten von Novus Prime können sich dank diesem Durchbruch in Sachen nebulonbetriebenen Schwebemöbeln endlich zwischen den Gefechten mal eine Pause gönnen. Aktiviere einfach den Touchscreen in der Armlehne und schwebe durch PlayStation®Home, während du unvergleichlichen Komfort genießt. Der Geschwindigkeitsschub setzt automatisch ein, wenn der Avatar sich mit voller Geschwindigkeit bewegt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le reclute Novus Prime possono finalmente godersi un po' di meritato riposo dalle battaglie grazie a quest'ultima innovazione futuristica partorita dalla mente dei Nebulon. Basta attivare il touch screen sul bracciolo per librarsi in volo attraverso PlayStation®Home in tutta comodità. È possibile incrementarne la velocità portando l'avatar alla sua massima velocità di spostamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los reclutas de Novus Prime pueden finalmente disfrutar de un poco de descanso entre las batallas gracias a este último avance en muebles flotantes impulsados por Nebulon. Simplemente activa la pantalla táctil de tu reposabrazos para flotar por PlayStation®Home con una comodidad sin precedentes. El aumento de velocidad se activa cuando el avatar se está moviendo a su máxima velocidad. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Novus Prime recruits can finally enjoy some rest between battles thanks to this latest breakthrough in Nebulon-powered hovering furniture. Simply activate the touchscreen on your armrest to float through PlayStation®Home in unparalleled comfort. The speed boost is engaged when the avatar is moving at its full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Novus Prime recruits can finally enjoy some rest between battles thanks to this latest breakthrough in Nebulon-powered hovering furniture. Simply activate the touchscreen on your armrest to float through PlayStation®Home in unparalleled comfort. The speed boost is engaged when the avatar is moving at its full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>