<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hidden Oak Retreat Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack de meubles du Refuge du grand chêne</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dunkeleichen-Zuflucht: Möbelset</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto arredamento Rifugio Quercia nascosta </LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de muebles refugio del roble escondido</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オータムロッジ家具セット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">숨겨진 떡갈나무 휴양지 가구 번들</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Hidden Oak Retreat Furniture Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">秘密橡木度假屋家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">秘密橡木度假屋家具組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hidden Oak Retreat Furniture Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Give your mountain getaway vacation home the relaxing look you always wanted. Bundle includes lounge chair, rug, lamp, couch, painting and table. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Donnez à votre maison dans les montagnes le style dont vous avez toujours rêvé. Le pack comprend une chaise longue, un tapis, une lampe, un canapé, tableau et une table. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verleihe deinem geheimen Ferienhaus in den Bergen eine entspannende Atmosphäre. Das Set enthält einen Loungestuhl, einen Teppich, eine Lampe, eine Couch, eine gemälde und einen Tisch. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dai alla tua casa per le vacanze in montagna l'aspetto rilassante che hai sempre desiderato. Il pacchetto include chaise longue, tappeto, lampada, divano, quadro e tavolo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Da a tu refugio de montaña el aspecto relajado que siempre quisiste. El conjunto incluye diván, alfombra, lámpara, sofá, cuadro y mesa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オータムロッジにぴったりなゆったりとした家具のセットです。\n\n本セットには以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n・「ラウンジチェア（オータムロッジ）」（チェア）\n・「テーブル（オータムロッジ）」（テーブル）\n・「ランプ（オータムロッジ）」（照明器具）\n・「ラグ（オータムロッジ）」（ラグ）\n・「カウチ（オータムロッジ）」（ソファー）\n※購入すると、絵画（オータムロッジ）\n※ 該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">산지에 자리한 당신의 휴양지를 완벽하게 꾸며 보십시오. 이 번들은 숨겨진 떡갈나무 휴양지 라운지 의자, 양탄자, 램프, 소파, 그림그리고 탁자를 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Give your mountain getaway vacation home the relaxing look you always wanted. Bundle includes the Hidden Oak Retreat Lounge Chair, Hidden Oak Retreat Rug, Hidden Oak Retreat Lamp, Hidden Oak Retreat Couch, Hidden Oak Retreat Painting and Hidden Oak Retreat Table. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">給你的山野度假屋一個你一直想擁有的舒泰環境。本組合包包括秘密橡木度假屋休息椅、秘密橡木度假屋小地毯、秘密橡木度假屋電燈、秘密橡木度假屋長沙發, 油畫及秘密橡木度假屋桌子。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">給你的山野度假屋一個你一直想擁有的舒泰環境。本組合包包括秘密橡木度假屋休息椅、秘密橡木度假屋小地毯、秘密橡木度假屋電燈、秘密橡木度假屋長沙發, 油畫及秘密橡木度假屋桌子。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Give your mountain getaway vacation home the relaxing look you always wanted. Bundle includes lounge chair, rug, lamp, couch, painting, and table. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>