<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Campfire with Animated Flames</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Feu de camp avec flammes animées et braises rougeoyantes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lagerfeuer mit bewegten Flammen und glühenden Kohlen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fuoco di bivacco con tizzoni luccicanti e fiamme animate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hoguera de campamento con llamas animadas y ascuas brillantes.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">揺らめく炎のキャンプファイア</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">불타는 캠프파이어</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Campfire with Animated Flames</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">有動態火焰的營火</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">有動態火焰的營火</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Campfire with Animated Flames</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Relax and watch this mesmerizing and beautiful campfire with flickering glow, animated flames, subtle smoke and glowing embers. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Relaxez-vous en regardant cet hypnotique et superbe feu de camp avec sa lumière vacillante, ses flammes animées, sa fumée subtile et ses braises rougeoyantes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Entspanne dich und genieße dieses bezaubernde Lagerfeuer mit flackerndem Glühen, bewegten Flammen, leichtem Raucheffekt und glühenden Kohlen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Rilassati mentre guardi questo affascinante fuoco di bivacco completo di fiamme animate, luce tremolante, fumo e tizzoni scintillanti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Relájate y observa esta hipnotizante y maravillosa hoguera de campamento con un brillo parpadeante, llamas animadas, un ligero humo y ascuas brillantes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">チラチラと揺らめく炎、かすかな煙、赤く燃え立つ薪を見ながら、心地よい魅惑のひとときをお楽しみください。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">가물가물한 온기, 살아 움직이는 화염, 어렴풋한 연기와 타오르는 잿불이 매혹적입니다. 아름다운 캠프파이어를 편안하게 바라보며 즐기세요.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Relax and watch this mesmerizing and beautiful campfire with flickering glow, animated flames, subtle smoke and glowing embers. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">靜靜看著這盆迷人的美麗營火，火光忽明忽暗、火舌跳動、炊煙栩栩如生，還有發亮的餘燼，讓人全身放鬆。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">靜靜看著這盆迷人的美麗營火，火光忽明忽暗、火舌跳動、炊煙栩栩如生，還有發亮的餘燼，讓人全身放鬆。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Relax and watch this mesmerizing and beautiful campfire with flickering glow, animated flames, subtle smoke and glowing embers. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>