<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Crackle – Hoodie (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Crackle – Sweat à capuche (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Crackle – Hoodie (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Thank you for visiting the LOOT™ Space Station Theater. In celebration of the arrival of Crackle, PlayStation®Home's first FREE full-length Hollywood movie service, enjoy this exclusive Crackle Hoodie. For additional rewards, please enter the theater and watch free full-length movies, TV shows and the coolest collection of original series! Hint: Try to find Crackle’s popcorn bag, cap, movie themed t-shirts and posters! There are dozens of free sweet rewards waiting for you. Learn more about Crackle at www.crackle.com. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Merci de visiter le Cinéma de la Station Spatiale LOOT™. Pour célébrer l'arrivée de Crackle, le premier service GRATUIT de films d'Hollywood de PlayStation®Home, profitez en exclusivité de ce Sweat à capuche  Crackle. Pour d'autres bonus, veuillez entrer dans le cinéma pour visionner gratuitement des films longs-métrages, des émissions télé et la collection la plus cool de séries originales ! Un petit indice : essayez de trouver le sac de popcorn Crackle, la casquette, les T-shirts sur le thème du cinéma et des posters ! Il y a une dizaine de récompenses sympas et gratuites qui vous attendent. Apprenez-en plus sur Crackle sur le site www.crackle.com. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Thank you for visiting the LOOT™ Space Station Theater. In celebration of the arrival of Crackle, PlayStation®Home's first FREE full-length Hollywood movie service, enjoy this exclusive Crackle Hoodie. For additional rewards, please enter the theater and watch free full-length movies, TV shows and the coolest collection of original series! Hint: Try to find Crackle’s popcorn bag, cap, movie themed t-shirts and posters! There are dozens of free sweet rewards waiting for you. Learn more about Crackle at www.crackle.com. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>