<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Brownie Bomb Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Brownie Bomb Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Brownie Bomb Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Brownie Bomb Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Brownie Bomb Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup01_RedHead</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup01_RedHead</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup01_RedHead</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup01_RedHead</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup01_RedHead</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Brownie Bomb Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Brownie Bomb is a call to your wild side!  This retro pin-up babe is a full character costume, sporting a sexy green and black leopard print swim dress, iconic pin-up hair and make-up, and nature inspired tattoos… along with custom walk, run and pin-up pose animations, she's one tiger you'll want to tame![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Brownie Bomb fait appel à ton cote primitif! Cette retro pin-up minette est un costume à part entière, affichant une sexy robe de bain vert et noir léopard, des cheveux et maquillage emblématiques de pin-up, et des tatouages inspires de la nature….en plus d'une marche personnalisées, course et pose animées,  de pin-up  , C'est une espèce de Tigre que tu voudrais dompter![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Brownie Bomb fordert die wilde Seite in dir heraus! Dieses Retro Pin-Up Babe kommt als komplettes Charakterkostüm, ein Badeanzug mit sexy grünem und schwarzem Leopardendruck, ikonischer Pin-Up Frisur und Make-Up, sowie naturinspirierten Tätowierungen… zusammen mit benutzerdefinierten Animationen für Gang, Lauf und Pin-Up Posen ist sie ein Tiger den es zu zähmen gilt! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Brownie Bomb fará uscire il tuo lato selvaggio!  Questa bambola retro pin-up é un costume completo del personaggio, portando un  costume da bagno sexy in verde e nero con stampa ghepardata, capelli e trucco da  pin-up, e tatuaggi ispirati nella natura… insieme ad animazioni di camminata particolare, corsa e pose da pin-up, questa é una tigre che vorresti domare! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Brownie Bomb es un llamado a tu lado salvaje!  Esta nena pin-up es un disfraz completo del personaje, lleva un traje de baño sexy en verde y negro con estampado de leopardo, maquillaje y peinado de pin-up, y tatuajes inspirados en la naturaleza… asi como animaciones de caminata especial, corrida y pose de pin-up, es un tigre que vas a querer domar![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup01_RedHead [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup01_RedHead [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup01_RedHead [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup01_RedHead [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup01_RedHead [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Brownie Bomb is a call to your wild side!  This retro pin-up babe is a full character costume, sporting a sexy green and black leopard print swim dress, iconic pin-up hair and make-up, and nature inspired tattoos… along with custom walk, run and pin-up pose animations, she's one tiger you'll want to tame![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>