<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Furniture_spelunker_skull</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Crystal Skull (Replica)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Crâne de cristal (Réplique)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kristallschädel (Kopie)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Teschio di cristallo (Riproduzione)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Calavera de cristal (réplica)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">水晶ドクロ（レプリカ）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">수정 해골 (복제품)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Crystal Skull (Replica)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">水晶骷髏頭(複製品)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">水晶骷髏頭(複製品)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Crystal Skull (Replica)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Furniture_spelunker_skull_description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A reproduction of a crystal skull said to have been carved by an ancient tribe. Although the real thing is made of an extremely durable purple crystal and is worth a fortune, this replica is only made of glass.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La reproduction d'un crâne de cristal dont on dit qu'il fut taillé par une tribu ancestrale. Bien que l'original soit fait d'un cristal pourpre à la longévité exceptionnelle valant une fortune, sa réplique est seulement fait de glace.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Reproduktion eines Kristallschädels, der von einem uralten Stamm gefertigt worden sein soll. Während das Original aus extrem haltbarem purpurnem Kristall gefertigt wurde und ein Vermögen wert ist, ist diese Kopie nur aus Glas gefertigt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Riproduzione di un teschio di cristallo. Il reperto originale, che si ritiene sia stato creato da un'antica tribù, è realizzato in resistente cristallo viola e vale una fortuna; questa riproduzione è in vetro comune.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Reproducción de una calavera de cristal supuestamente esculpida por una antigua tribu. Aunque la auténtica está hecha con un cristal morado muy resistente y valioso, esta réplica es de vidrio.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">古代人が水晶を磨き上げて作ったとされるドクロの複製。この複製品はガラス製であるが、実物は純度の高い紫水晶で作られており、高値で取引されている。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">고대인이 수정을 연마해 만들었다고 하는 해골 복제품. 이 복제품은 유리로 만들어졌는데, 실물은 순도 높은 자수정으로 만들어져, 고가에 거래되고 있다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A reproduction of a crystal skull said to have been carved by an ancient tribe. Although the real thing is made of an extremely durable purple crystal and is worth a fortune, this replica is only made of glass.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">古代人以水晶琢磨而成的骷髏頭複製品。此複製品雖是玻璃製的，但實物可是用高純度的紫水晶製成，是以高價在進行交易。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">古代人以水晶琢磨而成的骷髏頭複製品。此複製品雖是玻璃製的，但實物可是用高純度的紫水晶製成，是以高價在進行交易。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A reproduction of a crystal skull said to have been carved by an ancient tribe. Although the real thing is made of an extremely durable purple crystal and is worth a fortune, this replica is only made of glass.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>