<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Morphsuit™ - Slender Man (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Morphsuit™ - Slenderman (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Morphsuit™ - Slender Man (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Morphsuit™ - Slender Man (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Morphsuit™ - El Gallardo (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Slenderman is a tall, thin figure who wears a black suit and has a completely blank face. According to legend, he can stretch or shorten his arms, he also causes people to crap their pants. We think he's a legend because he wears a Morphsuit™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Slenderman est un personnage grand et mince au visage entièrement blanc qui porte un costume noir. Selon la légende, il peut étirer ou raccourcir ses bras, et, en sa présence, généralement les gens font dans leur pantalon. Nous pensons que c'est une légende parce qu'il porte un Morphsuit™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Slender Man ist eine dünne, hünenhafte Kreatur im schwarzen Anzug und mit einem völlig ausdruckslosen Gesicht. Der Legende nach kann er seine Arme nach Belieben verlängern, um Menschen damit zu Tode zu erschrecken. Wir glauben, er ist eine Legende, weil er einen Morphsuit™ trägt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Slenderman è una figura alta e snella che indossa un abito nero e ha il viso completamente bianco. Secondo la leggenda, è in grado di allungare o accorciare le braccia e ha il potere di fartela fare addosso. Lo consideriamo un mito perché indossa una tuta Morphsuit™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Gallardo es una figura alta y delgada que viste un traje negro y tiene un rostro completamente inexpresivo. Según la leyenda, puede alargar o encoger los brazos, y también induce a la gente a cagarse en los pantalones. Para nosotros es una leyenda porque lleva un Morphsuit™. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>