<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gold Dance Platform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plate-forme de Danse Or</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Goldenen Tanzplattform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Oro ballo Piattaforma</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Oro Plataforma de Baile</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gold Dance Platform</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gotta dance? Then why not pick a spot that is as flashy as you are!  Watch your step, you're about to elevate your skill as a performer.  Place this animated dance platform in your personal space and transform your spot into THE SPOT.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avez-vous besoin de danser? Alors, pourquoi ne pas choisir un spot qui est aussi voyant que vous êtes! Attention à la marche, vous êtes sur le point d'élever votre talents en tant qu'un artiste. Placez cette plate-forme de danse animée dans votre espace personnel et transformez votre place en LA PLACE.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Musst Tanzen? Also warum es nicht an einem Ort, so einzigartig wie du! Achtung, Sie sind im Begriff Ihre Effizienz bei Effekthascherei zu erhöhen.  Platzieren Sie diese Plattform lebhafter Tanz in Ihrem persönlichen Bereich und verwandeln Sie Ihren Ort zu DER STELLE! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Avere a ballare? Allora perché non scegliere un posto che sia il più appariscente come sei! Guarda il tuo passo, si sta per elevare voi abilità come performer. Inserire questa piattaforma danza animata nel vostro spazio personale e trasformare l'area in L'AREA![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tiene que bailar? Entonces ¿por qué no escoger un lugar que es tan llamativo como eres! Cuidado con el escalón, Usted está a punto de aumentar tu habilidad como artista intérprete o ejecutante. Coloque esta plataforma de baile animada en su espacio personal y transformar el lugar... a EL LUGAR! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gotta dance? Then why not pick a spot that is as flashy as you are!  Watch your step, you're about to elevate your skill as a performer.  Place this animated dance platform in your personal space and transform your spot into THE SPOT.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>