<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mona</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">모나</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">莫娜</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">莫娜</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mona</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LOOT™’s done it again; we searched high and low for the cutest companion we could find. PUPPIES! Take home your favourite Schnauzer today! Don’t worry, they’re already house-trained. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">LOOT™ vient encore de frapper et s' est donné beaucoup de mal pour trouver l'animal de compagnie le plus mignon possible. DES CHIOTS ! Ramenez chez vous aujourd'hui votre Schnauzer préféré ! Pas d'inquiétude, il sont déjà dressés et propres. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LOOT™ hat es schon wieder getan: Wir haben weit und breit nach den süßesten Begleitern gesucht, und wir sind fündig geworden. WELPEN! Nimm deinen Lieblings-Schnauzer mit nach Hause! Keine Sorge, sie sind alle stubenrein. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">LOOT™ ha colpito ancora! Abbiamo cercato i compagni di gioco più carini che ci potessero essere: i CUCCIOLI! Porta con te il tuo Schnauzer preferito! E niente paura, è già addestrato a stare in casa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LOOT™ lo ha vuelto a hacer. Hemos buscado por todas partes a los compañeros más monos que se puede encontrar: ¡PERRITOS! ¡Llévate hoy a casa tu Schnauzer favorito! No te preocupes, ya están entrenados para hacer sus necesidades fuera de casa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">LOOT™가 다시 한번 해냈어요, 우리는 높고 낮은 지역 모두 두루 살펴보고 가장 귀여운 동물을 찾았어요. 강아지들이에요! 귀여운 슈나우저를 오늘 집으로 데려가세요! 염려 마세요, 길이 잘 들여져 있거든요.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">LOOT™又做到了！我們盡力到處尋找，找到了最可愛的隨身夥伴，就是小狗！今天就把你最喜歡的雪納瑞犬帶回家吧！別擔心，他們都已經受過訓練了。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">LOOT™又做到了！我們盡力到處尋找，找到了最可愛的隨身夥伴，就是小狗！今天就把你最喜歡的雪納瑞犬帶回家吧！別擔心，他們都已經受過訓練了。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LOOT™’s done it again; we searched high and low for the cutest companion we could find. PUPPIES! Take home your favorite Schnauzer today! Don’t worry, they’re already house-trained. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>