<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Audi Jacket F Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A must-have item for female Le Mans fans: this sporty mauve women’s sweat jacket features a high collar, zipped pockets along the side seams, Le Mans patches and Le Mans embroidery on the right breast.  Colour: mauve. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un article incontournable pour les femmes fans du Mans : cette veste sportive mauve dispose d’un grand col, de poches à fermetures éclairs sur les coutures latérales, des écussons du Mans et de la broderie du Mans sur la poitrine, à droite.  Couleur : mauve. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Einfach ein Must-have für weibliche Le Mans-Fans: Die sportliche Sweat-Jacke in Mauve überzeugt durch ihren hohen Kragen und Reißverschlusstaschen an den Seitennähten. Mit Le Mans-Abzeichen und Le Mans-Stickverzierung auf der rechten Brusthöhe. Farbe: Mauve. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un oggetto che ogni donna appassionata di Le Mans non può non possedere: Questa felpa sportiva da donna color malva presenta un collo alto, tasche con zip lungo le cuciture laterali, toppe alla Le Mans e sulla parte frontale destra ricami ispirati a Le Mans. Colore: Malva. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una prenda imprescindible para las fans de Le Mans. Esta sudadera deportiva de color malva para mujer es de cuello alto, bolsillos con cremalleras en las costuras laterales, parches de Le Mans y bordado de Le Mans en la parte derecha de la pechera. Color: malva. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Audi Jacket F Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Le Mans sweat jacket: female</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Veste Le Mans : femme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Le Mans Sweat-Jacke: Damen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Felpa di Le Mans da donna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sudadera Le Mans: mujer</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Audi Jacket F Name_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Le Mans sweat jacket: female</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Veste Le Mans : femme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Le Mans Sweat-Jacke: Damen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Felpa di Le Mans da donna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sudadera Le Mans: mujer</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>