<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Music Unlimited Halo - Male</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Halo Music Unlimited - Homme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Music Unlimited-Heiligenschein - Herren</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aureola di Music Unlimited - Uomo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Halo de Music Unlimited - Hombre</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Get to the PlayStation®Store now and try a 30 day trial of Music Unlimited for free. Music Unlimited gives you access to all the music you could ever want at home, online or on the go via your PlayStation®3, PlayStation®4, Mobile Phone, PlayStation®Vita, PC, Tablet or other Sony connected devices. Enjoy millions of songs advert free and use offline features to listen to your playlists even when you have no internet connection! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Accédez au PlayStation®Store maintenant et bénéficiez d'un essai de 30 jours gratuits de Music Unlimited. Music Unlimited permet d'accéder à toute la musique que vous voulez, chez vous, en ligne ou en déplacement sur PlayStation®3, PlayStation®4, téléphone mobile, PlayStation®Vita, PC, tablette ou d'autres périphériques Sony connectés. Écoutez des millions de titres sans publicité et utilisez les fonctionnalités en ligne pour écouter vos listes de lecture même quand vous ne pouvez pas accéder à Internet ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Nichts wie ab zum PlayStation®Store, wo du dir die 30-tägige Testversion von Music Unlimited völlig kostenlos holen kannst!Mit Music Unlimited hast du Zugriff auf so viel Musik, wie dein Herz begehrt, ob zu Hause, online oder unterwegs über PlayStation®3, PlayStation®4, Mobiltelefon, PlayStation®Vita, PC, Tablet oder andere mit Sony verbundene Geräte. Genieße Millionen von Liedern ohne Werbeunterbrechungen und nutze Offline-Features, um dir deine Wiedergabelisten auch dann anzuhören, wenn du keine Internetverbindung hast. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Visita subito il PlayStation®Store e richiedi la prova di 30 giorni di Music Unlimited gratuitamente. Music Unlimited ti offre l'accesso a tutta la musica che potresti desiderare, a casa, online o in viaggio tramite PlayStation®3, PlayStation®4, cellulare, PlayStation®Vita, PC, tablet o altri dispositivi Sony connessi a Internet. Divertiti con milioni di brani senza interruzioni pubblicitarie e sfruttando funzionalità offline per ascoltare i tuoi elenchi di riproduzione anche quando non sei connesso a Internet! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ve a PlayStation®Store para disfrutar de una prueba de 30 días gratuita de Music Unlimited. Music Unlimited te permite acceder a toda la música que quieras desde tu casa, online o mientras te desplazas en tu sistema PlayStation®3, PlayStation®4, móvil, sistema PlayStation®Vita, PC, tablet u otros dispositivos con conexión a Internet de Sony. Disfruta de millones de canciones sin anuncios y usa el modo sin conexión para escuchar tus listas de reproducción incluso cuando no tengas Internet. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>