<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Kunai (Infiltrator Class)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Kunai (Classe d'infiltration)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kunai (Infiltrator-Klasse)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Kunai (classe infiltratori)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Kunai (Clase de infiltración)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">クナイ（潜入クラス）セット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">쿠나이 (기습 기체) 세트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Kunai (Infiltrator Class) (bundle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Kunai（潛入者級）組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Kunai（潛入者級）組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Kunai (Infiltrator Class)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Equipped with a very powerful, but close-range weapon, the Kunai utilizes a state-of-the-art cloaking system to sneak up on its enemies. This is currently the only type of ship in the fleet that can cloak, and there are only a few of them in operation. A special-issue pilot's helmet is included with the purchase of this ship. This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Equipé d'une arme très puissante mais à courte portée, le Kunai est doté d'un dispositif d'invisibilité dernier cri qui lui permet de s'approcher furtivement de l'ennemi. C'est actuellement le seul type de vaisseau de la flotte pourvu d'un tel dispositif, et seulement quelques exemplaires sont en opération. Une version spéciale du casque de pilote est incluse lorsque vous faites l'acquisition de ce vaisseau. Ce lot comprend les versions homme et femme. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ausgerüstet mit einer auf kurze Distanz sehr mächtigen Waffe, verwendet der Kunai eine hochmoderne Tarnvorrichtung, um sich an die Feinde heranzuschleichen. Er ist derzeit das einzige Schiff in der Flotte, das über eine Tarnvorrichtung verfügt, und nur wenige sind im Einsatz. Die Sonderanfertigung eines Pilotenhelms ist beim Kauf dieses Schiffs inklusive. Dieses Paket enthält sowohl männliche als auch weibliche Versionen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Equipaggiata con un'arma molto potente ma a breve gittata, la Kunai utilizza un sistema di occultamento all'avanguardia per sfuggire ai nemici. Al momento è l'unica astronave della flotta in grado di occultarsi e ve ne sono poche operative. L'acquisto di questa nave comprende un casco da pilota per missioni speciali. Il pacchetto comprende sia la versione femminile sia quella maschile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Equipada con un arma muy potente, pero de corto alcance, la Kunai utiliza un novedoso sistema de camuflaje para acercarse sigilosamente a sus enemigos. Actualmente es el único tipo de nave de la flota que se puede camuflar y sólo hay algunas en funcionamiento. Con la compra de esta nave, obtendrás un casco de piloto especial. Este paquete incluye las versiones masculina y femenina. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">非常にパワフルな近距離専用兵器を備えたクナイは、最新鋭の隠密機構を利用することで敵に忍び寄る。\n※購入すると、ミニゲーム「ノーバス・プライム」内で戦闘機を使って遊ぶことができます。\n\n
本セットには、アバターのカスタマイズ用の以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n・「パイロット用ヘルメット（男性用）」（頭）\n・「パイロット用ヘルメット（女性用）」（頭）\n※購入すると、「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">매우 강력하지만 사정거리가 짧은 무장을 갖춘 쿠나이는 최첨단 은폐 기술을 사용해 적에게 접근할 수 있습니다. 지구 함대 내에서 유일하게 은폐가 가능한 함선이며, 실제 작전에서 활동하고 있는 수는 소수입니다. 함선을 구입하면 조종사용 헬멧이 특별히 함께 지급됩니다. 이 번들에는 남성용과 여성용이 모두 포함되어 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Equipped with a very powerful, but close-range weapon, the Kunai utilizes a state-of-the-art cloaking system to sneak up on its enemies. This is currently the only type of ship in the fleet that can cloak, and there are only a few of them in operation. A special-issue pilot's helmet is included with the purchase of this ship. This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Kunai配備極強力的近距離武器，能沿用最先進的隱形系統來悄悄逼近敵人。這是現時艦隊裡唯一能隱形的戰鬥機，而且只有數艘在運行。購買此太空船附送男用及女用的特別版飛行員頭盔。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Kunai配備極強力的近距離武器，能沿用最先進的隱形系統來悄悄逼近敵人。這是現時艦隊裡唯一能隱形的戰鬥機，而且只有數艘在運行。購買此太空船附送男用及女用的特別版飛行員頭盔。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Equipped with a very powerful, but close-range weapon, the Kunai utilizes a state-of-the-art cloaking system to sneak up on its enemies. This is currently the only type of ship in the fleet that can cloak, and there are only a few of them in operation. A special-issue pilot's helmet is included with the purchase of this ship. This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>