<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Forsaken Planet – Pikalilly (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Forsaken Planet - Pikalilly (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Forsaken Planet – Pikalilly (weiblich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Forsaken Planet – Pikalilly (femmina)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Forsaken Planet – Pikalilly (chica)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Forsaken Planet – Pikalilly (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Pretty but Deadly! Now you can travel PlayStation®Home as Pikalilly from Forsaken Planet, a LOOT™ Entertainment videogame for tablets and smart phones! Looking for even sweeter Forsaken Planet deals and in-game rewards? Check out the Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle in the LOOT™ Store! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jolie mais Mortelle ! Maintenant vous pouvez parcourir  PlayStation®Home en tant que Pikalilly de Forsaken Planet, un jeu vidéo de  LOOT™ Entertainment  pour tablettes et téléphones intelligents ! Vous cherchez des affaires Forsaken Planet encore plus intéressantes et des récompenses dans le jeu ? Allez voir les Lots Forsaken Planet dans la Boutique LOOT™  !  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schön, aber tödlich! Jetzt kannst du als Pikalilly aus Forsaken Planet, einem LOOT™ Entertainment Videospiel für Tablets und Smartphones durch dein PlayStation®Home wandern! Möchtest du noch bessere Forsaken Planet Deals und Ingame-Vorteile abgreifen? Schau dir das Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle im LOOT™ Store an! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Graziosa ma letale! Puoi esplorare la tua PlayStation®Home nei panni di Pikalilly di Forsaken Planet, un videogioco di LOOT™ Entertainment per tablet e smartphone! Cerchi altre offerte e altri premi Forsaken Planet? Dai un'occhiata al Pacchetto Ultimate Forsaken Planet nel LOOT™ Store! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Hermoso y mortal a la vez! ¡Ya puedes viajar en PlayStation®Home como Pikalilly de Forsaken Planet, un videojuego de LOOT™ Entertainment para tabletas y smartphones! ¿Quieres ofertas y premios aún más jugosos de Forsaken Planet? ¡No te pierdas el Gran lote Forsaken Planet en la tienda LOOT™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Pretty but Deadly! Now you can travel PlayStation®Home as Pikalilly from Forsaken Planet, a LOOT™ Entertainment videogame for tablets and smart phones! Looking for even sweeter Forsaken Planet deals and in-game rewards? Check out the Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle in the LOOT™ Store! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>