<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Musicality Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appartement Musicality</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Musicality-Wohnung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Appartamento Musicality</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apartamento de Musicality</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ミュージカリティー・クラブ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Musicality 아파트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Musicality Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">動感音樂公寓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">動感音樂公寓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Musicality Apartment</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A unique live music venue - up to four players can grab an instrument and jam/compete against each other. Comes complete with the Dance music pack – additional packs are available to purchase at the Musicality shop.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un événement musical en direct unique -Une jam session compétitive peut accueillir jusqu'à quatre joueurs. En plus du pack Dance déjà inclus dans le jeu, vous pouvez vous procurer d'autres packs de musique à la boutique Musicality.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein einzigartiger Live-Musiktreff - bis zu vier Spieler können sich ein Instrument schnappen und miteinander jammen/ gegeneinander antreten. Beinhaltet das Dance-Musik-Set – weitere Sets können im Musicality Shop erworben werden.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una sede per esibizioni dal vivo unica in cui fino a quattro giocatori possono scegliere uno strumento e suonare insieme/competere tra loro. Completo di Dance music pack. I pacchetti aggiuntivi sono disponibili per l'acquisto nel Musicality shop.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una sala de conciertos única: hasta cuatro jugadores pueden coger un instrumento y tocar o competir unos contra otros. Incluye un paquete de música Dance, pero puedes comprar paquetes adicionales en la tienda Musicality.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このユニークなライブ・ミュージックのステージ付きパーソナルスペースでは、１～４人のプレーヤーがそれぞれ楽器を選択し、一緒にジャム･セッションやバトル対決などして遊べます。ダンスミュージックパック付き - 他の追加パックもミュージカリティーショップで購入可能。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">독특한 매력을 발산하는 라이브 베뉴입니다. 최대 네 명의 플레이어들이 협주하거나 경쟁할 수 있습니다. '댄스 팩'이 이미 포함되어 있으며, Musicality 쇼핑몰에서 추가 음악 팩을 구입할 수 있습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A unique live music venue - up to four players can grab an instrument and jam/compete against each other. Comes complete with the Dance music pack – additional packs are available to purchase at the Musicality shop.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">獨特的現場音樂集合處 - 最多可同時讓四名玩家遊玩，每人可以拿起一種樂器來即興演出，並且互相對抗競爭。另外可遊玩舞蹈音樂組合包。您可以動感音樂商店裡購買其他追加的組合包。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">獨特的現場音樂集合處 - 最多可同時讓四名玩家遊玩，每人可以拿起一種樂器來即興演出，並且互相對抗競爭。另外可遊玩舞蹈音樂組合包。您可以動感音樂商店裡購買其他追加的組合包。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A unique live music venue - up to four players can grab an instrument and jam/compete against each other. Comes complete with the Dance music pack – additional packs are available to purchase at the Musicality shop.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>