<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wizard Armor Set (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble d’armure de sorcier (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rüstungssatz Zauberer (Männer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set di armatura da mago (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de armadura del mago (chico)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_54</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_54</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_54</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_54</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_54</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Wizard Armor Set (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Destruction lies at your fingertips with this iconic set of Wizard armor from Diablo III. Channel your arcane energy through it to lay waste to your enemies. The set includes the Wizard's Storm Crow, Wizard Doublet, Wizard Breeches, Wizard Boots, and Wizard Deflectors.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Maîtrisez la puissance dévastatrice qui se trouve à portée de votre main grâce à cet ensemble complet d’armure emblématique du sorcier de Diablo III. Il comprend : corbeau des tempêtes de sorcier, pourpoint de sorcier, braies de sorcier, bottes de sorcier, déflecteurs de sorcier.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Zerstörung liegt in Ihrer Hand mit diesem unverwechselbaren Zauberer-Rüstungssatz aus Diablo III. Schöpfen Sie Ihre arkane Energie mit dieser Rüstung voll aus, um Ihre Feinde zu vernichten. Der Rüstungssatz umfasst Zauberer-Sturmkrähe, Zauberer-Wams, Zauberer-Hose, Zauberer-Stiefel und Zauberer-Abweiser.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La distruzione è a portata di mano con questo set di armatura da mago tratto da Diablo III. Sfruttalo per concentrare l'energia arcana e annientare i tuoi nemici. Il set include Corvotempesta da mago, Farsetto da mago, Calzoni da mago, Stivali da mago e Deflettori da mago.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El poder destructivo arde en tus manos con este simbólico conjunto de armadura del mago de Diablo III. Es el medio perfecto para canalizar tu energía arcana y aniquilar a tus enemigos. El conjunto incluye el cuervo de la tormenta, el jubón, los calzones, las botas y los deflectores del mago.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_54 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_54 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_54 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_54 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_54 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Destruction lies at your fingertips with this iconic set of Wizard armor from Diablo III. Channel your arcane energy through it to lay waste to your enemies. The set includes the Wizard's Storm Crow, Wizard Doublet, Wizard Breeches, Wizard Boots, and Wizard Deflectors.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>