<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Red, White and Blue PODI Fireworks</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Feux d'artifice IAEP Rouge, Blanc et Bleu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">PODI-Feuerwerk "Rot, Weiß, Blau"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fuochi d'artificio PODI rossi, bianchi e blu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fuegos artificiales IMAP rojos, blancos y azules</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">PODI - 赤、白、青キット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">적색, 백색 및 청색 PODI 불꽃놀이</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Red, White and Blue PODI Fireworks</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">紅、白、藍PODI煙火</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">紅、白、藍PODI煙火</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Red, White and Blue PODI Fireworks</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This box contains:\n\n • Old Glory Blue - Three blue explosions in quick succession\n • The Patriot - Red, white and blue bursts of light\n • By George!- A blindingly bright white triple flash\n • Tricolore Core - A red, white and blue halo with an explosive centrepiece\n • Stars and Lights - Stripes of red and blue followed by white sparkles\n • Liberty Rockets - Three red explosions in quick succession\n\n Important: PODI Fireworks can only be used in conjuction with the Pyrotechnic Overhead Display Interface Active Object. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette boîte contient:\n\n • Bleu Vieille Gloire - Trois explosions bleues successives\n • Le Patriote - Explosions de lumière rouges, blanches et bleues.\n • Par George!- Un triple flash blanc étincelant\n • Cœur Tricolore - Un halo rouge, blanc et bleu avec une pièce centrale explosive\n • Étoiles et Lumières - Trainées de rouge et bleu suivies d'étincelles blanches\n • Fusées de la Liberté - Trois explosions rouges successives\n\n Important: Les fusées IAEP peuvent être utilisées uniquement en liaison avec l'Objet Actif de l'Interface de Spectacle Pyrotechnique. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Paket enthält:\n\n • Glorreiches Blau - Drei blaue Explosionen in schneller Abfolge\n • Der Patriot - Rote, weiße und blaue Lichtblitze\n • Bei George!- Ein greller, weißer Dreifachblitz\n • Drillingsringe - Rote, weiße und blaue Ringe mit einer Explosion im Mittelpunkt\n • Sternenfeuer - Rote und blaue Streifen gefolgt von weißen Sternchen\n • Raketenzauber - Drei rote Explosionen in schneller Abfolge\n\n Wichtig: PODI-Feuerwerk kann nur mit dem aktiven Objekt "Pyrotechnisches Overhead-Display-Interface" verwendet werden. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa scatola contiene:\n\n • Blu dell'antica gloria - Tre esplosioni blu in rapida successione\n • Il patriota - Esplosioni di luce rossa, bianca e blu\n • Oh, George!- Tre bagliori bianchi e abbaglianti\n • Anima tricolore - Un alone rosso, bianco e blu con un cuore esplosivo \n • Luci e stelle - Strisce di rosso e blu seguite da scintillii bianchi\n • Razzi della libertà - Tre esplosioni rosse in rapida successione\n\n Importante: i fuochi d'artificio PODI possono essere utilizzati solo in combinazione con l'oggetto attivo dell'interfaccia dello spettacolo pirotecnico. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta caja contiene:\n\n • Bandera estadounidense azul - Tres explosiones azules, una tras otra\n • El patriota - Ráfagas de luz rojas, blancas y azules\n • ¡Por Dios!- Un deslumbrante destello triple de color blanco brillante\n • Núcleo tricolor - Un halo rojo, blanco y azul con un centro explosivo\n • Estrellas y luces - Rayas rojas y azules con una estela de destellos blancos\n • Cohetes de la libertad - Tres explosiones rojas, una tras otra\n\n Importante: los fuegos artificiales IMAP solo pueden utilizarse con el Objeto activo de interfaz de espectáculos pirotécnicos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">PODI - 赤、白、青キットは、PODIで使用出来ます。\n\n


• グローリー・ブルー - ３連続で青閃光\n 
• ザ・パトリオット – 赤、白、青\n 
• ジョージ作- まぶしい３連続の白閃光\n 
• トリコロール・コア - 赤、白、青の爆発的なセンターピース\n 
• 星空 - 赤と青のストライプの後に白のキラキラ\n 
• フリーダムロケット - ３連続で赤閃光\n\n 

 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 박스에 들어 있는 것들:\n\n • 올드 글로리 블루 - 짧은 간격으로 이어지는 3회의 청색 폭발\n • 패트리어트 - 적, 백 및 청색의 폭발 섬광\n • 바이 조지!- 눈이 멀 정도로 밝은 백색의 플래시 3회\n • 삼색 코어- 적, 백 및 청색의 후광과 함께 폭발하는 중앙부\n • 별들과 광선들 - 적색 및 청색의 줄무늬에 이어지는 백색의 불꽃들\n • 리버티 로켓 - 짧은 간격으로 이어지는 3회의 적색 폭발\n\n 중요 사항: PODI 퓨즈는 오로지 불놀이 오버헤드 디스플레이 인터페이스 액티브 오브젝트에서만 사용할 수 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This box contains:\n\n • Old Glory Blue - Three blue explosions in quick succession\n • The Patriot - Red, white and blue bursts of light\n • By George!- A blindingly bright white triple flash\n • Tricolore Core - A red, white and blue halo with an explosive centrepiece\n • Stars and Lights - Stripes of red and blue followed by white sparkles\n • Liberty Rockets - Three red explosions in quick succession\n\n Important: PODI Fireworks can only be used in conjuction with the Pyrotechnic Overhead Display Interface Active Object. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">包裝內容：\n\n  ●藍色古典榮耀：藍色連三發\n ●愛國者：紅、白、藍大放光芒\n ●大驚喜：三發炫目的白色煙火\n ●三色環：紅、白、藍三圈煙火，正中心爆炸\n ●星光大道：紅藍條狀煙火，最後是白色火花\n ●自由火箭：紅色連三發\n\n  ※注意：PODI煙火只能搭配煙火表演介面(PODI)動態道具使用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">包裝內容：\n\n  ●藍色古典榮耀：藍色連三發\n ●愛國者：紅、白、藍大放光芒\n ●大驚喜：三發炫目的白色煙火\n ●三色環：紅、白、藍三圈煙火，正中心爆炸\n ●星光大道：紅藍條狀煙火，最後是白色火花\n ●自由火箭：紅色連三發\n\n  ※注意：PODI煙火只能搭配煙火表演介面(PODI)動態道具使用。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This box contains:\n\n • Old Glory Blue - Three blue explosions in quick succession\n • The Patriot - Red, white and blue bursts of light\n • By George!- A blindingly bright white triple flash\n • Tricolore Core - A red, white and blue halo with an explosive centrepiece\n • Stars and Lights - Stripes of red and blue followed by white sparkles\n • Liberty Rockets - Three red explosions in quick succession\n\n Important: PODI Fireworks can only be used in conjuction with the Pyrotechnic Overhead Display Interface Active Object. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>