<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rockabilly Outfit (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tenue Rockabilly</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rockabilly-Outfit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aspetto Rockabilly</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje de Rockabilly</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_44</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_44</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_44</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_44</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_44</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rockabilly Outfit (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You admire the style and manners of yester-year with a hard edge. Show up in style with this rockabilly outfit complete with Tucked-in Button Up, Classic Jeans, Classic Shades and Rockabilly Hair.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous vouez un culte au look et à la façon de vivre d'autrefois. Prouvez-le en portant cette tenue rockabilly qui comprend la Chemise Boutonnée À Manches Courtes, les Lunettes De Soleil Classiques et la Coiffure Rockabilly.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Für harte Kerle, die den Stil und die Attitüde von damals bewundern und einen stilvollen Auftritt hinlegen wollen. Das vollständige Rockabilly-Outfit umfasst ein Hemd mit Knöpfen, eine klassische Jeans, eine klassische Sonnenbrille und eine Rockabilly-Frisur.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ti piacciono stile e modi dei tempi in cui andavano i contrasti di colore. Fatti vedere in grande stile con questo aspetto rockabilly completo di Camicia Abbottonata Dentro I Pantaloni, Jeans Classici, Occhiali Da Sole Classici e Capelli Rockabilly.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Admiras el estilo y las costumbres de los duros de los 50. Demuéstralo con este traje de rockabilly que viene con una camisa de manga corta, vaqueros clásicos, gafas de sol clásicas y pelo de rockabilly.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_44 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_44 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Home_Object_44 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_44 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_44 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You admire the style and manners of yester-year with a hard edge. Show up in style with this rockabilly outfit complete with Tucked-in Button Up, Classic Jeans, Classic Shades and Rockabilly Hair.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>