<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Large Playing Cards - Locomotion Item</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Grand Jeu de Cartes - élément de locomotion </LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Große Spielkarten - Fortbewegung Artikel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Grandi Carte da Gioco - Locomozione articolo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Grandes Cartas de Juego - Locomoción artículo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* 52 card pick- up</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* 52 card pick- up</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* 52 card pick- up</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* 52 card pick- up</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* 52 card pick- up</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Large Playing Cards - Locomotion Item</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If you had a super power what would it be? To summon cards at your whim so that you can run on them? Well, with this item now you can do that. It's a dash of super speed, a pinch of flying, and a sprinkle of casino all mixed into one locomotion item.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si vous aviez un super pouvoir, lequel serait-ce ? D'invoquer des cartes quand bon vous semble et de courir sur elles ? Avec cet objet vous pouvez le faire. C'est un zeste de super vitesse, une pincée de vol et quelques gouttes de casino, mixés dans un seul moyen de locomotion.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn Sie über eine außergewöhnliche Macht verfügen würden, worin bestünde sie?  Sich  nach Lust und Laune Karten herbeizurufen,  auf die Sie  setzen können? Mit  diesem  Spiel können Sie das jetzt tun. In dieser Locomotion finden Sie alles, was Sie brauchen:  einen Hauch Geschwindigkeit, eine Prise Fliegen und einen Schuss Casino.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se avessi un superpotere, quale sarebbe? Evocare le carte a tuo piacimento per poter correre su di loro? Bene, con questo nuovo oggetto potrai farlo.  Un  pizzico di super velocità, di volo e una spolverata al Casinò, tutti mixati in un'unica locomozione.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si tuvieras un superpoder cuál sería? Invocar cartas a tu capricho y así superarlos a todos? Bueno, con este objeto podrás hacerlo. Es una mezcla de súper velocidad, una pizca de vuelo y el toque del casino todo junto en un objeto de locomoción.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* Reward for winning the poker tournament  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Reward for winning the poker tournament  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Reward for winning the poker tournament  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Reward for winning the poker tournament  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Reward for winning the poker tournament  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">If you had a super power what would it be? To summon cards at your whim so that you can run on them? Well, with this item now you can do that. It's a dash of super speed, a pinch of flying, and a sprinkle of casino all mixed into one locomotion item.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>