<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Felucian Potted Plant (Mushrooms)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Plante verte felucienne (champignons)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Feluciansche Topfpflanze (Pilze)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pianta di Felucia in Vaso (Funghi)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Planta feluciana en maceta (Champiñones)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Felucian Potted Plant (Mushrooms)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Towering overhead, the massive plants of Felucia covered the ground in beautiful shadows. The small amount of light let through reflected off the prismatic animals scattering from my footsteps as I moved between the giant mushrooms. Leaning on one of these stalks to admire the sight, I noticed, trembling at my feet, the first growths of the next spore that would blot out the sun. A few of these I brought back with me; they keep their shadows confined to my home. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Se dressant au-dessus des têtes, les énormes plantes de Felucia couvraient le sol d'ombres magnifiques. Le peu de lumière qui passait réfléchissait la dispersion prismatique animale de mes empreintes, tandis que je me déplaçais parmi les champignons géants. Appuyé contre l'un de ces pieds pour admirer la vue, je remarquais, tremblant à mes pieds, les premières pousses de la prochaine spore que le soleil ferait pousser. J'en rapportai quelques-unes avec moi ; leurs ombres sont maintenant confinées dans ma demeure. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über mir bedeckten die riesigen Pflanzen von Felucia den Boden mit wundervollen Schatten. Das wenige Licht, das hindurchdrang, wurde von den prismatischen Tieren reflektiert, die sich vor meinen Füßen verstreuten, während ich mich zwischen den riesigen Pilzen bewegte. Als ich mich gegen einen der Stiele lehnte, um die Ansicht zu bewundern, bemerkte ich vor meinen Füßen die Anfänge der nächsten Sporen, die sich schon bald der Sonne entgegen richten würden. Ich nahm ein paar von ihnen mit. Ihre Schatten werfen sie nun nur bei mir zu Hause. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'aria umida e pesante di Felucia mi ha riempito in fretta i polmoni, all'uscita dalla mia nave. Essendo nuovo su questo pianeta, non avevo ancora capito cosa intendeva dire la gente che diceva che qui tu non respiri l'aria, ma l'aria 'respira te'. Mentre cercavo di abituarmi a questo fatto, ha iniziato a girarmi la testa e ho perso l'equilibrio, andando a finire in un cespuglio vicino - pieno delle felci che ora vi vendo per decorazione e filtraggio dell'aria. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Alzándose por todo lo alto, las enormes plantas de Felucia cubrían el suelo con bellas sombras. La poca luz que se colaba reflejaba a los animales huyendo de mis pisadas mientras me desplazaba entre los champiñones gigantes. Apoyándome en uno de estos tallos para admirar la vista, descubrí, temblando a mis pies, los primeros brotes de la siguiente espora que el sol haría brotar. Me llevé unos cuantos; sus sombras se encuentran confinadas en mi casa. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Towering overhead, the massive plants of Felucia covered the ground in beautiful shadows. The small amount of light let through reflected off the prismatic animals scattering from my footsteps as I moved between the giant mushrooms. Leaning on one of these stalks to admire the sight, I noticed, trembling at my feet, the first growths of the next spore that would blot out the sun. A few of these I brought back with me; they keep their shadows confined to my home. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>