<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hard polycarbonate soft rubber GAS MASK. (Male version)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Masque à gaz en caoutchouc et en polycarbonate. (version Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hartpolykarbonat-Weichgummi-GASMASKE (Herren).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">MASCHERA ANTIGAS di gomma morbida ai policarbonati duri (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">MÁSCARA DE GAS de policarbonato duro y goma blanda. (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The happy pink ponies ran up the flower filled field singing with joy. The rainbows sprinkled coloured candies down to earth, and the sun laughed and laughed. And from the chocolate rivers, toads leapt forth spewing CS-gas that essentially makes you blind and blocks your respiration, causing fainting and dizziness. Have a nice day. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les poneys roses joyeux couraient dans le champ empli de fleurs, en chantant avec joie. Les arcs-en-ciel répandaient des bonbons colorés sur la terre et le soleil riait, riait. Et des crapauds sautaient des rivières de chocolat, répandant du gaz CS qui provoque la cécité et bloque la respiration, causant des vertiges et l'évanouissement. Bonne journée. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die glücklichen rosafarbenen Ponys rannten freudig singend über die Blumenwiese. Aus Regenbögen regneten bunte Bonbons herab und die Sonne lachte und lachte. Und aus den Schokoflüssen hüpften Kröten und spuckten Tränengas aus, das alle erblinden und nach Atem ringen lässt und Ohnmacht und Schwindel auslöst. Schönen Tag auch. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I pony rosa felici corsero sul campo pieno di fiori cantando con gioia. Gli arcobaleni spruzzarono sulla terra caramelle colorate e il sole rise e rise ancora. E dai fiumi di cioccolato saltaron fuori dei rospi che sputavano gas CS, che ti acceca e ti blocca la respirazione, causando disorientamento e svenimenti. buona giornata. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los felices ponis rosas corrían por el campo repleto de flores cantando gozosos. Los arco iris derramaban dulces de colores sobre la tierra, y el sol reía y reía. Y de los ríos de chocolate, saltaron sapos escupiendo gas lacrimógeno, que, básicamente, provoca ceguera y asfixia, mareos y desvanecimientos. Que tengas un buen día. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>