<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Alessa Sweat Pants - Off Black (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Pantalon de survêtement Alessa - Noir mat (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Alessa Jogginghose - Dunkelgrau (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Alessa Pantaloni da tuta - Nero (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Alessa Pantalón de chándal - Negro apagado (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Super comfy french terry pants are just as happy chilling on the couch as they are covering up your bikini. Styled with an elastic waistband and a rope drawcord, along with a logo screen that runs down the left leg. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce pantalon confortable en molleton est tout aussi réjouissant pour vous vautrer dans votre canapé que pour passer par-dessus votre bikini. Stylé avec sa ceinture élastique et un cordon de serrage, avec un logo sérigraphié qui descend le long de la jambe gauche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Superbequeme Jogginghose aus französischem Frottee zum Entspannen auf der Couch oder als Accessoire zum Bikini. Mit Gummizug und Kordel und einem Logo, das längs am linken Hosenbein verläuft. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pantaloni ultra comodi in tessuto french terry perfetti sia per rilassarsi sul divano che come copricostume. Presentano una fascia in vita elasticizzata, cordoncino e stampa con logo lungo la gamba sinistra. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pantalón súper cómodo de tejido French Terry, igual de práctico para descansar en el sofá como para poner por encima del bikini. Con cintura elástica y cordones ajustables, también presenta el logotipo estampado en la pierna izquierda. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>