<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Locomotion - Small Black Wings, Back, Near</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Locomotion - Petites ailes noires, dos, proches</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Bewegungsgegenstand - Kleine schwarze Flügel am Rücken, nah</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Locomotion - Piccole ali nere vicine alla schiena</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Locomoción - Pequeñas alas negras, espalda, cerca</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">LMO-小さな黒い羽・背中・近</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Locomotion - Small Black Wings, Back, Near</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Small wings growing from the back. This type is close to the body, making them easy to match with tight clothes.\n
When using them, you can float and move through the air. Speed increases while pressing □.\n
Speed: ★★★~★★★★★\n
* Locomotion is a portable item.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Des petites ailes poussant dans le dos. Ce modèle est proche du corps, ce qui va bien avec les vêtements serrés.\n
Quand vous les utilisez, vous pouvez flotter et vous déplacer dans les airs. La vitesse augmente en appuyant sur □.\n
Vitesse : ★★★~★★★★★\n
* Un objet de locomotion est un objet portable.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Kleine Flügel, die aus dem Rücken wachsen. Da sie nah am Körper anliegen, kannst du sie mit engen Klamotten kombinieren.\n
Wenn du sie benutzt, kannst du schweben und dich durch die Luft bewegen. Geschwindigkeit erhöht sich durch das Drücken von □.\n
Geschwindigkeit: ★★★~★★★★★\n
* Bewegungsgegenstände sind tragbare Gegenstände.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Piccole ali che spuntano dalla testa. Questo tipo di ali è vicino al corpo, in modo da facilitarne l'abbinamento con abiti aderenti.\n
Indossandole, è possibile spostarsi fluttuando nell'aria. Tenendo premuto il tasto □, la velocità di spostamento aumenta.\n
Velocità: ★★★~★★★★★\n
* Gli oggetti Locomotion sono oggetti portatili.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Pequeñas alas que brotan de la espalda. Estas se colocan cerca del cuerpo, para que combinen bien con ropa ajustada.\n
Usándolas podrás flotar y moverte por el aire. Se incrementará la velocidad al presionar □.\n
Velocidad: ★★★-★★★★★\n
* Locomoción es un artículo portátil.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">背中に生える小さな羽。体との距離が近く、タイトな服装に合わせやすいタイプ。\n
使用すると、宙に浮いて移動することができます。□ボタンを押している間、移動速度がアップします。\n
移動速度：　◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆\n
※LMO(ロコモーション)はポータブルアイテムです。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Small wings growing from the back. This type is close to the body, making them easy to match with tight clothes.\n
When using them, you can float and move through the air. Speed increases while pressing □.\n
Speed: ★★★~★★★★★\n
* Locomotion is a portable item.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
