<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Unidentified Following Object (companion)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Unidentified objet suivant (compagnon)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Seltsame Nach Object (Begleiter)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Oggetto non identificato seguito (compagna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Después de objeto no identificado (compañero)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Unidentified Following Object (companion)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Look behind you!  No really, what is that? This strange metallic sighting is straight outta Area 51 and is sure to cause mass hysteria.  Buy one now before it's proven to be a hoax.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Regardez derrière vous! Non vraiment, ce que c'est? Cette observation est métallique étrange Straight Outta zone 51 et est sûr de provoquer l'hystérie de masse. Achetez-maintenant avant qu'il avérée être un canular.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schau hinter dich! Nein wirklich, was ist das? Diese seltsame metallische Sichtung ist Straight Outta Area 51 und ist sich sicher, Massenhysterie hervorrufen. Buy one jetzt, bevor es sich als Falschmeldung.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guarda dietro di te! No davvero, che cosa è? Questo avvistamento strano metallico è Straight Outta Area 51 ed è sicuro di provocare l'isteria di massa. Acquistarne uno prima che sia dimostrato di essere una bufala.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mira detrás de ti! No, en serio, ¿qué es eso? Este avistamiento metálico extraño es Straight Outta el Área 51 y va a hacer que la histeria colectiva. Comprar una ahora antes de que sea demostrado ser un engaño.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Look behind you!  No really, what is that? This strange metallic sighting is straight outta Area 51 and is sure to cause mass hysteria.  Buy one now before it's proven to be a hoax.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>