<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Empire Strikes Back All Furniture Items Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le lot Meubles de L'Empire contre-attaque</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Imperium schlägt zurück - Das Möbelkomplettpaket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Set completo mobilio de L'Impero colpisce ancora</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete con todos los muebles de El imperio contraataca</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* The Empire Strikes Back All Furniture Items Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* The Empire Strikes Back All Furniture Items Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Empire Strikes Back All Furniture Items Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* The Empire Strikes Back All Furniture Items Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* The Empire Strikes Back All Furniture Items Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Empire Strikes Back All Furniture Items Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is the complete set of The Empire Strikes Back 30th Anniversary furniture items.  This bundle contains all 10 furniture items being sold in the store, including all 6 pieces of the "living room" set, one Han Solo in Carbonite one ESB 30th Anniversary Logo Poster, one The Empire Strikes Back Concept Art Poster and one Star Wars™ Celebration V Poster.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C’est la collection complète de meubles de l’Empire contre-attaque  pour les 30 ans de l’Empire. Ce paquet contient les 10 meubles vendus en magasin, ainsi que les 6 pièces de la salle de séjour, une Han Solo en carbonite, un poster pour l’anniversaire des 30 ans, un poster de L’Empire contre-attaque de l’art conceptuel et un poster de Star Wars™ Celebration V. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In diesem Komplettpaket sind alle Möbel der Serie zum 30-jährigen Jubiläum von Das Imperium schlägt zurück enthalten. Das Paket enthält alle zehn Möbelteile, die im laden erhältlich sind sowie auch alle sechs Teile des "Wohnzimmer"-Sets, ein Han Solo in Karbonit, ein Das Imperium schlägt zurück-Plakat zum 30-jährigen Jubiläum, ein Das Imperium schlägt zurück-Conceptart-Plakat sowie ein Star Wars™ Celebration V-Plakat. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo è il set completo degli articoli di accessori di The Empire Strikes Back 30th Anniversary.  Questo pacchetto contiene tutti i 10 articoli di accessori venduti in negozio, compresi tutti i 6 pezzi del set "living room", un Han Solo in Carbonite, un Poster ESB 30th Anniversary Logo, un Poster The Empire Strikes Back Concept Art e un Poster Star Wars™ Celebration V. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta es la colección completa de todos los muebles del 30 aniversario de El imperio contraataca.  Este paquete contiene los 10 muebles que se venden en las tiendas, incluyendo las 6 piezas del set del "salón", un Han Solo de carbonita, un Póster con el Logotipo del 30 Aniversario de El imperio contraataca, un Póster de Diseño de Concepto de El imperio contraataca y un Póster de Star Wars™ Celebración V. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This is the complete set of The Empire Strikes Back 30th Anniversary furniture items.  This bundle contains all 10 furniture items being sold in the store, including all 6 pieces of the "living room" set, one Han Solo in Carbonite one ESB 30th Anniversary Logo Poster, one The Empire Strikes Back Concept Art Poster and one Star Wars™ Celebration V Poster.   [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This is the complete set of The Empire Strikes Back 30th Anniversary furniture items.  This bundle contains all 10 furniture items being sold in the store, including all 6 pieces of the "living room" set, one Han Solo in Carbonite one ESB 30th Anniversary Logo Poster, one The Empire Strikes Back Concept Art Poster and one Star Wars™ Celebration V Poster.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>