<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Giddy Goon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Giddy Goon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Giddy Goon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Giddy Goon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Giddy Goon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Giddy Goon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Giddy Goon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Giddy Goon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Giddy Goon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Giddy Goon</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Giddy Goon</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Giddy Goons natural habitats are the dark stairwells of mysterious and enchanted castles. They are a very territorial creature and will attack those who are not welcome in their vicinity. Domesticated Giddy Goons are very loyal to their masters and will follow them anywhere. Give them a sword and they will be your friend forever. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les habitats naturels des Giddy Goon sont les cages d’escaliers sombres des châteaux mystérieux et enchantés. Ce sont des créatures très territoriales qui attaquent ceux qui ne sont les bienvenus dans leur voisinage. Les Giddy Goons domestiqués sont très loyaux envers leurs maîtres et les suivent partout. Donnez-leur une épée et ils seront vos amis pour toujours. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Giddy Goons natürlicher Lebensraum sind die dunklen Gänge und Treppen verzauberter Schlösser und Burgen. Die sesshaften Kreaturen attackieren jeden, der es wagt, unbefugt in ihr Territorium einzudringen. Einmal gezähmt folgt ein Giddy Goon seinem Besitzer auf Schritt und Tritt. Schenke einem ein Schwert und er wird ein Leben lang Dein bester Freund sein. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'habitat naturale dei Giddy Goon sono le oscure trombe delle scale di castelli misteriosi e incantati. Sono creature molto legate al territorio e attaccheranno tutti coloro che non sono benvenuti nelle loro vicinanze. I Giddy Goon domestici sono molto fedeli ai loro padroni e li seguiranno dovunque. Dategli una spada e saranno vostri amici per sempre. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los hábitats naturales de los Goon Giddy son las escaleras oscuras de castillos misteriosos y encantados. Se trata de unas criaturas muy territoriales y atacan a los que no son bienvenidos en sus alrededores. Los Goons Giddy domesticados son muy fieles a sus amos y los siguen a todas partes. Dales una espada y serán tus amigos para siempre. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Giddy Goons [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Giddy Goons [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Giddy Goons [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Giddy Goons [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Giddy Goons [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Giddy Goons natural habitats are the dark stairwells of mysterious and enchanted castles. They are a very territorial creature and will attack those who are not welcome in their vicinity. Domesticated Giddy Goons are very loyal to their masters and will follow them anywhere. Give them a sword and they will be your friend forever. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>