<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Classic left earring</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Boucle d'oreille classique gauche</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Klassische linke Ohrring</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Orecchino classic sinistra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pendiente izquierda clásico</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Altamar delivers high quality, stylish clothes with this discreet but captivating line. It specializes in couture designs, suitable to dazzle at any occasion.  Perfection, beauty and taste are combined in this superb collection. Dress with taste, dress with Altamar[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Altamar fournit des vêtements élégants de haute qualité avec cette ligne discrète mais à la fois captivante. Nous nous spécialisons dans des conceptions de couture, appropriées pour briller à n'importe quelle occasion. La perfection, la beauté et le goût sont combinés dans cette collection superbe. Habillez vous avec goût, habillez vous avec Altamar.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit dieser bezaubernden, dezenten Linie liefert Altamar hochwertige, modische Kleidung. Das Unternehmen ist auf Haute Couture Designs spezialisiert, die bei jeder Gelegenheit blendend aussieht. Perfektion, Schönheit und Geschmack sind in dieser erstklassigen Kollektion vereint. Kleiden Sie sich mit Geschmack, kleiden Sie sich mit Altamar.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Altamar distribuisce vestiti alla moda e di alta qualità con questa linea discreta ma accattivante. È specializzato nel design di alta moda, adatto a risplendere in ogni occasione. Perfezione, bellezza e gusto sono ben combinati in questa superba collezione. Vestiti con gusto, vestiti con Altamar.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Altamar ofrece ropa elegante de gran calidad. Con una línea discreta pero cautivadora, se especializa en diseños de alta costura idóneos para deslumbrar en cualquier ocasión. Perfección, belleza y clase se combinan en esta magnífica colección. Viste con gusto, viste Altamar.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>