<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Golden Retro Flyers Value Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack Économique Retro Flyers Dorés</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Goldene Retroflieger Vorteilspaket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Retro Flyers dorato</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete de Valor Voladores Retro Dorados</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゴールデン・レトロフライヤー・バリューパック</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Golden Retro Flyers Value Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*IGNORE*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Golden Retro Flyers Value Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Save nearly 30% off retail price with this exclusive Golden Retro Flyers Value Pack! Includes the Golden Mysterious UFO, Golden Daredevil Biplane, and Golden Supersonic Jetpack. Access your Retro Flyers for a major speed boost when moving at full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Économisez environ 30% du prix de vente avec ce Pack Économique exlusif Retro Flyers dorés ! Inclut l'OVNI Mystérieux Doré, le Biplan Casse-cou Doré et le Jetpack Supersonique Doré. Accédez à vos Retro Flyers pour obtenir un boost de vitesse majeur quand vous vous déplacez à la vitesse maximale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spare fast 30% des Verkaufspreises mit diesem exklusiven goldenen Retroflieger Vorteilspaket! Enthält das goldene mysteriöse UFO, den goldenen Daredevil-Doppeldecker und den goldenen Überschall-Jetpack. Verwende deine Retroflieger für einen beachtlichen Geschwindigkeitsschub bei voller Geschwindigkeit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Risparmia il 30% sul prezzo di vendita con l'esclusivo Pacchetto Retro Flyers dorato! Questo pacchetto comprende Retro Flyers UFO misterioso dorato, Biplano incursore dorato e Jetpack supersonico dorato. Utilizza i Retro Flyers per aumentare di molto la tua velocità quando corri al massimo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Ahorra alrededor del 30% del precio de mercadeo con el Paquete de Valor Voladores Retro Dorados exclusivo! Incluye los Voladores Retro OVNI Misterioso Dorado, Biplano Temerario Dorado y Jetpack Supersónico Dorado. Accede tus Voladores Retro para incrementar tu velocidad cuando vayas a máxima velocidad. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この特売ゴールデン・レトロフライヤー・バリューパックで値段が30%オフになります！ゴールデン・ミステリアス・ＵＦＯ、ゴールデン・デアデビル・バイプレーン、ゴールデン・スーパーソニック・ジェットパックが含まれます。フルスピードでの走行時に、超スピードを出すためにレトロフライヤーにアクセスしよう。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Save nearly 30% off retail price with this exclusive Golden Retro Flyers Value Pack! Includes the Golden Mysterious UFO, Golden Daredevil Biplane, and Golden Supersonic Jetpack. Access your Retro Flyers for a major speed boost when moving at full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*IGNORE* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Save nearly 30% off retail price with this exclusive Golden Retro Flyers Value Pack! Includes the Golden Mysterious UFO, Golden Daredevil Biplane, and Golden Supersonic Jetpack. Access your Retro Flyers for a major speed boost when moving at full running speed. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>