<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Auto-Feeder</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Distributeur Automatique de Nourriture</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Automatischer Futterverteiler</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Distributore automatico di cibo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Auto alimentador</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* Auto-Feeder</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Auto-Feeder</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Auto-Feeder</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Auto-Feeder</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Auto-Feeder</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Auto-Feeder</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">When placed in your tank the Auto-Feeder will allow your fish to go longer between feedings. Fish will be continuously fed over the course of a week. Perfect for going on vacation. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lorsqu'il est placé dans votre aquarium, le Distributeur Automatique de Nourriture permet à votre poisson de tenir plus longtemps entre les repas. Votre poisson sera continuellement nourri durant une semaine. Parfait si vous partez en vacances. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn er in Ihrem Tank platziert wird, ermöglicht der automatische Futterverteiler Ihren Fischen länger zwischen den Fütterungen durchzuhalten. Fische werden kontinuierlich über den Verlauf einer Woche hinweg gefüttert. Perfekt, falls Sie in Urlaub fahren. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una volta inserito il distributore automatico di cibo nella vasca i vostri pesci potranno andare avanti più a lungo fra un'alimentazione e l'altra. I pesci saranno nutriti continuamente per una settimana. Perfetto per quando andate in vacanza. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuando se coloca en el tanque, el auto alimentador permite que tus peces esperen más tiempo entre comidas. Los peces serán alimentados continuamente en el transcurso de una semana. Es perfecto para irte de vacaciones.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">When placed in your tank the Auto-Feeder will allow your fish to go longer between feedings. Fish will be continuously fed over the course of a week. Perfect for going on vacation. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>