<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Wild Limits Totebag (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Fourre-tout Wild Limits (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Wild Limits Tragetasche (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Wild Limits Borsa (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Wild Limits Bolso de mano (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">With its oversize body and bold cheetah print, the Wild Limits tote is sure to prowl its way to the top of your must-get list. As part of our 4th And Bleeker capsule collection, this unstructured beach bag is exclusive and was made in limited supply. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avec sa taille surdimensionnée et son imprimé de guépard, le fourre-tout Wild Limits est sûr de trouver sa place en tête de votre liste des indispensables. Dans le cadre de notre collection capsule 4th And Bleeker, ce sac de plage déstructuré est une exclusivité et a été fabriqué en série limitée. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese extragroße Wild Limits Tragetasche mit auffälligem Gepardenmuster befindet sich auf dem Weg zur Nummer Eins auf der Liste der unbedingt benötigten Accessoires. Diese unstrukturierte Strandtasche ist Teil unserer exklusiven 4th And Bleeker Kollektion und nur in limitierter Auflage erhältlich. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Con le sue dimensioni ampie e la vivace stampa leopardata, la borsa Wild Limits andrà di sicuro in cima alla tua lista di accessori da avere. Come parte della nostra collezione di articoli intramontabili 4th And Bleeker, questa borsa da mare è esclusiva ed è stata realizzata in edizione limitata. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con su tamaño maxi y su atrevido estampado de guepardo, el bolso de mano Wild Limits pronto se encaramará a lo alto de tu lista de compras preferentes.  Como parte de nuestra colección perenne 4th And Bleeker, este bolso de playa desestructurado es totalmente exclusivo y ha sido fabricado en edición limitada. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>