<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Feisar Chair </LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Feisar Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fauteuil Feisar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Feisar-Stuhl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sedia Feisar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Silla de Feisar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Feisar Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Feisar 의자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Feisar Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Feisar 椅子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Feisar 椅子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Feisar Chair</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Feisar offer this distinctive chair emblazoned with their instantly, globally recognised logo. It’s deceptively simple construction offers supreme comfort. Sitting on the reinforced, composite weave is the closest thing to anti-gravity that you could experience in your home.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Feisar offer this distinctive chair emblazoned with their instantly, globally recognised logo. It’s deceptively simple construction offers supreme comfort. Sitting on the reinforced, composite weave is the closest thing to anti-gravity that you could experience in your home. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Feisar propose ce fauteuil unique, orné de son logo instantanément reconnaissable dans le monde entier. Sa fabrication étonnamment simple garantit un confort suprême. Asseyez-vous sur son tissu composite renforcé pour ressentir des sensations proches de l'anti-gravité dans l'intimité de votre domicile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Feisar bietet diesen unverwechselbaren Stuhl, versehen mit ihrem weltbekannten Firmenlogo. Seine täuschend simple Konstruktion bietet höchsten Komfort. In den eigenen vier Wänden wird ein Gefühl vermittelt, das der Schwerelosigkeit extrem nahe kommt, wenn man auf seinem verstärkten Kompositgewebe sitzt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Feisar presenta una sedia peculiare, decorata con il proprio logo facilmente riconoscibile in tutto il mondo. La struttura, apparentemente semplice, offre una comodità massima. Nell'ambito domestico, il tessuto composito rinforzato crea un effetto quasi antigravitazionale. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Feisar te ofrece esta distinguida silla, engalanada con su logotipo, mundialmente conocido. Su construcción, aparentemente sencilla, te ofrece un confort insuperable. Sentarse sobre su tejido compuesto reforzado es obtener la sensación más parecida a la antigravedad que pueda lograrse en el hogar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Feisar offer this distinctive chair emblazoned with their instantly, globally recognised logo. It’s deceptively simple construction offers supreme comfort. Sitting on the reinforced, composite weave is the closest thing to anti-gravity that you could experience in your home. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Feisar 의자에는 세계에서 널리 알려진 그들의 로고가 큼지막하게 새겨져 있습니다. 언뜻 보기에는 너무나 심플한 디자인이지만, 이 의자의 편안함을 실제로 체험해 보기 전에는 섣불리 판단하지 마세요. 반중력장에 들어온 것 같은 기분입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Feisar offer this distinctive chair emblazoned with their instantly, globally recognised logo. It’s deceptively simple construction offers supreme comfort. Sitting on the reinforced, composite weave is the closest thing to anti-gravity that you could experience in your home. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這張與別不同的椅子由Feisar製造，上面刻有他們世界知名的公司標誌。不要被它那簡單的外表所欺騙，這張椅子的舒適度會讓您大吃一驚，而經強化的複合表面將會讓您在家裡也能感受得到最貼近反重力的體驗。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這張與別不同的椅子由Feisar製造，上面刻有他們世界知名的公司標誌。不要被它那簡單的外表所欺騙，這張椅子的舒適度會讓您大吃一驚，而經強化的複合表面將會讓您在家裡也能感受得到最貼近反重力的體驗。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Feisar offer this distinctive chair emblazoned with their instantly, globally recognised logo. It’s deceptively simple construction offers supreme comfort. Sitting on the reinforced, composite weave is the closest thing to anti-gravity that you could experience in your home. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>