<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Star Wars™ Celebration V Poster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Poster Star Wars™ Célébration V</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Star Wars™ Celebration V-Plakat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Poster Star Wars™ Celebration V</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Póster de la V Celebración de La guerra de las galaxias</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スター・ウォーズ　セレブレーションＶポスター</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">스타 워즈 셀러브레이션 5 포스터</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Star Wars™ Celebration V Poster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">星際大戰五部曲紀念海報</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">星際大戰五部曲紀念海報</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Star Wars™ Celebration V Poster</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is the official poster of Star Wars Celebration V. If you were there, wanted to be there, knew someone who was there or thought about going but just couldn’t make it, you need this poster.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C'est le poster officiel de Star Wars Célébration V. Si vous y étiez, vouliez y être, connaissez quelqu'un qui y était ou avez pensé y aller mais sans y arriver, il vous faut ce poster.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dies ist das offizielle Plakat der Star Wars Celebration V. Wenn du dabei warst, dabei sein wolltest, jemanden kennst, der dabei war oder der daran dachte hinzugehen, es aber leider nicht schaffte, dann musst du dieses Plakat einfach haben.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Si tratta del poster ufficiale di Star Wars Celebration V. Se eri sul posto, se volevi esserci, se conosci qualcuno che c'era, o anche se ci volevi andare ma non potevi, questo poster non può mancare, nella tua collezione.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este es el póster oficial de la V Celebración de La guerra de las galaxias. Si estuviste allí, querías estar allí, conocías a alguien que estuvo allí o pensaste en ir pero no pudiste, necesitas este póster. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スター・ウォーズ　セレブレーションＶの公式ポスター。参加した方、参加した人を知っている方、参加したかった方、そして参加しそうだったけど参加しなかった方におススメです！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">스타 워즈 셀러브레이션 5 공식 포스터. 스타 워즈 셀러브레이션 5에[#Legal]  참석하는 분, 참석하길 원하는 분, 친구가 참석하는 분, 부득이한 사정으로 참석을 못하는 분 모두에게 필요한 포스터입니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This is the official poster of Star Wars Celebration V. If you were there, wanted to be there, knew someone who was there or thought about going but just couldn’t make it, you need this poster.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這是星際大戰五部曲的官方紀念海報。如果你有去、想去、知道有人去、或是差點就去了但沒去成，那麼你需要這個海報。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這是星際大戰五部曲的官方紀念海報。如果你有去、想去、知道有人去、或是差點就去了但沒去成，那麼你需要這個海報。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This is the official poster of Star Wars Celebration V. If you were there, wanted to be there, knew someone who was there or thought about going but just couldn’t make it, you need this poster.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>