<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stack Genius Game</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jeu "Stack Genius"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das "Stack Genius" Spiel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gioco Stack Genius</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Juego Stack Genius</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Stack Genius Game</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This game consists of 4 levels: the Red Chamber, the Green Chamber, the Blue Chamber, and finally the Yellow Chamber. This bundle contains all 4 levels in the form of private spaces, as well as the red Cube furniture item. You can solve the Red Chamber with the Red Cube. Completing the Red Chamber will give you a green block, to unlock the following level: the Green Chamber. And so on: complete the Green Chamber, in order to obtain the blue block that will solve the Blue Chamber; and finally, solving the Blue Chamber will in turn give you the yellow block, to solve the Yellow Chamber, and win the Stack Genius trophy. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce jeu comporte 4 niveaux: la chambre rouge, la chambre verte, la chambre bleue et enfin la chambre jaune. Ce bundle contient les 4 niveaux sous forme d'espaces privés, ainsi que le meuble "cube rouge". Vous pouvez compléter la chambre rouge à l'aide du cube rouge. Cela vous donnera un bloc vert, qui vous permettra de résoudre le niveau suivant: la chambre verte. Et ainsi de suite: complétez la chambre verte afin d'obtenir le bloc bleu, qui résoudra la chambre bleue. Enfin, compléter la chambre bleue vous donnera le bloc jaune, clé de la chambre jaune: résolvez la chambre jaune pour gagner le trophée Stack Genius. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Spiel besteht aus vier Ebenen: die roten Kammer, die Grüne Kammer, die Blaue Kammer, und schließlich die Gelb Kammer. Dieses Bundle enthält alle 4 Ebenen in Form von privaten Räumen, sowie die rote Cube Möbelstück. Sie können die Roten Kammer mit dem Red Cube zu lösen. Abschließen der Roten Kammer geben Ihnen einen grünen Block, um die folgende Level freizuschalten: Die grüne Kammer. Und so weiter: Abschluss der Grünen Kammer, um den blauen Block, der die Blue Chamber lösen kann, zu erhalten. Und schließlich, die Lösung des Blue Chamber wird wiederum geben Ihnen die gelben Block, um den Gelb Kammer zu lösen, und gewinnen Sie den Stack Genius Trophäe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo gioco ha quattro livelli: la sala rossa, la sala verde, la sala blu ed infine la sala gialla. Questo bundle contiene 4 livelli come spazi privati​​, così come mobili "cubo rosso". È possibile completare la sala rossa con il cubo rosso. Questo vi darà un blocco verde, si risolverà il prossimo livello: la sala verde. E così via: completare la sala verde per ottenere il blocco blu, che risolveràla sala blu. Infine, completare la sala blu vi darà la chiave di blocco giallo della camera gialla: Risolvere la sala gialla di vincere il trofeo "Stack Genius". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este juego consta de 4 niveles: la cámara roja, la cámara verde, la cámara azul, y finalmente la cámara amarilla. Este paquete contiene los 4 niveles en la forma de los espacios privados, así como el cubo mueble rojo. Usted puede resolver la cámara roja con el cubo rojo. Completandola cámara roja le dará un bloque verde, para desbloquear el nivel siguiente: la Sala Verde. Y así sucesivamente: completar la Sala Verde, con el fin de obtener el bloque azul que va a resolver la Sala Azul; y, finalmente, la resolución de la Sala Azul, a su vez le dará el bloque amarillo, para resolver la Cámara Amarillo, y ganar el trofeo "Stack Genius". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">&gt;This game consists of 4 levels: the Red Chamber, the Green Chamber, the Blue Chamber, and finally the Yellow Chamber. This bundle contains all 4 levels in the form of private spaces, as well as the red Cube furniture item. You can solve the Red Chamber with the Red Cube. Completing the Red Chamber will give you a green block, to unlock the following level: the Green Chamber. And so on: complete the Green Chamber, in order to obtain the blue block that will solve the Blue Chamber; and finally, solving the Blue Chamber will in turn give you the yellow block, to solve the Yellow Chamber, and win the Stack Genius trophy. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>