<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LOOT™ TV Wall Mount</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">SUPPORT MURAL DE TÉLÉVISEUR  LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LOOT™ TV-Wandhalterung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Staffa a muro TV LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Soporte de pared para televisor LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LOOT™ TV Wall Mount</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use the LOOT™ TV Wall Mount to hang your wall mounted LOOT EOD TVs on any wall that can hold a picture frame. Simply hang the mount on the wall like a picture frame then hook your Wall Mounted EOD TV on it. Decorating has never been so easy! The six incredible wall mounted EOD TV Models are exclusive to the LOOT™ EOD TV Bundle. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez le Support Mural de Téléviseur LOOT™ pour accrocher vos Téléviseurs muraux EOD LOOT sur tout mur supportant un cadre. Fixez simplement votre support au mur comme un cadre puis accrochez dessus votre Télé Murale EOD. La décoration devient un vrai jeu d'enfant ! Les six fabuleux modèles de Téléviseurs Muraux EOD sont exclusifs avec le lot de Téléviseurs EOD LOOT™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit der LOOT™ TV-Wandhalterung kannst du LOOT EOD-TV-Geräte an jeder Wand platzieren, an die ein Bilderrahmen passt. Hänge einfach die Halterung wie einen Bilderrahmen an die Wand und hake dein EOD-TV-Gerät darin ein. Einrichten war noch nie so leicht! Die sechs unglaublichen wandmontierten EOD-TV-Modelle sind nur im LOOT™ EOD-TV-Bundle enthalten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usa la staffa a muro TV LOOT™ per fissare la tua TV LOOT EOD su qualsiasi muro possa sostenere una cornice. Fissa la staffa al muro come una cornice e poi aggancia la TV EOD. Arredare è diventato un gioco da ragazzi! Dai un'occhiata ai sei fantastici modelli di TV EOD: sono esclusivi nel Pacchetto TV LOOT™ EOD. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Utiliza el soporte de pared del televisor LOOT™ para colgar los televisores de pared EOD de LOOT en cualquier pared en la que se pueda colgar un cuadro. Solo tienes que colgar el soporte en la pared como si fuese el marco de un cuadro y colgar en él tu televisor EOD de pared. ¡Decorar nunca ha sido tan fácil! Los seis increíbles modelos de televisores EOD de pared son exclusivos del lote de televisores EOD de LOOT™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Use the LOOT™ TV Wall Mount to hang your wall mounted LOOT EOD TVs on any wall that can hold a picture frame. Simply hang the mount on the wall like a picture frame then hook your Wall Mounted EOD TV on it. Decorating has never been so easy! The six incredible wall mounted EOD TV Models are exclusive to the LOOT™ EOD TV Bundle. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>