<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Musicality Club House</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pavillon Musicalité</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Musik-Clubhaus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Club House Musicality</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Musicalidad Club House</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ミュージッククラブハウス</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Musicality Club House</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Musicality Club House</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Musicality Club House</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Musicality Club House</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Musicality Club House</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A unique live music venue perfect for hosting club gatherings. Up to four players can grab an instrument and jam/compete against other club members. Comes complete with all music packs - Dance, Rock and RnB. Please note, in order to access this Club House you will need to have purchased the Club House slot from either the Estates Store or the Clubs menu (available in Options).[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une salle de concert unique et idéale pour se retrouver. Jusqu’à quatre joueurs peuvent saisir un instrument, jouer et se mesurer à d’autres membres. Tous les packs de musique sont inclus - Dance, Rock et RnB. Veuillez noter que pour accéder à ce pavillon, vous devez d’abord acheter l’espace Pavillon dans la boutique Propriétés ou le menu Pavillons (disponibles dans les Options).[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein einzigartiger Veranstaltungsort für Livemusik und Clubtreffen. Bis zu vier Spieler können sich ein Instrument schnappen und mit anderen Clubmitgliedern jammen/sich messen. Komplett mit allen Musik-Packs - Dance, Rock und RnB. Anmerkung - um Zugang zu diesem Clubhaus zu erhalten, musst du das Clubhaus-Grundstück erworben haben, entweder aus dem Immobilien-Store oder dem Club-Menü (verfügbar in Optionen).[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un locale con musica dal vivo unico e perfetto per incontrarsi. Fino a quattro giocatori possono afferrare i loro strumenti e suonare insieme o competere contro altri membri del club. Presenta tutti i pacchetti musicali: dance, rock e RnB. Nota: per accedere a questa Club House dovrai aver acquistato lo slot Club House dal Negozio Immobili o dal menu Club (disponibile nelle Opzioni).[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un local exclusivo de música en vivo, ideal para reuniones discotequeras. Hasta cuatro jugadores podrán pillar un instrumento y tocar y competir contra otros miembros. Viene incluido con paquetes de música: dance, rock y RnB. Ten en cuenta que, para acceder a este Club House tendrás que haber comprado el hueco del Club House o bien de la tienda de Estados o del menú de Clubs (disponible en Opciones).[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">クラブハウスのご利用には別途クラブの購入及びクラブ作成が必要となります。 クラブならびにクラブハウスの詳細については、ヘルプまたは公式Webサイトをご参照下さい。\n\nみんなで集まって音楽を楽しむのにピッタリの空間です。最大4人のプレイヤーが楽器を手に取り、他のクラブメンバーとジャムセッションしたり楽器の腕を競ったりすることができます。ダンス、ロック、RnBなどの各種音楽パックと合わせて遊んでください。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">A unique live music venue perfect for hosting club gatherings. Up to four players can grab an instrument and jam/compete against other club members. Comes complete with all music packs - Dance, Rock and RnB. Please note, in order to access this Club House you will need to have purchased the Club House slot from either the Estates Store or the Clubs menu (available in "Social" under the Menu Screen). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A unique live music venue perfect for hosting club gatherings. Up to four players can grab an instrument and jam/compete against other club members. Comes complete with all music packs - Dance, Rock and RnB. Please note, in order to access this Club House you will need to have purchased the Club House slot from either the Estates Store or the Clubs menu (available in "Social" under the Menu Screen). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">A unique live music venue perfect for hosting club gatherings. Up to four players can grab an instrument and jam/compete against other club members. Comes complete with all music packs - Dance, Rock and RnB. Please note, in order to access this Club House you will need to have purchased the Club House slot from either the Estates Store or the Clubs menu (available in "Social" under the Menu Screen). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">A unique live music venue perfect for hosting club gatherings. Up to four players can grab an instrument and jam/compete against other club members. Comes complete with all music packs - Dance, Rock and RnB. Please note, in order to access this Club House you will need to have purchased the Club House slot from either the Estates Store or the Clubs menu (available in "Social" under the Menu Screen). [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A unique live music venue perfect for hosting club gatherings. Up to four players can grab an instrument and jam/compete against other club members. Comes complete with all music packs - Dance, Rock and RnB. Please note, in order to access this Club House you will need to have purchased the Club House slot from either the Estates Store or the Clubs menu (available in Options). [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>