<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Penny Scarlett - Shoes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Penny Scarlett - Chaussures</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Penny Scarlett - Schuhe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Penny Scarlett - Scarpe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Penny Scarlett - Zapatos</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Penny Scarlett - Shoes</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to the world of the secret agent, where espionage and double dealings are a way of life.  Slip undercover oozing charm and sophistication with a deadly appeal, ruthlessly sexy and chillingly alluring.  Feel the bonds of love pull tighter; just be careful who you fall for! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue dans le monde des agents secrets où espionnage et double jeu sont les maîtres-mots. Faites en sorte que personne ne décèle votre couverture en usant de votre classe, finesse, charme et sex-appeal dévastateurs.  Laissez-vous envahir par vos sentiments, mais attention à ne pas craquer pour n’importe qui ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen in der Welt der Geheimagenten, in der Spionage und Betrug zum Leben gehören. Schlüpfe in den Untergrund und triefe vor Charme und Raffinesse mit einer tödlichen Anziehung, schonungslos sexy und eiskalt verführend. Fühle, wie sich die Fesseln der Liebe enger ziehen; sei aber vorsichtig, für wen du fällst! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Benvenuti nel mondo degli agenti segreti, dove spionaggio e doppio gioco la fanno da padroni.  Scivolate sotto copertura effondendo sensualità e classe con il vostro fascino letale, spietatamente sexy e terribilmente irresistibili. Lasciatevi incatenare dall’amore ma... attenzione a non invaghirvi della persona sbagliata! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido al mundo de los agentes secretos, donde el espionaje y las trampas son una forma de vida. Deslízate de incógnito rebosando encanto y sofisticación con un atractivo mortal, despiadadamente sexy y escalofriantemente seductor. Siente  como los lazos del amor te atrapan fuertemente, ¡pero  ten cuidado de quién te enamoras! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome to the world of the secret agent, where espionage and double dealings are a way of life.  Slip undercover oozing charm and sophistication with a deadly appeal, ruthlessly sexy and chillingly alluring.  Feel the bonds of love pull tighter; just be careful who you fall for! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>