<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Demon Crystal Throne</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Démon cristal Trône</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dämon Kristall Thron</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Demone di cristallo Trono</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Demonio de Cristal Trono</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Demon Crystal Throne</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You are dark and powerful.  Some would settle for a run-of-the-mill throne, not you!  You deserve the seat that is luxurious AND ominous.  The Demon Crystal Throne says "I'm better than you." Why would you sit on anything else?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous êtes sombre et puissante. Certains pourraient se contenter d'un trône run-of-the-mill, pas vous! Vous méritez le siège qui est luxueux et de mauvais augure. Démon Cristal Trône dit que je suis meilleur que toi. Pourquoi vous vous asseyez sur autre chose?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie sind dunkel und mächtig. Einige würden für einen run-of-the-mill Thron niederlassen, nicht du! Du verdienst den Sitz, die luxuriösen und bedrohlich ist. The Demon Kristall Thron sagt: "Ich bin besser als du". Warum würden Sie auf etwas anderes zu sitzen?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Voi siete scure e potenti. Qualcuno potrebbe accontentarsi di un run-of-the-mill trono, non tu! Ti meriti il ​​posto che è lusso e inquietante. Il Trono di cristallo Demone dice "Io sono meglio di te." Perché ci si siede su qualcos'altro?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Usted está oscura y poderosa. Algunos se conformarían con un trono run-of-the-mill, no usted! Usted merece el asiento que es de lujo y de mal agüero. El trono de cristal demonio dice: "Yo soy mejor que tú." ¿Por qué te sientas en cualquier otra cosa?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You are dark and powerful.  Some would settle for a run-of-the-mill throne, not you!  You deserve the seat that is luxurious AND ominous.  The Demon Crystal Throne says "I'm better than you." Why would you sit on anything else?[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>