<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Mini-skirt &amp; Socks 7-piece Set (Red Checked, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set 7 pièces Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes (rouge à carreaux, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Minirock &amp; Socken 7-teiliges Set (rotkariert, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set 7 minigonne (a scacchi rossi, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de siete artículos de minifalda y calcetines (roja a cuadros, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ミニスカート＆ソックス７点セット（赤チェック・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Mini-skirt &amp; Socks 7-piece Set (Red Checked, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">7-piece set of checked red mini skirts with different socks. No socks, 5 types of navy blue socks (ankle, crew, knee, over-the-knee, thigh), and black tights. \nDefensive Strength: ★\nYouth Level: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Mini-skirt &amp; No Socks (Red Checked, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Ankle Socks (Red Checked &amp; Navy, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Crew Socks (Red Checked &amp; Navy, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Knee Socks (Red Checked &amp; Navy, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Over-the-Knee Socks (Red Checked &amp; Navy, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Thigh High Socks (Red Checked &amp; Navy, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Tights (Red Checked &amp; Black, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set 7 pièces de mini-jupes à carreaux rouges avec différentes chaussettes. Sans chaussettes, et 5 types de chaussettes bleu marine (socquettes, chaussettes de sport, sous le genou, au-dessus du genou et aux cuisses) et des collants noirs. \nDéfense : ★\nNiveau de Jeunesse : ★★★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Mini-jupe Sans Chaussettes (rouge à carreaux, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Socquettes (rouge à carreaux &amp; marines, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes de Sport (rouge à carreaux &amp; marines, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes sous le Genou (rouge à carreaux &amp; marines, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes au-dessus du Genou (rouge à carreaux &amp; marines, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Chaussettes aux Cuisses (rouge à carreaux &amp; marines, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n- Mini-jupe &amp; Collants (rouge à carreaux &amp; noirs, femme) (Bas, Chaussures)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">7-teiliges Set eines rotkarierten Minirocks ohne Socken und mit 5 verschiedenen Typen marineblauer Socken (Söckchen, Waden, Knie, Overknee, Schenkel) und schwarzen Strumpfhosen. \nVerteidigung: ★\nJugendlichkeitslevel: ★★★\nDas Set beinhaltet die folgenden Kleidungsstücke:\n\n- Minirock ohne Socken (rotkariert, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Minirock &amp; Söckchen (rotkariert &amp; marineblau, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe) \n- Minirock &amp; Wadensocken (rotkariert &amp; marineblau, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Minirock &amp; Kniestrümpfe (rotkariert &amp; marineblau, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Minirock &amp; Overknees (rotkariert &amp; marineblau, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Minirock &amp; Schenkelstrümpfe (rotkariert &amp; marineblau, für Frauen) (Unterteil, Schuhe)\n- Minirock &amp; Strumpfhosen (rotkariert &amp; schwarz, für Frauen) Unterteil, Schuhe)\n \n- Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set composto da 7 minigonne decorate con una trama a scacchi rossa, senza calzini o accoppiate con diversi tipi di calzini bianchi (alla caviglia, calzettoni, sotto le ginocchia, sopra le ginocchia, collant) e calze nere.\nDifesa: ★\nLivello giovinezza: ★★★\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Minigonna (a scacchi rossi, senza calzini, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi rossi con calzini alla caviglia blu scuri, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi rossi con calzettoni blu scuro, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi rossi con calzini sotto le ginocchia blu scuro, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi rossi con calzini sopra le ginocchia blu scuro, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n- Minigonna (a scacchi rossi con collant blu scuro, da donna) (parti inferiori, scarpe)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de siete artículos con minifalda a cuadros rojos con diferentes calcetines. Sin calcetines, cinco tipos de calcetines azul marino (cortos, de deporte, a la altura de la rodilla, por encima de la rodilla y a la altura del muslo) y leotardos negros. \nDefensa: ★\nNivel de juventud: ★★★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Minifalda y sin calcetines (roja a cuadros, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines cortos (roja a cuadros y azul marino, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines de deporte (roja a cuadros y azul marino, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines hasta la rodilla (roja a cuadros y azul marino, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines por encima de la rodilla (roja a cuadros y azul marino, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y calcetines hasta el muslo (roja a cuadros y azul marino, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n- Minifalda y leotardos (roja a cuadros y negros, mujer) (piernas, zapatos)\n\n*Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría. [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">赤チェック柄ミニスカートの、足元違い７点セット。素足、紺ソックス５種（足首丈、スネ丈、膝下丈、膝上丈、太もも丈）、黒タイツ。\n防御力：　★\n青春度：　★★★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・ミニスカートと素足（赤チェック・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n・ミニスカートとアンクルソックス（赤チェック＆紺・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n・ミニスカートとクルーソックス（赤チェック＆紺・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n・ミニスカートとハイソックス（赤チェック＆紺・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n・ミニスカートとオーバーニーソックス（赤チェック＆紺・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n・ミニスカートとサイハイソックス（赤チェック＆紺・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n・ミニスカートとタイツ（赤チェック＆黒・女性）（ボトムズ・靴）\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">7-piece set of checked red mini skirts with different socks. No socks, 5 types of navy blue socks (ankle, crew, knee, over-the-knee, thigh), and black tights. \nDefensive Strength: ★\nYouth Level: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Mini-skirt &amp; No Socks (Red Checked, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Ankle Socks (Red Checked &amp; Navy, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Crew Socks (Red Checked &amp; Navy, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Knee Socks (Red Checked &amp; Navy, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Over-the-Knee Socks (Red Checked &amp; Navy, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Thigh High Socks (Red Checked &amp; Navy, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n- Mini-skirt &amp; Tights (Red Checked &amp; Black, Women) (Bottom, Shoes)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category. [#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
