<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Boba Fett Mandalorian Gloves</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Gants Mandaloriens Boba Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Boba Fett Mandalorianische Handschuhe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guanti Mandaloriani Boba Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guantes mandalorianos de Boba Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_Hands_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_Hands_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Boba Fett Mandalorian Gloves</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_Hands_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_Hands_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Boba Fett Mandalorian Gloves</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">These are the gloves of the most famous galactic bounty hunter, Boba Fett. He wore Mandalorian armor and was a clone of the famed Jango Fett. Boba Fett was one of six bounty hunters hired by Darth Vader to track and capture the Millennium Falcon. Fett was successful by setting a trap for the Millennium Falcon on Bespin.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce sont les gants du plus célèbre chasseur de primes de la galaxie, Boba Fett. Il a porté cette armure mandalorienne et est un clone du non moins célèbre Jango Fett. Boba Fett est l'un des six chasseurs de primes chargés par Dark Vador de traquer et de capturer le Faucon Millenium. Fett y a d'ailleurs réussi en tendant un piège au Faucon Millenium sur Bespin.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Handschuhe des berühmtesten galaktischen Kopfgeldjägers Boba Fett. Er trug mandalorianischen Schutzpanzer und war ein Klon vom berühmten Jango Fett. Boba Fett war einer von sechs Kopfgeldjägern, die Darth Vader anheuerte, um den Rasenden Falken zu finden und gefangen zu nehmen. Fett war es, der den Rasenden Falken auf dem Bespin in eine Falle locken konnte.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questi sono i guanti del più famoso dei cacciatori di taglie galattici, Boba Fett. Indossava un'armatura mandaloriana ed era un clone del rinomato Jargo Fett. Boba Fett era uno dei sei cacciatori di taglie assoldati da Darth Vader per rintracciare e catturare il Millenium Falcon. Fett era riuscito a tendere una trappola per la Millenium Falcon su Bespin.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estos son los guantes del cazarrecompensas más famoso de la galaxia, Boba Fett. Boba llevaba una armadura mandoloriana y era un clon del conocido Jango Fett.  Boba Fett es uno de los seis cazarrecompensas contratados por Darth Vader para dar con el Millennium Falcon y capturarlo. Fett consiguió con éxito ponerle una trampa al Millennium Falcon en Bespin.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_Hands_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_Hands_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">These are the gloves of the most famous galactic bounty hunter, Boba Fett. He wore Mandalorian armor and was a clone of the famed Jango Fett. Boba Fett was one of six bounty hunters hired by Darth Vader to track and capture the Millennium Falcon. Fett was successful by setting a trap for the Millennium Falcon on Bespin.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_Hands_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_Hands_Boba_Fett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">These are the gloves of the most famous galactic bounty hunter, Boba Fett. He wore Mandalorian armor and was a clone of the famed Jango Fett. Boba Fett was one of six bounty hunters hired by Darth Vader to track and capture the Millennium Falcon. Fett was successful by setting a trap for the Millennium Falcon on Bespin.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>