<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dead to Rights®: Retribution GAC Scout Top</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Haut d'éclaireur de GAC Dead to Rights®: Retribution</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dead to Rights®: Retribution - corazza esploratore GAC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Parte superior de observador del GAC de Dead to Rights®: Retribution</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">『DEAD TO RIGHTS®：RETRIBUTION』GACスカウトアーマー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">「Dead to Rights®: Retribution」 방탄 조끼(남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Dead to Rights®: Retribution GAC Scout Top (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「Dead to Rights®: Retribution」 GAC防彈上衣(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「Dead to Rights®: Retribution」 GAC防彈上衣(男用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dead to Rights®: Retribution GAC Scout Top</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">GAC model 12 Law Enforcement armour is a tactical body armour for urban terrain operations, custom-built for Grant City's Anti-Crime Division.  Designed for mobility, the model 12 armour provides maximum upper body protection, with the versatility of lighter short-sleeve armour.  Hard armour panels provide forearm, elbow, and upper arm protection, and are covered by a durable para-aramid weave. Asymmetrical shoulder armour provides maximum defence during tactical operations, and a low-profile ballistic collar offers minimum restriction in tight spaces.  Breathable mesh underarmour vents provide maximum temperature control.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le modèle 12 de l'armure des forces de l'ordre du GAC est une armure tactique conçue pour les opérations en milieux urbains et fabriquée sur mesure pour la division anti-crime de Grant City.  Conçu pour garantir une mobilité totale, ce modèle offre une protection maximale de la partie supérieure du corps, ainsi que la versatilité et la légèreté d'une armure à manches courtes.  Des plaques solides fournissent une protection pour les avant-bras, les coudes et le haut des bras, et sont recouvertes d'un tissage d'aramide. Une armure asymétrique pour les épaules offre une protection maximale lors des opérations tactiques, et une encolure balistique discrète entrave au minimum les mouvements dans les espaces étroits.  Enfin, un système de maille aérée sous l'armure permet un contrôle optimal de la température.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La corazza modello 12 GAC da azione è un'armatura tattica per operazioni civili, costruita appositamente per la divisione anti-crimine di Grant City.  Progettata per gli spostamenti, il modello 12 fornisce la massima protezione al busto, con la versatilità di una corazza a maniche corte.  Delle piastre rigide, ricoperte da uno strato resistente in kevlar, forniscono protezione agli avambracci, ai gomiti e alla parte superiore delle braccia. L'armatura  delle spalle asimmetrica garantisce un'ottima copertura durante le manovre tattiche, mentre il collare balistico offre la minor resistenza possibile negli spazi ristretti.  Gli spiragli in tessuto della corazza per la traspirazione garantiscono un controllo della temperatura ottimale.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La armadura policial modelo 12 del GAC es una armadura corporal táctica para operaciones en terreno urbano, personalizada para el Grupo de Asalto contra el Crimen.  Diseñada con la vista puesta en la movilidad, el modelo 12 proporciona una protección óptima del tren superior con la versatilidad de una armadura ligera de manga corta.  Los paneles de armadura cubiertos de resistentes fibras de para-aramida proporcionan protección para los antebrazos, codos y parte superior de los brazos. Las hombreras asimétricas proporcionan una defensa óptima durante las operaciones tácticas y el discreto collar balístico minimiza la restricción de movimiento en espacios estrechos.  La malla de licra transpirable proporciona un control óptimo de la temperatura.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">GACモデル12アーマーは、市街地作戦用のボディアーマーで、GACに特化して作られた装甲である。機動性を重視した作りとなっており、上半身を最大限に守りつつも、袖の短いアーマーならではの軽さで動きやすさを実現している。前腕、肘、上腕を守る強固なアーマーパネルは、耐久性の高いパラアラミド繊維で覆われており、左右非対称のショルダーアーマーは戦術行動時に強固な防御力を発揮する。また目立たないデザインで首周辺を守るバリスティックカラーは、狭い空間でも極力動きやすいよう作られている。また通気性の良いメッシュ素材のアンダーアーマーが、高いレベルの体温調節を可能にさせている。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">GAC 표준 모델 12 방어구는 도심 지역에서의 작전에 사용되는 전술적 개인 보호구입니다. GAC 부서를 위해 특수 제작되었습니다. 이동성에 중점을 두었으므로 모델 12 방어구는 대부분의 장갑을 상반신에 할애하였고, 짧은 소매를 두어 운동성을 높였습니다. 단단한 장갑판이 팔, 팔꿈치, 그리고 상박을 감싸며, 파라-아라미드 섬유로 짜여져 있습니다. 비대칭의 어깨 장갑은 전술적인 상황에서 최대한의 보호를 제공하며, 좁은 공간에서도 움직임에 제약을 가하지 않습니다. 장갑판 아래의 메쉬 소재는 뛰어난 통풍으로 체온을 일정하게 유지합니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">GAC model 12 Law Enforcement armour is a tactical body armour for urban terrain operations, custom-built for Grant City's Anti-Crime Division.  Designed for mobility, the model 12 armour provides maximum upper body protection, with the versatility of lighter short-sleeve armour.  Hard armour panels provide forearm, elbow, and upper arm protection, and are covered by a durable para-aramid weave. Asymmetrical shoulder armour provides maximum defence during tactical operations, and a low-profile ballistic collar offers minimum restriction in tight spaces.  Breathable mesh underarmour vents provide maximum temperature control.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">GAC的12號防護裝備用於市區作戰，經GAC特別強化。高度重視機動性的設計，除了可以全面保護上半身外，短袖的設計亦讓使用者可靈活行動。保護前腕、手肘和上臂的部份以非常耐用的對位芳香聚醯胺纖維覆蓋，左右不對稱的肩膀護甲亦可在戰術行動時發揮頑強的防護力。保護頸部的領口採用低調的彈道學設計，確保在狹窄空間仍可活動自如。此外，護甲的襯裡以透氣性極高的網線製成，可大幅調節體溫。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">GAC的12號防護裝備用於市區作戰，經GAC特別強化。高度重視機動性的設計，除了可以全面保護上半身外，短袖的設計亦讓使用者可靈活行動。保護前腕、手肘和上臂的部份以非常耐用的對位芳香聚醯胺纖維覆蓋，左右不對稱的肩膀護甲亦可在戰術行動時發揮頑強的防護力。保護頸部的領口採用低調的彈道學設計，確保在狹窄空間仍可活動自如。此外，護甲的襯裡以透氣性極高的網線製成，可大幅調節體溫。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">GAC model 12 Law Enforcement armor is a tactical body armor for urban terrain operations, custom-built for Grant City's Anti-Crime Division.  Designed for mobility, the model 12 armor provides maximum upper body protection, with the versatility of lighter short-sleeve armor.  Hard armor panels provide forearm, elbow, and upper arm protection, and are covered by a durable para-aramid weave. Asymmetrical shoulder armor provides maximum defence during tactical operations, and a low-profile ballistic collar offers minimum restriction in tight spaces.  Breathable mesh underarmor vents provide maximum temperature control.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>