<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Cats Game Dress - Cool Wip (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Robe Cats Game - Cool Wip (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Cats Game Kleid - Cool Wip (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Cats Game Vestito - Panna (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Cats Game Vestido - Color nata (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Criss cross cut outs at back and a flirty baby doll silhouette has the Cats Game winning the style scene. Bell sleeves and a flutter hem add even more drama to help you score big fashion points. Length hits above the knee. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ses découpes entrecroisées dans le dos et sa silhouette de poupée aguicheuse placent la robe Cats Game à la pointe de la mode. Les manches cloches et l'ourlet irrégulier ajoutent encore une touche dramatique qui vous fera marquer des points de mode. Elle tombe au-dessus du genou. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Cats Game Kleid im Baby-Doll-Stil besticht durch die kreuzweisen Ausschnitte auf dem Rücken und dem leicht-luftigen Look. Glockenärmel und Zipfelsaum verleihen diesem modischen Kleid weitere Pluspunkte. Überknielänge. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'ampia scollatura sulla schiena con laccetti incrociati e il seducente taglio baby doll rendono il vestito Cats Game unico in fatto di stile. Le maniche a campana e l'orlo svolazzante aggiungono un tocco ancora più trendy e suggestivo. La lunghezza è sopra il ginocchio. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los recortes entrecruzados en la espalda y la silueta de muñeca coqueta hacen que el Cats Game se lleve el premio al estilo. Mangas de campana y bajos con pliegues le dan mayor espectacularidad para subir escalones en el pódium de la moda. Su longitud va hasta justo por encima de la rodilla. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>