<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cabin Boy Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot Cabin Boy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Cabin-Boy-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Cabin Boy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lote Cabin Boy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Cabin Boy Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">No Cabin Boy collection is complete unless you have all the greatest items now available for PlayStation®Home. This bundle, made to the true die-hard Cabin Boy fans, is the only way to own the “Lil’ Missus Hoodie – Black” for the girls and “Lil’ Dickie Hoodie – Black“ for the boys.  Also included are the female “Lil’ Dickie Hoodie – Coral”, and the male “Lil’ Dickie Hoodie – Blue”. Life on the open seas is grand! Well, maybe not for our Cabin Boy. Help our hero in this side-scrolling adventure get through the day! Catch the fish Lil’ Dickie throws to him, keep Lil’ Missus from burning under the hot sun and whatever you do, watch out for Chairman Meow!! Get to level 30 and win a free Cabin boy shirt: Lil’ Dickie for the boys, Lil’ Missus for the girls! For you hardcore gamers out there, accumulate 12,000 points over time to win the Golden Trout Trophy! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Votre collection Cabin Boy ne sera pas complète sans les meilleurs articles disponibles pour PlayStation®Home. Ce lot, conçu pour les vrais fans pur et dur de Cabin Boy, est le seul moyen d'avoir le sweat à capuche “Lil’ Missus – Noir” pour les filles et le sweat à capuche “Lil’ Dickie – Noir“ pour les garçons. Sont également inclus le sweat à capuche “Lil’ Dickie  – Corail” pour femme, et le sweat à capuche “Lil’ Dickie – Bleu” pour homme. La vie en pleine mer est grandiose ! Enfin, peut-être pas pour notre Cabin Boy. Aidez notre héros à tenir la journée dans cette aventure ! Attrapez le poisson Lil' Dickie qui lui est lancé, empêchez Lil' Missus de brûler au soleil et quoi que vous fassiez, prenez garde à Président Miaou !! Allez au niveau 30 et gagnez une chemise Cabin Boy gratuite : Lil's Dickie pour les garçons, Lil's Missus pour les filles ! Et pour vous joueurs inconditionnels, accumulez avec le temps 12 000 points pour gagner le Trophée Truite Dorée ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Keine Cabin-Boy-Sammlung ist komplett ohne die allertollsten Artikel, die es jetzt für PlayStation®Home gibt. Dieses Paket für die ganz harten Cabin-Boy-Fans ist die einzige Möglichkeit, den "Lil' Missus Kapuzenpulli - Schwarz" für Mädchen und den "Lil' Dickie Kapuzenpulli - Schwarz" für Jungs zu besitzen. Ebenfalls eingeschlossen sind der "Lil' Dickie Kapuzenpulli - Koralle" für Mädchen und "Lil' Dickie Kapuzenpulli -Blau" für Jungs. 
Das Leben auf dem offenen Meer ist toll! Nun ja, vielleicht nicht für unseren Cabin Boy. Hilf unserem Helden in diesem Abenteuer, es durch den Tag zu schaffen! Fang den Fisch, den Lil' Dickie ihm zuwirft, verhindere, dass Lil' Missus in der heißen Sonne verbrennt, und was du auch tust, pass auf den Vorsitzenden Miau auf!! Erreiche Level 30 und gewinne ein kostenloses Cabin-Boy-T-Shirt: Lil' Dickie für die Jungs, Lil' Missus für die Mädchen. Und für euch Hardcore-Gamer da draußen, sammelt 12.000 Punkte an, um die Trophäe der Goldenen Forelle zu gewinnen! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La vostra collezione Cabin Boy non è completa se non avete tutti gli articoli disponibili per PlayStation®Home. Questo pacchetto, creato per i fan più appassionati di Cabin Boy, è l'unico modo per avere la "Felpa con cappuccio Lil' Missus - Nera" da donna e la "Felpa con cappuccio Lil' Dickie - Nera" da uomo. Il pacchetto include anche la "Felpa con cappuccio Lil' Dickie - Corallo" da donna e la "Felpa con cappuccio Lil' Dickie - Blu" da uomo. La vita in mare aperto è fantastica! Be', forse non per il nostro Cabin Boy. Aiuta il nostro eroe in questa avventura del giorno! Cattura i pesci che gli lancia Lil' Dickie, stai attento che Lil' Missus non si scotti al sole e, qualsiasi cosa tu faccia, attento a Chairman Meow!! Raggiungi il livello 30 e vinci una maglia Cabin Boy: Lil' Dickie da uomo, Lil' Missus da donna! E voi, giocatori più appassionati, accumulate 12.000 punti per vincere il Trofeo Trota Dorata! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ninguna colección de Cabin Boy está completa sin los mejores artículos y productos ya disponibles para PlayStation®Home.  Este lote, hecho para los auténticos aficionados a Cabin Boy, es el único medio de disponer de la sudadera con capucha de Lil’ Missus Negra para  chicas, y la sudadera con capucha de Lil’ Dickie Negra para  chicos. También incluye la sudadera con capucha de Lil’ Missus Coral para  chicas, y la sudadera con capucha de Lil’ Dickie Azul  para  chicos. ¡La vida en alta mar es grandiosa! Bueno, tal vez no para nuestro Cabin Boy. ¡Ayuda a nuestro héroe a superar esta aventura! ¡Coge los peces que Lil’ Dickie le arroja, evita que Lil’ Missus se queme al sol, y hagas lo que hagas, ten cuidado con Presidente Miau! Consigue llegar al nivel 30 y gana una camiseta Cabin Boy gratuita: ¡Lil’ Dickie para los chicos y Lil’ Missus para las chicas! ¡Para los jugadores más duros, acumula 12.000 puntos para ganar el Trofeo de la Trucha Dorada! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">No Cabin Boy collection is complete unless you have all the greatest items now available for PlayStation®Home. This bundle, made to the true die-hard Cabin Boy fans, is the only way to own the “Lil’ Missus Hoodie – Black” for the girls and “Lil’ Bastard Hoodie – Black“ for the boys.  Also included are the female “Lil’ Missus Hoodie – Coral”, and the male “Lil’ Bastard Hoodie – Blue”. Life on the open seas is grand! Well, maybe not for our Cabin Boy. Help our hero in this  adventure to get through the day! Catch the fish Lil’ Bastard throws to him, keep Lil’ Missus from burning under the hot sun and whatever you do, watch out for Chairman Meow!! Get to level 30 and win a free Cabin boy shirt: Lil’ Bastard for the boys, Lil’ Missus for the girls! For you hardcore gamers out there, accumulate 12,000 points over time to win the Golden Trout Trophy! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>