<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Witch Bundle (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack sorcière (pour Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hexen-Paket (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Strega (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de bruja (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">마녀 번들 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Witch Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">女巫服裝組(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">女巫服裝組(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Witch Bundle (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Let it be known that those who dress as witches are sure to hold Halloween close to their hearts. Bundle includes a hat, top, gloves, and bottom. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si vous aimez la fête d'Halloween, cette tenue de sorcière est pour vous. Le pack comprend un chapeau, un haut, des gants et un bas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lass alle wissen, dass nur wer sich als Hexe verkleidet, den wahren Geist von Halloween in sich trägt. Im Paket enthalten sind ein Hut, Ober- und Unterteil und Handschuhe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chi si veste da strega ha Halloween nel cuore: più chiaro di così...! Il pacchetto include cappello, corsetto, guanti e parte sotto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Que se sepa que las que se visten de bruja aprecian el aspecto más tradicional de Halloween. El conjunto incluye un sombrero, corsé, guantes y falda. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">할로윈의 정신을 가슴에 받아들인 사람만이 마녀의 복장을 입을 수 있습니다. 이 번들은 마녀 모자, 마녀 상의, 마녀 장갑, 그리고 마녀 하의를 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Let it be known that those who dress as witches are sure to hold Halloween close to their hearts. Bundle includes the Witch Hat, Witch Top, Witch Gloves, and Witch Bottom. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">讓所有人都知道，打扮成巫婆的人肯定不會忘記萬聖節。本服裝組包括女巫帽、女巫服裝-上身、女巫手套和女巫服裝-下身。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">讓所有人都知道，打扮成巫婆的人肯定不會忘記萬聖節。本服裝組包括女巫帽、女巫服裝-上半身、女巫手套和女巫服裝-下半身。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Let it be known that those who dress as witches are sure to hold Halloween close to their hearts. Bundle includes a hat, top, gloves, and bottom. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>