<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Infinite Oasis Ranch Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Infinis oasis de ranch clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Endlose Oase"-Ranch: Clubhaus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sede del club Ranch oasi infinita</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sede del club Rancho del oasis infinito</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Infinite Oasis Ranch Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">무한의 오아시스 목장 클럽하우스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Infinite Oasis Ranch Clubhouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">無限綠洲牧場聯盟俱樂部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">無限綠洲牧場聯盟俱樂部</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Infinite Oasis Ranch Clubhouse</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The perfect place for a mid-summer retreat, the Infinite Oasis Ranch has it all. From lively cacti and ageless palm trees to panoramic views of the surrounding mountain ridge, this space packs it all. The Infinite Oasis Ranch space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'endroit idéal pour une retraite mi-été, Infinis oasis de ranch a tout. De vifs cactus et les palmiers intemporel d'une vue panoramique sur la crête des montagnes environnantes, cet espace packs tout. Infinis oasis de ranch clubhouse est un espace où chacun est invité à se joindre. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der perfekte Ort für den Sommer – die "Endlose Oase"-Ranch ist unglaublich vielseitig. Von wilden Kakteen und uralten Palmen bis zum Panoramablick auf die Bergkämme in der Umgebung findest du hier alles. Die "Endlose Oase"-Ranch ist ein Clubhaus, in dem jeder Gast willkommen ist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Ranch oasi infinita è il luogo perfetto per una seconda casa di mezza estate. Dai vivaci cactus e palme senza tempo, alle viste panoramiche delle circostanti catene montuose, questo spazio offre di tutto. Il Ranch oasi infinita è una sede del club dove chiunque è il benvenuto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El lugar perfecto para una retiro veraniego, el Rancho del oasis infinito lo tiene todo. Este espacio es de lo más variado, desde cactus alegres y palmeras eternas a vistas panorámicas de la cadena montañosa alrededor. La sede del club Rancho del oasis infinito es un espacio al que todos están invitados. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">The perfect place for a mid-summer retreat, the Infinite Oasis Ranch has it all. From lively cacti and ageless palm trees to panoramic views of the surrounding mountain ridge, this space packs it all. The Infinite Oasis Ranch space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">한여름에 휴가를 가기에 최적의 장소인 무한의 오아시스 목장은 모든 것이 준비되어 있습니다. 활력 넘치는 선인장과 오랜 시간 자라온 야자수부터 주변 산맥의 아름다운 경관까지, 이 스페이스에는 모두 있습니다. 무한의 오아시스 목장 스페이스는 누구나 환영받는 클럽하우스입니다. *무한의 오아시스 목장 클럽하우스 에 입장하려면 먼저 클럽을 구매해야 합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The perfect place for a mid-summer retreat, the Infinite Oasis Ranch has it all. From lively cacti and ageless palm trees to panoramic views of the surrounding mountain ridge, this space packs it all. The Infinite Oasis Ranch space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">無限綠洲牧場設備齊全，最適合用來當仲夏度假屋。這個空間應有盡有，具備充滿生氣的仙人掌、百年棕櫚樹、還有山脈全景。和大家一起在無限綠洲牧場聯盟俱樂部內相聚吧。※請注意，要使用無限綠洲牧場聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">無限綠洲牧場設備齊全，最適合用來當仲夏度假屋。這個空間應有盡有，具備充滿生氣的仙人掌、百年棕櫚樹、還有山脈全景。和大家一起在無限綠洲牧場聯盟俱樂部內相聚吧。※請注意，要使用無限綠洲牧場聯盟俱樂部，您必須要事先購買「聯盟」。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The perfect place for a mid-summer retreat, the Infinite Oasis Ranch has it all. From lively cacti and ageless palm trees to panoramic views of the surrounding mountain ridge, this space packs it all. The Infinite Oasis Ranch space is a clubhouse where everyone is invited to join. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>