<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Cruiser Pullover Hoodie - Blue (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Sweat à capuche Cruiser - Bleu (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Cruiser Kapuzenpullover - Blau (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Cruiser Pullover con cappuccio - Blu (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Cruiser Sudadera con capucha - Azul (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Cruiser wears nice and easy with the great feel of a soft cotton fleece fabric. Styled with tonal stripes at front, the long sleeves, hood and chest pocket offer a cool contrast with solid colouring. Includes side pockets and a woven flag label above the pocket. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Cruiser se porte bien et facilement avec la sensation agréable d'un tissu polaire en coton doux. Agrémenté de rayures aux tons différents sur le devant, de manches longues, d'une capuche et d'une poche poitrine, il offre un contraste décontracté aux couleurs unies. Comporte des poches latérales et une étiquette-drapeau tissée au-dessus de la poche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Cruiser Kapuzenpulli aus weichem Baumwollfleece ist wunderbar leicht und bequem. Die gestreifte Vorderseite steht im Kontrast zu den einfarbigen Ärmeln, der Kapuze und den Brusttaschen. Mit Seitentaschen und einem gewebten Flaggenetikett über der Tasche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il pullover Cruiser è facile e comodo da indossare grazie al morbido tessuto di cotone. Con righe tono su tono sul davanti, maniche lunghe, cappuccio e tasca sul petto, questa felpa offre un fantastico contrasto con i colori a tinta unita. Comprende tasche laterali e un'etichetta in tessuto con la bandiera sulla tasca. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Cruiser es cómodo y agradable de llevar con su tejido polar de suave tacto de algodón. Con un estilo a rayas tonales por delante y de manga larga, la capucha y el bolsillo en el pecho ofrecen un atrevido contraste con los demás colores sólidos. Incluye bolsillos laterales y etiqueta por encima del bolsillo, cosida por un lado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Cruiser wears nice and easy with the great feel of a soft cotton fleece fabric. Styled with tonal stripes at front, the long sleeves, hood and chest pocket offer a cool contrast with solid coloring. Includes side pockets and a woven flag label above the pocket. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>