<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Secret Peacekeeping Base, Yuma Café</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une base secrète pour faire respecter la paix, Yuma Café</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Geheimbasis zur Wahrung des Friedens, Café Yuma</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caffé Yuma, la base segreta per la salvaguardia dell'umanità</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La base secreta para mantener la paz, Café Yuma</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Secret Peacekeeping Base, Yuma Café</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">At a glance it appears to be a tasteful coffee shop, but behind a door in the rear is a secret base for heroes that utilise the most advanced science to battle evil. Well then, let's defend our tranquil planet Earth from the clutches of evil![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">À première vue, cela ressemble à un café de bon goût, mais derrière la porte, il y a à l'arrière une base secrète pour les héros, qui utilisent les technologies les plus avancées pour combattre le mal. Bien, allons protéger notre belle planète Terre des griffes du mal ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Auf den ersten Blick wirkt es wie ein geschmackvolles Café, aber im hinteren Bereich führt eine Tür zu einer Geheimbasis für Helden, die mit der neusten Technologie das Böse bekämpfen. Lasst uns unseren friedlichen Planeten Erde vor den Fängen böser Mächte beschützen![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ad un primo sguardo sembra un semplice bar, ma una porta sul retro conduce a una base segreta, dove un gruppo di eroi sfrutta apparecchiature tecnologicamente all'avanguardia per affrontare il male. Difendi anche tu il pianeta dai malvagi invasori![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">A primera vista parece una cafetería corriente, pero tras sus puertas se esconde la base secreta desde donde los héroes combaten el mal, usando los métodos científicos más avanzados. ¡Defendamos pues nuestro apacible planeta de las garras del mal![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">At a glance it appears to be a tasteful coffee shop, but behind a door in the rear is a secret base for heroes that utilise the most advanced science to battle evil. Well then, let's defend our tranquil planet Earth from the clutches of evil!#Legal] [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>