<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Russian Rose Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Russian Rose Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Russian Rose Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Russian Rose Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Russian Rose Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup02_BlondeUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup02_BlondeUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup02_BlondeUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup02_BlondeUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup02_BlondeUniform</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Russian Rose Pin-Up Girl</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Do svidaniya, comrade!  This sexy pin-up girl is a full character costume, complete with a sizzling hot uniform, tattoos, retro pin-up hair and make-up and comes with custom walk, run and pin-up pose!  You'll be sure to capture your enemy with this one![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Do Svidaniya, Comrade! Cette sexy Pin-up nana est un costume à part entière, complet avec un  uniforme sensationnel, tatouages, des cheveux et maquillage de Pin-up retro et vient avec une marche personnalisée, course et pose pin-up! Tu sera sure de capturer ton ennemie avec celle- la![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Do svidaniya, comrade! Dieses sexy Pin-Up Girl kommt als komplettes Charakterkostüm zusammen mit einer super heißen Uniform, Tätowierungen, Retro Pin-Up Frisur und Make-Up inklusive benutzerdefiniertem Gang, Lauf und Pin-Up Posen! Damit wirst du deinen Gegner sicher fangen! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Do svidaniya, comrade!  Questa bimba sexy pin-up é un costume completo del personnaggio, insieme ad un uniforme super eccitante, tatuaggi, capelli e trucco retro da pin-up insieme a camminata, corse e pose da pin-up particolari!  Con questa qui di sicuro catturerai al tuo nemico! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Do svidaniya, comrade!  Esta sexy nena pin-up es un disfraz completo del personaje, viene con uniforme muy provocativo, tatuajes, maquillaje y peinado retro de pin-up e incluye caminata especial, corrida y pose de pin-up!  De seguro con ella agarrarás a tu enemigo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Pinup02_BlondeUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Pinup02_BlondeUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Pinup02_BlondeUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Pinup02_BlondeUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Pinup02_BlondeUniform [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Do svidaniya, comrade!  This sexy pin-up girl is a full character costume, complete with a sizzling hot uniform, tattoos, retro pin-up hair and make-up and comes with custom walk, run and pin-up pose!  You'll be sure to capture your enemy with this one![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>