<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Arthropod Tattoos [Female]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tatouages Arthropode [femme]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Arthropod-Tattoos [Weiblich]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tatuaggi Artropode [femminili]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tatuajes Artrópodo [mujer]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_60</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_60</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Arthropod Tattoos [Female]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_60</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_60</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Arthropod Tattoos [Female]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take inspiration from the Sea and get all the female Arthropod tattoos. Includes Obsidian Arthropod Forearm and Calf Tattoos[F], Obsidian Arthropod Lower Back Tattoo[F], Ivory Arthropod Forearm and Calf Tattoos[F], and Ivory Arthropod Lower Back Tattoo[F].

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Puisez votre inspiration de la mer et prenez tous les tatouages Arthropode pour femme. Comprend: Tatouages Arthropode Obsidienne pour avant-bras et mollet [femme], Tatouages Arthropode Obsidienne bas du dos et mollet [femme], Tatouages Arthropode Ivoire pour avant-bras et mollet [femme], et Tatouages Arthropode Ivoire bas du dos et mollet [femme].

Remarque : Tous les tatouages pour torse ou jambe ne sont pas égaux. Lors de l’achat de cet accessoire de tatouage, il est possible qu’il ne soit pas adapté à tous les habits. N’hésitez pas à prendre notre article gratuit « Torse nu » pour homme ou femme afin d’afficher correctement votre nouveau tatouage ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lass dich vom Meer inspirieren und hol dir alle weiblichen Arthropod-Tattoos. Beinhaltet: Obsidian Arthropod-Tattoos für Unterarm und Wade [Weiblich], Obsidian Arthropod-Tattoos für den unteren Rücken und Wade [Weiblich], Ivory Arthropod-Tattoos für Unterarm und Wade [Weiblich], und Ivory Arthropod-Tattoos für den unteren Rücken und Wade [Weiblich].

Hinweis: Nicht alle Gegenstände für Oberkörper oder Beine sind gleich gestaltet. Wenn du dieses Tattoo-Zubehör kaufst, könnte es nicht mit allen Kleidungsstücken harmonieren. Gerne kannst du dir unseren kostenlosen “blanken” Oberkörper für Männer/Frauen holen, um deine neuen Tattoos angemessen zeigen zu können![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Trai ispirazione dal mare e acquista tutti i tatuaggi femminili Artropode. Il pacchetto si compone di Tatuaggi Artropode nero ossidiana per avambraccio e polpaccio [femminili], Tatuaggi Artropode nero ossidiana per la parte inferiore della schiena e polpaccio [femminili], Tatuaggi Artropode bianco per avambraccio e polpaccio [femminili], e Tatuaggi Artropode bianco per la parte inferiore della schiena e polpaccio [femminili].

Nota: non tutti gli oggetti per torso o gamba sono creati allo stesso modo. Il tatuaggio che ti appresti ad acquistare potrebbe non andare bene su tutti gli articoli di abbigliamento. A questo scopo non esitare a scaricare gratuitamente l'oggetto unisex "Tela nuda" torso per visualizzare correttamente i tuoi nuovi tatuaggi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Inspírate en el mar y consigue todos los tatuajes Artrópodo para mujer. Incluye: Tatuajes Artrópodo obsidiana antebrazo y pantorrilla [mujer], Tatuajes Artrópodo obsidiana parte baja de la espalda y pantorrilla [mujer], Tatuajes Artrópodo marfil antebrazo y pantorrilla [mujer], y Tatuajes Artrópodo marfil parte baja de la espalda y pantorrilla [mujer].

Nota: no todos los objetos para torso y piernas se crean por igual. Cuando compres este accesorio para un tatuaje, quizá no quede bien con cualquier prenda de ropa. ¡Elige nuestro "Lienzo en blanco" de regalo para hombre o mujer y así podrás lucir tu nuevo tatuaje como se merece![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_60 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_60 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Take inspiration from the Sea and get all the female Arthropod tattoos. Includes Obsidian Arthropod Forearm and Calf Tattoos[F], Obsidian Arthropod Lower Back Tattoo[F], Ivory Arthropod Forearm and Calf Tattoos[F], and Ivory Arthropod Lower Back Tattoo[F].

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_60 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_60 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Take inspiration from the Sea and get all the female Arthropod tattoos. Includes Obsidian Arthropod Forearm and Calf Tattoos[F], Obsidian Arthropod Lower Back Tattoo[F], Ivory Arthropod Forearm and Calf Tattoos[F], and Ivory Arthropod Lower Back Tattoo[F].

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>