<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Obsidian Rune Blades (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lames de Rune d'Obsidienne (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Obsidian-Runenklinnge (männliche)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lame della runa Obsidian (per uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cuchillas Runa Obsidian (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オブシディアンルーンブレイド（男性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">옵시디언 룬검 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Obsidian Rune Blades (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">黑曜石符文刀（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">黑曜石符文刀（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Obsidian Rune Blades (male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Brimming with raw power, these seemingly-primitive blades vibrate with incredible force, allowing their wielder to cut through steel with ease.  Enemies of the Obsidian have learned to respect their vicious melee weapons, which are ready to repeat their lesson at any time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Débordant de puissance brute, ces lames en apparence primitives vibrent avec une force incroyable, permettant à leur porteur de trancher l'acier avec facilité. Les ennemis de l'obsidienne ont appris à respecter leurs vicieuses armes de mêlée, qui sont prêtes à leur redonner une leçon à tout moment. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Überschäumend vor roher Energie, vibrieren diese scheinbar primitiven Klingen mit unglaublicher Kraft und erlauben  seinem Besitzer mit Leichtigkeit durch Stahl zu schneiden. Die Feinde der Obsidianer haben gelernt, diese bösartigen Nahkampfwaffen zu respektieren, welche jederzeit in der Lage sind, jemandem eine weitere Lektion zu erteilen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Piene di energia alla stato puro, queste lame, che possono sembrare estremamente primitive, vibrano spaventosamente, e permettono a chi le adopera di tagliare l'acciaio come fosse burro. I nemici degli Obsidian hanno imparato a rispettare le loro spaventose armi per gli scontri ravvicinati, sempre pronte ad affettare chi gli si para difronte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Llenas de potencia, estas aparentemente primitivas cuchillas vibran con fuerza increíble, permitiendo a su portador cortar a través del acero con facilidad. Los enemigos de los Obsidian han aprendido a respetar sus feroces armas de riña, las cuales están listas para repetir su lección en cualquier momento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">原始的なパワーで満ちた、この一見無骨なブレードは途方も無い力で振動し、使用する者は鋼さえ簡単に切断できる。オブシディアンの敵は、これまでに何度もその力を見せつけられてきたこの危険な近接兵器を恐れている。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">파워가 흘러 넘칩니다. 이들은 언뜻 보면 -원시적으로 보일수는 있지만, 강력한 힘으로 진동하며, 그들의 사용자가 강철조차도 쉽게 잘라낼 수 있도록 합니다. 옵시디언의 적들은 언제라도 자신의 힘을 과시 할 수 있는 맹렬한 근접 무기에 존경을 표합니다.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Brimming with raw power, these seemingly-primitive blades vibrate with incredible force, allowing their wielder to cut through steel with ease.  Enemies of the Obsidian have learned to respect their vicious melee weapons, which are ready to repeat their lesson at any time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這看似原始的高振動刀片隱藏著恐怖的力量。憑藉著令人難以相信的破壞力，讓玩家能輕鬆的切斷鋼鐵。黑曜石的敵人吃盡苦頭，因此非常害怕這個接近戰武器。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這看似原始的高振動刀片隱藏著恐怖的力量。憑藉著令人難以相信的破壞力，讓玩家能輕鬆的切斷鋼鐵。黑曜石的敵人吃盡苦頭，因此非常害怕這個接近戰武器。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Brimming with raw power, these seemingly-primitive blades vibrate with incredible force, allowing their wielder to cut through steel with ease.  Enemies of the Obsidian have learned to respect their vicious melee weapons, which are ready to repeat their lesson at any time. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>