<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Nucleus  Boardshorts - Black Aqua (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Short de planchiste Nucleus - Aqua noir (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Nucleus  Boardshorts - Schwarz/Blau (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Nucleus  Short da mare - Nero Aqua (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Nucleus  Bermudas - Negro Aqua (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The dominate design in high performance boardshorts, delivering superior movement and momentum with exceptionally fast drying time. Team rider Joel Parkinson has made the Nucleus his official boardshort of 2014, as well as provided insight on its technical features and engineered fade print. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le style qui domine les shorts de planchiste haute performance, offrant une liberté de mouvement supérieure et de la vitesse grâce à son séchage exceptionnellement rapide. L'équipier Joel Parkinson a fait du Nucleus son short de planchiste officiel pour 2014, il a fourni des recommandations concernant ses caractéristiques techniques et a conçu l'imprimé en dégradé. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das führende Design im Bereich High-Performance-Boardshorts für Komfort, optimale Bewegungsfreiheit und schnelles Trocknen. Der australische Surfer Joel Parkinson hat die Nucleus zu seinen offiziellen Boardshorts für 2014 erklärt und sich dabei besonders lobend über das Design und den attraktiven Fade-Print geäußert. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il design perfetto per short da mare ad alte prestazioni, che offre una libertà di movimento superiore e un'asciugatura ultra rapida. Il surfista Joel Parkinson ha fatto dei Nucleus i suoi short da mare ufficiali per il 2014, oltre ad aver fornito un approfondimento sulle caratteristiche tecniche e sulla stampa ingegnerizzata con effetto sbiadito di questo capo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Es el diseño que se impone en bermudas surferas de alto rendimiento,  ya que facilita la capacidad de movimiento y la velocidad, además de tener un secado excepcionalmente rápido. El surfista del equipo, Joel Parkinson, ha hecho de las Nucleus sus bermudas oficiales en 2014, y ha contribuido con su conocimiento al perfeccionamiento de las características técnicas y la estampado difuminado con ingeniería. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>