<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Succubus Wing Set (White Wings)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set d'ailes de succube (ailes blanches)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Succubus-Flügel-Set (weiße Flügel)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set ali da succuba (ali bianche)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de alas de súcubo (alas blancas)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">サキュバスのウィングセット（ホワイトウィング）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Succubus Wing Set (White Wings)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 2-piece set featuring locomotion succubus head wings and succubus wings &amp; tail, and the wings are white on the back.\nLocomotion Speed ★★★~★★★★★\n*Locomotion is a portable item.\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Locomotion - Succubus Head Wings (White Wings) (Portable Item)\n- Locomotion - Succubus Wings &amp; Tail (White Wings) (Portable Item)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 2 pièces contenant des ailes de tête de succube et des ailes et queue de succube. Les ailes sont blanches derrière.\nVitesse : ★★★~★★★★★\n*Un objet de locomotion est un objet portable.\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Locomotion - Ailes de tête de succube (ailes blanches) (Objet portable)\n- Locomotion - Ailes et queue de succube (ailes blanches) (Objet portable)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 2-teiliges Set, das die Bewegungsgegenstände "Succubus-Flügel" und "Succubus-Flügel &amp; Schwanz" enthält. Die Flügel haben eine weiße Rückseite.\nGeschwindigkeit ★★★~★★★★★\n*Bewegungsgegenstände sind tragbare Gegenstände.\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Bewegungsgegenstand - Succubus-Flügel am Kopf (weiße Flügel) (tragbarer Gegenstand)\n- Bewegungsgegenstand - Succubus-Flügel &amp; Schwanz (weiße Flügel) (tragbarer Gegenstand)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set composto da 2 oggetti Locomotion, ali sulla testa da succuba e ali e coda da succuba, con la parte interna delle ali bianca.\nVelocità di spostamento:★★★~★★★★★\n* Gli oggetti Locomotion sono oggetti portatili.\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Locomotion - Ali sulla testa da succuba (ali bianche) (oggetto portatile)\n- Locomotion - Ali e coda da succuba (ali bianche) (oggetto portatile)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos artículos de locomoción que incluye alas de súcubo para la cabeza, además alas y cola de súcubo, todas ellas con el dorso de color blanco.\nVelocidad de locomoción ★★★-★★★★★\n*Locomoción es un artículo portátil.\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Locomoción - Alas de súcubo para la cabeza (alas blancas) (artículo portátil)\n- Locomoción - Alas y cola de súcubo (alas blancas) (artículo portátil)\n\n* Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ロコモーションのサキュバスのヘッドウィングと、サキュバスのウィング＆テールの2点セット。羽根の裏の色は白。\nロコモーションの移動速度：　◆◆◆～◆◆◆◆◆\n※LMO(ロコモーション)はポータブルアイテムです。\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・LMO-サキュバスのヘッドウィング（ホワイトウィング）/ポータブルアイテム\n・LMO-サキュバスのウィング＆テール（ホワイトウィング）/ポータブルアイテム\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 2-piece set featuring locomotion succubus head wings and succubus wings &amp; tail, and the wings are white on the back.\nLocomotion Speed ★★★~★★★★★\n*Locomotion is a portable item.\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Locomotion - Succubus Head Wings (White Wings) (Portable Item)\n- Locomotion - Succubus Wings &amp; Tail (White Wings) (Portable Item)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
