<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Animal Avatars - Radioactive Arachnids - Stalker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avatars animaliers - Arachnides radioactifs - Stalker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tieravatare - Radioaktive Spinnentiere - Tarantula</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Avatar Animali - Aracnidi Radioattivi - Stalker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Avatares de animales - Arácnidos radioactivos - Acechante</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The powerful Stalker spider uses its immense strength and crippling poison to capture its prey.\n
Make your friend's skin crawl with this creepy crawly arachnid themed Animal Avatars locomotion object.\n
\n
This locomotion object will boost your speed:\n
・Standard = 5.25 m/s\n
\n
※ This item is a portable item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La puissante araignée Stalker utilise sa force immense et son venin paralysant pour capturer sa proie.\n
Donnez la chair de poule à vos amis avec ces objets de locomotion avatars animaliers effrayants sur le thème des arachnides.\n
\n
Ce moyen de déplacement vous permettra d'augmenter votre vitesse : \n
・Standard = 5,25 m/s\n
\n
※ Cet article est un article portable. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Tarantula, die größte aller Spinnen, nutzt ihre immense Kraft und ihr lähmendes Gift, um ihre Beute zu bezwingen.\n
Mit dieser gruseligen krabbelnden Spinnentier-Locomotion-Funktion läuft es Ihren Freunden kalt den Rücken herunter!\n
\n
Dieses Locomotion-Objekt macht Sie noch schneller:\n
・Standard = 5,25 m/s\n
\n
※ Bei diesem Artikel handelt es sich um einen tragbaren Artikel. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il potente ragno Stalker utilizza la sua immensa forza e il veleno paralizzante per catturare la sua preda.\n
Fai venire la pelle d'oca ai tuoi amici con questo raccapricciante oggetto di trasporto Aracnide di Avatar Animali.\n
\n
Questo oggetto di trasporto farà aumentare la tua velocità:\n
・Standard = 5,25 m/s\n
\n
※ Questo articolo è portatile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La poderosa araña acechante utiliza su enorme fuerza y su veneno paralizante para capturar a su presa.\n
Aterroriza a tus amigos con este bicharraco en objeto dinámico de Avatares de animales de la línea arácnido.\n
\n
Este artículo dinámico potenciará tu velocidad:\n
・Estándar = 5,25 m/s\n
\n
※ Éste es un artículo móvil. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>