<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Men School Uniform Top Wearable by Women (Black, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Costume scolaire masculin porté par une fille, haut (Noir, Femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Männliche Schuluniform, die von einem Mädchen getragen wird, Oberteil (schwarz, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Parte superiore uniforme scolastica maschile indossata da una ragazza (nera, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Uniforme escolar para chico usado por una chica, parte superior (Negro, Mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">女の子が着る男子用学生服・上（黒・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">여학생이 입는 남자용 교복 상의 (검은색, 여성)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">Men School Uniform Top Wearable by Women (Black, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">女孩穿的男用校服 - 上身（黑色/女用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">女孩穿的男用校服 - 上半身（黑色/女用）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Male School Uniform Worn by a Girl, Top (Black, Female)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A man's school uniform top that can be worn by a woman.\nThe size doesn't match, making it baggy and hard to move around in.\nYouthness:★★★\nDefensive Strength:★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Uniforme de garçon porté par une fille.\nIl est baggy car trop grand et pas pratique.\nJeunesse: ★★★\nDéfense: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Eine männliche Schuluniform, die von einer Frau getragen wird.\nDie Größe stimmt nicht, so dass sie schlotterig wirkt und man sich schlecht darin bewegt.\nJugendlichkeitslevel: ★★★\nVerteidigung: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Uniforme di uno studente indossati da una studentessa.\nLa taglia non è adatta, per cui è larga e rende difficili i movimenti.\nLivello giovinezza: ★★★\nDifesa: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Uniforme escolar para chico que pueden vestir las chicas.\nNo es a la talla, es bastante holgado por lo que es difícil moverse.\nNivel de juventud: ★★★\nDefensa: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">女性が着た、男子用学生服。\nサイズが合っておらず、ぶかぶかで動きにくい。\n青春度　：★★★\n防御力　：★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">여학생이 입은 남자용 교복 상의. \n사이즈가 안 맞아 헐렁헐렁해서 움직이기 불편하다.\n청춘도　：★★★\n방어력　：★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">A man's school uniform top that can be worn by a woman.\nThe size doesn't match, making it baggy and hard to move around in.\nYouthness:★★★\nDefensive Strength:★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">女生穿的男用學生服。\n尺碼不合，寬鬆的衣服讓人行動不便。\n青春指數：★★★\n防禦力：★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">女生穿的男用學生服。\n尺碼不合，寬鬆的衣服讓人行動不便。\n青春指數：★★★\n防禦力：★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A male student uniform worn by a female.\nThe size isn't right, it's baggy and is difficult to move in.\nYouth Level: ★★★\nDefense: ★[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
