<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Bottom Line (male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La Ligne du Bas (mâle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">In Der Unteren Zeile (männlich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La Linea Di Fondo (maschio)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La Línea de Fondo (masculino)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Bottom Line (male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Can't come up with anything witty to type in your chat window?  Just turn around and bend over, that'll say something.  It used to be your buttocks, now . . .your butt talks!  Comes with 5 preset phrases.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ne pouvez pas d'arriver à quelque chose rigoleux à taper dans votre fenêtre de chat? Il suffit de tourner autour et se pencher, ca vais dire quelque chose. Ils ont été votre fesses, maintenant . . . votre cul parle! Contient 5 phrases prédéfinies. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kann nicht kommen mit etwas witzig zu geben Ihrem chat-fenster? Einfach umdrehen und bücken, das wird etwas zu sagen. Früher war es Ihr gesäß, jetzt  . . . deinen hintern gespräche! Kommt mit 5 voreingestellte Phrasen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non può venire fuori con qualcosa di spiritoso tipo nella finestra di chat? Basta girarsi e piegarsi, che dirà qualcosa. Ha usato per essere i glutei, adesso  . . . parla il tuo culo! Viene fornito con 5 frasi preimpostate. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No se puede llegar a nada ingenioso para escribir en tu ventana de chat? Sólo da la vuelta y agacharse, que voy a decir algo. Lo que solía ser sus nalgas, ahora  . . . sus conversaciones a tope! Viene con cinco frases predefinidas. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Can't come up with anything witty to type in your chat window?  Just turn around and bend over, that'll say something.  It used to be your buttocks, now . . .your butt talks!  Comes with 5 preset phrases.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>