<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Umpire Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaise d'arbitre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schiedsrichterstuhl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sedia da Arbitro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Silla de juez</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Umpire Chair</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The umpire chair is ideal for tennis courts, golf tees, pool areas and any other sport venue where a judge is required and style is appreciated. It is a reward from the SeaClyff Retreat personal space. This is an interactive active object item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La chaise d'arbitre est idéale pour les cours de tennis, les terrains de golf, les zones de piscine et tout autre lieu sportif où un arbitre est nécessaire et où le style est apprécié. C'est une récompense de l'espace personnel SeaClyff Refuge. Il s'agit d'un objet actif interactif. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Schiedsrichterstuhl ist ideal für Tennisplätze, Golfplätze, Schwimmhallen und andere Sportplätze, auf denen man einen Schiedsrichter braucht und Stil erwünscht ist. Du erhältst ihn als Belohnung im persönlichen Raum "Rückzugsort an der Meeresklippe". Dies ist ein interaktiver, aktiver Gegenstand. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La sedia da arbitro è l'ideale per i campi da tennis, da golf, le aree piscina e qualsiasi altro campo sportivo dove ci sia necessità di un arbitro e lo stile sia apprezzato. È un premio dallo spazio personale del Seaclyff Retreat. È un oggetto attivo interattivo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La silla de juez es ideal para canchas de tenis, tees de salida de golf, piscinas y cualquier otra pista deportiva donde haga falta un juez y el estilo sea apreciado. Es un premio del espacio personal del Refugio SeaClyff. Es un artículo-objeto interactivo activo.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The umpire chair is ideal for tennis courts, golf tees, pool areas and any other sport venue where a judge is required and style is appreciated. It is a reward from the SeaClyff Retreat personal space. This is an interactive active object item. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SetTargetableText</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">S'asseoir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sitzen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Siedi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sentarse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>