<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Kimono Top (M, Year of the Tiger)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Haut de kimono (H, Année du Tigre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kimono-Oberteil (M, Jahr des Tigers)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Parte superiore kimono (U, Anno della Tigre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Parte superior de kimono (H, Año del Tigre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">浴衣・上（男性・寅年）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">유카타 상의(남성, 인)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Yukata Top (Men/Year of the tiger)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">日式浴衣 上 (男用／寅年）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">日式浴衣 上 (男用／寅年）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Kimono Top (M, Year of the Tiger)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The top half of a single-layer kimono dyed yellow and black, with a large Chinese character symbolizing the Year of the Tiger featured on the back.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le haut d'un kimono simple de teinte jaune et noir, avec au dos un imposant caractère chinois symbolisant l'Année du Tigre.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die obere Hälfte eines einfachen gelb-schwarzen Kimonos mit einem chinesischen Zeichen auf dem Rücken, welches das Jahr des Tigers symbolisiert.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La parte superiore di un kimono a singolo strato, tinto in giallo e nero. Decorato sulla schiena con un grande carattere cinese che indica l'Anno della Tigre.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La mitad superior de un kimono de una sola capa teñido de color amarillo y negro, con un enorme carácter chino en la espalda que simboliza el Año del Tigre.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">背中に大きく「寅」と書かれた、黄色と黒のひとえの着物。帯より上の半身。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">등에 큰 글씨로 「인」이라고 쓰여진, 노란색과 검은색의 전통 복장. 허리띠 위의 상의.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The top of a yellow and black unlined kimono with a large "Tora" written on the back. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">背上寫上大大的「寅」字、黃黑相襯的一重和服。腰帶之上的上半身部份。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">背上寫上大大的「寅」字、黃黑相襯的一重和服。腰帶之上的上半身部份。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The top half of a single-layer kimono dyed yellow and black, with a large Chinese character symbolizing the Year of the Tiger featured on the back.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>