<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Armored Pilot's Leggings with Deflection Shield</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jambières de pilote renforcées avec un bouclier déflecteur</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gepanzerte Piloten-Leggins mit Abwehrschild</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gambali armati da pilota con scudo deflettore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mallas de piloto blindadas con escudos de refracción</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">防衛シールド付き装甲パイロットレギンスセット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">조종사용 장갑 각반과 반사 방어막 세트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Armored Pilot's Leggings with Deflection Shield Set</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">裝甲飛行員護脛&amp;偏離防護罩組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">裝甲飛行員護脛&amp;偏離防護罩組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Armored Pilot's Leggings with Deflection Shield</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Rebound enemy shots with the Deflection Shielding system! This turret-mounted shield generator allows you to aim the shield in any direction you wish, bouncing enemy fire harmlessly away. This bundle includes both the male and female versions of the Armored Pilot's Leggings.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Renvoyez les tirs ennemis avec le générateur de bouclier déflecteur ! Ce générateur monté sur tourelle vous permet de diriger un bouclier déflecteur dans n'importe quelle direction, déviant ainsi les tirs ennemis sans dommages. Ce pack inclut les versions homme et femme des jambières de pilote renforcées. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wirf feindliche Schüsse mit dem Ablenkungs-Schild-System zurück! Dieser auf einem Turm angebrachte Schildgenerator läßt dich den Schild in jede gewünschte Richtung ausrichten. Gegnerisches Feuer wird harmlos und einfach abprallen. Dieses Paket enthält die männliche und die weibliche Version der gepanzerten Piloten-Leggins. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ferma il fuoco nemico con il sistema di scudi deflettori! Questo generatore di scudi montato a torretta ti permette di puntare uno scudo deflettore in qualsiasi direzione, respingendo senza danni gli attacchi nemici. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este generador de escudo montado en torre te permite apuntar los escudos en cualquier dirección que desees, rebotando el fuego enemigo en otras direcciones. Este paquete incluye las versiones masculinas y femeninas de las mallas de piloto blindadas.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">防衛シールドシステムで敵からのショットを撃ち返せ！このタレット付きシールドジェネレイターはどの方向にも防衛シールドを向けることができ、敵の攻撃をはね返せる。\n※購入すると、ミニゲーム「ノーバス・プライム」内の戦闘機にこの武器が装備されます。\n\n本セットには、アバターのカスタマイズ用の以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n・「装甲パイロットレギンス（男性用）」（ボトムズ）\n・「装甲パイロットレギンス（女性用）」（ボトムズ）\n※購入すると、「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">반사 시스템으로 적탄을 되돌리십시오! 이 포탑 탑재형 방어장 생성기는 원하는 방향으로 방어막을 펼치고, 적탄을 튕겨낼 수 있도록 해줍니다. 이 번들에는 조종사용 장갑 각반의 남성용과 여성용이 포함되어 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Rebound enemy shots with the Deflection Shielding system! This turret-mounted shield generator allows you to aim the shield in any direction you wish, bouncing enemy fire harmlessly away. This bundle includes both the male and female versions of the Armored Pilot's Leggings.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用偏離防護罩系統反彈敵人的攻擊！這個裝有迴轉砲塔的防護罩可調向任何方向，安然反彈敵方的攻擊。本組合包包括男用及女用的裝甲飛行員護脛。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用偏離防護罩系統反彈敵人的攻擊！這個裝有迴轉砲塔的防護罩可調向任何方向，安然反彈敵方的攻擊。本組合包包括男用及女用的裝甲飛行員護脛。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Rebound enemy shots with the Deflection Shielding system! This turret-mounted shield generator allows you to aim the shield in any direction you wish, bouncing enemy fire harmlessly away. This bundle includes both the male and female versions of the Armored Pilot's Leggings.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>