<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Picnic Table</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Table de pique-nique</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Picknicktisch</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tavolo da picnic</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mesa de picnic</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Picnic Table</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A picnic table made from natural wood where you can sit and enjoy life with your friends. It seats four comfortably. Great for picnics, meetings, or watching sunsets. This is an interactive active object item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une table de pique-nique en bois naturel où s'asseoir et passer un bon moment avec ses amis. Quatre personnes peuvent s'y asseoir pour des pique-niques, des rencontres, ou pour regarder le soleil couchant. Il s'agit d'un objet actif interactif. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Picknicktisch aus Naturholz, an dem du mit Freunden sitzen und das Leben genießen kannst. Hier können bis zu vier Leute gemütlich sitzen. Toll für Picknicks, Treffen oder zum Betrachten des Sonnenuntergangs. Dies ist ein interaktiver, aktiver Gegenstand. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un tavolo da picnic in legno, per sedersi e godersi la vita insieme agli amici. Ci si sta comodamente in quattro. Perfetto per i picnic, gli incontri e per guardare il tramonto. Questo è un oggetto attivo interattivo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una mesa de picnic hecha de madera natural en la que puedes sentarte y disfrutar la vida con tus amigos. Se pueden sentar cuatro con holgura. Genial para picnics, reuniones o ver atardeceres. Es un artículo-objeto interactivo activo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A picnic table made from natural wood where you can sit and enjoy life with your friends. It seats four comfortably. Great for picnics, meetings, or watching sunsets. This is an interactive active object item. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">sit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">S'asseoir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sitzen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Siedi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sentarse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>