<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Power-Mech Suit with Nebulon Magnet (bundle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tenue de mecha avec aimant à nébulon (lot)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Power-Mech-Anzug mit Nebulon-Magnet (paket)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esoscheletro mecha con magnete nebulon (pacchetto)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje Power-Mech con imán de nebulones (paquete)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ネブロンマグネットパワーメカニックスーツセット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">네뷸론 자석 제공 파워멕 슈츠 세트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Power-Mech Suit with Nebulon Magnet (bundle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">附Nebulon磁石的威力機械服裝組</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">附Nebulon磁石的威力機械服裝組</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Power-Mech Suit with Nebulon Magnet (bundle)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This fully-automated mech features state-of-the-art movement and stabilization technology, allowing for custom maneuvers, self-balanced walking, and even flight!  A Nebulon Magnet is included, which  draws Nebulon towards your fighter ships during Novus Prime missions. This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce mecha totalement automatisé inclut les toutes dernières technologies de mouvement et de stabilisation, permettant d'effectuer des manœuvres customisées, une marche auto-équilibrée et même de voler ! Un aimant à nébulon est intégré et attire le nébulon alentour vers vos vaisseaux de combat durant les missions Novus Prime. Ce lot comprend les versions homme et femme. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser vollautomatisierte Mech zeichnet sich durch modernste Bewegungs- und Stabilisationstechnologie aus, welche individuelle Manöver, ausbalanciertes Laufen und sogar Fliegen ermöglicht!  Der beigefügte Nebulon-Magnet deines Kampfschiffes zieht während Novus Prime Missionen Nebulon an. Dieses Paket ist beinhaltet sowohl die männliche als auch die weibliche Version. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo mecha automatico vanta della tecnologia di stabilizazzione e di movimento di ultima generazione, che permette manovre personalizzate, camminata autobilanciata e addirittura il volo! Vi è incluso un magnete nebulon, che attira i nebulon alle tue navi da combattimento durante le missioni della Novus Prime. Questo pacchetto include sia la versione maschile che femminile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este mech totalmente automatizado ofrece movimiento de punta, permitiendo maniobras personalizadas, caminado auto-balanceado, ¡e incluso vuelo! Un imán de nebulón está incluido, el cual atrae nebulón hacia tus naves de combate durante las misiones Novus Prime. Este paquete incluye las versiones masculina y femenina. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このフルオートメーションメカの特徴は、最先端の動作と安定化技術を採用したことで、カスタム操縦、自己平衡歩行、さらに飛行も可能！ノーバス・プライムでのミッションの間、あなたの戦闘機にネブロンを引き寄せるネブロンマグネットが搭載されています。\n\n
本セットには、アバターのカスタマイズ用の以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n
・「ネブロンマグネットパワーメカニックスーツ（男性用）」（組み合わせ）\n
・「ネブロンマグネットパワーメカニックスーツ（女性用）」（組み合わせ）\n
※購入すると、「アバターのカスタマイズ」内の該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。\n
※購入すると、ミニゲーム「ノーバス・プライム」内でネブロンを自動的に集めてくれます。\n
+ユニークモーション対応[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">본 전자동 멕의 특징은 자체 전술을 펼칠 수 있게 해 주는 안정화 기술, 스스로 균형을 잡으며 움직이는 이동 기능, 그리고 비행이 가능한 최첨단 장치입니다. 노부스 프라임에서 임무를 수행하는 동안 자신의 전함으로 네뷸론을 끌어당길 수 있는 공업 자석도 포함되어 있습니다. 본 제품은 남녀 버전이 모두 포함된 세트입니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This fully-automated mech features state-of-the-art movement and stabilization technology, allowing for custom maneuvers, self-balanced walking, and even flight!  A Nebulon Magnet is included, which  draws Nebulon towards your fighter ships during Novus Prime missions. This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這種完全自動化的機械服裝搭載了最先進的動作和穩定技術，允許自訂操作，自我平衡步行，甚至飛行！裝備包括了Nebulon磁石，讓你的戰鬥機在Novus Prime任務當中吸引Nebulon。本服裝組包含男用和女用。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這種完全自動化的機械服裝搭載了最先進的動作和穩定技術，允許自訂操作，自我平衡步行，甚至飛行！裝備包括了Nebulon磁石，讓你的戰鬥機在Novus Prime任務當中吸引Nebulon。本服裝組包含男用和女用。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This fully-automated mech features state-of-the-art movement and stabilization technology, allowing for custom maneuvers, self-balanced walking, and even flight!  A Nebulon Magnet is included, which  draws Nebulon towards your fighter ships during Novus Prime missions. This bundle includes both male and female versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>