<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Apollo Lunar Module</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Module Lunaire Apollo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Apollo-Mondlandefähre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Modulo Lunare Apollo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Módulo Apolo Lunar</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">アポロ月着陸船（装飾品）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Apollo Lunar Module</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">NASA’s Lunar Excursion Module (LEM), also known as the Apollo Lunar Module, is the portion of the Apollo spacecraft that landed on the moon and returned to lunar orbit. The 6.65 m³ module was designed to carry a crew of two. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Module d'Excursion Lunaire de la NASA (LEM), connu aussi sous le nom de Module Lunaire Apollo, est la portion du vaisseau spatial Apollo qui atterrit sur la lune et retourna en orbite lunaire. Le module de 6,65 m³ fut conçu pour un équipage de deux personnes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Lunar Excursion Module (LEM), auch bekannt als die Mondlandefähre der Apollo, ist der Teil des Apollo-Raumschiffs, der auf dem Mond landete und dann wieder in die Mondumlaufbahn zurückkehrte. Das 6,65 m³ große Modul war für eine Besatzung von zwei Mann konzipiert. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Modulo Lunare della NASA (LEM), meglio conosciuto col nome di Modulo Lunare Apollo, è una parte della navicella Apollo atterrata sulla luna e poi tornata sull'orbita lunare. Il modulo di 6,65 m³ è stato progettato per un equipaggio di 2 persone. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Módulo Lunar LEM de la NASA, también conocido como Módulo Apolo Lunar, es la parte de la nave espacial Apolo que aterrizó sobre la luna y regresó a la órbita lunar. El módulo, de 6,65 m³, fue diseñado para dos tripulantes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ＮＡＳＡの月着陸帰還モジュール(LEM)‐別名：アポロ月着陸船‐はアポロ宇宙船の一部。この6.65m³のモジュールは2名の乗組員を乗せて月に着陸した後、また月周回軌道に戻ってきた。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">NASA’s Lunar Excursion Module (LEM), also known as the Apollo Lunar Module, is the portion of the Apollo spacecraft that landed on the moon and returned to lunar orbit. The 6.65 m³ module was designed to carry a crew of two. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>