<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Domingo Stool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tabouret Domingo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Domingo-Hocker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sgabello Domingo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Taburete de Domingo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドミンゴ椅子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">도밍고 의자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Domingo Stool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">多明哥椅子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">多明哥椅子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Domingo Stool</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If you've ever dreamed of sitting on a big fluffy stuffed animal, this stool is for you! Boldly incorporates the design of the popular LocoRoco™ character, Domingo. So cute you may want to give him a big hug!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 Domingo and 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space. Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Domingo can be added only once. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si tu as déjà rêvé de t'asseoir sur un gros animal empaillé, alors ce tabouret est pour toi ! Intègre de manière audacieuse le motif du célèbre personnage LocoRoco™ Domingo. Il est si mignon que ça te donnerait envie de lui faire un gros câlin !\n\nAcheter cet objet ajoute 1 Domingo et 1 LocoRoco à ton espace personnel de l'île Loco.
Tu peux ajouter jusqu'à 20 LocoRoco à l'île Loco, mais un seul Domingo.
Une fois le maximum atteint, tu ne peux plus ajouter d'unités.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn du davon träumst, auf einem großen, flauschigen Tier zu sitzen, ist dies dein Hocker! Kühn verkörpert er die Gestalt des beliebten LocoRoco™-Charakters Domingo. So niedlich, dass man ihn umarmen möchte!\n\nDieser Gegenstand fügt deinem Loco-Insel-Apartment 1 Domingo und 1 LocoRoco hinzu. Du kannst bis zu 20 LocoRoco sowie einen Domingo hinzufügen. Ist das Maximum erreicht, können keine weiteren Einheiten hinzugefügt werden.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se hai sempre desiderato sederti su un morbido peluche, questo sgabello fa al caso tuo! Si rifà agli amati personaggi di LocoRoco™, i Domingo. È così irresistibile che ti viene voglia di abbracciarlo!\n\nAcquistando questo oggetto, aggiungerai un Domingo e un LocoRoco al tuo spazio personale su Loco Island. Puoi aggiungere fino a 20 LocoRoco su Loco Island. Puoi aggiungere un solo Domingo. Una volta raggiunto il numero massimo, non potrai aggiungerne altri.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si alguna vez has soñado con sentarte en un animal disecado grande y suave, ¡este taburete es para ti! Incorpora con audacia el diseño del popular personaje de LocoRoco™, Domingo. ¡Tan lindo que te entrarán ganas de darle un gran abrazo!\n\nComprar este objeto añade 1 Domingo y 1 LocoRoco a tu espacio personal en la Loco Isla. Puedes añadir un máximo de 20 LocoRoco a la Loco Isla. Solo podrás añadir a Domingo una vez.  Cuando hayas alcanzado este número, no podrás añadir más unidades.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">大きなぬいぐるみに座りたい・・・そんなあなたの夢を叶えるスツールです。
LocoRoco®の人気キャラクター”ドミンゴ”をデザインとして大胆に取り入れました。
思わず抱きつきたくなる可愛さです！\n\nこのアイテムを購入するとパーソナルスペース”ロコアイランド”に”ロコロコ”と”ドミンゴ”が１匹ずつ追加されます。\n\n

”ロコアイランド”には最大20匹まで”ロコロコ”が追加できます。”ドミンゴ”の追加は１回限りです。最大数に達した場合、それ以上の追加はされません。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">커다란 인형 위에 앉고 싶어…그런 당신의 꿈을 이뤄줄 스툴이에요. LocoRoco™의 인기 캐릭터 '도밍고'를 대범하게 디자인. 나도 모르게 꽉 껴안고 싶어지는 매력 덩어리!\n\n이 아이템을 구입하면 퍼스널 스페이스 '로코 아일랜드'에 '로코로코'와 '도밍고'가 1마리 추가됩니다.  '로코 아일랜드'에는 최대 20마리까지 '로코로코'를 추가할 수 있습니다. '도밍고'의 추가는 1회뿐입니다. 최대치에 다다르면 더 이상은 추가할 수 없습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">If you've ever dreamed of sitting on a big fluffy stuffed animal, this stool is for you! Boldly incorporates the design of the popular LocoRoco™ character, Domingo. So cute you may want to give him a big hug!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 Domingo and 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space. Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Domingo can be added only once. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">好想坐在大玩偶上・・・這是把能實現有這樣夢想的您的一人座椅。大膽嘗試將LocoRoco™的人氣角色”多明哥”加以設計。這麼可愛，真叫人不由得想緊緊抱住！\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間各追加一隻”樂克樂克”和”多明哥”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。”多明哥”的追加僅限一次。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">好想坐在大玩偶上・・・這是把能實現有這樣夢想的您的一人座椅。大膽嘗試將LocoRoco™的人氣角色”多明哥”加以設計。這麼可愛，真叫人不由得想緊緊抱住！\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間各追加一隻”樂克樂克”和”多明哥”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。”多明哥”的追加僅限一次。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ever dreamed of sitting atop of a giant stuffed doll? Well, this stool is perfect for you!Taking motifs of the favored character "Domingo" from the LocoRoco™ series, this chair is lovable and begging for a hug!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 Domingo and 1 LocoRoco to your LocoIsland personal space. Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to LocoIsland. Domingo can be added only once. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>