<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Grey Shirt with Dark Red Stripes, Rolled-up Sleeves and Dark Red Tie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chemise grise à rayures rouge sombre, manches retroussées et cravate rouge sombre</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Graues Langarmhemd mit dunkelroten Streifen, aufgerollten Ärmeln und dunkelroter Krawatte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Camicia grigia a righe rosso scuro con maniche arrotolate e cravatta rosso scuro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camisa gris con rayas rojo oscuro, mangas remangadas y corbata rojo oscuro</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">짙은 붉은색 줄무늬 회색 셔츠와 걷은 소매와 짙은 붉은색 넥타이</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Grey Shirt with Dark Red Stripes, Rolled-up Sleeves and Dark Red Tie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">卷袖、暗红色领带、暗红色条纹的灰色衬衫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">捲袖、暗紅色領帶、暗紅色條紋的灰色襯衫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gray Shirt with Dark Red Stripes, Rolled-up Sleeves and Dark Red Tie</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Untucked shirt with rolled up sleeves and tie - they look great paired with anything from smart trousers casual pants. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chemise non rentrée,  manches retroussées et cravate – elles sont parfaites avec un pantalon chic ou décontracté. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein lässig getragenes Langarmhemd mit aufgerollten Ärmeln und Krawatte - ein Superlook, der zu Allem passt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Camicie fuori dai pantaloni con maniche arrotolate e cravatta, perfette per qualsiasi abbinamento, dai pantaloni eleganti a quelli casual. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camisa por fuera del pantalón con mangas remangadas y corbata – quedan perfectas con pantalones de vestir o casuales. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">袖が捲り上げられたはみ出しシャツ、ネクタイ付き - どんなズボンと組み合わせることができます。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">겉으로 내논 셔츠와 걷은 소매와 넥타이 - 스마트 바지 캐쥬얼 바지등과 멋지게 잘 어울립니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Untucked shirt with rolled up sleeves and tie - they look great paired with anything from smart trousers casual pants. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">卷袖、配领带的无褶衬衫 - 与任何时尚长裤或休闲长裤都能完美搭配。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">捲袖、配領帶的無褶襯衫- 與任何時尚長褲或休閒長褲都能完美搭配。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Untucked shirt with rolled up sleeves and tie - they look great paired with anything from smart trousers casual pants. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>