<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Spunland Rocket (LMO)</LANG>
	<LANG ID="de-DE">Spunland-Rakete (LMO)</LANG>
	<LANG ID="en-US">Spunland Rocket (LMO)</LANG>
	<LANG ID="es-ES">Cohete Spunland (LMO)</LANG>
	<LANG ID="fr-FR">Fusée Spunland (LMO)</LANG>
	<LANG ID="it-IT">Razzo Spunland (Locomotion)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Feel the firework force by mounting the Spunland Rocket and go streaking through PlayStation®Home! By equipping this Locomotion Item, your avatar's run speed will be faster. LMO (Locomotion) is a Portable Item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erlebe die ganze Wucht des Feuerwerks! Steige auf die Spunland-Rakete und hebe ab zu einem rasanten Streifzug durch PlayStation®Home! Wenn Sie sich mit einem Bewegungsobjekt ausrüsten, wird die Laufgeschwindigkeit Ihres Avatars schneller. Bewegungsobjekte sind tragbare Gegenstände. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Feel the firework force by mounting the Spunland Rocket and go streaking through PlayStation®Home! By equipping this Locomotion Item, your avatar's run speed will be faster. LMO (Locomotion) is a Portable Item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Siente la fuerza de los fuegos artificiales al montar en el cohete Spunland y desplazarte a toda velocidad por PlayStation®Home! Al equipar este objeto de locomoción, la velocidad de carrera de tu avatar aumentará. LMO (locomoción) es un objeto portátil. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ressentez toute la puissance des feux d'artifice en assemblant la Fusée Spunland en traversant PlayStation®Home en trombe ! La vitesse de déplacement de votre avatar sera bien plus importante si vous équipez cet objet de locomotion. LMO (Locomotion) è un oggetto portatile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sperimenta la potenza dei fuochi artificiali in sella al Razzo Spunland e muoviti in PlayStation®Home alla velocità del lampo! Equipaggiando questo accessorio di movimento, la velocità di corsa del tuo avatar aumenterà. LMO (Locomotion) è un oggetto portatile. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>