<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Doctor Who - Silent Costume</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Doctor Who ™ - Le Costume du Silence</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Doctor Who - Kostüm des Silent</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Doctor Who - Costume del Silente</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Doctor Who - Traje del Silent</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Doctor Who - Silent Costume</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Doctor Who - Silent Costume</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Silence are a terrifying race who invaded Earth at an undetermined point in our history. They have powers of telepathy and can kill using a deadly discharge from their hands. But every Silent has a far eerier ability because even if you see a Silent, you’ll never remember it. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les Silents sont une race terrifiante qui a envahit la Terre à un moment indéterminé de notre histoire. Ils ont des pouvoirs de télépathie et peuvent tuer grâce à une décharge mortelle provenant de leurs mains. Mais tout Silent a une capacité encore plus étrange parce que même si vous voyez un Silent, vous ne vous rappellerez jamais. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Silence sind ein schreckliches Volk, das zu einem nicht näher angegebenen Zeitpunkt über die Erde hergefallen ist. Sie haben telepathische Kräfte und können durch eine tödliche Entladung aus ihren Händen töten. Doch jeder Silent besitzt noch eine weitaus unheimlichere Fähigkeit, denn selbst dann, wenn du einen Silent sehen solltest, wirst du dich nie daran erinnern. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Silenzio è una razza terrificante che ha invaso la Terra in un momento indefinito della nostra storia. Gli appartenenti a questa specie hanno poteri telepatici e possono uccidere con una scarica elettrica sprigionandola dalle mani. Tuttavia i Silenti hanno un'abilità ancora più inquietante, perché anche se puoi vederli, non lo ricorderai mai. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los Silence son una raza aterradora que invadió la Tierra  en un punto indeterminado de nuestra historia. Tienen el poder de la telepatía y pueden matar utilizando una descarga mortal con las manos. Pero todos los Silent tienen una habilidad mucho más sorprendente porque, si ves a un Silent, nunca lo recordarás. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Silence are a terrifying race who invaded Earth at an undetermined point in our history. They have powers of telepathy and can kill using a deadly discharge from their hands. But every Silent has a far eerier ability because even if you see a Silent, you’ll never remember it. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Silence are a terrifying race who invaded Earth at an undetermined point in our history. They have powers of telepathy and can kill using a deadly discharge from their hands. But every Silent has a far eerier ability because even if you see a Silent, you’ll never remember it. Doctor Who logo © 2013 and TM BBC. Licensed by BBC WW Ltd. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>