<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Morbids: Scarecrow - Full Outfit (Male) (Silhouette)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">The Morbids : Épouvantail - Costume intégral (Homme) (Silhouette)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">The Morbids: Vogelscheuche - Komplettes Kostüm (männlich) (Silhouette)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">The Morbids: Spaventapasseri - Completo (uomo) (sagoma)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los macabros: espantapájaros, atuendo completo (hombre) (silueta)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">モービッド：かかし - 衣装一式（男性用）（シルエット）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">모비드: 허수아비 - 전신 복장 (남성) (실루엣)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Morbids: Scarecrow - Full Outfit (Men) (Silhouette)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">恐怖使者：稻草人 — 全身套裝（男用）（黑影）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">恐怖使者：稻草人 — 全身套裝（男用）（黑影）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Morbids: Scarecrow - Full Outfit (Male) (Silhouette)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This totally unique outfit will take your avatar to a dark world, a world of shadows. Dare you join the growing numbers of silhouetted avatars? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce costume réellement unique entraînera votre avatar vers un monde sombre, peuplé d'ombres. Oserez-vous rejoindre le nombre croissant d'avatars à silhouette ? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses einzigartige Kostüm versetzt deinen Avatar in eine dunkle Welt der Schatten. Wagst du es, dich der ständig wachsenden Zahl an Silhouetten-Avataren anzuschließen? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo completo assolutamente unico porterà il tuo avatar in un mondo oscuro, fatto di ombre. Hai il coraggio di unirti al crescente numero di avatar sagomati? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este atuendo completamente único llevará tu avatar a un mundo tenebroso lleno de sombras. Únete al resto de siluetas avatares, si es que te atreves. ¡Cada vez hay más! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この独特の衣装があなたのアバターを暗黒の世界、暗闇の世界へといざないます。続々と増えているシルエットアバターの仲間入りをしますか？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 독특한 복장은 당신의 아바타를 어두운 그림자의 세계로 데려갈 것입니다. 늘어만 가는 실루엣 아바타의 행렬에 동참하시겠습니까? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This totally unique outfit will take your avatar to a dark world, a world of shadows. Dare you join the growing numbers of silhouetted avatars? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這身真正獨一無二的套裝將您的化身帶到完全陰暗的世界。您敢加入越來越多的黑影化身隊列嗎？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這身真正獨一無二的套裝將您的化身帶到完全陰暗的世界。您敢加入越來越多的黑影化身隊列嗎？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This totally unique outfit will take your avatar to a dark world, a world of shadows. Dare you join the growing numbers of silhouetted avatars? [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>