<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Active Object - Gypsy Fortune Teller</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Objet interactif - Machine de bonne aventure gitane</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aktives Objekt - Wahrsagemaschine</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Oggetto attivo - Indovina</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Objeto activo: gitana adivina</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Active Item - Gypsy Fortune Teller</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ask anything about your future, just don't ask to be big. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Posez des questions sur votre avenir, mais ne soyez pas trop gourmand. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fragen Sie alles zu Ihrer Zukunft, aber bitten Sie nicht, groß sein zu wollen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chiedi tutto quello che vuoi sapere sul futuro, ma non chiedere di essere grande. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pregunta lo que quieras sobre tu futuro, tal vez se cumpla. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ask anything about your future, just don't ask to be big. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans0</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Great wealth awaits you just over the horizon.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La richesse vous attend par-delà l'horizon.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Großer Reichtum erwartet dich - direkt hinter dem Horizont.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una grande ricchezza ti aspetta appena oltre l'orizzonte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una gran riqueza te aguarda en el horizonte.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Great wealth awaits you just over the horizon.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"Keep your friends close and your enemies even closer." - Sun Tzu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"Soyez proches de vos amis, et encore plus de vos ennemis." Sun Tzu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Behalte deine Freunde nahe bei dir und deine Feinde noch näher." – Sun Tzu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"Tieni i tuoi amici vicino, e i tuoi nemici ancora più vicino." - Sun Tzu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">“Ten cerca a tus amigos y más cerca aún a tus enemigos”. - Sun Tzu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"Keep your friends close and your enemies even closer." - Sun Tzu</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Holding on to the past only weakens your grip on the future.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">S'accrocher au passé empêche de se concentrer sur l'avenir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">An der Vergangenheit festzuhalten, schwächt nur den Zugriff auf die Zukunft.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se ti aggrappi al passato, perdi la presa sul futuro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aferrarse al pasado solo sirve para agarrar con menos fuerza el futuro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Holding on to the past only weakens your grip on the future.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You will be standing at a crossroad in the near future, will you take the road less travelled?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous allez bientôt vous retrouver à la croisée des chemins. Oserez-vous prendre la route déserte ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn du an einer Weggabelung stehst, nimmst du dann den weniger betretenen Weg?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Nel prossimo futuro ti troverai ad un bivio: imboccherai la strada meno battuta?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Muy pronto te encontrarás en una encrucijada, ¿tomarás el camino menos andado?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You will be standing at a crossroad in the near future, will you take the road less traveled?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A dark mist clouds your future, better to stay indoors for the next couple of days.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un épais brouillard flotte sur votre avenir. Restez à la maison dans les jours qui viennent.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein dunkler Nebel verschleiert deine Zukunft. Bleib in den nächsten Tagen besser im Haus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una nebbia scura offusca il tuo futuro, meglio restare a casa nei prossimi giorni.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una niebla oscura ensombrece tu futuro; mejor no salgas durante un par de días.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A dark mist clouds your future, better to stay indoors for the next couple of days.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans5</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Success is right around the corner.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La réussite vous attend au coin de la rue.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Erfolg liegt gleich um die Ecke.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il successo è dietro l'angolo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El éxito está a la vuelta de la esquina.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Success is right around the corner.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans6</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You will find what you are looking for in the last place you ever thought to look.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous trouverez votre bonheur là où vous vous y attendez le moins.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du wirst das, was du suchst, am letzten Ort finden, mit dem du gerechnet hättest.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Troverai ciò che cerchi nell'ultimo posto dove pensavi di trovarlo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Encontrarás lo que buscas en el último lugar en el que busques.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">You will find what you are looking for in the last place you ever thought to look.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans7</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">I recommend you take an umbrella if you go outside today.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Je vous conseille de prendre un parapluie si vous sortez aujourd'hui.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ich empfehle, heute einen Schirm mitzunehmen, wenn du nach draußen gehst.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ti consiglio di prendere l'ombrello se hai intenzione di uscire oggi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te recomiendo llevar paraguas si sales hoy.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">I recommend you take an umbrella if you go outside today.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans8</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Clear skies ahead.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pas de tempête en vue.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dich erwartet ein wolkenloser Himmel.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il futuro promette bene.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Se esperan cielos despejados.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Clear skies ahead.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans9</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Before the day is over, someone will ask you for your help.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quelqu'un va vous demander de l'aide avant la fin de la journée.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bevor der Tag vorbei ist, wird dich jemand um Hilfe bitten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Prima che il giorno finisca, qualcuno chiederà il tuo aiuto.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Antes de que acabe el día, alguien te pedirá ayuda.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Before the day is over, someone will ask you for your help.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans10</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Don't you think we'd be doing something else if we could tell the future?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous ne croyez pas qu'on ferait autre chose si on pouvait vraiment prédire le futur ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Würden wir nicht etwas anderes tun, wenn wir wirklich in die Zukunft sehen könnten?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non credi che faremmo altro se fossimo capaci di predire il futuro?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿No crees que no estaríamos haciendo esto si de verdad pudiéramos ver el futuro?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Don't you think we'd be doing something else if we could tell the future?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">I'm sorry, but I'm on my lunch break.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Désolé, je suis en pause déjeuner.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Entschuldigung, aber ich habe jetzt Mittagspause.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mi spiace, ma sono in pausa pranzo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lo siento, estoy en la pausa de la comida.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">I'm sorry, but I'm on my lunch break.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans12</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hypothetically speaking, how much of this do you actually expect to come true?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Franchement, vous croyez vraiment à tout ça ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mal hypothetisch gesprochen: Was glaubst du, wie viel hiervon tatsächlich wahr werden wird?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">In via del tutto ipotetica, quanto di questo ti aspetti che si avveri?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Francamente, ¿crees que algo de esto se hará realidad?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hypothetically speaking, how much of this do you actually expect to come true?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans13</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">We guarantee you'll regret not asking him/her out for a cup of coffee.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si vous ne l'invitez pas à prendre un café, vous allez vous en mordre les doigts.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wir garantieren, dass du es bereuen wirst, ihn/sie nicht auf eine Tasse Kaffee eingeladen zu haben.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ti assicuriamo che ti pentirai di non avergli/averle chiesto di uscire a prendere un caffè.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te garantizamos que te arrepentirás de no pedirle que vaya a tomar un café contigo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">We guarantee you'll regret not asking him/her out for a cup of coffee.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans14</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">We promise you're missing out by not going with him for that cup of coffee.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous allez passer à côté de quelque chose si vous n'allez pas prendre un café avec lui.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wir versprechen, dass du etwas verpasst, wenn du dich von ihm/ihr nicht zum Kaffee einladen lässt.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ti garantiamo che perderai un'occasione se non accetti il suo invito a prendere un caffè.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te prometemos que te vas a arrepentir de no ir a tomar un café con esa persona.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">We promise you're missing out by not going with him for that cup of coffee.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans15</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Trust us, cut the hair off.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il est temps d'aller chez le coiffeur.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Glaub uns. Schneid dir die Haare ab.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fidati: tagliati i capelli.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Confía en nosotros; córtate el pelo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Trust us, cut the hair off.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans16</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Every passing moment is another chance to turn it all around.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chaque seconde qui passe est l'occasion de faire de grandes choses.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jeder verstreichende Moment ist eine weitere Gelegenheit, alles umzukehren.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ogni istante che passa è una nuova occasione per dare una sterzata alla tua vita.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cada instante es una nueva oportunidad de cambiarlo todo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Every passing moment is another chance to turn it all around.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans17</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sorry, but you're not getting a call back.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Désolé, on ne vous rappellera pas.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Leider bist du nicht in der nächsten Runde.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ci dispiace, ma non ti richiamerà.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lo sentimos, pero no te va a llamar.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sorry, but you're not getting a call back.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans18</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">My vision is blurry, please try again later.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ma vision est trouble, réessayez plus tard.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Meine Sicht ist getrübt. Bitte versuch es später noch einmal.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ho una visione confusa... Per favore riprova più tardi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Veo borroso... Inténtalo de nuevo más tarde.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">My vision is blurry, please try again later.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans19</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Donations are greatly appreciated, and they certainly help your fortune's outlook.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les dons sont les bienvenus et ils favorisent la chance.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spenden sind gerne gesehen und verbessern auf jeden Fall die Aussichten für deine Zukunft.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le donazioni sono molto apprezzate e certamente aiuteranno la previsione del tuo futuro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los donativos son de agradecer y seguro que ayudan a mejorar tu fortuna.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Donations are greatly appreciated, and they certainly help your fortune's outlook.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans20</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">How many other fortune teller's did you go to before me?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous êtes allé voir combien de voyants avant moi ?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wie viele andere Wahrsager hast du vor mir besucht?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Da quante altre indovine sei stato prima di me?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿A cuántos adivinos has consultado antes?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">How many other fortune teller's did you go to before me?</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">ans21</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">We should warn you beforehand, it's impossible to tell the future.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nous devons avant tout vous prévenir, c'est impossible de prédire l'avenir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wir sollten dich vorher warnen: Es ist unmöglich, die Zukunft vorherzusagen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dobbiamo avvisarti in anticipo: è impossibile prevedere il futuro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Te lo advertimos de antemano: es imposible adivinar el futuro.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">We should warn you beforehand, it's impossible to tell the future.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">gypsy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gypsy</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Gitane</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wahrsagerin</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Indovina</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Gitana adivina</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gypsy</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>