<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Casino Host Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Costume d'hôte de casino</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kasino Gastgeber Anzug</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vestito da host di casinò</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje para el Anfitrión del Casino</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_TorsoLegs_Casino_HostSuit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_TorsoLegs_Casino_HostSuit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Male01_TorsoLegs_Casino_HostSuit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_TorsoLegs_Casino_HostSuit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_TorsoLegs_Casino_HostSuit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Casino Host Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">It's time to really show you're part of the casino scene. This classy Casino Host Suit will have everyone turning their heads.  Tour the tables, help out patrons or simply dance the night away with this stylish suit. This bundle includes the Casino Host Suit, a Fedora and Shoes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il est temps de vraiment montrer que vous faites partie du casino. Le costume élégant d' hôte de casino fera tourner toutes les têtes. Visitez les tables, aidez les clients ou  tout simplement dansez toute la nuit avec ce costume élégant. Ce paquet inclut le costume d'accueil Casino, une Fedora et chaussures. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es ist an der Zeit nun richtig zu zeigen, dass Sie Teil der Kasinoszene sind.  Der todschicke Kasino Gastgeber Anzug wird jedem den Kopf verdrehen. Drehen Sie eine Runde um die Tische, helfen Sie den Gästen, oder tanzen Sie die Nacht durch auf dem Tanzboden.  Dieses Paket enthält das Casino Host-Anzug, ein Fedora und Schuhe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">È ora di mostrare davvero che siete parte del casinò. L'elegante vestito da host di casinò farà girare lo sguardo a tutti. Fate un giretto tra i tavoli, date una mano ai clienti o semplicemente danzate tutta la notte con questo elegante vestito. Questo bundle comprende la tuta Host Casino, uno Fedora e calzature. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Es tiempo de mostrar realmente que es parte del mundo del casino. El elegante juego de anfitrión de Casino hará que todo el mundo lo volteé a ver.  Recorra las mesas, ayude a los clientes o simplemente baile toda la noche con este elegante juego. Este paquete incluye el traje de anfitrión Casino, un Fedora y los zapatos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Male01_TorsoLegs_Casino_HostSuit [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Male01_TorsoLegs_Casino_HostSuit [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Male01_TorsoLegs_Casino_HostSuit [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Male01_TorsoLegs_Casino_HostSuit [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Male01_TorsoLegs_Casino_HostSuit [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">It's time to really show you're part of the casino scene. This classy Casino Host Suit will have everyone turning their heads.  Tour the tables, help out patrons or simply dance the night away with this stylish suit. This bundle includes the Casino Host Suit, a Fedora and Shoes. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>