<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Male01_Legs_R2_SRPA</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Resistance 2™ S.R.P.A Costume (Legs)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Costume du SRPA pour Resistance 2(TM) (Jambes)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Resistance 2™-SRPA-Kostüm (Beine)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Resistance 2(TM) - Costume S.R.P.A (Gambe)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje S.R.P.A de Resistance 2TM (Piernas)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">レジスタンス®2:S.R.P.A コスチューム（脚）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Resistance 2™ S.R.P.A 코스튬 (하체)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Resistance 2™ S.R.P.A Costume (Legs)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Resistance 2™ S.R.P.A 服裝 (下半身)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Resistance 2™ S.R.P.A 服裝 (下半身)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Section of an exclusive new costume for your Home avatar. Download this Resistance 2(TM) outfit to join the human forces protecting Home from the invading Chimera.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Section d'un nouveau costume exclusif pour votre avatar de Home. Téléchargez cette tenue pour Resistance 2(TM) et protégez Home de l'invasion chimérienne aux côtés des forces humaines.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Teil eines exklusiven neuen Kostüms für deinen Home-Avatar. Lade dir dieses "Resistance 2™"-Outfit herunter, um zu den Streitkräften der Menschen zu gehören, die Home vor dem Angriff der Bestien beschützen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sezione di un nuovo costume esclusivo per il tuo avatar in Home. Scarica questa tenuta di Resistance 2™ per unirti agli esseri umani nella difesa di Home dall'invasione dei Chimera.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sección de un nuevo y exclusivo traje para tu avatar de Home. Descárgate este conjunto de Resistance 2(TM) para unirte a las fuerzas de humanos que protegen tu Home de las quimeras invasoras.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">PS Homeアバターのための新コスチューム。このレジスタンス®2のコスチュームをダウンロードして、侵略してくるキメラからPS Homeを守ろう。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">PlayStation®Home 아바타를 위한 한정판 의상의 일부입니다. Resistance 2™ 의상을 다운로드 하시고, 침공하는 키메라들에 맞서 PlayStation®Home을 지켜내는 인류의 마지막 방어선이 되십시오.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Section of an exclusive new costume for your PlayStation®Home avatar. Download this Resistance 2™ outfit to join the human forces protecting PlayStation®Home from the invading Chimera.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">PlayStation®Home虛擬分身專用的獨家新服裝之一部分。下載這個Resistance 2™服裝組來加入人類軍隊的行列，並阻止Chimera入侵PlayStation®Home吧。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">PlayStation®Home虛擬分身專用的獨家新服裝之一部分。下載這個Resistance 2™服裝組來加入人類軍隊的行列，並阻止Chimera入侵PlayStation®Home吧。</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>