<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fridge Freezer – Flag (Great Britain)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Combiné réfrigérateur/congélateur -  Drapeau (Grande-Bretagne)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kühl-/Gefrierkombination -  Flagge (Großbritannien)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Frigorifero con congelatore -  Bandiera (Gran Bretagna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Frigorífico con congelador – Bandera (Gran Bretaña)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Fridge Freezer – Flag (Great Britain)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The LIVING luxury furniture brand combines style with affordability.  Covering a range of designs, this collection with answer all your decorating needs; remember...Fashion passes, style remains, LIVING is the key! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">LIVING, marque de meubles haut de gamme de qualité à prix abordables. Quelles que soient vos préférences en matière de décoration,  cette collection variée et haute en couleurs s’adaptera à toutes les pièces et à toutes les envies. N’oubliez jamais : la mode passe, le style reste, et LIVING en est la preuve ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die LIVING Luxusmöbel-Marke kombiniert Stil mit Erschwinglichkeit. Diese Kollektion wird alle Ihre Anforderungen an Dekorationen beantworten, da sie einen großen Bereich an Designs abdeckt; Denken Sie daran … Mode vergeht, Stil bleibt, LIVING ist der Schlüssel! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">IL marchio di arredi di lusso LIVING combina stile e convenienza. Qualunque siano i vostri gusti, questa collezione risponderà a tutti i vostri bisogni in fatto di arredamento. Ricordate...le mode passano, lo stile rimane. LIVING è la risposta. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LIVING es la marca de muebles de lujo con estilo al mejor precio. Con una amplia gama de diseños, en esta colección encontrarás lo que necesitas. Recuerda: la moda pasa, pero el estilo permanece. LIVING es la respuesta. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The LIVING luxury furniture brand combines style with affordability.  Covering a range of designs, this collection with answer all your decorating needs; remember...Fashion passes, style remains, LIVING is the key! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>