<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Jade Stoned White Bikini Bundle (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bikini blanc avec pierres de jade (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weißer Bikini mit Jadesteinen (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bikini bianco con pietre di giada (donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bikini blanco con jade (mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">옥색 화이트 비키니 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Jade Stoned White Bikini Bundle (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">附有翡翠石的白色比堅尼服裝組（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">附有翡翠石的白色比基尼（女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Jade Stoned White Bikini Bundle (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A clean and comfortable fit, this all white bikini bundle is accented by a handful of jade stones. Bundle includes a top, bottom, and heels. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour compléter sa coupe classe et confortable, ce bikini blanc arbore plusieurs pierres de jade. L'ensemble comprend un haut, un bas et des chaussures à talon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit einem engen und gemütlichen Sitz ist dieses komplett weiße Bikini-Kostümpaket mit einer Handvoll Jadesteine besetzt. Das Paket enthält Oberteil, Unterteil und Pumps. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Completo bikini bianco, comodo, essenziale e impreziosito da pietre di giada. Include la parte superiore ed inferiore del bikini e sandali alti. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cómodo y sencillo, este conjunto de bikini blanco queda resaltado con unos pocos adornos de jade. El conjunto incluye las partes superior e inferior del bikini y zapatos de tacón. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">깔끔하고 편안한 피트입니다. 이 화이트 비키니 번들은 옥 장식으로 더욱 우아해 보입니다. 이 번들은 상의, 하의, 그리고 하이힐을 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A clean and comfortable fit, this all white bikini bundle is accented by a handful of jade stones. Bundle includes a top, bottom, and heels. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這套整潔舒適的白色比堅尼服裝組，裝飾了一些翡翠石。服裝組包括上身、下身及高跟鞋。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這套整潔舒適的白色比基尼服裝組，裝飾了一些翡翠石。服裝組包括上半身、下半身及高跟鞋。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A clean and comfortable fit, this all white bikini bundle is accented by a handful of jade stones. Bundle includes a top, bottom, and heels. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>