<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blackhawk Combat Suit Bundle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble armure de Blackhawk (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blackhawk-Kampfanzug: Set (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto tuta da combattimento Blackhawk (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de traje de combate Blackhawk (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블랙호크 전투 수트 세트 (남성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Blackhawk Combat Suit Bundle (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">黑鷹戰鬥服裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">黑鷹戰鬥服裝組（男用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blackhawk Combat Suit Bundle (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bring the assault from the skies with this advanced Blackhawk outfit. Bundle includes a helmet, top, bottom, gloves and shoes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Donnez l'assaut depuis le ciel avec cette armure de pointe de Blackhawk. L'ensemble comprend un casque, un haut, un bas, des gants et des bottes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit diesem Blackhawk-Anzug greifen Sie aus der Luft an. Das Set beinhaltet Helm, Oberteil, Unterteil, Handschuhe und Stiefel. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sferra l'assalto dal cielo con questa tuta stile Blackhawk all'avanguardia. Il pacchetto include casco, corazza, pantaloni, guanti e scarpe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Asalta al enemigo desde los cielos con este avanzado traje Blackhawk. El conjunto comprende casco, parte superior, parte inferior, guantes y calzado. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">고성능 블랙호크 의상을 입고 하늘에서 맹공격을 퍼부으십시오. 이 세트는 헬멧, 상의, 하의, 장갑, 그리고 신발을 포함합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Bring the assault from the skies with this advanced Blackhawk outfit. Bundle includes a helmet, top, bottomm, gloves and shoes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">穿上這套先進的黑鷹套裝，攻擊空中的敵人。本服裝組包括頭盔、上身、下身、手套及鞋。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">穿上這套先進的黑鷹套裝，攻擊空中的敵人。本服裝組包括頭盔、上半身、下半身、手套及鞋。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Bring the assault from the skies with this advanced Blackhawk outfit. Bundle includes a helmet, top, bottomm, gloves and shoes. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>