<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ella Vam Pire Tattooed Lady Bustier</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bustier tatoué pour femme Ella Vam Pire</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ella Vam Pire Tattoo-Bustier</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bustino e tatuaggio di Ella Vam Pire</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bustier y tatuajes de Teresa Vampiresa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">엘라 뱀 파이어 문신이 새겨진 레이디 뷔스티에 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ella Vam Pire Tattooed Lady Bustier (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Ella吸血鬼紋身少女緊身上衣(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Ella吸血鬼紋身少女緊身上衣(女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ella Vam Pire Tattooed Lady Bustier</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ella is from an 'old money' family. VERY old money. Some say centuries. She's a modern girl herself, preferring gothic fashion to gothic crypts any day of the week. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ella vient d'une "vieille" famille. TRÈS vieille. Certains disent même vieille de plusieurs siècles. C'est une fille moderne, qui préfère la mode gothique aux cryptes glauques. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ella stammt aus einer alten Adelsfamilie. Wirklich SEHR alt! Manche sagen Jahrhunderte alt. Sie ist aber ein sehr modernes Mädel, das die Gotik-Modeviel schöner als Gotik-Gruften findet. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ella proviene da una famiglia antica e benestante. MOLTO antica e benestante. Alcuni parlano di secoli. È una ragazza moderna e preferisce la moda gotica alle tombe gotiche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Teresa proviene de una familia de abolengo cuyos orígenes se remontan a varios siglos en el pasado. No obstante, tiene un estilo moderno hasta el punto de preferir la moda gótica actual a las criptas góticas de antaño. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">엘라는 '오래된 부자' 가문 출신입니다. 아주 오래된 부자이지요. 어떤 사람들은 수 백년을 이어 왔다고 얘기합니다. 그녀 자신은 현대적이어서, 주중 어떤 날에도 고딕풍 무덤보다는 현대적인 고딕풍의 패션을 선호한답니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ella is from an 'old money' family. VERY old money. Some say centuries. She's a modern girl herself, preferring gothic fashion to gothic crypts any day of the week. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Ella來自歷史悠久的大戶人家，真的非常悠久。據說能追溯到數百年以前。不過她本人是現代女性，一年到頭都穿陰森詭異的服飾。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Ella來自歷史悠久的大戶人家，真的非常悠久。據說能追溯到數百年以前。不過她本人是現代女性，一年到頭都穿陰森詭異的服飾。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ella is from an 'old money' family. VERY old money. Some say centuries. She's a modern girl herself, preferring gothic fashion to gothic crypts any day of the week. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>