<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Animated glowing biker boots for men</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bottes de motard lumineuses animées pour homme</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Animierte glühenden Stiefeln</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Moto stivali luce animata</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Botas de moto luz animada</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Animated glowing biker boots for men</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Animated glowing biker boots for men</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Those timeless black leather boots have a futuristic touch: an ever-changing pulsating neon light is embedded in their soles, varying in intensity, as well as gently cycling through all the colours of the rainbow! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ces bottines en cuir indémodables ont un coté futuriste: une lumière changeante est incrustée dans la semelle, variant en intensité, elle passe lentement par toutes les couleurs de l'arc en ciel! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese zeitlose schwarze LederStiefeln haben einen futuristischen Touch: eine sich ständig verändernde pulsierenden Neon-Licht ist in den Sohlen eingebettet unterschiedlicher Intensität, als auch sanft durch alle Farben des Regenbogens geht![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questi stivali in pelle hanno un lato futuristico senza tempo: cambiamenti di luce è incorporato nella suola, più o meno intenso, passa lentamente attraverso tutti i colori dell'arcobaleno![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">botas de cuero son intemporales tienen un lado está incrustado futurista luz cambiante en la planta del pie, que varían en intensidad, pasa lentamente a través de todos los colores del arco iris.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Those timeless black leather boots have a futuristic touch: an ever-changing pulsating neon light is embedded in their soles, varying in intensity, as well as gently cycling through all the colors of the rainbow! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Those timeless black leather boots have a futuristic touch: an ever-changing pulsating neon light is embedded in their soles, varying in intensity, as well as gently cycling through all the colors of the rainbow! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>