<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Drey Bolero Jacket - Plumtastic</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Veste Bolero Drey - Plumtastic</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drey Bolero-Jacke - Plumtastic</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Giacca bolero Drey - Meravigliosa prugna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Torera Drey - Ciruela</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">【Drey】ボレロ ジャケット（プラム・女性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"드레이" 볼레로 재킷 - 짙은 보라색 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Drey Bolero Jacket - Plumtastic (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Drey波雷若外套：百花齊放 (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Drey波雷若外套：百花齊放 (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Drey Bolero Jacket - Plumtastic</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Drey's tailored bolero jackets come in several eye-popping colours. Teamed with a seamless crop-top for a ravishing smart-casual look. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les vestes boleros sur mesure de Drey existent en plusieurs couleurs flashy. Combiné avec un haut court sans coutures pour un look intelligent-détendu ravissant. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dreys maßgeschneiderte Bolero-Jacke ist in vielen bestechenden Farben erhältlich. Kombiniert mit einem nahtlosen, kurzen Top sorgt sie für einen umwerfend smart-lässigen Look. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Le eleganti giacche bolero di Drey sono disponibili in numerosi colori sgargianti. Abbinata a un mini top senza cuciture per un look sportivo ma alla moda assolutamente incantevole. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Torera confeccionada por Drey disponible en varios colores llamativos. A juego con un top sin costuras para un deslumbrante look elegante-informal. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">様々な斬新なカラーを展開するDreyシリーズ。セクシーなこのインナーと合わせて街中の目線を集めてみては？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"드레이"의 잘 재단된 볼레로 재킷은 눈에 확 띄는 몇 가지 색상으로 출시됩니다. 재봉선이 없는 크롭 탑과 함께 입고 화려하면서도 스마트한 캐주얼 모드를 연출해 보세요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Drey's tailored bolero jackets come in several eye-popping colors. Teamed with a seamless crop-top for a ravishing smart-casual look. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Drey推出的波雷若訂做外套，擁有多種鮮豔的顏色款式。可搭配成套短上衣，讓你亮麗帥氣又隨性。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Drey推出的波雷若訂做外套，擁有多種鮮豔的顏色款式。可搭配成套短上衣，讓你亮麗帥氣又隨性。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Drey's tailored bolero jackets come in several eye-popping colors. Teamed with a seamless crop-top for a ravishing smart-casual look. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>