<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Tycoon Penthouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Maison de magnat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Tycoon-Penthouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Attico magnate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ático Magnate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">タイクーン・ペントハウス</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">재벌의 펜트하우스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Tycoon Penthouse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">大亨豪宅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">大亨豪宅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Tycoon Penthouse</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Take your living experience to new heights with the Tycoon Penthouse, perched high above the city sky. The window-walled space comes with your own private helipad, an aquarium that reaches from floor to ceiling, and a spiralling staircase that gives the space its modern design. 
Dare to defy gravity and add this little slice of heaven to your collection today. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Découvrez de nouveaux horizons et dominez toute la ville avec la Maison de magnat. Profitez de murs entièrement vitrés, de votre propre piste d'hélicoptère, d'un aquarium sur deux étages et d'un escalier en colimaçon pour une touche de modernité. Osez défier la loi de la gravité en ajoutant dès maintenant ce petit coin de paradis à votre collection. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erlebe mit dem Tycoon-Penthouse hoch über den Dächern der Stadt ein völlig neues Wohnerlebnis. Das Apartment mit den großen Fensterfronten bietet einen eigenen Hubschrauber-Landeplatz, ein Aquarium, das vom Boden bis zur Decke reicht, sowie eine Wendeltreppe, die dem Apartment sein modernes Aussehen verleiht.
Überwinde die Schwerkraft und ergänze deine Sammlung heute um dieses Stück vom Himmel. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Porta il tuo stile di vita a livelli davvero alti con l'Attico magnate che domina il panorama urbano. Questo spazio delimitato da vetrate è dotato di eliporto privato, di un acquario che arriva fino al soffitto e di una scala a chiocciola che contribuisce a creare un look moderno. 
Sfida la gravità e aggiungi oggi questo piccolo angolo di paradiso alla tua collezione. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lleva tu residencia a nuevas cotas con el ático Magnate, situado en lo alto de la ciudad. Además de impresionantes ventanales, en el espacio podrás disfrutar de tu propio helipuerto privado, un acuario que abarca la totalidad de la pared y una escalera en espiral que le otorgan un carácter moderno a su diseño. 
Desafía a la gravedad y añade hoy mismo un trocito de cielo a tu colección. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">超高層ビルから大都市を一望できる新感覚のタイクーン・ペントハウスです。全面ガラス張りのこのパーソナルスペースは自家用ヘリパッドが付いています。部屋の中には一階から二階へかけて水槽が伸びており、らせん状の階段がモダンなアクセントを出します。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이름만 들어도 짜릿한 재벌의 펜트하우스에서 삶의 질을 극한으로 끌어 올려 보십시오. 유리로 둘러싸인 공간에서 도시를 내려다보는 장관을 경험해 보지 못한 사람은 이해할 수 없습니다. 당신을 위한 헬리콥터 착륙장, 천장과 맡닿을 정도로 높은 키의 수족관, 그리고 나선형 계단은 현대적인 디자인 감성의 극치를 보여 줍니다. 
높은 곳에 위치한 천국의 한 조각을 맛보고 싶다면 지금 즉시 구입하세요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Take your living experience to new heights with the Tycoon Penthouse, perched high above the city sky. The window-walled space comes with your own private helipad, an aquarium that reaches from floor to ceiling, and a spiralling staircase that gives the space its modern design. 
Dare to defy gravity and add this little slice of heaven to your collection today. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這間居高臨下的大亨豪宅，將你的生活提昇至全新的層次。豪宅內用了落地玻璃，附有你的私人直升機場、由地下高聳至二樓天花的水族箱和為空間帶來現代設計味道的螺旋樓梯。放膽違抗地心吸力，將這片小天堂加到你的收藏吧。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這間居高臨下的大亨豪宅，將你的生活提昇至全新的層次。豪宅內用了落地玻璃，附有你的私人直升機場、由地下高聳至二樓天花的水族箱和為空間帶來現代設計味道的螺旋樓梯。放膽違抗地心吸力，將這片小天堂加到你的收藏吧。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Take your living experience to new heights with the Tycoon Penthouse, perched high above the city sky. The window-walled space comes with your own private helipad, an aquarium that reaches from floor to ceiling, and a spiralling staircase that gives the space its modern design. 
Dare to defy gravity and add this little slice of heaven to your collection today. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>