<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Helicopter Hit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'hélicoptère Frapper</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Helikopter Schlagen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Elicottero Colpire</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Helicóptero Golpear</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Helicopter Hit [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'hélicoptère Frapper [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Helikopter Schlagen [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Elicottero Colpire [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Helicóptero Golpear [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">FailNone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You haven't even prevented one of them from escaping! You know you want to, so try again.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous n’avez même pas réussi à leur empêcher de s’enfuir ! Vous savez que vous voulez le faire. Réessayez donc !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben keinen Einzigen am Entkommen gehindert! Das möchten Sie bestimmt noch mal versuchen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non sei riuscito a impedire la fuga per nessuno di loro. So che vuoi farcela. Dai, riprova!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">1- No has impedido la fuga de ninguno de ellos. Sé que quieres hacerlo. ¡Prueba!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">FailOne</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You only prevented one of them from escaping. I'm not angry, but I am disappointed.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez réussi à empêcher à un seul d’entre eux de s’enfuire. Je ne suis pas fâché, seulement un peu déçu.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben nur einen am Entkommen gehindert. Ich bin nicht böse, aber schwer enttäuscht.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sei riuscito a impedire la fuga di uno solo di loro. Non sono arrabbiato, ma deluso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">2- Has impedido la fuga de uno de ellos. No estoy enojado, estoy desilusionado.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">game over</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Game Over</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Partie terminée</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spiel vorbei</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Game over</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Fin de la partida</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameOver2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">furry fiends from escaping, good work pilot!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">créatures poilues ne s'échappent. Beau travail, pilote !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">pelzige Feinde an der Flucht gehindert. Gute Arbeit, Pilot!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">diavoletti pelosi, ottimo lavoro pilota!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">demonios peludos escapen! ¡Buen trabajo, piloto!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameOver1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You prevented</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez empêché que</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai evitato la fuga di</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has evitado que</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">startup help</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">CUT THE BALLOON'S WIRES SO NO ONE ESCAPES!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">COUPEZ LES CÂBLES DES BALLONS POUR QU'IL N'Y AIT AUCUN RESCAPÉ !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">DURCHTRENNEN SIE DIE SEILE DER BALLONS, DAMIT KEINER ENTKOMMT!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">RECIDI I CAVI DEI PALLONI, NON DEVE SCAPPARE NESSUNO!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡CORTA LOS CABLES DE LOS GLOBOS PARA QUE NO ESCAPE NADIE!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">out of fuel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Out of fuel!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Panne d'essence !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kein Treibstoff mehr!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Carburante esaurito!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Sin combustible!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Anleitung</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Istruzioni</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Instrucciones</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">apply thrust</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Apply thrust</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Poussée</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Schub geben</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Applica spinta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Impulso</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">move chopper</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Control helicopter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Piloter l'hélicoptère</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Helikopter steuern</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Controlla elicottero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Controlar helicóptero</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Beenden</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">fuel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fuel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Essence</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Treibstoff</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Carburante</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Combustible</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Score</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Punkte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Punteggio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Puntos</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">lives</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Lives</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vies</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Leben</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vite</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Vidas</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">the instructions</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Fly your helicopter into the balloon wires to cut them but avoid hitting the balloons themselves as this will destroy your helicopter! Balloons of the same colour as your helicopter will score points. Other player's balloons are not worth points but will give you a small amount of fuel. Collect bonus fuel to stay in the air for longer.\n\nGood luck, pilot!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez l'hélice de votre hélicoptère pour couper les câbles qui relient les ballons aux nacelles des passagers. Ils vont tomber de haut ! Ne touchez pas le ballon ou votre hélicoptère sera détruit. Gagnez des points en attaquant les ballons de la couleur de votre hélicoptère. Les ballons des autres joueurs ne vous rapportent aucun point, mais ils vous rapportent une petite quantité d'essence.\n\nBonne chance, pilote !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Durchtrennen Sie mit den Rotorblättern Ihres Helikopters die Seile, die die Ballons mit den Ballonkörben verbinden, und lassen Sie die kleinen Passagiere in die Tiefe stürzen! Aber erwischen Sie nicht den Ballon selbst, denn das zerstört Ihren Helikopter. Verdienen Sie Punkte, indem Sie Ballons in derselben Farbe wir Ihr Helikopter angreifen. Die Ballons der anderen Spieler bringen keine Punkte, aber einen kleinen Treibstoffbonus.\n\nViel Glück, Pilot!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Utilizzando le pale del tuo elicottero, recidi i cavi che collegano il pallone al cesto dei passeggeri e fai cadere le dolci creaturine verso il loro inevitabile destino! Attenzione, cerca di non urtare il pallone, o il tuo elicottero verrà distrutto. Se colpisci i palloni del tuo stesso colore guadagnerai punti; attaccando i palloni dell'altro giocatore non guadagnerai punti ma otterrai un piccolo bonus carburante.\n\nIn bocca al lupo, pilota!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Utiliza las cuchillas del rotor de tu helicóptero para cortar los cables que conectan los globos con la cesta de pasajeros. ¡Harás caer en picado a todas esas criaturas tan monas! Sin embargo, ten cuidado de no golpear el propio globo ya que destruiría el helicóptero. Gana puntos atacando globos que sean del mismo color que tu helicóptero. Los globos de otros jugadores no dan puntos aunque sí que proporcionan un poco de combustible.\n\n¡Buena suerte, piloto!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>