<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mount Olympus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mont Olympe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Olymp</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Monte Olimpo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Monte Olimpo</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Mount Olympus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">올림푸스 산</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Mount Olympus</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">奧林帕斯山</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">奧林帕斯山</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mount Olympus</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Lounge like the gods as you sit atop the clouds in your very own Mt. Olympus. Take your rightful place on the throne, overlooking your impluvium (a water basin for you mortals). Take a stroll out back in your peristylium to catch some sun. Make sure to have one of your worshippers pull up your chariot for you when you leave. Reward your guests with a Mount Olympus Bolts (Male or Female), exclusive to the Mount Olympus personal space. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Détendez-vous comme les dieux, assis sur les nuages au sommet de votre propre Mont Olympe. Occupez la place qui vous revient de droit sur le trône, avec vue sur votre impluvium (les mortels appellent cela une bassine d'eau). Promenez-vous dans votre peristylium pour profiter du soleil. Assurez-vous que l'un de vos fidèles fasse amener votre chariot lors de votre départ. Offrez à vos invités des Éclairs du Mont Olympe (pour homme ou femme), en exclusivité dans l'espace personnel Mont Olympe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fühle dich wie ein Gott, während du über den Wolken auf deinem eigenen Olymp sitzt. Nimm deinen rechtmäßigen Platz auf dem Thron ein und blicke über dein Impluvium (ein Wasserbecken für euch Sterbliche). Lustwandle draußen in deiner Säulenhalle und genieße die Sonne. Sorge dafür, dass einer deiner Verehrer deinen Streitwagen zieht, wenn du rausgehst. Belohne deine Gäste mit Olymp-Blitzen (für Damen oder Herren), die es nur im persönlichen Apartment "Olymp" gibt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Rilassati come un vero dio e goditi il panorama da sopra le nubi, mentre ti siedi in cima al tuo Monte Olimpo personale. Prendi posto sul tuo legittimo trono, al di sopra del tuo impluvio (una vasca piena d'acqua, per voi mortali). Passeggia per il tuo peristilio per prendere un po' di sole e assicurati che quando andrai via ci sia uno dei tuoi adoratori alla guida del tuo carro. Ricompensa i tuoi ospiti con dei Fulmini Monte Olimpo (per uomo o per donna), oggetti esclusivi per lo spazio personale Monte Olimpo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Siéntete como los dioses mientras te acomodas sobre las nubes de tu propio monte Olimpo. Ocupa tu legítimo lugar en el trono y contempla tu propio impluvio (para los mortales, una pileta de agua). Date un paseo por el peristilo para tomar un poco el solecito. No olvides tener a uno de tus fieles devotos para empujar la cuadriga cuando tengas que irte. Obsequia a tus invitados con rayos del monte Olimpo (para hombre o mujer), que son exclusivos del espacio personal de monte Olimpo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Lounge like the gods as you sit atop the clouds in your very own Mt. Olympus. Take your rightful place on the throne, overlooking your impluvium (a water basin for you mortals). Take a stroll out back in your peristylium to catch some sun. Make sure to have one of your worshippers pull up your chariot for you when you leave. Reward your guests with a Mount Olympus Bolts (Male or Female), exclusive to the Mount Olympus personal space. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">여러분이 소유하는 올림푸스 산의 구름 위에서 신처럼 쉬어보세요. 당신의 수반(별볼일 없는 인간 언어로는 세숫데야)을 볼 수 있는 왕좌에 자리를 잡으세요. 여러분의 정원에서 햇빛도 받으시고요. 떠날 때는 여러분을 섬기는 자에게 마차를 끌라고 하세요. 손님들에게는 오직 올림푸스 산 퍼스널 스페이스에서만 제공되는 올림푸스 산 번개(남성, 여성)를 선물하세요. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Lounge like the gods as you sit atop the clouds in your very own Mt. Olympus. Take your rightful place on the throne, overlooking your impluvium (a water basin for you mortals). Take a stroll out back in your peristylium to catch some sun. Make sure to have one of your worshippers pull up your chariot for you when you leave. Reward your guests with a Mount Olympus Bolts (Male or Female), exclusive to the Mount Olympus personal space. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">在屬於你的奧林帕斯山裡，如眾神般高坐雲端上。坐上你應有的皇座，鳥瞰方形儲水池（予凡人使用）。在周柱中庭散散步，曬曬太陽，並確保離開時你的禮拜者已經為你準備了馬車。給你的賓客送上奧林帕斯山個人空間限定的奧林帕斯山閃電（男用或女用）。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">在屬於你的奧林帕斯山裡，如眾神般高坐雲端上。坐上你應有的皇座，鳥瞰方形儲水池（予凡人使用）。在周柱中庭散散步，曬曬太陽，並確保離開時你的禮拜者已經為你準備了馬車。給你的賓客送上奧林帕斯山個人空間限定的奧林帕斯山閃電（男用或女用）。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Lounge like the gods as you sit atop the clouds in your very own Mt. Olympus. Take your rightful place on the throne, overlooking your impluvium (a water basin for you mortals). Take a stroll out back in your peristylium to catch some sun. Make sure to have one of your worshippers pull up your chariot for you when you leave. Reward your guests with a Mount Olympus Bolts (Male or Female), exclusive to the Mount Olympus personal space. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>