<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Over-shoulder Suit Jacket and trousers (Black, Outfit, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Veste de costume sur les épaules et pantalon (noirs, tenues, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Jackett über der Schulter und Hose (schwarz, Kombination, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Giacca appoggiata sulle spalle e pantaloni (completo nero, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Chaqueta sobre los hombros y pantalón de vestir (negros, combinación, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">上着を肩に羽織ったスーツの上下（黒・組み合わせ・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Over-shoulder Suit Jacket and Pants (Black, Outfit, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A black suit jacket slung over a red shirt, and coordinated black trousers.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nCoolness: ★★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Une veste de costume noir posée sur les épaules et une chemise rouge combinées à un pantalon noir.\nDéfense : ★\nNiveau de cool : ★★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein schwarzes Jackett, das über der Schulter eines roten Hemds hängt, und die dazu passende schwarze Hose.\nVerteidigung: ★\nCoolness: ★★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Una giacca nera di un completo appoggiata sulle spalle sopra una camicia rossa, con dei pantaloni neri in coordinato.\nDifesa: ★\nRicercatezza: ★★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Chaqueta negra colgada de los hombros sobre una camisa roja, y pantalón negro a juego.\nDefensa: ★\nPorte: ★★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">赤いシャツの肩に羽織った黒いスーツの上着と、黒いスラックスの組み合わせ。\n防御力：　★\nかっこよさ：　★★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">A black suit jacket slung over a red shirt, and coordinated black slacks.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nCoolness: ★★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">A black suit jacket slung over a red shirt, and coordinated black slacks.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nCoolness: ★★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">A black suit jacket slung over a red shirt, and coordinated black slacks.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nCoolness: ★★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A black suit jacket slung over a red shirt, and coordinated black pants.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nCoolness: ★★★★[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
