<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Summer Rain</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Pluie d'été</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Sommerregen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Pioggia d'estate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Lluvia de Verano</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_16</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - 여름비</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Summer Rain</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - 梅雨季</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - 梅雨季</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Summer Rain</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Let the Sunshine in with with warm rays of Sunshine Peep!  Bring Sunshine Peep with you into your apartment and let the fun begin.  You can control your Peep with custom animations and special Peep moves![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Laisse entrer les rayons du soleil de Sunshine Peep! Ramène Sunhine Peep avec toi  à ton appartement et que la fête commence. Tu peux contrôler ton Peep avec des animations personnalisées et des manœuvres spéciales Peep![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Lass die Sonne mit warmen Strahlen herein mit Sunshine Peep! Bring Sunshine Peep mit in deine Wohnung und der Spaß beginnt. Du kannst dein Peep mit benutzerdefinierten Animationen und speziellen Peep-Bewegungen steuern![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lascia entrare i caldi raggi del sole di Sunshine Peep! Porta Sunshine Peep nel tuo appartamento e che il divertimento abbia inizio. Puoi controllare il tuo Peep con animazioni fatte a posta e movimenti speciali Peep![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Deja que entre el Sol con los rayos de sol de Sunshine Peep!  Lleva a Sunshine Peep a tu departamento y que empieze la diversión.  Puedes controlar a tu Peep con animaciones personalizadas y movimientos Peep especiales![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_16 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sunshine Peep의 따뜻한 햇살을 느껴 보세요!  Sunshine Peep을 아파트에 데려와 신나게 놀아 보세요.  사용자 지정 애니메이션과 특수 Peep 모션으로 컨트롤할 수 있습니다![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Let the Sunshine in with warm rays of Sunshine Peep!  Bring Sunshine Peep with you into your apartment and let the fun begin.  You can control your Peep with custom animations and special Peep moves![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sunshine Peep帶來溫暖的陽光！帶SunshinePeep進入您家，開始玩樂。您可以用自訂動態和專屬Peep動作來控制Peep！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sunshine Peep帶來溫暖的陽光！帶SunshinePeep進入您家，開始玩樂。您可以用自訂動態和專屬Peep動作來控制Peep！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Let the Sunshine in with with warm rays of Sunshine Peep!  Bring Sunshine Peep with you into your apartment and let the fun begin.  You can control your Peep with custom animations and special Peep moves![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>