<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Pirate Galleon Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appartements du Galion Pirate</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Apartment der Piraten-Galeone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Appartamento del Galeone Pirata</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Apartamento del Galeόn Pirata</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">海賊船ガレオン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">해적 갈레온선 아파트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Pirate Galleon Apartment</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">海盜船公寓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">海盜船公寓</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Pirate Galleon Apartment</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Moored by a tropical island, this ship comes complete with playable cannon mini-game and four Pirate themed furniture rewards. A very desirable residence that has suddenly become available, due to the imprisonment of the previous owner.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ancré près d’une île tropicale, ce bateau complet propose également un mini-jeu de canons et quatre récompenses sous forme de meubles aux couleurs des pirates. Cette demeure de rêve est désormais disponible, suite à l’emprisonnement de son ex-propriétaire.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Schiff hat an einer tropischen Insel festgemacht und kommt mit einem spielbaren Kanonen-Minispiel, sowie mit vier Belohnungen, die Einrichtungsgegenstände des Piratenthemas sind. Eine sehr gesuchte Unterkunft wurde plötzlich frei, da der Vorbesitzer ins Gefängnis gewandert ist.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ormeggiata presso un'isola tropicale, questa nave comprende un mini-gioco di cannoni e quattro arredi della linea Pirateria come premi. Una residenza molto desiderata che è diventata disponibile grazie all'arresto del suo precedente proprietario.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Amarrado en una isla tropical, este barco viene con un divertido mini juego con cañones y cuatro premios de mobiliario con motivos piratas. Debido al encarcelamiento del antiguo propietario, una deseable residencia está ahora disponible.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">熱帯の島に係留されたこの船に、大砲ミニゲームと海賊をテーマにした４つの家具のご褒美が用意されている。前の持ち主が投獄されたため、この魅力的な住まいのテナントを急募！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 선박은 열대 섬 근처에 고정시켜 캐논 미니 게임을 즐길 수 있게 된다. 그리고 4가지 해적 테마를 보상으로 주었다. 이전 소유자의 징역으로 인해 급격히 사용할 수 있게 된  매우 바람직한 집.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Moored by a tropical island, this ship comes complete with playable cannon mini-game and four Pirate themed furniture rewards. A very desirable residence that has suddenly become available, due to the imprisonment of the previous owner.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這艘停泊在熱帶小島旁的船，在船上可以進行加農砲襲擊小遊戲，並且可獲得四個海盜主題的家具。由於前任屋主被監禁的緣故，你也有機會可以成為這個令人嚮往的公寓的主人![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這艘停泊在熱帶小島旁的船，在船上可以進行加農砲襲擊小遊戲，並且可獲得四個海盜主題的家具。由於前任屋主被監禁的緣故，你也有機會可以成為這個令人嚮往的公寓的主人![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Moored by a tropical island, this ship comes complete with playable cannon mini-game and four Pirate themed furniture rewards. A very desirable residence that has suddenly become available, due to the imprisonment of the previous owner.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>