<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mercury Capsule Memorabilia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Souvenir de la Capsule Mercury</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mercury-Raumkapsel-Fanartikel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cimelio della capsula Mercury</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Memento cápsula Mercurio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">マーキュリーカプセル記念品（装飾品）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mercury Capsule Memorabilia</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mercury mission represents NASA’s first “man-in-space program”. On May 5, 1961 astronaut Alan Shepard became the first American in space. Three weeks later, on May 25, 1961, President John F. Kennedy announced the goal of sending astronauts to the moon before the end of the decade. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La mission Mercury constitue le premier programme "Homme dans l'espace" de la NASA. Le 5 mai 1961, l'astronaute Alan Shepard est le premier Américain dans l'espace. Trois semaines plus tard, le 25 mai 1961, le Président John F. Kennedy annonce le projet d'envoyer des astronautes sur la lune avant la fin de la décennie. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Mercury-Mission war das erste bemannte Raumfahrtprogramm der NASA. Am 5. Mai 1961 wurde der Astronaut Alan Shepard der erste Amerikaner im All. Drei Wochen später, am 25. Mai 1961, kündigte John F. Kennedy an, noch vor Ende des Jahrzehnts Astronauten zum Mond zu schicken. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La missione Mercury rappresenta il primo "programma dell'uomo nello spazio" della NASA. Il 5 maggio 1961 l'astronauta Alan Shepard è il primo cittadino americano nello spazio. Tre settimane dopo, il 25 maggio 1961, il presidente John F. Kennedy annuncia il piano di mandare degli astronauti sulla luna prima della fine del decennio. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La misión Mercurio marca el primer "programa hombre en el espacio" de la NASA. El 5 de mayo de 1961 el astronauta Alan Shepard se convirtió en el primer americano en el espacio. Tres semanas después, el 25 de mayo de 1961, el presidente John F. Kennedy hizo público su objetivo de enviar astronautas a la luna antes de que terminara la década. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">マーキュリー計画はＮＡＳＡ初の「有人宇宙計画」だった。1961年5月5日にアラン・シェパードが米国人で初めての宇宙飛行士となった。その3週間後の1961年5月25日にケネディー大統領が10年以内に月に宇宙飛行士を送る計画を発表した。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mercury mission represents NASA’s first “man-in-space program”. On May 5, 1961 astronaut Alan Shepard became the first American in space. Three weeks later, on May 25, 1961, President John F. Kennedy announced the goal of sending astronauts to the moon before the end of the decade. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>