<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Find Oakie The Clown's Lost Cake</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Retrouvez le gâteau perdu du clown Oakie</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Finden Sie den Kuchen, den Oakie, der Clown, verloren hat.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Trova la torta che il pagliaccio Oakie ha perso</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Encuentra el pastel perdido de Roblecito el Payaso</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Cake Hunt [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chasse au gâteau [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Suche nach dem Geburtstagskuchen [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Caccia alla Torta [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La Búsqueda del pastel [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Quit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Abbrechen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Salir</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Play</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Play</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Jouer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spielen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gioca</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Jugar</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GetEgg</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Collect Cake</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Récupérez le gâteau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kuchen abholen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Raccogli Torta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Recoger pastel</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">InstructionText1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Oakie the Clown is sad, he has lost all of his Birthday cake!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Oakie le clown est triste, il a perdu tout son gâteau d'anniversaire !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Oakie, der Clown, ist traurig, denn er hat seinen ganzen Geburtstagskuchen verloren!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Pagliaccio Oakie è triste perché ha perso la sua torta di Compleanno!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Roblecito el Payaso está triste, ¡ha perdido todo el Pastel de cumpleaños!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">InstructionText2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Using your dog's keen sense of smell, sniff out those pieces of cake and put a smile on Oakie's face!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En tirant parti du flair aiguisé de votre chien, reniflez ces morceaux de gâteau et redonnez le sourire à Oakie !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Setzen Sie Ihren Hund als Spürhund ein. Finden Sie die Kuchenstücke und zaubern Sie ein Lächeln auf Oakies Gesicht!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usa il senso dell'olfatto del tuo cane e trova tutti i pezzi di torta per far tornare il sorriso a Oakie!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Usando el agudo olfato de tu perro, ¡encuentra esos trozos de pastel y devuélvele la sonrisa a Roblecito!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">InstructionText3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There's special rewards for those who come back to help Oakie as much as possible...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Des récompenses spéciales sont réservées à celles et ceux qui reviendront aider Oakie autant que possible...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wer Oakie noch einmal so viel wie möglich hilft, erhält eine ganz besondere Belohnung!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">C'è un premio speciale per chi torna ad aiutare Oakie più volte possibile...</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hay premios especiales para quienes vengan a ayudar a Roblecito en todo lo posible…</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">RewardText</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">WOOF WOOF! You Found All The Cake!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">WOOF WOOF ! Vous avez trouvé toutes les parts du gâteau !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wau, wau! Sie haben den Kuchen gefunden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">BAU BAU! Hai trovato tutta la torta!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡GUAU, GUAU! ¡Has encontrado todo el pastel!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">NoRewardText</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Keep Looking! There's still more cake around here somewhere!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Continuez à chercher ! Il reste encore d'autres gâteaux dans les parages !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Suchen Sie weiter! Irgendwo in dieser Gegend ist noch mehr Kuchen zu finden.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Continua a cercare! Ci sono ancora dei pezzi di torta nascosti da queste parti!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Sigue buscando! ¡Todavía queda más pastel en algún sitio!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">But_Accept</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[ACCEPT]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">But_Decline</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">NoDogEquipped</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You need a dog to help Oakie the Clown sniff out those lost cakes!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous devez posséder un chien pour aider Oakie le clown à rechercher ces parts de gâteau perdues !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie brauchen einen Hund, um den Kuchen zu finden, den Oakie verloren hat!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai bisogno di un cane per aiutare il Pagliaccio Oakie a trovare i pezzi di torta!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Necesitas un perro para ayudar a Roblecito el Payaso a olisquear y encontrar los pasteles perdidos!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">AlreadyPlayed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You've collected the cake for today! Try again tomorrow!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez récupéré assez de gâteau pour aujourd'hui ! Essayez à nouveau demain !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sie haben für heute genug Kuchen gefunden. Machen Sie morgen weiter.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hai raccolto tutti i pezzi di torta per oggi! Riprova domani!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Has recogido el pastel por hoy! ¡Vuelve a intentarlo mañana!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>