<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Forsaken Planet - Pimento (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Forsaken Planet - Pimento (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Forsaken Planet - Pimento  (männlich)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Forsaken Planet - Pimento (maschio)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Forsaken Planet - Pimento (chico)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Forsaken Planet - Pimento (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Are you trigger happy? Travel PlayStation®Home as Pimento from Forsaken Planet, a LOOT™ Entertainment videogame for tablets and smart phones! Looking for even sweeter Forsaken Planet deals and in-game rewards? Check out the Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle in the LOOT™ Store! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous avez la gachette facile ? Parcourez  PlayStation®Home en tant que Pimento de Forsaken Planet, un jeu vidéo de  LOOT™ Entertainment  pour tablettes et téléphones intelligents ! Vous cherchez des affaires Forsaken Planet encore plus intéressantes et des récompenses dans le jeu ? Allez voir les Lots Forsaken Planet dans la Boutique LOOT™  !  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hast du Bock auf Ballern? Jetzt kannst du dein PlayStation®Home als Pimento aus Forsaken Planet, einem LOOT™ Entertainment Videospiel für Tablets und Smartphones durchwandern! Möchtest du noch bessere Forsaken Planet Deals und Ingame-Vorteile abgreifen? Schau dir das Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle im LOOT™ Store an! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sei stra felice? Esplora la PlayStation®Home nei panni di Pimento di Forsaken Planet, un videogioco di LOOT™ Entertainment per tablet e smartphone! Cerchi altre offerte e altri premi Forsaken Planet? Dai un'occhiata al Pacchetto Ultimate Forsaken Planet nel LOOT™ Store! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Tienes el gatillo suelto? ¡Viaja en PlayStation®Home como Pimento de Forsaken Planet, un videojuego de LOOT™ Entertainment para tabletas y smartphones! ¿Quieres ofertas y premios aún más jugosos de Forsaken Planet? ¡No te pierdas el Gran lote Forsaken Planet en la tienda LOOT™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Are you trigger happy? Travel PlayStation®Home as Pimento from Forsaken Planet, a LOOT™ Entertainment videogame for tablets and smart phones! Looking for even sweeter Forsaken Planet deals and in-game rewards? Check out the Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle in the LOOT™ Store! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>