<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ascendance - Data Eye-Piece V3.0 (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ascendance - Oculaire Data V3.0 (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ascendance - Datenbrille V3.0 (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ascendance - Oculare per dati V3.0 (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ascendance - Accesorio ocular de datos V3.0 (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Keep up to date with all the The Bureau's news bulletins with this Data Eye-Piece V3.0. You wouldn't want to miss information on how The Bureau is keeping your streets safe. The V3.0 model boasts far less bugs than the previous, inferior versions. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tenez-vous au courant des derniers bulletins de The Bureau grâce à cet oculaire Data V3.0. Vous ne voudriez manquer aucune information sur la manière dont The Bureau garantit la sécurité de vos rues. Le modèle V3.0 présente bien moins de bogues que les versions antérieures ou inférieures. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bleiben Sie auf dem neusten Stand und erhalten Sie aktuelle Nachrichten vom The Bureau mit der neuen Datenbrille V3.0. Sie wollen doch sicher keine Updates vom The Bureau über die Sicherheit in Ihrer Nachbarschaft verpassen, oder? Die Datenbrille V3.0 übertrifft alle vorigen Modelle was Störungsfreiheit und problemlose Datenübertragung betrifft. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Mantieniti aggiornata sui bollettini di The Bureau con questo Oculare per dati V3.0. Non vorrai perderti nessuna informazione su come The Bureau  mantiene la sicurezza delle tue strade. Il modello V3.0 presenta molti meno errori della versione precedente. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Estate al corriente de los nuevos boletines del The Bureau con este Accesorio ocular de datos V3.0. Mejor que no te pierdas ninguna información sobre cómo el The Bureau mantiene la seguridad en la calle. El modelo V3.0 presenta muchos menos fallos que las versiones anteriores e inferiores. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>