<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Miss Stripes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Mademoiselle de Rayure</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fräulein Streifen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Signorina Strisce</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Señorita Raya</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Miss Stripes</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Be bold and proud and stand out from the crowd in our range of body paint effects!  Get in touch with your inner artist and show off in unique style.... complete the look with the accessories and show your artistic flair, be Painted Bare! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Faites preuve d’audace et de courage pour vous démarquer grâce à notre gamme de peintures pour le corps ! Réveillez l’artiste qui sommeille en vous et cultivez votre différence à l’aide d’un style unique. Complétez votre look avec les accessoires assortis et montrez toute l’étendue de votre savoir-faire avec Painted Bare! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sei mutig und stolz und steche mit unserer Palette an Körperfarben-Effekten aus der Masse heraus! Berühre den Künstler in dir und prahle mit deinem einzigartigen Stil ... vervollständige dein Aussehen mit den Accessoires und zeige deine künstlerische Ader, sei Painted Bare! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vestiti di audacia e coraggio e distinguiti dalla massa con la nostra collezione di colori per il corpo! Entra in contatto con l'artista che è in te e fatti notare per il tuo stile unico... completa il look scegliendo gli accessori ed esprimi la tua vena artistica con Painted Bare! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Atrévete de destacar con orgullo entre la multitud con nuestra amplia gama de efectos de body painting. Saca al artista que llevas dentro y presume de estilo único. ¡Completa tu nuevo look con accesorios y muestra tu vena artística con la colección Painted Bare! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Be bold and proud and stand out from the crowd in our range of body paint effects!  Get in touch with your inner artist and show off in unique style.... complete the look with the accessories and show your artistic flair, be Painted Bare! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>