<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Vortex Attractor (50)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Attracteur du Vortex (50)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vortex-Attraktor (50)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Attrattore Vortice (50)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Atractor del Vórtice (50)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ボルテックスアトラクター（５０個入り）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">볼텍스 유인기 (50)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Vortex Attractor (50)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">旋渦魚巢 (50)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">旋渦魚巢 (50)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Vortex Attractor (50)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Vortex Attractors can be used in the Aurora Sky Fishing game to dramatically reduce the waiting time and distance between you and your catch, making it much easier to reel in the rarer catches. This is a pack of 50 Vortex Attractors. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les attracteurs du Vortex sont utilisables dans le jeu de pêche d'Aurora Sky, permettant de réduire considérablement le temps d'attente et la distance vous séparant de votre prise, ce qui facilite considérablement le moulinage pour les prises rares. Il s'agit d'un lot de 50 attracteurs du Vortex [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vortex-Attraktoren können beim Aurora Sky Fishing benutzt werden, um die Wartezeit beim Angeln und die Entfernung zwischen dir und deinem Fang erheblich zu verkürzen. Also wird es viel einfacher, einen seltenen Fang einzuholen! Dies ist ein Paket mit 50 Vortex-Attraktoren. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gli Attrattori Vortice possono essere usati nel gioco Pesca del cielo di Aurora per ridurre in maniera considerevole il tempo d'attesa e la distanza tra te e le catture, aiutandoti molto a tirar fuori le catture più rare. Questo è un pacchetto di 50 Attrattori Vortice. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Puedes usar los atractores del Vórtice en el juego de pesca espacial de Aurora para reducir de forma drástica el tiempo de espera y la distancia con la presa, de forma que es más fácil recoger el carrete con las presas raras. El paquete contiene 50 atractores del Vórtice. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラのスカイフィッシングゲームでボルテックスアトラクターを使うと、魚がかかるまでの時間が短縮され、さらに釣り上げられる距離が伸びるため、よりレアな魚をたくさん釣ることができます。５０個入りパックです。\n※本アイテムは消費型アイテムです。追加購入が可能です。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">볼텍스 유인기는 오로라 스카이 피싱 게임에서 무언가를 잡을 때 기다리는 시간을 현저히 줄어들게 해줍니다. 그것은 기다리는 시간은 줄어들고 실제 낚시하는 시간은 늘어난다는 뜻입니다! 이것은 50개의 볼텍스 유인기 팩입니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Vortex Attractors can be used in the Aurora Sky Fishing game to dramatically reduce the waiting time and distance between you and your catch, making it much easier to reel in the rarer catches. This is a pack of 50 Vortex Attractors. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">旋渦魚巢可在極光空中釣魚遊戲中使用，可大幅減少等魚上鉤的等待時間。這意味著減少等待時間，大量增加釣魚時間！本道具包含50個旋渦魚巢。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">旋渦魚巢可在極光空中釣魚遊戲中使用，可大幅減少等魚上鉤的等待時間。這意味著減少等待時間，大量增加釣魚時間！本道具包含50個旋渦魚巢。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Vortex Attractors can be used in the Aurora Sky Fishing game to dramatically reduce the waiting time and distance between you and your catch, making it much easier to reel in the rarer catches. This is a pack of 50 Vortex Attractors. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>