<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Mercia Scout Beetle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Scarabée éclaireur de Mercia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mercia-Kundschafterkäfer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Coleottero esploratore di Mercia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Escarabajo explorador de Mercia</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mercia Scout Beetle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Beetles come from desolate lands where ancient gods older than Mercia sit and wait in the darkness. The Beetles have emerged into Mercia and now multiply, draining life from everything in their path until nothingness remains, creating a suitable world for their elder gods. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les scarabées viennent de terres désolées où d'anciens dieux plus vieux que Mercia elle-même attendent dans l'ombre. Les scarabées sont apparus dans Mercia et se multiplient, aspirant la vie de tout ce qu'ils trouvent sur leur passage et ne laissant rien derrière eux, préparant ainsi un monde prêt à accueillir leurs dieux anciens. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Käfer stammen aus einem unwirtlichen Land, in dem uralte Götter, die älter als Mercia selbst sind, in Finsternis warten. Die Käfer haben in Mercia Fuß gefasst und vermehren sich schnell. Sie entziehen allem in ihrem Weg das Leben und hinterlassen eine Schneise der Verwüstung, um eine geeignete Welt für ihre höchsten Götter zu schaffen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I coleotteri provengono da terre desolate dove antiche divinità più antiche della Mercia si nascondo nell'oscurità. I coleotteri sono comparsi in Mercia e ora si moltiplicano, succhiando vita da tutto ciò che trovano sul loro cammino fino a che non resta nulla, creando un mondo adatto alle loro antiche divinità. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los escarabajos proceden de tierras desoladas donde dioses más viejos que Mercia esperan sentados en la oscuridad. Los escarabajos han llegado a Mercia y ahora se reproducen, absorbiendo la vida de todo lo que encuentran en su camino hasta que no queda nada para crear un mundo apto para sus ancianos dioses. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Beetles come from desolate lands where ancient gods older than Mercia sit and wait in the darkness. The Beetles have emerged into Mercia and now multiply, draining life from everything in their path until nothingness remains, creating a suitable world for their elder gods. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>