<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Wrangler - Mid Stone Western Denim Jacket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Wrangler — Chemise western denim délavage moyen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wrangler - Western-Jeansjacke Mid Stone</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Wrangler - Giacca in jeans stile Western effetto Stone Wash medio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Wrangler - Chaqueta Vaquera Western con medio efecto lavado a la piedra</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Wrangler - Mid Stone Western Denim Jacket (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Wrangler - Mid Stone Western Denim Jacket (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Wrangler - Mid Stone Western Denim Jacket (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Wrangler - Mid Stone Western Denim Jacket (Men)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A piece of history from Wrangler: classic Western jacket in a mid stone wash, with through button fastening, two chest pockets, two side pockets and stylish stitch detail throughout. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une pièce historique de Wrangler : chemise western classique délavage moyen, fermeture à boutons à boutonnière, deux poches poitrine, deux poches latérales et coutures stylées sur l'ensemble. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein Stück Wrangler-Geschichte: Klassische Westernjacke in Mid-Stone-Wash, mit durchgehendem Knopfverschluss, zwei Brusttaschen, zwei Seitentaschen und stylischen Nahtdetails. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un pezzo di storia della Wrangler: Giacca classica stile western a effetto Stone wash di media intensità, con allacciatura frontale a bottoni, due tasche sul petto , due tasche laterali ed eleganti cuciture a contrasto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una prenda histórica de Wrangler: clásica chaqueta western con ligero efecto de lavado a la piedra, botones convencionales hasta abajo, dos bolsillos en el pecho y estilosos bordados en toda la prenda. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>