<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">AudiVRunGameRules</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Audi Vertical Run Game Rules</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Règles du jeu Audi Vertical Run</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Spielregeln Audi Vertical Run Spiel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Regole del gioco Audi Vertical Run</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Reglas del juego Audi Vertical Run</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesSpeedUp</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Red markers increase the speed of the Audi e-tron.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les marqueurs rouges font augmenter la vitesse de l'Audi e-tron.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rote Markierungen erhöhen die Geschwindigkeit des Audi e-tron.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gli indicatori rossi servono ad aumentare la velocità dell'Audi e-tron.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los marcadores rojos aumentan la velocidad del Audi e-tron.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesSlowDown</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blue markers decrease the speed of the Audi e-tron.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les marqueurs bleus font diminuer la vitesse de l'Audi e-tron.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blaue Markierungen reduzieren die Geschwindigkeit des Audi e-tron.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gli indicatori blu servono a ridurre la velocità dell'Audi e-tron.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los marcadores azules disminuyen la velocidad del Audi e-tron.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesBoost</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Collecting electrical charges will help you launch further at the end of the track.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En ramassant des charges électriques, vous pourrez vous lancer plus haut en bout de piste.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Aufnehmen elektrischer Ladungen hilft Dir dabei, am Ende der Schanze weiter zu fliegen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Accumulare cariche elettriche ti aiuterà a lanciarti più lontano alla fine della pista.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Recaudar cargas eléctricas te ayudará a lanzar más lejos al final de la pista.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesSteering</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use [LEFTSTICK] to steer the Audi e-tron left and right.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez [LEFTSTICK] pour diriger l'Audi e-tron à droite ou à gauche.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verwende [LEFTSTICK], um den Audi e-tron nach links und rechts zu steuern.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Usare [LEFTSTICK] per svoltare a sinistra e destra con la tua Audi e-tron.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Utiliza [LEFTSTICK] para pilotar el Audi a derecha e izquierda.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesActivateBoost</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [CROSS] to activate an electrical charge.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyez sur [CROSS] pour activer une charge électrique.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücke [CROSS], um die elektrische Ladung zu aktivieren.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premere [CROSS] per attivare una carica elettrica.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Presiona [CROSS] para activar una carga eléctrica.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesJumpBoost1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">You can build up a supercharge to give you an extra auto-boost when you leave the ramp.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Accumulez une super-charge pour bénéficier d'une poussée supplémentaire en quittant la rampe.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Du kannst eine Superladung aufbauen, um beim Verlassen der Schanze einen automatischen Zusatzantrieb zu erhalten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Puoi accumulare sovralimentazione per darti una spinta in più quando ti stacchi dalla rampa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Puedes acumular una supercarga para darte extra auto-impulsión cuando sales de la rampa.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesJumpBoost2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">To increase your supercharge keep your speed above 200kph.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pour faire augmenter votre super-charge, roulez à une vitesse supérieure à 200 KM/H.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Um die Superladung zu erhöhen, musst Du Deine Geschwindigkeit über 200 KM/H halten.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Per aumentare la sovralimentazione tieni la velocità al di sopra dei 200 KM/H.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Para aumentar tu supercarga, mantén tu velocidad arriba de 200 KM/H.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesJumpBoost4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If your speed drops below 100kph your supercharge will decrease.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si votre vitesse tombe en dessous de 100 KM/H, votre super-charge va commencer à diminuer.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn Deine Geschwindigkeit unter 100 KM/H fällt, reduziert sich Deine Superladung.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se la tua velocità scende al di sotto dei 100 KM/H, la sovralimentazione si riduce.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si tu velocidad baja a menos de 100 KM/H, tu supercarga disminuirá.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesFallOff</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Watch out for the gaps in the barriers. If you fall off, the game ends.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Attention aux espaces entre les barrières. Si vous chutez, la partie sera terminée.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Pass auf Lücken in den Leitplanken auf. Wenn Du runterfällst, ist das Spiel zu Ende.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Fai attenzione agli spazi vuoti fra le barriere. Se precipiti, la tua partita termina.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Atento a los intervalos en las barreras. Si te caes, el juego terminará.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesAim1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Use your collected electrical charges when you lift off at the end of the ramp.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Utilisez les charges électriques que vous ramassez au moment du décollage en bout de rampe.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verwende Deine elektrischen Ladungen, nachdem Du am Ende der Rampe abgehoben hast.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Utilizza le cariche elettriche accumulate quando prendi quota alla fine della rampa.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Utiliza tus cargas eléctricas recaudadas al despegar al final de la rampa.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesAim2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">If you launch far enough you will win the Audi apartment.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si vous vous volez assez loin, vous remporterez l'appartement Audi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wenn Du weit genug fliegst, gewinnst Du das Audi Apartment.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se col lancio copri una distanza sufficientemente lunga, ti aggiudicherai l'appartamento Audi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si lanzas lo suficientemente lejos, ganarás el apartamento Audi.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesHighScore1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Race again to beat your own and your friends high scores.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Faites encore la course pour vaincre votre meilleur score et celui de vos amis.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Fahre das Rennen erneut, um Deine eigene High Score und die Deiner Freunde zu schlagen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gareggia di nuovo per migliorare i tuoi punteggi alti e battere quelli dei tuoi amici.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Compite nuevamente para superar tu alta puntuación y la de tus amigos.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesHighScore2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">With a perfect drive you may even reach the top 10.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avec une conduite parfaite, vous pourrez atteindre les 10 meilleurs scores.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bei einem perfekten Rennen kannst Du vielleicht die TOP 10 erreichen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Con una guida perfetta potresti perfino raggiungere la top 10.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con una carrera perfecta podrás incluso llegar a las 10 puntuaciones más altas.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesHint</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hint</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Astuce</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hinweis</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Suggerimento</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sugerencia</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesLeftStick</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[LEFTSTICK]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">GameRulesCross</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[CROSS]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>