<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Dragon House Furniture Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Dragon Maison paquet de meubles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drachenhaus Möbel-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Casa Drago pacchetto mobili</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Casa Dragón paquete de muebles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">龍パック家具ハウス</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">드래곤 팩 가구의 집</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Dragon House Furniture Pack</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">龙包家具屋</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">龙包家具屋</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Dragon House Furniture Pack</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A loyal banner-man of House Thaon should own all of the finely crafted furniture pertaining to that house. It's basic respect. Or you just like the color palette! Includes House Thaon Throne, House Thaon Ottoman, House Thaon Circular Coffee Table, House Thaon Rectangular Coffee Table, House Thaon Grand Vase, House Thaon Daybed, House Thaon  King Bed, House Thaon Grand Chair, House Thaon Chair, House Thaon Loveseat, House Thaon Grand Dining Chair, House Thaon Dining Chair, House Thaon Wardrobe, and House Thaon Shield.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un fidèle porte-bannière de la Maison Thaon devrait posséder tous les meubles de belle facture se rapportant à cette maison. C'est le respect fondamental. Ou vous aimez tout simplement la palette de couleurs! Maison Thaon Trône, Maison Thaon pouf, Maison Thaon table à café circulaire, Maison Thaon table à café rectangulaire, Maison Thaon grande vase, Maison Thaon Méridienne, Maison Thaon roi lit, Maison Thaon chaise grande, Maison Thaon chaise, Maison Thaon petit canapé, Maison Thaon chaise dinante Grand, Maison Thaon chaise dinante, Maison Thaon Armoire, et Maison Thaon Bouclier.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein treuer Bannerträger des Hauses Thaon sollten alle Möbel haben, schön gemacht im Zusammenhang mit diesem Haus. Dies ist der grundlegende Respekt. Liebe oder einfach nur die Farbe! Haus Thaon Thron, Haus Thaon Ottomane, Haus Thaon kreisförmigen Couchtisch, Haus Thaon rechteckiger Couchtisch, Haus Thaon große Vase, Haus Thaon Schlafcouch, Haus Thaon Königs Bett, Haus Thaon großartigen Stuhl, Haus Thaon Stuhl, Haus Thaon kleines Sofa, Haus Thaon großen Speisesaal Stuhl, Haus Thaon Speisesaal Stuhl, Haus Thaon Schrank, und Haus Thaon Wappenschild.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un fedele alfiere della Thaon casa dovrebbe avere tutti i mobili, ben fatto appartenenti a questa casa. Questo è il rispetto fondamentale. O semplicemente ama il colore! Casa Thaon Trono, Casa Thaon pouf, Casa Thaon circolare tavolino, Casa Thaon tavolino rettangolare, Casa Thaon grande vaso, Casa Thaon divanoletto, Casa Thaon letto del re, Casa Thaon grande sedia, Casa Thaon sedia, Casa Thaon piccolo divano, Casa Thaon gran pranzo sedia, Casa Thaon pranzo sedia, Casa Thaon armadio, e Casa Thaon scudo.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un fiel estandarte de la Casa Thaon deben tener todos los muebles, muy bien hecho concernientes a esta casa. Este es el aspecto fundamental. O me encanta el color! Casa Thaon Trono, Casa Thaon otomana, Casa Thaon mesa de café circular, Casa Thaon mesa de café rectangular, Casa Thaon de gran jarrón, Casa Thaon sofá cama, Casa Thaon la cama del rey, Casa Thaon gran silla, Casa Thaon silla, Casa Thaon pequeño sofá, Casa Thaon gran silla de comedor, Casa Thaon silla de comedor, Casa Thaon armario, y Casa Thaon escudo.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ハウスThaonの忠実なバナー男はその家に関連する精巧な家具のすべてを所有する必要があります。これは、基本的な敬意です。または、カラーパレットを単に好きです！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">하우스 Thaon의 충성도 배너 - 사람이 그 집에 관련된 잘게 만들어진 가구를 모두 소유해야합니다. 그것은 기본 예의입니다. 또는 색상 팔레트를 똑같아![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A loyal banner-man of House Thaon should own all of the finely crafted furniture pertaining to that house. It's basic respect. Or you just like the color palette! Includes House Thaon Throne, House Thaon Ottoman, House Thaon Circular Coffee Table, House Thaon Rectangular Coffee Table, House Thaon Grand Vase, House Thaon Daybed, House Thaon  King Bed, House Thaon Grand Chair, House Thaon Chair, House Thaon Loveseat, House Thaon Grand Dining Chair, House Thaon Dining Chair, House Thaon Wardrobe, and House Thaon Shield.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">一位忠诚的旗帜内务Thaon人应该拥有的所有有关那家精心制作的家具。这是基本的尊重。或者你只是想调色板！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">一位忠诚的旗帜内务Thaon人应该拥有的所有有关那家精心制作的家具。这是基本的尊重。或者你只是想调色板！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A loyal banner-man of House Thaon should own all of the finely crafted furniture pertaining to that house. It's basic respect. Or you just like the color palette! Includes House Thaon Throne, House Thaon Ottoman, House Thaon Circular Coffee Table, House Thaon Rectangular Coffee Table, House Thaon Grand Vase, House Thaon Daybed, House Thaon  King Bed, House Thaon Grand Chair, House Thaon Chair, House Thaon Loveseat, House Thaon Grand Dining Chair, House Thaon Dining Chair, House Thaon Wardrobe, and House Thaon Shield.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>