<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Patient Zero Poster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Poster Patient Zero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Patient Zero"-Poster</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Poster del Paziente Zero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Póster de Patient Zero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">患者第1号 ポスター</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Patient Zero Poster</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Decorate your PlayStation®Home private spaces with this Sideshow Collectibles® original Patient Zero premium poster from The Dead collection. Lumbering from his hiding place, Patient Zero reaches for an unseen target. His contorted face gives a haunting picture of The Dead, jaw open in a silent scream, eyes milky and glazed with death. This premium poster of Sideshow Collectibles® original artwork of Patient Zero is an outstanding addition to any display. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Décorez vos espaces privés PlayStation®Home avec ce poster original Sideshow Collectibles® de la collection The Dead. Surgissant de sa cachette d’un air menaçant, Patient Zero tend le bras pour saisir un objet invisible. Son visage crispé donne une image tourmentée de The Dead, mâchoire grande ouverte poussant un cri silencieux, avec les yeux vitreux et glacés de la mort. Ce poster de qualité Sideshow Collectibles®, oeuvre originale du Patient Zero apporte une touche exceptionnelle à toute décoration. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dekorier deine PlayStation®Home-Privatbereiche mit diesem originellen "Patient Zero"-Hochglanzposter aus der "The Dead"-Kollektion von Sideshow Collectibles®. Aus seinem Versteck hervortorkelnd greift Patient Zero nach einem unsichtbaren Ziel. Sein Gesicht ist verzerrt, sein Mund zu einem stummen Schrei geöffnet, die Augen milchig und ausdruckslos. Dieses Hochglanzposter nach einer Originalzeichnung von Patient Zero ist ein Muss in jeder "Sideshow Collectibles®"-Ausstellung. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Addobba i tuoi spazi privati PlayStation®Home con questo super poster del Paziente Zero della raccolta The Dead. Mentre esce dal suo nascondiglio, il Paziente Zero punta a un bersaglio nascosto. La sua espressione contorta, con la bocca spalancata in un urlo silenzioso e gli occhi umidi e vitrei di morte, dà l'idea della voracità. Questo super poster del Paziente Zero della produzione Sideshow Collectibles® è un'aggiunta notevole per qualsiasi display. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Decora tus espacios privados PlayStation®Home con este póster original de Patient Zero de Sideshow Collectibles® de la colección The Dead. Arrastrándose desde su escondite, Patient Zero se abalanza sobre una víctima oculta. Su retorcido rostro es una espeluznante imagen de The Dead, con la boca abierta en un silencioso grito y los ojos en blanco y vidriosos, llenos de muerte. Este póster original de Sideshow Collectibles® de Patient Zero es una adquisición perfecta que mostrar. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">PlayStation®Homeプライベートラウンジをサイドショー・コレクティブルズ®オリジナル、ザ・デッド・コレクションからきたプレミアム患者第1号 ポスターで飾ろう。隠れ家からうごめいてきた患者第1号は眼に見えない目標に手を伸ばしている。彼の歪んだ顔は頭にこびりついて離れない。声のない叫び声のため開いた顎、死によって眼は濁り、どんよりとしている…。サイドショー・コレクティブルズ®オリジナルアートワーク、患者第1号のプレミアムポスターはどんなディスプレイでも目立つことウケアイ。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Decorate your PlayStation®Home private spaces with this Sideshow Collectibles® original Patient Zero premium poster from The Dead collection. Lumbering from his hiding place, Patient Zero reaches for an unseen target. His contorted face gives a haunting picture of The Dead, jaw open in a silent scream, eyes milky and glazed with death. This premium poster of Sideshow Collectibles® original artwork of Patient Zero is an outstanding addition to any display. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>