<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">AlphabeTees “M” (Female)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">AlphabeTees “M” (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">AlphabeTees “M” (Frau)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">AlphabeTees “M” (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">AlphabeTees “M” (Mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">AlphabeTees “M” (Female)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Not so much a range of T's as a people-powered gaming movement. This full 26 letter Alphabet T-shirt set (with punctuation marks included) is all about getting together and making a statement (literally). Make the longest word or the weirdest words with your friends. Host your own Alphabet Party. Challenge others to a body based quiz game. All brought to you by individual letters, the hard-working characters behind words.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pas tant une gamme de T-shirts qu'un mouvement de jeu alimenté par les joueurs. Ce lot complet de T-shirts Alphabet 26 lettres (y compris les signes de ponctuation) appelle à se réunir et à formuler une réponse (littéralement). Composez le mot le plus long ou le plus étrange avec vos amis. Organisez votre propre Alphabet Party. Défiez les autres dans un jeu de quiz humain. Tout cela à portée de lettres, les fourmis travailleuses derrière les mots. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mehr als eine T-Shirtserie. Eher eine von allen Teilnehmern gestaltete Gaming-Bewegung. Bei diesem 26 Buchstaben (plus Satzzeichen) umfassenden ABC-T-Shirtset geht es darum, Leute zusammenzubringen und ein Statement abzugeben, und das buchstäblich. Mach gemeinsam mit Freunden das längste oder auch das seltsamste Wort, das euch einfällt. Gib deine eigene ABC-Party. Fordere andere zu einem Quizspiel heraus. Das alles ist mit einzelnen Buchstaben – die Schwerarbeiter, die hinter jedem Wort stecken - zu erreichen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non è solo una gamma di T-shirt ma soprattutto un movimento per dare potere al popolo dei gamer. Questa serie di magliette con le 26 lettere dell'alfabeto (compresa la punteggiatura) serve a mettersi insieme ed esprimersi a chiare lettere (letteralmente). Componi con i tuoi amici la parola più lunga o le parole più strane. Organizza il tuo Alphabet Party. Sfida gli altri a un quiz che si basa sul corpo. Il tutto grazie alle singole lettere, i personaggi dal bel caratterino che formano le parole. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No es sólo una gama de camisetas, sino que es un juego novedoso en el que las personas son las protagonistas. Este conjunto de camisetas con las 26 letras del abecedario (con signos de puntuación incluidos) tiene como objeto la colaboración para realizar una declaración (literal). Construye la palabra más larga o la más original con tus amigos. Celebra tu propia fiesta del abecedario. Compite con otros en un concurso en el que hay que utilizar el cuerpo. Todo es posible gracias a las letras, los personajes que trabajan duro tras las palabras. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Not so much a range of T's as a people-powered gaming movement. This full 26 letter Alphabet T-shirt set (with punctuation marks included) is all about getting together and making a statement (literally). Make the longest word or the weirdest words with your friends. Host your own Alphabet Party. Challenge others to a body based quiz game. All brought to you by individual letters, the hard-working characters behind words.  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>