<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hellbug Companion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Compagnon messoran</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hellbug-Gefährte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hellbug Companion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hellbug Companion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hellbug Companion</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The hellbugs are a product of the Arkfall and the subsequent terraforming of Earth. They’re deadly and destructive, yet somehow adorable.  You'll never be alone with this skittering companion by your side! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Les Messorans sont issus de la Chute des arches et du processus de terraformation consécutif de la Terre. Ces créatures mortelles et destructrices ont pourtant un petit je-ne-sais-quoi qui les rend adorables, à leur façon. Dites au revoir à la solitude et voyagez en compagnie de cet Ouvrier messoran ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Hellbugs sind durch den Archenfall und den anschließenden Terraform-Prozess der Erde entstanden. Sie sind tödlich und destruktiv, aber irgendwie auch so richtig niedlich. Mit diesem räuberischen Hellbug-Gefährten an deiner Seite wirst du niemals mehr allein sein! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Gli hellbug sono un prodotto delle Arkfall e del successivo processo di terraforming subito dalla Terra. Sono letali e distruttivi, ma sono anche stranamente adorabili. Non ti sentirai mai solo con questo amico zampettante! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Los hellbugs son producto del Arkfall y la consiguiente terraformación de la Tierra. Son letales y destructivos pero a la vez adorables. Con estos escurridizos seres a tu lado, ¡nunca estarás solo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The hellbugs are a product of the Arkfall and the subsequent terraforming of Earth. They’re deadly and destructive, yet somehow adorable.  You'll never be alone with this skittering companion by your side! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kCompanionName1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hellbug Companion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Compagnon messoran</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hellbug-Gefährte</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Hellbug Companion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hellbug Companion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hellbug Companion</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>