<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gothic Cathedral</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cathédrale gothique</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gotische Kathedrale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cattedrale gotica</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Catedral gótica</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gothic Cathedral</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This ancient abandoned cathedral on the cliff is a sanctuary and a place you call home.  From the majestic room, moonlit courtyard, to the massive candlelit hall, you can be the ruler of the night. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette ancienne cathédrale abandonnée sur la falaise est un sanctuaire et votre maison. De la pièce majestueuse, en passant par la cour au clair de lune jusqu'à l'énorme entrée éclairée aux chandelles, vous pouvez être le maître de la nuit. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Diese alte verlassene Kathedrale auf der Klippe ist ein Heiligtum und ein Ort, das man Zuhause nennen kann. Vom majestätischen Saal, dem mondbeschienenen Hof bis zur massiven mit Kerzenlicht beleuchteten Halle können Sie der Herrscher der Nacht sein. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Quest'antica cattedrale abbandonata sul ciglio del dirupo è un santuario e un luogo che puoi chiamare casa. Dall'imponente sala, dal cortile al chiaro di Luna, fino all'enorme atrio illuminato a lume di candela, potrai essere il signore della notte. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Esta antigua y abandonada catedral que está sobre el acantilado es un santuario y el lugar al que llamas hogar. Desde la majestuosa habitación, el patio iluminado por la luna, hasta el gran vestíbulo lleno de velas, tú puedes ser el que gobierne la noche. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">*Not Localised* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>