<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Hollywood Hills House Nighttime Clubhouse Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot de Club-House de nuit de Hollywood Hills</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Klubhaus eines Hauses in Hollywood Hills bei Nacht-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Circolo notturno Casa di Hollywood Hills Pacchetto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Casa Hollywood Hills, clubhouse de noche lote</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Hollywood Hills House Nighttime Clubhouse Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Hollywood Hills House Nighttime Clubhouse Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Entertain like an industry mogul in this ultimate clubhouse, set in the Hollywood Hills above the LA skyline! Invite your friends into your home theater for a social viewing experience with videos, trailers and exclusive content from Sony Pictures! Features include:\n
• Built-in Entertainment On Demand theater system;\n
• A swimming feature for the infinity pool!\n
THIS is where the party is for you and your club. Purchase of this clubhouse comes bundled with the LOOT™ Active Camera and Active Light, so you can film your parties and upload them to YouTube at no extra cost!\n\n PLEASE READ:  Due to contractual and rights agreements, all content may not be available in all countries. Content availability is dependent on the geolocation of the device. CRACKLE content is only available in US, CA, UK, and AU. RADIOIO is only available in US and CA. Only one LOOT™ TV or LOOT™ Radio can be active at a time. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Recevez comme un magnat de l'industrie dans ce  club-house haut de gamme situé sur les hauteurs de Hollywood Hills, dominant ainsi tout Los Angeles ! Invitez vos amis dans le home cinéma pour regarder en société des vidéos, des bandes-annonces et des contenus exclusifs de Sony Pictures ! Les fonctions comprennent : \n 
• Un Système Ciné de Loisirs à la Demande Intégré ; \n 
• Une fonction natation pour la piscine panoramique ! \n
VOILÀ l'endroit idéal pour faire la fête avec votre club ! L'achat de ce club-house vient avec les lots Caméra Active LOOT™ et Lumière Active, pour que vous puissiez filmer vos fêtes et les télécharger sur YouTube sans frais supplémentaire. \n
\n 
Veuillez lire :  En raison d'accords contractuels et juridiques, les contenus ne sont pas disponibles dans tous les pays. La disponibilité du contenu dépend de la géolocalisation du système.  Le contenu Crackle est disponible uniquement aux USA, au Canada, en Grande-Bretagne et en Australie. RadioIO est disponible UNIQUEMENT aux USA et au Canada. Vous ne pouvez faire fonctionner qu'une Télé LOOT™ ou qu'une Radio LOOT™ à la fois. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unterhalte in diesem todschicken Klubhaus in Hollywood Hills über der Skyline von Los Angeles deine Gäste wie ein Industriemogul! Lade deine Freunde zu einer geselligen Kinorunde mit Videos, Trailern und exklusiven Inhalten von Sony Pictures in dein Heimkino ein! Das Paket enthält:\n
• Integriertes EOD-Heimkino\n
• Schwimmfunktion für den Unendlichkeits-Swimmingpool!\n
DIES ist der richtige Ort, um für dich und deinen Klub Parties steigen zu lassen. Dieses Klubhauspaket enthält auch die aktive LOOT™-Kamera und das aktive LOOT™-Licht, damit du deine Parties ohne weitere Kosten filmen und auf YouTube hochladen kannst!\n\n BITTE LESEN:
Aufgrund vertraglicher und rechtlicher Vereinbarungen sind einige EOD-Kanäle auf bestimmte Länder beschränkt. Inhalt von Crackle ist NUR in den Vereinigten Staaten, in Kanada, im Vereinigten Königreich und in Australien verfügbar. RadioIO ist NUR in den Vereinigten Staaten und in Kanada verfügbar. Darüber hinaus ist es aus rechtlichen Gründen möglich, dass bestimmte Länder innerhalb der Kanäle nicht dieselben Inhaltsauswahlen erhalten. Der Inhalt ist nur in englischer Sprache verfügbar. Falls Freunde aus anderen Ländern bei dir sind, kann nur Inhalt angezeigt werden, der in allen Ländern verfügbar ist. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vesti i panni di un magnate dell'industria in questo circolo spettacolare di Hollywood Hills e goditi la vista su Los Angeles! Invita i tuoi amici nel tuo cinema privato per guardare insieme video, trailer e contenuti esclusivi di Sony Pictures! Sono incluse le seguenti funzionalità:\n
• Sistema cinematografico di intrattenimento su richiesta integrato;\n
• Funzionalità di nuoto per la piscina a sfioro!\n
QUESTO è il posto giusto per festeggiare con gli amici. Con l'acquisto di questo circolo sono disponibili gli oggetti di LOOT™ Telecamera attiva e Illuminazione attiva che ti permetteranno di filmare le tue feste e di caricarle su YouTube senza costi aggiuntivi!\n\n LEGGERE:
A causa di accordi contrattuali e sui diritti, alcuni canali EOD sono disponibili solo per determinate nazioni. I contenuti Crackle sono disponibili SOLAMENTE per Stati Uniti, Canada, Regno Unito e Australia. RadioIO è disponibile SOLAMENTE per Stati Uniti e Canada. Inoltre, alcuni paesi potrebbero non ricevere le stesse selezioni di contenuto per i vari canali. I contenuti sono disponibili solo in lingua inglese. Se con te ci sono amici provenienti da altre nazioni, possono essere visualizzati solo contenuti disponibili per tutti i paesi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Recibe a tus invitados como un gran magnate con esta fantástica clubhouse, ¡situada en Hollywood Hills, en lo alto del horizonte de Los Ángeles!  ¡Invita a tus amigos a disfrutar de tu Home Cinema y de un acontecimiento social con vídeos, tráilers y contenidos exclusivos de Sony Pictures! Incluye:\n
• Entertainment On Demand con sistema Home Cinema;\n
• ¡Función de natación para la piscina infinita!\n
AQUÍ está la fiesta, para ti y para tu club. La compra de esta clubhouse incluye en el lote la Active Camera y la Active Light de LOOT™, ¡para que puedas filmar tus fiestas y subirlas a YouTube sin coste adicional!\n
\n 
LEER DETENIDAMENTE:
Debido a acuerdos contractuales y derechos, algunos canales solo se emiten en determinados países. El contenido Crackle SOLO está disponible en Estados Unidos, Canadá, Reino Unido y Australia. RadioIO SOLO está disponible en Estados Unidos y Canadá. Además, los derechos hacen que cada país pueda recibir selecciones de contenidos diferentes en los canales. Contenidos solo disponibles en inglés. Si estás con amigos de otros países, solo se verán los contenidos disponibles en todos los países.\n
\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Entertain like an industry mogul in this ultimate clubhouse, set in the Hollywood Hills above the LA skyline! Invite your friends into your home theater for a social viewing experience with videos, trailers and exclusive content from Sony Pictures! Features include:\n
• Built-in Entertainment On Demand theater system;\n
• A swimming feature for the infinity pool!\n
THIS is where the party is for you and your club.\n\n PLEASE READ:  Due to contractual and rights agreements, all content may not be available in all countries. Content availability is dependent on the geolocation of the device. CRACKLE content is only available in US, CA, UK, and AU. RADIOIO is only available in US and CA. Only one LOOT™ TV or LOOT™ Radio can be active at a time. ※Please note, in order to access the clubhouse you will need to have purchased the Club Slot. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Entertain like an industry mogul in this ultimate clubhouse, set in the Hollywood Hills above the LA skyline! Invite your friends into your home theater for a social viewing experience with videos, trailers and exclusive content from Sony Pictures! Features include:\n
• Built-in Entertainment On Demand theater system;\n
• A swimming feature for the infinity pool!\n
THIS is where the party is for you and your club. Purchase of this clubhouse comes bundled with the LOOT™ Active Camera and Active Light, so you can film your parties and upload them to YouTube at no extra cost!\n\n PLEASE READ:  Due to contractual and rights agreements, all content may not be available in all countries. Content availability is dependent on the geolocation of the device. CRACKLE content is only available in US, CA, UK, and AU. RADIOIO is only available in US and CA. Only one LOOT™ TV or LOOT™ Radio can be active at a time. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>