<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LOOT™ City Building Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot de bâtiments de LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LOOT™ Stadtbau-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Costruzione Città LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de edificios de LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LOOT™ 街づくりパック</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LOOT™ City Building Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Finally, LOOT™ has given you what you’ve always wanted: Building blocks so you can create tiny cities to terrorize with your own avatar monsters!!! Yes, we have been reading your diary. And with this bundle you get all 15 stackable pieces which includes the LOOTville Power Line - Exclusive only to the LOOT™ City Building Bundle! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">LOOT™ vous propose enfin ce dont vous avez toujours rêvé : des bâtiments pour créer de petites villes que vos monstres avatars pourront terroriser !!! Oui, nous avons lu votre journal intime. Et dans ce lot, vous aurez les 15 blocs superposables ainsi que la ligne haute tension de LOOTville. Offre exclusive avec ce lot de bâtiments de LOOT™ ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Endlich hat dir LOOT™ das gegeben, was du immer gewollt hast: Bauelemente – so kannst du kleine Städte bauen, die du mit deinen Avatar-Monstern in Angst und Schrecken versetzen kannst!! Ja, wir haben dein Tagebuch gelesen. Und mit diesem Paket kriegst du alle 15 stapelbaren Teile, einschließlich der LOOTville Stromleitung – Exklusiv nur für das LOOT™ Stadtbau-Paket! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Finalmente, la LOOT™ vi dà quello che avete sempre desiderato: potrete costruire degli edifici e creare piccole città da terrorizzare coi vostri mostri avatar!!! Sì, abbiamo letto il vostro diario. Con questo pacchetto avrete tutti e 15 i pezzi componibili, inclusa la Linea Elettrica LOOTville - In esclusiva solo nel Pacchetto Costruzione Città LOOT™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡¡¡Por fin, LOOT™ te da lo que siempre has querido: edificios con los que  crear pequeñas ciudades para aterrorizar a los monstruos que haya entre tus avatares!!! Sí, hemos leído tu diario. Y con este juego de edificios recibirás 15 piezas superponibles, incluyendo la línea de alta tensión de LOOTville - ¡Oferta exclusiva solo con el juego de edificios de la ciudad de LOOT™! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">街づくりブロックで小さな街を作り、アバターモンスターで街を恐怖のどん底にたたき落としましょう！！！（これが欲しかったんでしょう！？）\n本コンテンツには、プライベートラウンジのカスタマイズ用の以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n\n
・「LOOT村 オブザーバーA」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT村 オブザーバーB」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT村 合同会社A」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT村 合同会社B」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT村 タワーA」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT村 タワーB」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT™工業A」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT™工業B」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT村ハイツA」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT村ハイツB」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT村テック A」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT村テックB」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT村病院A」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT村病院B」（装飾品）\n
・「LOOT村 – 電力線」（装飾品）\n\n
※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。
 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Finally, LOOT™ has given you what you’ve always wanted: Building blocks so you can create tiny cities to terrorize with your own avatar monsters!!! Yes, we have been reading your diary. And with this bundle you get all 15 stackable pieces which includes the LOOTville Power Line - Exclusive only to the LOOT™ City Building Bundle! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>