<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Spacecraft – Column</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vaisseau spatial - Colonne</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Raumschiff – Säule</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Astronave - Colonna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nave espacial - Columna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">宇宙船 - 支柱</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Spacecraft – Column</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">With the LOOT™ Spacecraft Set you can build your very own space station interior location. Put on your captain’s space-goggles, assemble your crew, and get to building! The great universe beyond isn’t going to discover itself! Collect all 8 pieces! Intended for use in the LOOT™ Stageset Personal Space. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avec le lot Vaisseau Spacial de LOOT™, vous pourrez concevoir l' intérieur  de votre propre station spaciale. Chaussez vos lunettes spaciales de capitaine, rassemblez votre équipage  et commencez à construire !  L'univers de l'au-delà ne viendra pas à vous tout seul !  Collectionnez les 8 articles !   À utiliser dans l'Espace Personnel Plateau de Tournage de LOOT™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit dem LOOT™ Raumschiff-Set kannst du dir das Innere deiner eigenen Raumstation bauen. Setz dir die Weltraum-Schutzbrille des Captains auf, stelle deine Besatzung zusammen und dann ran! Das große Universum entdeckt sich nicht von selbst! Sammle alle 8 Teile! Für den Einsatz beim LOOT™ Stageset Personal Space. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Col Pacchetto Astronave LOOT™ puoi costruire l'interno della tua stazione spaziale. Indossa gli occhiali spaziali del tuo capitano, raduna l'equipaggio e inizia a costruire! Il grande universo non si scoprirà da solo! Colleziona tutti gli 8 pezzi! Da utilizzare nello Spazio Personale Palcoscenico LOOT™. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con la nave espacial de LOOT™ podrás diseñar el interior de tu propia estación espacial. ¡Ponte las gafas de capitán, reúne a la tripulación y comienza a construir! ¡El universo no va a descubrirse solo! ¡Colecciona las 8 piezas! Para su uso en el Espacio personal del plató de rodaje de LOOT™.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">本コンテンツは、パーソナルスペース「LOOT™スタジオ・ステージ・セット・バンドル」用にカスタマイズされております。このため、パーソナルスペース「ベーシック」などの天井の低いプライベートラウンジ（パーソナルスペース/クラブハウス）において、正常に設置できない場合があります。予めご了承ください。\n\n
キャプテンになった気分でクルーを集め、宇宙基地を作りましょう！広い宇宙はまだまだ未開拓！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">With the LOOT™ Spacecraft Set you can build your very own space station interior location. Put on your captain’s space-goggles, assemble your crew, and get to building! The great universe beyond isn’t going to discover itself! Collect all 8 pieces! Intended for use in the LOOT™ Stageset Personal Space. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>