<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Armed Soldier Bundle (Male)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pack Soldat armé (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Bewaffneter Soldat"-Paket (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Soldato armato (uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto de soldado armado (hombre)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Armed Soldier Bundle (Male)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This outfit comes fully equipped with weapons to fit in any combat situation. Bundle includes a helmet, camouflage jacket, camouflage combats, boots, and fingerless gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette tenue est fournie avec des armes indispensables pour faire face à n'importe quelle situation de combat. Ce pack inclut un casque, une veste de camouflage, un pantalon de camouflage, des bottes et des mitaines. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Outfit wird komplett mit Waffen geliefert, um auf jede Kampfsituation vorbereitet zu sein. Das Packet umfasst Helm, Tarnjacke, Tarnhose, Stiefel und fingerlose Handschuhe. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo completo è equipaggiato con armi adatte a ogni situazione di battaglia. Il pacchetto include elmetto, giacca mimetica, pantaloni mimetici, stivali e guanti senza dita. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este atuendo incorpora las armas necesarias para cualquier situación de combate. El conjunto comprende casco, chaqueta de camuflaje, pantalones de camuflaje, botas y mitones. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This outfit comes fully equipped with weapons to fit in any combat situation. Bundle includes a helmet, camouflage-jacket, camouflage-pants, boots, and finger-less gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>