<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Creek Falls - Bed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Creek Falls - Lit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Creek Falls - Bett</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Creek Falls - Letto</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Creek Falls: cama</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">クリークフォール：フロアベッド</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">계곡의 폭포수 - 침대</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Creek Falls - Bed</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">小溪瀑布-床</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">小溪瀑布-床</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Creek Falls - Bed</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Give your bedroom the contemporary look it longs for with this low-rise bed. As an added bonus, now two avatars may lay in the bed at the same time. This is an active item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Donnez à votre chambre l'ambiance moderne dont elle a besoin avec ce lit rabaissé. En bonus, deux avatars peuvent se coucher dans le lit. Cet objet est actif. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Bett verleiht dem Schlafzimmer das moderne Aussehen, das es verdient. Als Bonus können nun zwei Avatare gleichzeitig im Bett liegen. Dies ist ein aktives Objekt. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">In una stanza da letto dal look contemporaneo non può mancare un letto basso. Inoltre è ora possibile far sdraiare sullo stesso letto due avatar. Questo è un oggetto attivo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dale a tu dormitorio el aspecto contemporáneo que merece con esta cama baja. Como extra, podrán acostarse en ella dos avatares a la vez. Esto es un objeto activo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ベッドルームを現代的な印象に仕上げてくれるフロアベッドです。二人まで横になれる素敵な機能が追加されています。\n\n※このアイテムは、アニメーションや機能が追加されているアドバンスド家具です。この種類のアイテムは配置できる数に制限があります。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">낮은 스타일의 침대와 함께 당신의 침실을 현대적으로 탈바꿈하십시오. 보너스로 이제 두 명의 아바타가 같은 침대에 누울 수 있습니다. 액티브 아이템입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Give your bedroom the contemporary look it longs for with this low-rise bed. As an added bonus, now two avatars may lay in the bed at the same time. This is an active item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">用這張低架床給您的睡房營造應有的當代風格。它是動態道具，現在有一個額外好處：能讓兩個分身角色同時躺下。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">用這張低架床給您的睡房營造應有的當代風格。它是動態道具，現在有一個額外好處：能讓兩個分身角色同時躺下。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Give your bedroom the contemporary look it longs for with this low-rise bed. As an added bonus, now two avatars may lay in the bed at the same time. This is an active item. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>