<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LOOT™ Tiki Totem</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Totem Tiki LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LOOT™ Tiki-Totem</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Totem Tiki LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tótem Tiki LOOT™</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">LOOT™ティキ・トーテム</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LOOT™ Tiki Totem</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Your buddies at LOOT have carved you an exquisite sculpture of the iconic Tiki. In Rarotonga, Tiki is considered to be the Guardian of the passage to the Underworld, so we're pretty sure he'll do ok guarding the entrance to any of your personal spaces! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vos potes de LOOT vous ont fait une belle sculpture du fameux Tiki. À Rarotonga, Tiki est connu pour être le Gardien du passage aux Enfers, donc on est pratiquement sûrs qu'il fera du bon boulot pour surveiller toutes les entrées de vos espaces personnels ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Deine Kumpel bei LOOT haben eine exquisite Statue eines typischen Tiki geschnitzt. Auf Raratonga gilt der Tiki als Wächter des Passage zur Unterwelt. Er ist also super geeignet, den Eingang zu einem deiner Privaträume zu bewachen! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I tuoi amici di LOOT hanno creato questa deliziosa scultura del leggendario Tiki. A Rarotonga Tiki è considerato il Guardiano del passaggio negli Inferi, quindi siamo sicuri che farà del suo meglio a guardia dei tuoi spazi! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tus amigos de LOOT te han tallado una escultura del icónico Tiki de una belleza exquisita. En Rarotonga, el Tiki es considerado el guardián del pasaje al submundo, ¡así que seguro que protegemos bien la entrada a cualquiera de tus espacios personales! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">いつもあなたを想っている私たちLOOT™がアイコニックなティキをかたどった絶妙な彫像を刻んでおきました！ラロトンガではティキは冥土の門番とされていますので、きっとあなたのパーソナルスペースもしっかりと守ってくれますよ！ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Your buddies at LOOT have carved you an exquisite sculpture of the iconic Tiki. In Rarotonga, Tiki is considered to be the Guardian of the passage to the Underworld, so we're pretty sure he'll do ok guarding the entrance to any of your personal spaces! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>