<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Jedi Order Shirt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chemise de l'Ordre Jedi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jedi-Orden-Hemd</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maglietta Ordine Jedi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta de la Orden Jedi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Jedi Order Shirt</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A Jedi's strength flows from the Force. But beware the dark side. Anger, fear, aggression. The dark side of the Force are they. Easily they flow, quick to join you in a fight. If once you start down the dark path, forever will it dominate your destiny.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un Jedi tire sa puissance de la Force. Mais attention au côté obscur. Colère, crainte, agressivité. Le côté obscur de la Force, elles sont. Elles affluent facilement, lors des combats. Empruntez une fois le chemin obscur, et à jamais votre destinée celui-ci dominera. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die Stärke eines Jedis kommt von der Macht. Aber hüte dich vor der dunklen Seite. Wut, Furcht, Aggression. Die dunkle Seite der Macht sind sie. Leicht fließen sie, schnell helfen sie dir im Kampf. Wenn du erst einmal den dunklen Pfad betreten hast, wird er dein Schicksal für immer bestimmen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La potenza di un Jedi scorre dalla Forza. Ma attenzione al lato oscuro. Rabbia, paura, aggressività. Questi rappresentano il lato oscuro della Forza. Essi scorrono con facilità e sono sempre pronti a unirsi a te nella lotta. Se anche una volta intraprendi il cammino oscuro, esso per sempre dominerà il tuo destino. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La resistencia de un Jedi procede de la Fuerza. Pero estate atento al lado oscuro. Ira, miedo, agresividad. El lado oscuro de la Fuerza son todas esas cosas. Fluyen con facilidad y te conquistan rápidamente en una pelea. Una vez tomas el camino de la oscuridad, este siempre dominará tu destino. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A Jedi's strength flows from the Force. But beware the dark side. Anger, fear, aggression. The dark side of the Force are they. Easily they flow, quick to join you in a fight. If once you start down the dark path, forever will it dominate your destiny. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>