<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LMO – Musical Flusho Spunner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">LMO – Spunner Flusho musical</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LMO – Musikalischer Flusho-Spunner</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">LMO - Flusho Spunner musicale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">LMO – Spunner Flusho Musical</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LMO – Musical Flusho Spunner</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ride around PlayStation®Home on this cutest of toilet cows, playing music as you go! Plays spun note on button press. By equipping this Locomotion Item, your avatar's run speed will be faster. LMO (Locomotion) is a Portable Item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die coolste aller Toiletten-Kühe lässt sich reiten und spielt unterwegs Musik ab! Spielt auf Tastendruck Spun-Note. Wenn Sie sich mit einem Bewegungsobjekt ausrüsten, wird die Laufgeschwindigkeit Ihres Avatars schneller. Bewegungsobjekte sind tragbare Gegenstände. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ride around PlayStation®Home on this cutest of toilet cows, playing music as you go! Plays spun note on button press. By equipping this Locomotion Item, your avatar's run speed will be faster. LMO (Locomotion) is a Portable Item. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pasea por todo PlayStation®Home a lomo de la más bonita de las vacas de baño, ¡llevando música a todas partes! Toca una nota Spun al pulsar un botón. Al equipar este objeto de locomoción, la velocidad de carrera de tu avatar aumentará. LMO (locomoción) es un objeto portátil. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Déambulez à travers PlayStation®Home sur la plus adorable des vaches-toilettes, en diffusant de la musique sur votre passage ! Jouez des notes Spun en appuyant sur une simple touche. La vitesse de déplacement de votre avatar sera bien plus importante si vous équipez cet objet de locomotion. LMO (Locomotion) è un oggetto portatile. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Esplora stile le vie di PlayStation®Home a bordo del coniglio musicale saltellante Spunland e ascolta la musica mentre salti! Suona le note Spun alla semplice pressione di un pulsante. Equipaggiando questo accessorio di movimento, la velocità di corsa del tuo avatar aumenterà. LMO (Locomotion) è un oggetto portatile. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>