<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Mermaid 73 Top - White (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Haut Mermaid 73- Blanc (femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Mermaid 73 Oberteil - Weiß (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Mermaid 73 Maglia - Bianco (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Mermaid 73 Camiseta - Blanco (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our Sisters Of The Sun collection is a celebration of fashions that play up your natural beauty with their boho-chic vibe and warrior spirit. Alive with earthy colours and energy, each style easily transitions from days of soaking up the sun to nights spent dancing in the moonlight. This relaxed fit football tee features a scoop neckline and a scallop hem. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Notre collection Sisters Of The Sun célèbre les articles de mode qui restituent notre beauté naturelle grâce à leur atmosphère chic-bohème et leur esprit guerrier. Vivants grâce à leurs couleurs terreuses et énergiques, chaque style passe facilement des journées à lézarder au soleil aux nuits passées à danser au clair de lune. Ce T-shirt de football à coupe détente comporte une encolure arrondie et un ourlet ondulé. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unsere Sisters Of The Sun Kollektion akzentuiert Ihre natürliche Schönheit mit modischen Kreationen und einer Verschmelzung von Folklore-Chic und Kampfgeist. Der Stil in lebhaften Naturtönen und durchwachsen mit der Energie der Erde passt sich nahtlos an alle Anforderungen des Tages an - vom Sonnenbaden am Strand bis hin zum Tanzen im Mondschein. Dieses bequeme Fußballhemd weist einen tiefen U-Ausschnitt und einen attraktiven Rollsaum auf. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La nostra collezione Sisters Of The Sun celebra la moda che mette in risalto la bellezza naturale grazie a uno stile boho-chic unito allo spirito guerriero. Pieno di energia e caratterizzato dai colori della natura, ogni stile passa elegantemente dalle giornate passate a prendere il sole alle notti trascorse a ballare sotto le stelle.  Questa comoda t-shirt da football presenta ampia scollatura e orlo stondato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nuestra colección Sisters Of The Sun es una exaltación de esa tendencia que realza tu belleza natural, con su toque bohemio-chic y su espíritu guerrero. De gran viveza gracias a sus colores terrosos y su energía, cada estilo se adapta con sencillez para pasar de un día de bronceado al sol a una noche bailando a la luz de la luna. Esta camiseta de fútbol americano de talle flojo presenta un amplio escote y el bajo en curva. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Our Sisters Of The Sun collection is a celebration of fashions that play up your natural beauty with their boho-chic vibe and warrior spirit. Alive with earthy colors and energy, each style easily transitions from days of soaking up the sun to nights spent dancing in the moonlight. This relaxed fit football tee features a scoop neckline and a scallop hem. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>