<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Defender's Pack [Male]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Défenseur paquet [Homme]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Defender-Paket [männlich]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Difensore pacchetto [maschio]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Defensor del paquete [Mujer]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ディフェンダーパッケージ[男性]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">수비수 패키지 [남성]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Defender's Pack [Male]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">后卫包[男]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">后卫包[男]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Defender's Pack [Male]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Defend your Keep with a plethora of weapons! Includes Blunt Axe, Chained Mace, Short Mace, Warrior's Sword, Thief's Dagger, Knight's Lance, and Basic Shield.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Défendez votre donjon avec une pléthore d'armes! Comprend Contondant hache, Enchaîné macis
Court macis, Guerrier épée, Voleur poignard, Chevalier lance, et Bouclier de base.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Verteidigen Sie Ihre Kerker mit einer Vielzahl von Waffen! Beinhaltet Stumpfen Axt, Angekettet Muskatblüte, Kurze Muskatblüte, Krieger Schwert, Dieb Dolch, Ritter startet, und Schild Basis.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Difendi la tua prigione con una pletora di armi! Include Smussato ax, Incatenato macis, Corta macis, La spada del guerriero, Ladro pugnale, Cavaliere lancia, e Shield di base.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Defiende tu mazmorra con una gran cantidad de armas! Incluye Embotado hacha, Encadenado maza, Corto maza, Guerrero con espada, Rogue daga, Caballero lanza, y Escudo de la base.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">武器の過剰を使用してくださいを守れ！ブラントアックス、揺らすメイス、ショートメイス、戦士の剣、盗賊の短剣、ナイトのランス、および基本的なシールドが含まれています。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">무기의 과다로 유지를 지켜라! 무딘 도끼, 섹시한 메이스, 숏 메이스, 전사의 검, 도적의 단검, 나이트의 랜스, 기본 쉴드가 포함되어 있습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Defend your Keep with a plethora of weapons! Includes Blunt Axe, Chained Mace, Short Mace, Warrior's Sword, Thief's Dagger, Knight's Lance, and Basic Shield.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">过多的武器捍卫你保持！包括钝斧，摇摆锤，锤短，战士的剑，匕首贼的，骑士的长矛，和基本的盾。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">过多的武器捍卫你保持！包括钝斧，摇摆锤，锤短，战士的剑，匕首贼的，骑士的长矛，和基本的盾。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Defend your Keep with a plethora of weapons! Includes Blunt Axe, Chained Mace, Short Mace, Warrior's Sword, Thief's Dagger, Knight's Lance, and Basic Shield.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>