<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Storm of the North -  Barbarian Chief - Bundle (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tempête du nord - Chef barbare - Lot (homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Storm of the North -  Barbarenhäuptling - Paket (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tempesta del Nord - Capo dei Barbari - Set (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tormenta del Norte - Jefe Bárbaro - Pack (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Lead the barbarian tribe with this Barbarian Chief Bundle.\n
\n
This bundle contains:\n 
(1) Storm of the North - Barbarian Chief - Autumn Pelt Tunic (Men)\n
(2) Storm of the North - Barbarian Chief - Leggings (Men)\n
(3) Storm of the North - Barbarian Chief - Headpiece (Men)\n
(4) Storm of the North - Barbarian Chief - Sickle (Men) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Commandez la tribu de barbares avec ce lot Chef barbare.\n
\n
Ce lot contient :\n
(1) Tempête du nord - Chef barbare - Tunique de peau d'automne (Homme)\n
(2) Tempête du nord - Chef barbare - Legging (Homme)\n
(3) Tempête du nord - Chef barbare - Casque (Homme)\n
(4) Tempête du nord - Chef barbare - Faucille (Homme) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Führen Sie Ihren Barbarenstamm an - mit diesem Paket für Barbarenhäuptlinge.\n
\n
Dieses Bündel enthält:\n
(1) Storm of the North - Barbarenhäuptling - Pelztunika für den kühlen Herbst (Herren)\n
(2) Storm of the North - Barbarenhäuptling - Leggings (Herren)\n
(3) Storm of the North - Barbarenhäuptling - Kopfschmuck (Herren)\n
(4) Storm of the North - Barbarenhäuptling - Sichel (Herren) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guida la tribù di barbari con questo Set Capo dei Barbari.\n
\n
Il set comprende:\n
() Tempesta del Nord - Capo dei Barbari - Casacca di pelle di animale autunnale (Uomo)\n
() Tempesta del Nord - Capo dei Barbari - Pantaloni (Uomo)\n
() Tempesta del Nord - Capo dei Barbari - Copricapo(Uomo)\n
() Tempesta del Nord - Capo dei Barbari - Falce (Uomo)\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guía a la tribu bárbara con este Pack de Jefe Bárbaro.\n
\n
Este pack contiene:\n
(1) Tormenta del Norte - Jefe Bárbaro - Túnica otoñal de piel (Hombre)\n
(2) Tormenta del Norte - Jefe Bárbaro - Mallas (Hombre)\n
(3) Tormenta del Norte - Jefe Bárbaro - Tocado (Hombre)\n
(4) Tormenta del Norte - Jefe Bárbaro - Hoz (Hombre) [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>