<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">DUST 514™: Gallente Scout Dropsuit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">DUST 514™ : Combinaison d'éclaireur Gallente</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">DUST 514™: Kampfanzug für Gallente-Späher</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">DUST 514™: Armatura ricognitore Gallente</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">DUST 514™: traje de salto de explorador Gallente</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not localised</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not localised</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not localised</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not localised</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not localised</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">DUST 514™: Gallente Scout Dropsuit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gallente military doctrine places a premium on human life, favoring technological solutions that augment or even entirely replace human combatants in a conflict as part of an on-going effort to minimize loss of life on the battlefield. To this end, Gallente forces have access to some of the most advanced armor systems in the cluster. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La doctrine militaire de Gallente accorde une grande importance à la vie humaine, en favorisant les solutions technologiques qui augmentent ou même remplacent entièrement les combattants humains dans les conflits, afin de continuer à minimiser les pertes de vie sur le champ de bataille. À ce titre, les forces de Gallente disposent de certains des systèmes d'armures les plus avancés dans la galaxie. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Laut den Grundsätzen des Gallente-Militärs ist das Menschenleben das höchste Gut. Daher bevorzugen die Gallente nach Technologien, die menschliche Soldaten augmentieren oder gänzlich ersetzen, um weiterhin den Verlust von Menschenleben in der Schlacht zu minimieren. Zu diesem Zweck haben Gallente-Streitkräfte Zugang zu einigen der fortschrittlichsten Panzerungssystem im Cluster. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La dottrina militare di Gallente attribuisce particolare importanza alla vita umana, offrendo soluzioni tecnologiche che  sostituiscono in tutto o in parte i soldati umani durante un conflitto, nel continuo sforzo di ridurre al minimo le perdite di vite sui campi di battaglia. A questo scopo, le forze di Gallente hanno accesso ad alcune delle armature tecnologicamente più avanzate. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La doctrina militar de Gallente da prioridad a la vida humana, favoreciendo los productos tecnológicos capaces de aumentar o incluso remplazar a combatientes humano en un conflicto y así reducir las muertes en batalla. Por ello, los ejércitos de Gallente tienen acceso a los más avanzados sistemas de blindaje de todos los grupos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not localised [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not localised [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not localised [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not localised [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not localised [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gallente military doctrine places a premium on human life, favoring technological solutions that augment or even entirely replace human combatants in a conflict as part of an on-going effort to minimize loss of life on the battlefield. To this end, Gallente forces have access to some of the most advanced armor systems in the cluster. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>