<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Island Warrior Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ensemble Guerrier des îles</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Island Warrior-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Guerriero dell'isola</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conjunto Guerrero de la isla</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Island Warrior Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_11</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Island Warrior Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Embrace tribal values of appreciating the masculine and feminine inherent in everyone with this complete Island Warrior Tattoo bundle for both males and females. This bundle includes: Obsidian Island Warrior Forearm and Calf Tattoos [M], Obsidian Island Warrior Tattoo [M], Ivory Island Warrior Forearm and Calf Tattoos [M], Ivory Island Warrior Tattoo [M], Obsidian Island Warrior Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F], Obsidian Island Warrior Lower Back Tattoos [F], Ivory Island Warrior Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F], and Ivory Island Warrior Lower Back Tattoos [F].

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Adoptez les valeurs tribales appréciant la facette masculine et féminine en chacun de nous avec cet ensemble de tatouages complet Guerrier des îles. Cet ensemble comprend: Tatouages Guerrier des îles Obsidienne pour avant-bras et mollet [homme], Tatouage Guerrier des îles Obsidienne [homme], Tatouages Guerrier des îles Ivoire pour avant-bras et mollet [homme], Tatouage Guerrier des îles Ivoire [homme], Tatouages Guerrier des îles Obsidienne pour avant-bras et mollet [femme], Tatouages Guerrier des îles Obsidienne bas du dos et mollet [femme], Tatouages Guerrier des îles Ivoire pour avant-bras et mollet [femme], et Tatouages Guerrier des îles Ivoire bas du dos et mollet [femme].

Remarque : Tous les tatouages pour torse ou jambe ne sont pas égaux. Lors de l’achat de cet accessoire de tatouage, il est possible qu’il ne soit pas adapté à tous les habits. N’hésitez pas à prendre notre article gratuit « Torse nu » pour homme ou femme afin d’afficher correctement votre nouveau tatouage ![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bekenne dich mit diesem kompletten Island Warrior-Tattoo-Paket zu den Stammeswerten, die die in jedem von uns enthaltene maskuline und feminine Seite würdigen. Dieses Paket ist für männliche oder weibliche Avatare und beinhaltet: Obsidian Island Warrior-Tattoos für Unterarm und Wade [Männlich], Obsidian Island Warrior-Tattoo [Männlich], Ivory Island Warrior-Tattoos für Unterarm und Wade [Männlich], Ivory Island Warrior-Tattoo [Männlich], Obsidian Island Warrior-Tattoos für Unterarm und Wade [Weiblich], Obsidian Island Warrior-Tattoos für den unteren Rücken und Wade [Weiblich], Ivory Island Warrior-Tattoos für Unterarm und Wade [Weiblich], und Ivory Island Warrior-Tattoos für den unteren Rücken und Wade [Weiblich].

Hinweis: Nicht alle Gegenstände für Oberkörper oder Beine sind gleich gestaltet. Wenn du dieses Tattoo-Zubehör kaufst, könnte es nicht mit allen Kleidungsstücken harmonieren. Gerne kannst du dir unseren kostenlosen “blanken” Oberkörper für Männer/Frauen holen, um deine neuen Tattoos angemessen zeigen zu können![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Grazie a questo pacchetto di tatuaggi unisex Guerriero dell'isola potrai abbracciare i valori tribali di rispetto nei confronti della parte maschile e di quella femminile propria di ogni individuo. Esso include: Tatuaggi Guerriero dell'isola nero ossidiana per avambraccio e polpaccio [maschili], Tatuaggio Guerriero dell'isola nero ossidiana avorio [maschili], Tatuaggi Guerriero dell'isola bianco per avambraccio e polpaccio [maschili], Tatuaggio Guerriero dell'isola bianco avorio [maschili], Tatuaggi Guerriero dell'isola nero ossidiana per avambraccio e polpaccio [femminili], Tatuaggi Guerriero dell'isola nero ossidiana per la parte inferiore della schiena e polpaccio [femminili], Tatuaggi Guerriero dell'isola bianco per avambraccio e polpaccio [femminili], e Tatuaggi Guerriero dell'isola bianco per la parte inferiore della schiena e polpaccio [femminili].

Nota: non tutti gli oggetti per torso o gamba sono creati allo stesso modo. Il tatuaggio che ti appresti ad acquistare potrebbe non andare bene su tutti gli articoli di abbigliamento. A questo scopo non esitare a scaricare gratuitamente l'oggetto unisex "Tela nuda" torso per visualizzare correttamente i tuoi nuovi tatuaggi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Defiende los valores tribales y valora el lado masculino y femenino que todos llevamos dentro con este conjunto de tatuajes completo Guerrero de la isla para hombre y mujer. El conjunto incluye: Tatuajes Guerrero de la isla obsidiana antebrazo y pantorrilla [hombre], Tatuaje Guerrero de la isla obsidiana [hombre], Tatuajes Guerrero de la isla marfil antebrazo y pantorrilla [hombre], Tatuaje Guerrero de la isla marfil [hombre], Tatuajes Guerrero de la isla obsidiana antebrazo y pantorrilla [mujer], Tatuajes Guerrero de la isla obsidiana parte baja de la espalda y pantorrilla [mujer], Tatuajes Guerrero de la isla marfil antebrazo y pantorrilla [mujer], y Tatuajes Guerrero de la isla marfil parte baja de la espalda y pantorrilla [mujer].

Nota: no todos los objetos para torso y piernas se crean por igual. Cuando compres este accesorio para un tatuaje, quizá no quede bien con cualquier prenda de ropa. ¡Elige nuestro "Lienzo en blanco" de regalo para hombre o mujer y así podrás lucir tu nuevo tatuaje como se merece![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_11 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Home_Object_11 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Embrace tribal values of appreciating the masculine and feminine inherent in everyone with this complete Island Warrior Tattoo bundle for both males and females. This bundle includes: Obsidian Island Warrior Forearm and Calf Tattoos [M], Obsidian Island Warrior Tattoo [M], Ivory Island Warrior Forearm and Calf Tattoos [M], Ivory Island Warrior Tattoo [M], Obsidian Island Warrior Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F], Obsidian Island Warrior Lower Back Tattoos [F], Ivory Island Warrior Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F], and Ivory Island Warrior Lower Back Tattoos [F].

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Home_Object_11 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Home_Object_11 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Embrace tribal values of appreciating the masculine and feminine inherent in everyone with this complete Island Warrior Tattoo bundle for both males and females. This bundle includes: Obsidian Island Warrior Forearm and Calf Tattoos [M], Obsidian Island Warrior Tattoo [M], Ivory Island Warrior Forearm and Calf Tattoos [M], Ivory Island Warrior Tattoo [M], Obsidian Island Warrior Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F], Obsidian Island Warrior Lower Back Tattoos [F], Ivory Island Warrior Forearm and Calf Tattoos [F], and Ivory Island Warrior Lower Back Tattoos [F].

Note: Not all Torso or Leg items are created equal. When purchasing this Tattoo accessory item it may not work well on all clothing items. Please feel free to pick up our complimentary “Bare Canvas” torso item for male/female to properly display your new ink![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>