<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Female01_Legs_yukata_02</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Yukata Bottom (Sky Blue Chrysanthemums, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bas de Yukata (Chrysanthèmes bleu ciel, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Yukata-Unterteil (Himmelblaue Chrysantheme, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Yukata parte inferiore (crisantemi azzurro cielo, da donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Parte inferior de Yukata (crisantemo azul cielo, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">浴衣・下（菊日和・女性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">유카타 하의 (하늘색 국화, 여성）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Yukata – Bottom (Chrysanthemum Harmony/Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">日式浴衣 下(菊日和/女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">日式浴衣 下(菊日和/女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Yukata Bottom (Sky Blue Chrysanthemums, F)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Female01_Legs_yukata_02_description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A single-layer white cotton kimono designed with a sky blue chrysanthemum motif. This is only the bottom half, below the obi belt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Un kimono blanc composé d'une seule couche de coton, décoré avec un motif de chrysanthèmes bleu ciel. C'est seulement le bas, au-dessous de la ceinture obi. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ein einfacher, weißer Kimono aus Baumwolle mit dem Motiv einer blauen Chrysantheme. Dies ist nur die untere Hälfte, die sich unterhalb des Obigürtels befindet.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Un kimono leggero decorato con motivi a crisantemo azzurro cielo su sfondo di cotone bianco. Questa è solo la parte inferiore, dalla cintola (obi) in giù.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Un kimono de algodón blanco de una sola capa diseñado con un motivo de crisantemo azul cielo. Esta es solo la mitad inferior, por debajo del cinturón obi.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">白い木綿地に、空色の菊が描かれている、ひとえの着物。帯から下の半身。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">흰 목면지에 하늘색 국화가 그려진 홑겹 옷. 하의. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">A single-layer, white cotton kimono, with skyblue chrysanthemums; the section below the belt.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">白色棉織布上畫著天空藍菊花的單層和服。腰帶以下的下半身衣物。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">白色棉織布上畫著天空藍菊花的單層和服。腰帶以下的下半身衣物。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A single-layer white cotton kimono designed with a sky blue chrysanthemum motif. This is only the bottom half, below the obi belt.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>