<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Junkmobile Sofa with Radio (yellow)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le canapé Junkmobile avec Radio (jaune)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Junkmobile Sofa mit Radio (gelb).</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Sofà Junkmobile dotato di Radio (giallo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El Sofá Junkmobile con Radio (amarillo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Junkmobile Sofa with Radio (yellow)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">
        Junkmobile Sofa with Radio (yellow). Modeled after the car version, this item can be placed in any of your private spaces for all of your friends to enjoy (non-Locomotion). Sit on the hood, behind the wheel or just play the radio. \n

        *Active Item  - The Junkmobile Sofa with Radio is not a Locomotion.
        [#Legal]
       [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">
        (Elément Interactif) Le canapé Junkmobile avec Radio (jaune). A l’image de la version voiture, il peut être placé à l’endroit que vous souhaitez pour que tous vos amis puissent l’apprécier (non- Locomotion). Asseyez-vous sur le capot, devant le volant ou écoutez seulement la radio.\n

        *Elément Interactif - Le Canapé Junkmobile avec radio (non Locomotion).
        [#Legal]
       [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">
        (Aktiver Artikel) Das Junkmobile Sofa mit Radio (gelb). Nach der Wagen-Version modelliert, es kann für die Vergnügung ihrer Freunde in jedem privaten Raum gestellt werden (keine-Locomotion). Sitze auf der Motorhaube, hinter dem Lenkrad oder ganz einfach Radio hören.\n

        * Activer Artikel  - Das weiche Junkmobile Sofa mit Radio (keine Locomotion).
        [#Legal]
       [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">
        (Articolo attivo) Il Sofà Junkmobile dotato di Radio (giallo). Modellato come la versione della macchina, può essere collocato in qualsiasi punto dei luoghi casalinghi per il divertimento dei tuoi amici (non-Locomotion). Siediti sulla capote, dietro al volante oppure ascolta semplicemente la radio. \n

        *Articolo Attivo  - Il Sofà Junkmobile morbido con la Radio (non un Locomotion).
        [#Legal]
       [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">
        (Artículo Interactivo) El Sofá Junkmobile con Radio (amarillo). Inspirado en el modelo del coche, puede ser colocado en cualquiera de tus espacios privados para disfrute de todos tus amigos (no conducible). Siéntate en el capó, detrás del volante o simplemente escucha la radio. \n

        *Artículo Interactivo  - El Sofá Junkmobile con Radio (no conducible).
        [#Legal]
       [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">
        Junkmobile Sofa with Radio (yellow). Modeled after the car version, this item can be placed in any of your private spaces for all of your friends to enjoy (non-Locomotion). Sit on the hood, behind the wheel or just play the radio. \n

        *Active Item  - The Junkmobile Sofa with Radio is not a Locomotion.
        [#Legal]
       [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">SetTargetableText</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">S'asseoir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sitzen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Siedi</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sentarse</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">prompt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Press [SQUARE] to toggle radio on/off</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Appuyez sur [SQUARE] pour basculer la radio on / off</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Drücken Sie [SQUARE], um Radio an / aus schalten</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Premere [SQUARE] per attivare la radio on / off</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pulse [SQUARE] para cambiar la radio on / off</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Press [SQUARE] to toggle radio on/off</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>