<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Long-term Memory Conditioning with Conduit Pilot Gloves (bundle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Conditionnement de mémoire à long terme avec Gants de Pilote (version bundle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Langzeitgedächnis-Konditionierung mit Verbindungshandschuhen für Piloten (Paket)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Lavaggio del cervello ad effetto prolungato e Guanti da pilota in guaina (pacchetto)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Acondicionador de memoria a largo plazo con Guantes de Piloto Conducto (paquete)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">長期記憶調整つきコンジットパイロットグローブセット</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">콘듀잇 조종사용 글러브와 장기간 메모리 콘디셔닝(번들)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Long-term Memory Conditioning with Conduit Pilot Gloves (bundle)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">長期記憶管理和領航飛行員手套組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">長期記憶管理和領航飛行員手套組合包</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Long-term Memory Conditioning with Conduit Pilot Gloves (bundle)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This advanced mental conditioning process permanently enhances long-term memory retention.  As a result, all experience point gains in Novus Prime are increased to 300%.  The Mental Conditioning Chamber furniture item is included, along with both the male and female versions of the Conduit Pilot Gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce processus de pointe de conditionnement mental améliore la rétention de la mémoire permanente à long terme. En conséquence, tous les gains de points d'expérience dans le Novus Prime sont augmentés de 300%. La chambre de conditionnement mental est incluse, avec les deux versions homme et femme des Gants de pilotes. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser fortgeschrittene, mentale Konditionierungsprozess erhöht dauerhaft das Langzeitgedächnis. Im Ergebnis werden alle erhaltenen Erfahrungspunkte auf Novus Prime um 300% erhöht. Dazu gehört als Ausrüstungsgegenstand die mentale Konditionierungskammer, zusammen mit der männlichen und weiblichen Version der Verbindungshandschuhe für Piloten. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo processo di condizionamento mentale agisce sulla memoria a lungo termine con efficacia. Pertanto, i punti esperienza accumulati dalla Novus Prime aumentino del 300%. La Stanza per il lavaggio del cervello è inclusa nel set, insieme ai Guanti da pilota in guaina sia per uomo che per donna. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este proceso avanzado de acondicionamiento mental mejora permanentemente la retención de memoria a largo plazo. Como resultado, todos los puntos de experiencia ganados en Novus Prime son incrementados en 300%. El mueble Cámara de acondicionamiento mental está incluido, así como las versiones hombre y mujer de los Guantes de Piloto Conducto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">この最新のメンタル調整処理は、長期記憶の保存を恒久的に高め続ける。結果、ノーバス・プライムで手に入れた全ての経験値は300％になる。\n\n
本セットには、以下のアイテムが含まれています。\n
・「コンジットパイロットグローブ（男性用）」（手）\n
・「コンジットパイロットグローブ（女性用）」（手）\n
・ノーバス・プライム メンタル調整ベッド（テーブル）\n
※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。\n
※購入すると、ミニゲーム「ノーバス・プライム」内で経験値が3倍になります。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이 최첨단 멘털 콘디셔닝 프로세스는 영구적으로 장기 메모리 보존 능력을 향상시킵니다. 결과적으로 노부스 프라임에서 획득하는 모든 경험치가 300%로 늘어납니다.\n
이 번들은 다음을 포함합니다.\n
●노부스 프라임 멘털 콘디셔닝실\n
●콘듀잇 조종사용 글러브 (남성)\n
●콘듀잇 조종사용 글러브 (여성)\n
[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This advanced mental conditioning process permanently enhances long-term memory retention. As a result, all experience point gains in Novus Prime are increased to 300%.\nThis bundle includes the following:\n• Novus Prime Mental Conditioning Chamber\n• Conduit Pilot Gloves (Men)\n• Conduit Pilot Gloves (Women)[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">經過此精神管理程式，長期的記憶管理將不斷增加。所有在Novus Prime所得到的經驗值會增加300%。\n本組合包包含以下商品：\n●Novus Prime心理調節室\n●領航飛行員手套(男用)\n●領航飛行員手套（女用）[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">經過此精神管理程式，長期的記憶管理將不斷增加。所有在Novus Prime所得到的經驗值會增加300%。\n本組合包包含以下商品：\n●Novus Prime心理調節室\n●領航飛行員手套(男用)\n●領航飛行員手套（女用）[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This advanced mental conditioning process permanently enhances long-term memory retention.  As a result, all experience point gains in Novus Prime are increased to 300%.  The Mental Conditioning Chamber furniture item is included, along with both the male and female versions of the Conduit Pilot Gloves. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>