<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Alak Mak Gragor's Bow (Legendary Weapon)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Arc d'Alak Mak Gragor (arme légendaire)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Alak Mak Gragors Bogen (Legendäre Waffe)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Arco di Alak Mak Gragor (Arma leggendaria)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Arco de Alak Mak Gragor (Arma legendaria)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Alak Mak Gragor's Bow (Legendary Weapon)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Legendary Bow which Alak Mak Gragor used to fight those who would despoil Mercia, allying himself and his people with the Mercian forces. \n\nDuring the battle the Guardian of the Conquering Bezerkers shot an arrow into the sky and wounded the sun. Darkness fell in day and the cowardly marauders fled in fear never to return.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'arc légendaire avec lequel Alak Mak Gragor combattait ceux qui voulait piller Mercia, en s'alliant avec les forces mercianes. \n\nAu cours d'une bataille, le gardien des Bezerkers conquérants a tiré une flèche dans le ciel et blessé le soleil. L'obscurité s'est abattue en plein jour et les maraudeurs terrifiés se sont enfuis pour ne jamais revenir.\n\nDÉBLOQUE DES ARTICLES DU JEU MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS – N'OFFRE PAS DE COMPOSANTS D'AVATAR POUR UN USAGE GÉNÉRAL SUR PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBLE POUR LES UTILISATEURS DU JAPON ET DE L'ASIE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der legendäre Bogen mit dem Mak Gragor, zusammen mit seinem Volk im Bündnis mit den Streitkräften Mercias, gegen diejenigen kämpfte, die Mercia zu plündern suchten. \n\nWährend der Schlacht schoss der Wächter der erobernden Berserker einen Pfeil gen Himmel und verletzte die Sonne. So wurde der Tag zur Nacht und die feigen Plünderer suchten angsterfüllt das Weite und kehrten nie wieder zurück.\n\nZUM FREISCHALTEN VON GEGENSTÄNDEN IN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS - NICHT ZUM ERHALT VON AVATAR-KOMPONENTEN ZUR ALLGEMEINEN NUTZUNG AUF PLAYSTATION®HOME. NICHT VERFÜGBAR FÜR BENUTZER IN JAPAN UND ASIEN [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'arco leggendario che Alak Mak Gragor usò per affrontare chi voleva sfruttare Mercia alleandosi insieme alla sua gente con le forze Mercian. \n\nDurante la battaglia il guardiano dei Bezerker conquistatori scoccò una freccia verso il cielo ferendo il sole. L'oscurità piombò sul giorno e i predatori codardi scapparono terrorizzati senza mai più fare ritorno.\n\nSBLOCCA OGGETTI ALL'INTERNO DEL GIOCO MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS. NON REGALA COMPONENTI PER AVATAR PER USO GENERICO CON PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBILE PER GLI UTENTI IN ASIA E GIAPPONE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El legendario arco que utilizó Alak Mak Gragor para luchar contra aquellos que querían arrasar Mercia, aliándose junto a su pueblo con las fuerzas de Mercia. \n\nDurante la batalla, el Guardián de los Bezerkers conquistadores disparó una flecha al aire e hirió al sol. La oscuridad cayó sobre el día y los maleantes cobardes huyeron aterrorizados para no volver jamás.\n\nDESBLOQUEARÁ ELEMENTOS EN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS GAME. NO REGALARÁ COMPONENTES DE AVATAR PARA EL USO GENERAL EN CASA DE PLAYSTATION. NO DISPONIBLE PARA LOS USUARIOS DE JAPÓN Y ASIA. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Legendary Bow which Alak Mak Gragor used to fight those who would despoil Mercia, allying himself and his people with the Mercian forces. \n\nDuring the battle the Guardian of the Conquering Bezerkers shot an arrow into the sky and wounded the sun. Darkness fell in day and the cowardly marauders fled in fear never to return.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>