<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Space Table Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Lot de Tables de l'Espace</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Space-Tisch-Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Tavoli spaziali</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lote "mesa espacial"</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Space Table Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Space Table Bundle is a must-have for any Space Apartment. This rainbow collection gives you the space table and side table in 6 colours each: Red, blue, green, white, pink and orange! Twelve items for one awesome low price. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le Lot de Tables de l'Espace est un must pour tout Appartement Spatial. Cette collection arc-en-ciel vous permet d'avoir la Table de l'espace et la Petite Table dans les six couleurs (pour chaque table) : rouge, bleu, vert, blanc, rose et orange ! Douze articles à un seul incroyable et tout petit prix. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Space-Tisch-Bundle ist ein Muss für jedes Space-Apartment. Mit dieser Regenbogen-Kollektion erhältst du Space-Tisch und den Beistelltisch in jeweils sechs Farben: Rot, Blau, Grün, Weiß, Rosa und Orange! Zwölf Tische zu einem unschlagbar günstigen Preis. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il pacchetto Tavoli spaziali non può mancare in uno Space Apartment. Questa collezione variopinta ti mette a disposizione il tavolo e il tavolino in 6 colori: rosso, blu, verde, bianco, rosa e arancione! Dodici pezzi a prezzo stracciato. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El lote "mesa espacial" es un elemento que no puede faltar en ningún apartamento espacial. Esta colorida colección te ofrece la mesa espacial y la mesa auxiliar en seis colores: rojo, azul, verde, blanco, rosa y naranja. ¡Doce artículos a un precio increíblemente bajo! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Space Table Bundle is a must-have for any Space Apartment. This rainbow collection gives you the space table and side table in 6 colors each: Red, blue, green, white, pink and orange! Twelve items for one awesome low price. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>