<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LocoRoco T-shirt (Chavez/women's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">T-shirt LocoRoco (Chavez / pour femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LocoRoco-T-Shirt (Chavez/Frau)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">T-shirt LocoRoco (Chavez) da donna</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta LocoRoco (Chavez/mujer)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ロコロコTシャツ（チャベス・女性用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">로코로코 T셔츠(챠베스/여성용)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">LocoRoco T-shirt (Chavez/women's)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">樂克樂克T恤（茶貝斯/女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">樂克樂克T恤（茶貝斯/女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LocoRoco T-shirt (Chavez/women's)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Ordinary T-shirt design on front, cute LocoRoco face on back.\nSpread the LocoRoco love as you walk past!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Design de t-shirt ordinaire devant, adorable visage de LocoRoco au dos.
Diffusez votre amour pour les LocoRoco où que vous alliez !\n\nAcheter cet objet ajoute 1 LocoRoco à ton espace personnel de l'île Loco.
Tu peux ajouter jusqu'à 20 LocoRoco à l'île Loco. Une fois le maximum atteint, tu ne peux plus ajouter d'unités.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Gewöhnliches T-Shirt-Design vorne und niedliches LocoRoco-Gesicht am Rücken.
Verbreite die Liebe für LocoRoco im Vorbeigehen!\n\nDieser Gegenstand fügt deinem Loco-Insel-Apartment 1 LocoRoco hinzu.
Du kannst bis zu 20 LocoRoco hinzufügen. Ist das Maximum erreicht, können keine weiteren Einheiten hinzugefügt werden.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Una semplice stampa davanti, l'adorabile faccino di un LocoRoco sulla schiena!
Diffondi il tuo amore per i LocoRoco mentre passeggi!\n\nAcquistando questo oggetto, aggiungerai un LocoRoco al tuo spazio personale su Loco Island.
Puoi aggiungere fino a 20 LocoRoco su Loco Island. Una volta raggiunto il numero massimo, non potrai aggiungerne altri.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una camiseta con un diseño normal en la parte delantera y la cara de un simpático LocoRoco en la espalda.
¡Difunde el amor LocoRoco allí por donde pases!\n\nComprar este objeto añade 1 LocoRoco a tu espacio personal en la Loco Isla.
Puedes añadir un máximo de 20 LocoRoco a la Loco Isla. Cuando hayas alcanzado este número, no podrás añadir más unidades.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">一見普通のＴシャツですが、背中にロコロコの顔がデザインされています。
あなたの後ろ姿をキュートに演出しちゃいます！\n\nこのアイテムを購入するとパーソナルスペース”ロコアイランド”に\n”ロコロコ”が１匹追加されます。”ロコアイランド”には最大20匹まで”ロコロコ”を追加できます。最大数に達した場合は、それ以上の追加はされません。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">겉보기에는 평범한 T셔츠지만, 등에 로코로코의 얼굴이 디지인 되어 있어요.
당신의 뒷모습을 큐트하게 연출해 줄 거에요!\n\n이 아이템을 구입하면 퍼스널 스페이스 '로코 아일랜드'에 '로코로코'가 1마리 추가됩니다.
'로코 아일랜드'에는 최대 20마리까지 '로코로코'를 추가할 수 있습니다. 
최대치에 다다르면 더 이상은 추가할 수 없습니다.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Ordinary T-shirt design on front, cute LocoRoco face on back.\nSpread the LocoRoco love as you walk past!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your Loco Island personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to Loco Island. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">乍看之下是普通的T恤，背面畫著樂克樂克的臉。可將你的背影妝點得十分可愛喔！\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">乍看之下是普通的T恤，背面畫著樂克樂克的臉。可將你的背影妝點得十分可愛喔！\n\n購買本商品，便會在「樂克島嶼」個人空間追加一隻”樂克樂克”。「樂克島嶼」上最多可追加20隻”樂克樂克”。若達到最大數，便不會再被追加。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Ordinary T-shirt design on front, cute LocoRoco face on back.
Spread the LocoRoco love as you walk past!\n\nPurchasing this item adds 1 LocoRoco to your LocoIsland personal space.
Up to 20 LocoRoco can be added to LocoIsland. Once the maximum is reached, no further units can be added.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>