<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Game Space Beta Message [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Accueil espace Game [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Game Space Beta-Nachricht [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Messaggio Beta spaziale di GAME [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Mensaje de la beta espacial de GAME [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Game Space Beta Message [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Intro_Title</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to the GAME Moonbase</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue dans la Base lunaire GAME !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen zum GAME Mondbasis</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ti diamo il benvenuto nello Base lunare di GAME</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bienvenido/a a la base lunar de GAME.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome to the GAME Moonbase</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Intro_Body_1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Check out the GAME V virtual goods store selling game-based items and apparel exclusively for Home users and the Moonbase Shop - a PlayStation Home first offering direct sale of PS3 titles from The Moonbase delivered straight to your (real) door courtesy of GAME.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La Base lunaire a été mise à jour, alors pourquoi ne pas essayer notre jeu Duel lunaire pour deux joueurs au niveau supérieur ? Encore plus de jeux à venir !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Wir haben die Mondbasis auf den neuesten Stand gebracht. Unser neues 2-Spieler Spiel "Lunar Duel"findest du auf der oberen Etage. Weitere Spiele folgen bald.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Abbiamo aggiornato la Base lunare, perciò perché non provi il nostro nuovo gioco per due giocatori Duello lunare al piano superiore? Presto saranno disponibili altri giochi.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Hemos actualizado la Base lunar así que, ¿por qué no pruebas nuestro nuevo Duelo lunar de dos jugadores en el siguiente nivel? Más juegos próximamente.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">We have updated the Moonbase so why not try our new Lunar Duel two-player game on the upper level. More games coming soon.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Intro_Body_2</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Si ce n'est déjà fait, pourquoi ne pas essayer notre jeu Bond lunaire et poster vos scores dans le tableau des scores !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Hast du auch schon "Lunar Leap" gespielt? Falls nicht, versuch es doch einmal und trage deine Punktzahl in der Highscore-Tabelle ein.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se non lo hai ancora fatto, perché non provi il gioco Balzo lunare e pubblichi il tuo punteggio nella classifica?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Si todavía no lo has probado, ¿por qué no juegas a Salto lunar y publicas tus puntuaciones en la tabla de récords?</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">If you've not tried it out yet, why not play Lunar Leap and post your score on the highscore table.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Intro_Body_3</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">En vous rendant aux Pods GAME, vous pouvez acheter des jeux à l'aide de l'option d'achat express de GAME.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Über die GAME Stationen kannst du Spiele mit dem GAME Express-Checkout kaufen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Accedendo alle capsule di GAME, puoi acquistare giochi usando la nostra cassa veloce di GAME.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Desde las cápsulas de GAME, puedes comprar juegos utilizando nuestro pago exprés GAME.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">By accessing the GAME Pods you can purchase games using our GAME express checkout.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Intro_Body_4</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Amusez-vous bien !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Viel Spaß!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Divertiti!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡A divertirse!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Enjoy!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>