<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">LeChuck Pirate Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Baluchon du Pirate LeChuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">LeChuck Piraten-Komplettpaket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pacchetto Pirata LeChuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paquete Pirata de LeChuck</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">LeChuck Pirate Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The complete outfit of an evil ghost pirate. It's suits like this that make you glad to be dead. You are glad to be dead, RIGHT? Includes LeChuck's Coat, Pants, Boots, Hat, and Beard. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'attirail complet d'un méchant pirate fantôme. C'est ce genre de tenue qui vous rend content d'être mort. Vous êtes content d'être mort, N'EST-CE PAS ? Comprend le manteau, le pantalon, le chapeau et la barde du Pirate LeChuck. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das komplette Outfit für den bösen Geisterpiraten. Bei so einem Kostüm ist man froh, tot zu sein. Das ist doch dein Wunsch, RICHTIG? Beinhaltet LeChucks Umhang, Hose, Stiefel, Hut und Bart. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il completo di un malvagio pirata fantasma. Sono completi come questi che ti fanno sentire felice di essere morto. Sei contento di essere morto, VERO? Include Cappotto, Pantaloni, Stivali, Cappello e Barba di LeChuck. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El conjunto completo de un fantasma pirata malvado. Con trajes como este no da pena estar muerto. ¿Te alegras de estar muerto, VERDAD? Incluye el abrigo, los pantalones, las botas, el sombrero y la barba de LeChuck. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The complete outfit of an evil ghost pirate. It's suits like this that make you glad to be dead. You are glad to be dead, RIGHT? [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>