<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Superhero Madhouse - Arcade Cabinet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Superhero Madhouse — Console Arcade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Superhero Madhouse - Arcade-Automat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Superhero Madhouse - Videogioco arcade</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Superhero Madhouse - Máquina recreativa</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Superhero Madhouse - 아케이드 캐비닛</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Superhero Madhouse - Arcade Cabinet</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">超級英雄瘋人院 - 街機台</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">超級英雄瘋人院 - 街機台</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The SuperHero Madhouse arcade cabinet, complete with exclusive mad hero themed clothing for anyone who purchases the cabinet. To get the clothing, place the cabinet in your apartment and play the game. Any visitors to your personal space can play the full game, post high-scores, and gain trophies in the in-game trophy cabinet.  Can you escape from the madhouse...or just your mind?\n\n

After placing your cabinet and playing it for the first time you will receive the follow items:\n
\n
1. Superhero Madhouse - T-Shirt - Male\n
2. Superhero Madhouse - T-Shirt - Female
3. Superhero Madhouse - Fleece - Male\n
4. Superhero Madhouse - Fleece - Female\n
5. Superhero Madhouse - Hat - Male\n
6. Superhero Madhouse - Hat - Female [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La console arcade SuperHero Madhouse, complétée d'une tenue exclusive aux couleurs du héros fou pour quiconque achète la console. Pour obtenir la tenue, placez la console dans votre appartement et jouez au jeu. Tous les visiteurs de votre espace personnel peuvent profiter intégralement du jeu, réaliser des scores élevés, et gagner des trophées dans la console trophée intégrée au jeu. Pouvez-vous vous échapper de l'asile… ou bien juste votre esprit ?
\n\n

Après avoir installé votre console et joué la première partie, vous recevrez les articles suivants :
\n
\n
1. Superhero Madhouse - T-Shirt - Homme\n
2. Superhero Madhouse - T-Shirt - Femme\n
3. Superhero Madhouse - Polaire - Homme\n
4. Superhero Madhouse - Polaire - Femme
\n
5. Superhero Madhouse - Chapeau - Homme\n
6. Superhero Madhouse - Chapeau - Femme [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Der Arcade-Automat SuperHero Madhouse, komplett mit exklusiver thematischer Mad Hero-Kleidung für alle, die den Automaten kaufen. Die Kleidung erhältst du, wenn du den Automaten in deiner Wohnung aufstellst und das Spiel spielst. Alle deine Besucher können das ganze Spiel spielen, Highscores anlegen und Trophäen in der spielinternen Trophäenvitrine ergattern. Entkommst du aus dem Irrenhaus…oder nur aus deinem Kopf?\n\n

Nach dem Aufstellen deines Automaten und dem ersten Spiel erhältst du die folgenden Artikel:
\n
\n
1. Superhero Madhouse - T-Shirt - Männlich
\n
2. Superhero Madhouse - T-Shirt - Weiblich\n
3. Superhero Madhouse - Fleecepullover - Männlich\n
4. Superhero Madhouse - Fleecepullover - Weiblich
\n
5. Superhero Madhouse - Hut - Männlich\n
6. Superhero Madhouse - Hut - Weiblich [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il videogioco arcade SuperHero Madhouse è accompagnato da abbigliamento esclusivo ispirato al tema "un eroe tra i pazzi", disponibile a quanti acquistano il videogioco. Per aggiudicarti i capi d'abbigliamento, sistema il videogioco nel tuo appartamento e comincia a giocare. Chi visita il tuo ambiente privato può giocare una partita per intero, salvare i punteggi più alti e vincere i trofei in vetrina. Sei in grado di scappare dal manicomio…o di preservare almeno la tua mente?
\n\n

Dopo aver sistemato il videogioco ed aver giocato la prima partita riceverai:
\n
\n
1. Superhero Madhouse - T-Shirt - Da Uomo\n
2. Superhero Madhouse - T-Shirt - Da Donna\n
3. Superhero Madhouse - Felpa - Da Uomo\n
4. Superhero Madhouse - Felpa - Da Donna
\n
5. Superhero Madhouse - Cappello - Da Uomo\n
6. Superhero Madhouse - Cappello - Da Donna [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La máquina recreativa The SuperHero Madhouse, íntegra y con ropa temática exclusiva de nuestro héroe loco para quien la compre. Para conseguir las prendas instala la máquina en tu apartamento y juega. Cualquier visitante en tu espacio personal puede jugar una partida entera, registrar sus puntuaciones y ganar trofeos de la vitrina de trofeos del juego. ¿Podrás escapar de este manicomio, o al menos salvar tu mente?\n\n

Tras emplazar la máquina y jugar por primera vez, recibirás los artículos siguientes:\n
\n
1. Superhero Madhouse - Camiseta - Hombre
\n
2. Superhero Madhouse - Camiseta - Mujer\n
3. Superhero Madhouse - Polar - Hombre\n
4. Superhero Madhouse - Polar - Mujer
\n
5. Superhero Madhouse - Gorro - Hombre\n
6. Superhero Madhouse - Gorro - Mujer [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">SuperHero Madhouse 아케이드 캐비닛은 구매하시는 모든 분들께 독점적인 미친 영웅 테마 의상을 제공합니다. 의상을 받으려면 캐비넷을 아파트에 배치하고 게임을 플레이하세요. 여러분의 퍼스널 스페이스에 방문하는 플레이어는 누구나 게임을 즐길 수 있으며, 고득점을 기록하거나, 게임 내 트로피 캐비닛에 트로피를 획득할 수 있습니다. 당신은 과연 정신병원에서 탈출할 수 있을까요… 아니면 오직 당신의 정신세계로부터?\n
\n
캐비닛을 설치하고 처음 플레이 후, 여러분은 다음 아이템을 받을 수 있습니다:\n
\n
1. Superhero Madhouse - 티셔츠 (남성)\n
2. Superhero Madhouse - 티셔츠 (여성)\n
3. Superhero Madhouse - 스웨터 (남성)\n
4. Superhero Madhouse - 스웨터 (여성)\n
5. Superhero Madhouse - 모자 (남성)\n
6. Superhero Madhouse - 모자 (여성) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The SuperHero Madhouse arcade cabinet, complete with exclusive mad hero themed clothing rewards for anyone who purchases the cabinet. To get the clothing, place the cabinet in your personal space and play the game. Any visitors to your personal space can play the full game, post high-scores, and gain trophies in the in-game trophy cabinet.  Can you escape from the madhouse...or just your mind?\n
\n
After placing your cabinet and playing it for the first time you will receive the follow items:\n
\n
1. Superhero Madhouse - T-Shirt (Men)\n
2. Superhero Madhouse - T-Shirt (Women)\n
3. Superhero Madhouse - Fleece (Men)\n
4. Superhero Madhouse - Fleece (Women)\n
5. Superhero Madhouse - Hat (Men)\n
6. Superhero Madhouse - Hat (Women) [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">超級英雄瘋人院 - 街機台，提供以下獨家瘋狂英雄主題服裝獎品道具給購買這街機台的玩家。要獲得這些服裝，請將本街機台設置在您的個人空間並進行遊玩。所有到您的個人空間的訪客也可以自由遊玩完整版遊戲、記錄得分、並在遊戲中獲得獎盃。你能逃出的是瘋人院，或者只是你的自我精神呢？\n
\n
在將本街機台設置在您的個人空間並進行第一次遊玩時，您便會獲得以下道具：\n
\n
1. 超級英雄瘋人院 - T恤（男用）\n
2. 超級英雄瘋人院 - T恤（女用）\n
3. 超級英雄瘋人院 - 長袖襯衣（男用）\n
4. 超級英雄瘋人院 - 長袖襯衣（女用）\n
5. 超級英雄瘋人院 - 帽子（男用）\n
6. 超級英雄瘋人院 - 帽子（女用） [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">超級英雄瘋人院 - 街機台，提供以下獨家瘋狂英雄主題服裝獎品道具給購買這街機台的玩家。要獲得這些服裝，請將本街機台設置在您的個人空間並進行遊玩。所有到您的個人空間的訪客也可以自由遊玩完整版遊戲、記錄得分、並在遊戲中獲得獎盃。你能逃出的是瘋人院，或者只是你的自我精神呢？\n
\n
在將本街機台設置在您的個人空間並進行第一次遊玩時，您便會獲得以下道具：\n
\n
1. 超級英雄瘋人院 - T恤（男用）\n
2. 超級英雄瘋人院 - T恤（女用）\n
3. 超級英雄瘋人院 - 長袖襯衣（男用）\n
4. 超級英雄瘋人院 - 長袖襯衣（女用）\n
5. 超級英雄瘋人院 - 帽子（男用）\n
6. 超級英雄瘋人院 - 帽子（女用） [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="GAME">Superhero Madhouse [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>