<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Nis_Dots_No009</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Personnage 2D: Thursday</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドットオブジェ　万能型ムテキロボット　サーズデイ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">도트 오브제 만능형 무적 로봇 써즈데이</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"Thursday: All-Purpose Robot" Sprite Statue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">像素雕像 萬能型無敵機器人THURSDAY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">像素雕像 萬能型無敵機器人THURSDAY</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">2D Character Objects: Thursday</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nis_Dots_No009</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Untitled</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La statuette d'un personnage que tu peux mettre dans ta chambre pour décorer.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">天使すらも恐れおののく冷静な分析及びツッコミも忘れない、情にも溢れる超高性能ロボットサーズデイもドットオブジェ化。地球勇者助手ジェニファー（当時５歳）により作られました。地球勇者一行のゴードン・ジェニファー・サーズデイの絆は熱い。万能ですが、あくまでオブジェなのでお手伝いはできません。ごめんなさい。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">천사조차도 무서워 벌벌 떨 정도의 냉정한 분석 및 철처하게 파고드는 날카로움도 잊지 않는, 정이 넘치는 초고성능 로봇 써즈데이도 도트 오브제화. 지구용사 조수 제니퍼(당시5세)에 의해 만들어졌습니다. 지구용사 일행의 고든, 제니퍼, 써즈데이의 인연은 남다르다. 만능이지만, 어디까지나 오브제이므로 도움은 드릴 수 없습니다. 죄송합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Thursday is a highly-efficient, all-purpose super robot who can be calm and analytical, but also overflows with passion at times. He was created by Jennifer, Captain Gordon's beautiful sidekick (when she was 5 years old), and has now been commemorated as a Sprite Statue just for you. He is very close to Jennifer and Captain Gordon, as they are all Defenders of Earth. Unfortunately, this one can't do your chores since it's only a Sprite Statue. Sorry... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">超高性能機器人Thursday，擁有連天使也畏懼的冷靜分析力，及時時不忘吐槽的個性，終於也加入了像素雕像的行列；他是由地球勇者的助手Jennifer（當時五歲）所製作產生的。地球勇者一行人Gordon、Jennifer、Thursday有著深厚的羈絆。雖說是萬能，他也只是雕像，並不能幫到您什麼忙，敬請見諒。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">超高性能機器人Thursday，擁有連天使也畏懼的冷靜分析力，及時時不忘吐槽的個性，終於也加入了像素雕像的行列；他是由地球勇者的助手Jennifer（當時五歲）所製作產生的。地球勇者一行人Gordon、Jennifer、Thursday有著深厚的羈絆。雖說是萬能，他也只是雕像，並不能幫到您什麼忙，敬請見諒。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A small character statue that you can place to decorate your own room.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>