<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">SingStar® Bad Girl Pin-Up Outfit (Red and Blue)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tenue SingStar® de pin-up (rouge et bleue)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">SingStar®-Kostüm: Böses Pin-up-Mädchen (Rot und Blau)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Abito da ragazzaccia pin up SingStar® (rosso e blu)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje chica mala pin-up SingStar® (rojos y azules)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">SingStar® Bad Girl Pin-Up Outfit (Red and Blue)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">SingStar® Bad Girl Pin-Up Outfit (Red and Blue): Beehive hair, denim threads and bad girl tattoos ... only for the rebellious! Includes Red and Blue Tops, Shorts, Shoes, both Hair Styles and two stitched together Outfits for dressing convenience!. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Tenue SingStar® de pin-up (rouge et bleue) : coiffure choucroute, vêtements en jean et tatouages de bad girl... Réservé aux rebelles ! Comprend le haut, le short et les chaussures en versions rouge et bleue, ainsi que les 2 coiffures et 2 tenues complètes pour un habillage plus facile !. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">SingStar®-Kostüm: Böses Pin-up-Mädchen (Rot und Blau): Turmfrisur, Jeans und Böse-Mädchen-Tätowierungen ... nur für rebellische Naturen! Enthält Oberteile in Blau und Rot, Shorts, Schuhe, beide Frisuren und zwei zusammengenähte Kostüme für hohen Tragekomfort!. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Abito da ragazzaccia pin up SingStar® (rosso e blu): capelli cotonati, calzoncini in jeans, tatuaggi da ragazzaccia... solo per vere ribelli! Comprende top blu e rossi, calzoncini, scarpe, entrambe le acconciature e due abiti completi per la massima comodità!. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Traje chica mala pin-up SingStar®: pelo enmarañado, tejidos vaqueros y tatuajes de chica mala... ¡solo para las más rebeldes! Incluye top, pantalones cortos y zapatos rojos y azules, los dos peinados y los dos trajes con todo junto para que sea más fácil vestirse.. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* Object Description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">SingStar® Bad Girl Pin-Up Outfit (Red and Blue): Beehive hair, denim threads and bad girl tattoos ... only for the rebellious! Includes Red and Blue Tops, Shorts, Shoes, both Hair Styles and two stitched together Outfits for dressing convenience!. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>