<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bakenrek Greasepan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bakenrek Greasepan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bakenrek Greasepan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bakenrek Greasepan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bakenrek Greasepan</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">There is no better companion for long journeys that this Goblin! You will never go hungry, you just have to get used to his special diet ... tree roots, squirrels in sauce, and how about eye of newt?![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Es gibt keinen besseren Kumpan für lange Touren als diesen Goblin! Du wirst nie hungern und musst dich lediglich an seine besondere Diät gewöhnen... Baumwurzeln, Eichhörnchen in ihrer Sauce und warum nicht, auch Molchaugen![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Il n'y a pas de meilleur compagnon pour les longs voyages que ce Gobelin! Tu ne mourras jamais de faim à  condition de t'habituer à son régime particulier… racines d'arbres,  écureuils en sauce et pourquoi pas, des yeux de triton![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Non c'è compagno migliore per i viaggi lunghi, di questo Goblin! Non avrai mai fame, basta abituarti alla loro speciale dieta... radici degli alberi , scoiattoli al sugo e, perché no? Occhio di tritone![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No hay mejor compañero para travesías largas que este Goblin!  Nunca pasarás hambre, sólo te tendrás que acostumbrar a su dieta especial... raíces de árbol, ardillas en su salsa y porqué no? ojos de tritón![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
   <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kCompanionName1</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Bakenrek Greasepan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bakenrek Greasepan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Bakenrek Greasepan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Bakenrek Greasepan</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Bakenrek Greasepan</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>