<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Royal Blade (Legendary Weapon)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">L'épée royale (arme légendaire)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die königliche Klinge (Legendäre Waffe)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">La spada reale (Arma leggendaria)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La espada real (Arma legendaria)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised*</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Royal Blade (Legendary Weapon)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">A Legendary Blade said to be forged in the heart of a volcano and capable of splitting flames in two. \n\nWielded in battle by Queen Lidicea as she united the many kingdoms and far off lands so they may grow strong, together as one, against the forces of darkness and those who would seek to attack Mercia.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Une épée légendaire qui aurait été forgée au cœur d'un volcan et serait capable de couper une flamme en deux. \n\nBrandie au combat par la reine Lidicea, qui a uni les nombreux royaumes et autres territoires lointains de sorte qu'ils puissent se renforcer, ne faisant qu'un face aux forces de l'ombre et à ceux qui cherchaient à attaquer Mercia.\n\nDÉBLOQUE DES ARTICLES DU JEU MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS – N'OFFRE PAS DE COMPOSANTS D'AVATAR POUR UN USAGE GÉNÉRAL SUR PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBLE POUR LES UTILISATEURS DU JAPON ET DE L'ASIE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Eine legendäre Klinge, die der Sage nach im Herzen eines Vulkans geschmiedet wurde und Flammen zerteilen kann. \n\nDas Schwert wurde von Königin Lidicea im Kampf geführt, als sie Königreiche und ferne Länder vereinte, auf dass sie als Einheit stärker werden und sich gegen die Mächte der Finsternis und die Feinde Mercias erwehren konnten.\n\nZUM FREISCHALTEN VON GEGENSTÄNDEN IN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS - NICHT ZUM ERHALT VON AVATAR-KOMPONENTEN ZUR ALLGEMEINEN NUTZUNG AUF PLAYSTATION®HOME. NICHT VERFÜGBAR FÜR BENUTZER IN JAPAN UND ASIEN [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Si narra che questa spada leggendaria sia stata forgiata nel cuore di un vulcano e sia in grado di tagliare in due le fiamme. \n\nBrandita in battaglia dalla regina Lidicea mentre combatteva per unire i molti regni e le terre lontane affinché diventassero più forti, contro le forze dell'oscurità e coloro che tentavano di attaccare Mercia.\n\nSBLOCCA OGGETTI ALL'INTERNO DEL GIOCO MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS. NON REGALA COMPONENTI PER AVATAR PER USO GENERICO CON PLAYSTATION®HOME. NON DISPONIBILE PER GLI UTENTI IN ASIA E GIAPPONE. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Una espada legendaria que se cree que fue forjada en el centro de un volcán y capaz de dividir las llamas en dos. \n\nBlandida en la batalla por la Reina Lidicea cuando se unió a muchos otros reinos y tierras lejanas para ser más fuertes, juntos, contra las fuerzas de la oscuridad y contra aquellos que pretendían atacar Mercia.\n\nDESBLOQUEARÁ ELEMENTOS EN MERCIA: FRACTURED REALMS GAME. NO REGALARÁ COMPONENTES DE AVATAR PARA EL USO GENERAL EN CASA DE PLAYSTATION. NO DISPONIBLE PARA LOS USUARIOS DE JAPÓN Y ASIA. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localised* [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A Legendary Blade said to be forged in the heart of a volcano and capable of splitting flames in two. \n\nWielded in battle by Queen Lidicea as she united the many kingdoms and far off lands so they may grow strong, together as one, against the forces of darkness and those who would seek to attack Mercia.\n\nWill unlock items within the Mercia: Fractured Realms game – will not give avatar components for general PlayStation®Home use. Not available to users in Japan and Asia. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>