<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Dress &amp; Jacket for Long Hair + Stockings (Orange &amp; Khaki, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Robe et veste pour cheveux longs + collants (orange et kaki, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Kleid &amp; Jacke für langes Haar + Strümpfe (orange &amp; khaki, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Vestito intero con giacca per capelli lunghi e calze (arancione e cachi, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Vestido y chaqueta para pelo largo + medias (naranja y caqui, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">ワンピース＆ジャケット・ロングヘア用＋ストッキング（オレンジ＆カーキ・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Dress &amp; Jacket for Long Hair + Stockings (Orange &amp; Khaki, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Orange dress with a khaki-coloured leather jacket worn over it and wearing orange stockings.\nThe shape of the clothing has been adjusted to go with long hair.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nCuteness: ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Une robe orange avec une veste en cuir de couleur kaki portée par dessus et avec des collants orange.\nLa forme des vêtements a été ajustée pour s'accorder avec des cheveux longs.\nDéfense : ★\nCharme : ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Orangefarbenes Kleid mit einer khakifarbenen Lederjacke und orangefarbenen Strümpfen.\nDiese Form der Kleidung wurde angepasst, damit sie mit langem Haar getragen werden kann.\nVerteidigung: ★\nNiedlichkeit: ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Vestito intero arancione con una giacca di pelle color cachi indossata sopra e delle calze arancioni.\nLa linea di questi capi di abbigliamento è stata pensata per adattarsi alla perfezione alle chiome lunghe.\nDifesa: ★\nBellezza: ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Vestido naranja bajo una chaqueta de cuero caqui, y medias naranjas a juego.\nSe ha ajustado la forma de las prendas para que queden bien con el pelo largo.\nDefensa: ★\nEncanto: ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">オレンジ色のワンピースの上にカーキ色のレザージャケットを羽織り、オレンジ色のストッキングを履いたスタイル。\nロングヘアに合わせて服の形を調整したタイプ。\n防御力：　★\nかわいさ：　★★[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Orange dress with a khaki-colored leather jacket worn over it and wearing orange stockings.\nThe shape of the clothing has been adjusted to go with long hair.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nCuteness: ★★[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
