<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Taisho-era Student Cloak Outfit Set (White, Men)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set de tenue d'étudiant de l'ère Taishō (blanche, homme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Set: Schüler der Taisho-Zeit (weiß, für Männer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set completo mantellina da studente dell'era Taisho (bianco, da uomo)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego con el atuendo de la capa de estudiante de la era Taisho (blanca, hombre)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">大正時代風の学生マント着こなしセット（白・男性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Taisho-era Student Cloak Outfit Set (White, Men)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 3-piece set consisting of clothes with a cloak attached, a cap, and shoes of a Japanese student in the Taisho era.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nYouth Level: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Taisho-era Student Cap (White, Men) (Head)\n- Taisho-era Student Clothes &amp; Cloak (White, Men) (Outfits)\n- Taisho-era Student Shoes (White, Men) (Feet)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 3 pièces incluant des vêtements avec un manteau, une casquette et des chaussures pour un étudiant japonais de l'ère Taishō.\nDéfense : ★\nJeunesse : ★★★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Casquette d'étudiant de l'ère Taishō (blanche, homme) (Tête)\n- Vêtements et manteau d'étudiant de l'ère Taishō (blancs, homme) (Tenues)\n- Chaussures d'étudiant de l'ère Taishō (blanches, homme) (Pieds)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 3-teiliges Set, das Kleidung mit Mantel, eine Mütze und Schuhe eines japanischen Schülers der Taisho-Zeit enthält.\nVerteidigung: ★\nJugendlichkeit: ★★★\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Schüler der Taisho-Zeit: Mütze (weiß, für Männer) (Kopf)\n- Schüler der Taisho-Zeit: Kleidung &amp; Mantel (weiß, für Männer) (Outfits)\n- Schüler der Taisho-Zeit: Schuhe (weiß, für Männer) (Füße)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set formato da 3 elementi comprendente una mantellina, un cappello e delle scarpe da studente giapponese dell'era Taisho.\nDifesa: ★\nLivello giovinezza: ★★★\nNel suddetto set sono inclusi i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Cappello da studente dell'era Taisho (bianco, da uomo) (cappelli)\n- Vestiti e mantellina da studente dell'era Taisho (bianchi, uomo) (aspetti)\n- Scarpe da studente dell'era Taisho (bianche, da uomo) (Piedi)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettiva categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de tres prendas que consiste en el uniforme con la capa incorporada, una gorra y unos zapatos de estudiante de la era Taisho.\nDefensa: ★\nNivel de juventud: ★★★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Gorra de estudiante de la era Taisho (blanca, hombre) (cabeza)\n- Uniforme y capa de estudiante de la era Taisho (blancos, hombre) (trajes)\n- Zapatos de estudiante de la era Taisho (blancos, hombre) (pies)\n\n* Adquiriendo este conjunto, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">日本の大正時代風の、マントつき学生服、学生帽、学生靴の３点セット。\n防御力：　★\n青春度：　★★★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・大正時代風の学生帽（白・男性）/頭\n・大正時代風の学生服とマント（白・男性）/組み合わせ\n・大正時代風の学生靴（白・男性）/靴\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 3-piece set consisting of clothes with a cloak attached, a cap, and shoes of a Japanese student in the Taisho era.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nYouth Level: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Taisho-era Student Cap (White, Men) (Head)\n- Taisho-era Student Clothes &amp; Cloak (White, Men) (Outfits)\n- Taisho-era Student Shoes (White, Men) (Feet)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
