<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Name</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">GZ Burger</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">GZ Burger</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">GZ Burger</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">GZ Burger</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">GZ Burger</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">GZバーガー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">GZ Burger</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Desc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">"GZ Burger", a hamburger shop neighboring a large lake, is all yours. The interior layout of the tables, chairs, etc. is up to your imagination. Create your own unique restaurant and invite your friends![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">"GZ Burger", un restaurant de hamburger à côté d'un grand lac, vous appartient. L'aménagement des tables, chaises, etc. peut être arrangé comme vous le souhaitez. Créez votre propre restaurant unique, et invitez vos amis![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"GZ Burger", ein Hamburgerladen angrenzend an einen großen See, liegt in deiner Hand. Die Innenausstattung an Tischen, Stühlen, usw. ist deiner Phantasie überlassen. Gründe dein eigenes einzigartiges Restaurant und lade deine Freunde ein![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">"GZ Burger", un fast food situato vicino ad un grande lago, è tutto tuo. Sarai tu ad arredarne gli interni con tavoli, sedie, ecc. in base ai tuoi gusti. Crea il tuo fast food personalizzato ed invita i tuoi amici![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">"GZ Burger", es una hamburguesería que está cerca de un gran lago, toda tuya. La disposición interior de las mesas, sillas, etc. va a tu gusto. ¡Crea tu propio restaurante e invita a tus amigos![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">大きな湖のほとりのハンバーガーショップ「GZバーガー」が、まるごとあなたのものに。テーブルや椅子など、店内のレイアウトはあなたの思うがまま。あなただけのお店を作って、友達を招待しよう！[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">"GZ Burger", a hamburger shop neighboring a large lake, is all yours. The interior layout of the tables, chairs, etc. is up to your imagination. Create your own unique restaurant and invite your friends![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>