<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Chim Peep - Bundle Pack - Red on White</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chim Peep - Panoplie - Rouge sur Blanc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Chim Peep - Gebündeltes Paket - Rot auf Weiß</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chim Peep - Pacchetto - Rosso su Bianco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chim Peep - Paquete - Rojo sobre Blanco</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_0</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Chim Peep - 번들팩 - 레드온화이트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Chim Peep - Bundle Pack - Red on White</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Chim Peep 組合包 - 白間紅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Chim Peep 組合包 - 白間紅</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Chim Peep - Bundle Pack - Red on White</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">More fun than a barrel of monkeys is Chim Peep!  Dressed to the nines in his monkey suit it's three for one with extra Peep fun!  Bring your Heavy Pet Peep into your apartment and let the fun begin.  You can control your Peep with custom animations and moves.  Take him outside of your apartment as a Companion or place him on display in your apartment in his Peep-a-Boo box.  Collect them all and stack them for all to see!\nThis set includes the following items.\n\n

・Chim Peep - Red on White\n
・Chim Peep - Static Mini - Red on White\n
・Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Red on White\n\n

※ All of the above items will become available in their relevant categories on purchasing this bundle.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chim Peep est plus amusant qu'une bande de singes! Habillé à quatre épingles en costume. C'est 3 en un avec  Peep fun supplémentaire. Ramène ton Heavy Pet Peep à ton appartement et que la fête commence. Tu peux contrôler ton peep avec des animations personnalisées et manœuvres spéciales. Prends le à l'extérieur de ton appartement comme compagne ou expose le à ton appartement dans une boîte Peep-a- Boo. Rassemble les tous et entasse les pour que tous puissent les voir.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mehr Spaß als ein Affenhaus verspricht Chim Peep! Wie aus dem Ei gepellt in seinem Affenoutfit bekommst du ihn im Dreier-Pack mit extra Peep-Spaß! Bring dein Heavy Pet Peep in deine Wohnung und der Spaß beginnt. Du kannst dein Peep mit benutzerdefinierten Animationen und Bewegungen steuern. Nimm ihn als Gefährten mit nach draußen oder stelle ihn in deiner Wohnung in seiner Peep-a-Boo Kiste aus. Sammle sie alle und stelle sie für Alle zur Schau aus! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Chim Peep é piú divertente di tante scimmie messe insieme!  Vestito alla grande con il suo vestito di scimmia é tre per uno con extra divertimento Peep!  Porta il tuo Heavy Pet Peep nel tuo appartamento e che il divertimento abbia inizio. Puoi controllare il tuo Peep con animazioni e movimenti fatti a posta. Portalo fuori dal tuo appartamento come il tuo Companion o mettilo in mostra nel tuo appartamento nella sua scatola Peep-a-Boo. Colleziona tutti quanti e mettili in mostra perché tutti possano vederli![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Chim Peep es más divertido que un barril lleno de monos!  Vestido de fiesta en su traje de mono es más diversión Peep al tres por uno!  Lleva a tu Heavy Pet Peep a tu departamento y que empieze la diversión.  Puedes controlar a tu Peep con animaciones y movimientos personalizados.  Sácalo de tu departamento como Companion o pónlo de muestra en tu departamento en su propia caja Peep-a-Boo.  Colecciónalos todos y amontónalos para que los vea todo el mundo![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">*Not Localised* Home_Object_0 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">원숭이보다 더 재미있는 원숭이 Chim Peep!  원숭이에게 우아한 몽키 수트를 입혀 추가 Peep으로 세 가지 즐거움을 누려보세요!  Heavy Pet Peep을 아파트로 데려와 신나게 놀아 보세요.  사용자 지정 애니메이션과 모션으로 Peep을 컨트롤할 수 있습니다!  친구처럼 아파트 밖에 데려가거나 Peep-A-Boo 박스에 디스플레이된 Mini-Peep을 아파트에 데려다 놓아보세요.  Mini-Peep을 모두 모아 친구들에게 자랑해 보세요!\n본 세트에는 하기 아이템이 포함되어 있습니다. \n\n

●Chim Peep - 레드온화이트\n
●Chim Peep - Static Mini - 레드온화이트\n
●Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - 레드온화이트\n\n

※ 상기 모든 아이템들은 이 번들 구입과 동시에 적절한 카테고리에서 이용할 수 있습니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">More fun than a barrel of monkeys is Chim Peep!  Dressed to the nines in his monkey suit it's three for one with extra Peep fun!  Bring your Heavy Pet Peep into your apartment and let the fun begin.  You can control your Peep with custom animations and moves.  Take him outside of your apartment as a Companion or place him on display in your apartment in his Peep-a-Boo box.  Collect them all and stack them for all to see!\nThis set includes the following items.\n\n

・Chim Peep - Red on White\n
・Chim Peep - Static Mini - Red on White\n
・Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Red on White\n\n

※ All of the above items will become available in their relevant categories on purchasing this bundle.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Chim是非常有趣的Peep！穿著高級西裝的Chim，一次過滿足您三個願望！帶Heavy PetPeep進入您家，盡情享樂。您可以用自訂動態和動作來控制Peep。他可以作為隨身夥伴和您一起外出，或者您可以將他放進專用Peep-A-Boo盒子並成為家居擺設。集齊全套，向朋友炫耀一下吧！本組合包含以下商品：\n\n 

●Chim Peep - 白間紅\n
●Chim Peep 靜態迷你公仔 - 白間紅\n
●Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - 白間紅\n\n

※ 購買組合包後，以上所有物品都會加入相關的類別中。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Chim是非常有趣的Peep！穿著高級西裝的Chim，一次過滿足您三個願望！帶Heavy PetPeep進入您家，盡情享樂。您可以用自訂動態和動作來控制Peep。他可以作為隨身夥伴和您一起外出，或者您可以將他放進專用Peep-A-Boo盒子並成為家居擺設。集齊全套，向朋友炫耀一下吧！本組合包含以下商品：\n\n 

●Chim Peep - 白間紅\n
●Chim Peep 靜態迷你公仔 - 白間紅\n
●Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - 白間紅\n\n

※ 購買組合包後，以上所有物品都會加入相關的類別中。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">More fun than a barrel of monkeys is Chim Peep!  Dressed to the nines in his monkey suit it's three for one with extra Peep fun!  Bring your Heavy Pet Peep into your apartment and let the fun begin.  You can control your Peep with custom animations and moves.  Take him outside of your apartment as a Companion or place him on display in your apartment in his Peep-a-Boo box.  Collect them all and stack them for all to see![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>