<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Harimau Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Harimau Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Fauteuil Harimau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Harimau-Stuhl</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sedia Harimau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Silla de Harimau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Harimau Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Harimau 의자</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Harimau Chair</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Harimau 椅子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Harimau 椅子</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Harimau Chair</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Always with the protection and rejuvination of the environment at their hearts, Harimau are delighted to have teamed up with the good people at Italian furniture giants “Sieda” to bring this 100% recycled, octo-carbon piece to your eco-home. Take a load off safe in the knowledge that no planets were harmed in the making of your comfortable new chair.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Always with the protection and rejuvination of the environment at their hearts, Harimau are delighted to have teamed up with the good people at Italian furniture giants “Sieda” to bring this 100% recycled, octo-carbon piece to your eco-home. Take a load off safe in the knowledge that no planets were harmed in the making of your comfortable new chair. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Toujours engagée en faveur de la protection et de la restauration de l'environnement, Harimau est ravie de s'être associée avec le merveilleux personnel du géant italien du mobilier, "Sieda", pour vous proposer cette œuvre écologique, réalisée en octocarbone 100 % recyclé. Décontractez-vous en sachant qu'aucune planète n'a été maltraitée pour fabriquer votre nouveau fauteuil si confortable. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Umweltschutz und Aufforstung liegen Harimau am Herzen. Deshalb freuen wir uns, in Kooperation mit den netten Leuten des italienischen Möbelgiganten „Sieda“ diesen zu 100 % aus recyceltem Material bestehenden Okto-Karbon-Sessel anbieten zu können. Wir bieten Entspannung in der Gewissheit, dass keinem Planeten bei der Produktion dieses neuen, bequemen Stuhles geschadet wurde. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tenendo sempre conto della protezione e del rinnovamento ambientale, la Harimau è lieta di presentare, con la collaborazione dei giganti italiani dell'arredamento “Sieda”, questa sedia in materiale riciclato al 100% in fibra di carbonio per la vostra casa ecologica. Rilassatevi nella consapevolezza che nessun pianeta ha sofferto per la produzione della vostra nuova sedia. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sin renunciar a la protección y al rejuvenecimiento del medio ambiente, Harimau se complace en ofrecerte, de la mano del gigante italiano Sieda, líder del sector mobiliario, esta silla de octocarbono, 100% reciclada, para tu hogar ecológico. Descansa con la seguridad de que no has contribuido al deterioro planetario con la adquisición de este nuevo y cómodo modelo. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Always with the protection and rejuvination of the environment at their hearts, Harimau are delighted to have teamed up with the good people at Italian furniture giants “Sieda” to bring this 100% recycled, octo-carbon piece to your eco-home. Take a load off safe in the knowledge that no planets were harmed in the making of your comfortable new chair. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">친환경 소재와 자연 보호를 기업 철학으로 삼는 Harimau가 이탈리아 가구의 명가 "Sieda"와 손을 잡고 100% 재생 가능한 친환경 가구를 만들었습니다. 당신의 멋진 의자를 만들기 위해 희생된 행성은 하나도 없습니다! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Always with the protection and rejuvination of the environment at their hearts, Harimau are delighted to have teamed up with the good people at Italian furniture giants “Sieda” to bring this 100% recycled, octo-carbon piece to your eco-home. Take a load off safe in the knowledge that no planets were harmed in the making of your comfortable new chair. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Harimau最關心環境的保護和保育，所以特地與意大利家具業界鉅子“Sieda”合作，以100%經循環再造的物料為您的環保家居打造這套沙發。您可以完全放心，這套沙發的製造過程中絕對沒有為任何星球的環境造成傷害。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Harimau最關心環境的保護和保育，所以特地與意大利家具業界鉅子“Sieda”合作，以100%經循環再造的物料為您的環保家居打造這套沙發。您可以完全放心，這套沙發的製造過程中絕對沒有為任何星球的環境造成傷害。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Always with the protection and rejuvination of the environment at their hearts, Harimau are delighted to have teamed up with the good people at Italian furniture giants “Sieda” to bring this 100% recycled, octo-carbon piece to your eco-home. Take a load off safe in the knowledge that no planets were harmed in the making of your comfortable new chair. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>