<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Distress Crewneck Sweater - Rustic Heather (Men)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Pull col rond Distress - Bruyère rustique (Homme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Distress Pullover mit Rundhalsausschnitt - Rustikale Heide (Herren)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Distress Maglione con scollo tondo - Ruggine puntinato (Uomo)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Distress Jersey de cuello redondo - Brezo rústico (Hombre)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Knit wit. What this means is that you'd be extremely smart to stock up on Billabong sweaters. Especially if you place any importance on style. Surf authentic with street influences, Billabong sweaters keep up with your everyday with just enough edge to enhance your individuality. The Distress crew sweater helps you stay on point with a plush, 12 gauge twisted yarn fabric. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Joli pull tissé. Vous serez toujours stylé avec un pull Billabong. En particulier si vous accordez de l'importance à votre look. Marque préférée des surfeurs avec une influence streetwear, Billabong crée des pulls classiques à porter quotidien, mais toujours avec une note d'originalité. Le pull à col rond Distress vous aidera à rester stylé avec son tissu en fil retors haute qualité. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Jetzt ist der richtige Zeitpunkt, um sich mit nagelneuen Billabong Strickpullis einzudecken - insbesondere, wenn Sie Wert auf eine modische Erscheinung legen. Die surf-authentischen, coolen Billabong Pullis mit Rundhalsausschnitt machen alles mit und sind trotzdem völlig individuell. Die Distress Pullover aus kuschelig dickem Zwirn halten im Winter außerdem schön warm. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questa maglia ha la stoffa! Fatti furbo e fai rifornimento di maglioni Billabong. Soprattutto se per te lo stile è importante. I maglioni Billabong  uniscono autenticità e stile di strada, per dare al tuo look quotidiano un tocco di individualità. Il maglione Distress con scollo tondo è in morbido tessuto con filato intrecciato da 12 gg. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">De punto y a punto. Es decir que sería muy inteligente por tu parte hacer reserva de jerseys Billabong. Sobre todo si te importa el estilo. Con un auténtico toque surf e influencias "street",  los jerseys Billabong te sirven en el día a día con una modernidad que potencia tu individualidad. El jersey de cuello redondo Distress te pone a punto con un tejido afelpado e hilos trenzados de calibre 12. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>