<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="ja-JP" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Nis_Dots_No031</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Personnage 2D: Book Zetta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドットオブジェ　宇宙最強魔王　ゼタ本</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">도트 오브제 우주 최강의 마왕 제타책</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">"The Sacred Tome Zetta" Sprite Statue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">像素雕像　宇宙最強魔王　Zetta之書</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">像素雕像　宇宙最強魔王　Zetta之書</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">2D Character Objects: Book Zetta</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Nis_dot_No031</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Untitled</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La statuette d'un personnage que tu peux mettre dans ta chambre pour décorer.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">宇宙最強どころか、最もアホな書物がドットオブジェで見参！宇宙最強と自負する「魔王ゼタ」は、近隣の魔王・予言者プラム（「ドットオブジェ　崇拝用プラム」で配信中）より「ゼタが統括する魔界が滅びる」との予言を受け、運命から逃れるために全知全能の書を手に入れる‥‥が、自らの行動によって魔界、そして自分自身の肉体をも消滅させてしまう！「魔王ゼタ」は全知全能の書と一体化し難を逃れるものの、見た目も本、名前すら「ゼタ本」と変わり果て、魔王の威厳も消滅。魔王仲間や手下のモンスターにすら「魔王ゼタ」と気づいてもらえない苦悩の日々が始まった！彼は魔界の復活を成し遂げ、「魔王ゼタ」に戻ることができるのか！？[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">A small character statue that you can place to decorate your own room.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">우주 최강은 커녕, 가장 어리석은 서적이 도트 오브제로 등장! 우주 최강이라고 자부하는 ｢마왕 제타｣는, 마왕・예언자 프람(「도트 오브제 숭배용 프람」으로 공개 중)으로부터 「제타가 통치하는 마계는 멸망한다」는 예언을 받고 운명을 피하기 위해 전지전능의 책을 손에 넣는데… 이 행동으로 인해 마계와 자신의 육체마저도 소멸시켜 버린다! 「마왕 제타」는 전지전능의 책과 일체화해 난을 피하지만, 외형도 책, 이름조차 「제타책」이라고 변해 버려 마왕의 위엄은 확실히 소멸. 마왕 동료나 부하의 몬스터들조차 「마왕 제타」라고 눈치채 주지 않는 고뇌의 날들이 시작되었다! 그는 마계의 부활을 완수해 「마왕 제타」로 돌아올 수 있는 것인가![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Meet the most badass, freakin'... no, the funniest sprite statue ever! After Overlord Pram prophesized that the netherworld ruled by Zetta would be destroyed, self-proclaimed badass, Overlord Zetta, sought out the Sacred Tome in hopes of avoiding his fate. Ironically, the Sacred Tome ended up destroying the netherworld and Zetta's body! By merging with the tome he was able to avoid total annihilation, but looks much like a book with a face on it. With his dignity as an overlord tarnished and his loyal friends and subjects failing to recognize him, can he ever rebuild the netherworld and return to his human form?[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">什麼宇宙最強，根本是宇宙最蠢的一本書終於也推出像素雕像了！自詡為宇宙最強的「魔王Zetta」，在聽了附近的魔王‧預言者Pram（「像素雕像　崇拜用PRAM」熱賣下載中）對他預告「由Zetta統治的魔界將會滅亡」之後，為了逃過這樣的命運，而設法取得了全知全能之書。沒想到反而是他這樣的行動為魔界以及他自己的肉體帶來了滅亡的命運！雖然「魔王Zetta」藉由和全知全能之書同化逃過一劫，但是外型卻變成了一本書，名字也改成了「Zetta之書」，魔王的威嚴蕩然無存。就連魔王的夥伴和手下的怪物們，也都沒有發現它就是「魔王Zetta」，於是它苦惱的日子就這樣展開了！它能成功復興魔界，重新取回魔王Zetta的身份嗎？[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">什麼宇宙最強，根本是宇宙最蠢的一本書終於也推出像素雕像了！自詡為宇宙最強的「魔王Zetta」，在聽了附近的魔王‧預言者Pram（「像素雕像　崇拜用PRAM」熱賣下載中）對他預告「由Zetta統治的魔界將會滅亡」之後，為了逃過這樣的命運，而設法取得了全知全能之書。沒想到反而是他這樣的行動為魔界以及他自己的肉體帶來了滅亡的命運！雖然「魔王Zetta」藉由和全知全能之書同化逃過一劫，但是外型卻變成了一本書，名字也改成了「Zetta之書」，魔王的威嚴蕩然無存。就連魔王的夥伴和手下的怪物們，也都沒有發現它就是「魔王Zetta」，於是它苦惱的日子就這樣展開了！它能成功復興魔界，重新取回魔王Zetta的身份嗎？[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>