<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Vector DX Flight Computer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ordinateur de bord Vector DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Vector DX-Flugcomputer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Computer di volo Vector DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Ordenador de vuelo Vector DX</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">Vector DX フライトコンピュータ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Vector DX 제어장치</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Vector DX Flight Computer</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Vector DX  飛行電腦</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Vector DX  飛行電腦</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Vector DX Flight Computer</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The latest in flight computer technology will constantly update the trajectory of your Sodium2 racer to greatly increase stability and turn response, but an extended time to break the Mach 1 barrier may let your opponents in. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le dernier cri en matière de technologie informatique corrigera de façon constante les trajectoires de votre véhicule Sodium2 pour une meilleure stabilité et réactivité dans les virages, mais un délai plus long avant d'atteindre Mach 1 favorisera vos concurrents. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieser hochmoderne Flugcomputer berechnet die Flugbahn deines Sodium2-Gleiter in Echtzeit und verbessert so die Stabilität und Kurvenlage erheblich. Durch die längere Zeit bis zum Durchbrechen der Schallmauer könnten deine Gegner vor dir Mach 1 erreichen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'ultima novità nel settore della tecnologia dei computer di volo. Aggiornando costantemente la traiettoria del tuo veicolo da corsa Sodium2, consente un notevole aumento della stabilità e tempi di reazione ridotti in curva. Attenzione: l'incremento di tempo necessario a infrangere la barriera del Mach 1 potrebbe favorire i tuoi avversari. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lo último en tecnología de ordenadores de vuelo, este dispositivo actualizará constantemente la trayectoria de tu corredor de Sodium2 para aumentar en gran medida la estabilidad y la respuesta de giro, pero la necesidad de más tiempo para romper la barrera del Mach 1 puede comportar que tus contrincantes te superen. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">最新鋭テクノロジーを誇るこのフライトコンピュータは車体を常に水平に保ち、車体の安定性とコーナーでの操作反応を向上します。マッハ1に達するまで長時間を必要とするので、競争相手から遅れがちになるのが欠点です。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">최신 기술을 접목한 제어장치입니다. Sodium2 레이서의 운행 정보가 실시간으로 제공되며, 안정성과 회전 속도를 크게 향상합니다. 그러나 마하 1을 주파하는 시간은 느린 편에 속합니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The latest in flight computer technology will constantly update the trajectory of your Sodium2 racer to greatly increase stability and turn response, but an extended time to break the Mach 1 barrier may let your opponents in. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這是最新的飛行電腦技術，能經常更新你的Sodium2飛船軌道來大大提升穩定性和反應，但要越過馬赫1障礙的需要更多時間，可能讓你的對手有機可乘。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這是最新的飛行電腦技術，能經常更新你的Sodium2飛船軌道來大大提升穩定性和反應，但要越過馬赫1障礙的需要更多時間，可能讓你的對手有機可乘。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The latest in flight computer technology will constantly update the trajectory of your Sodium2 racer to greatly increase stability and turn response, but an extended time to break the Mach 1 barrier may let your opponents in. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>