<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Dragon’s Green - Light Golf Club</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Dragon's Green - Club léger</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dragon's Green – Leichter Golfschläger</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dragon's Green - Golf Club Facile</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dragon’s Green - Palo de golf ligero</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ドラゴンズ・グリーン - ライトゴルフクラブ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">드래곤스 그린 골프 클럽 - 라이트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Dragon’s Green - Light Golf Club</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Dragon’s Green輕量級高爾夫球球桿</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Dragon’s Green輕量級高爾夫球球桿</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Dragon’s Green - Light Golf Club</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Become a Master of the Aftertouch utilizing this club's improved ability to control the air around the ball and guide it much further. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Devenez le roi du Réajustement en utilisant ces clubs permettant de contrôler les mouvements d'air autour de la balle afin de la guider encore plus loin. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Werde zum Meister der Nachbearbeitung. Mit diesem Schläger kannst du die Luft um den Ball herum besser kontrollieren und ihn so weiter steuern. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Diventa maestro del Ritocco utilizzando l'abilità potenziata di queste mazze per controllare l'aria attorno alla pallina e guidarla molto più lontano. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Conviértete en un maestro del Retoque utilizando la capacidad de Retoque mejorada de este palo, controlando el aire que rodea la pelota y llevándola así mucho más lejos. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">このクラブを使用するとボールの周りの空気を操ってもっと先までコントロールできます。これでアトオシの名人になれるかも！\n※購入するとこのコンテンツは「パーソナルスペースのカスタマイズ/家具を追加する」内の「装飾品」に追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">해당 클럽의 향상된 타구 조절력은 공 주변의 공기를 움직여 훨씬 먼 비거리가 나올 수 있도록 도와줍니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Become a Master of the Aftertouch utilizing this clubs improved ability to control the air around the ball and guide it much further. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">試試這些經改良的球桿，能更有效控制球附近的氣流、令它飛得更遠，讓您成為壓力感應的專家。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">試試這些經改良的球桿，能更有效控制球附近的氣流、令它飛得更遠，讓您成為壓力感應的專家。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Become a Master of the Aftertouch utilizing this club's improved ability to control the air around the ball and guide it much further. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>