<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sodium Small Tasselled Floor Pillow: Blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Petit coussin de sol à pompons Sodium : bleu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Kleines Sodium-Kissen mit Quasten: Blau</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Grande cuscino nappato da pavimento Sodium: blu</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Cojín de suelo de borlas grande Sodium: azul</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">房付きSodium小判座布団：青</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Sodium 의 술 달린 바닥용 방석: 청색</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sodium Small Tasselled Floor Pillow: Blue</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Sodium小型流蘇靠枕：藍色</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Sodium小型流蘇靠枕：藍色</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sodium Small Tasselled Floor Pillow: Blue</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Want to deck out your apartment as centre for lounging and relaxation? Now you can with this excellent floor pillow!   [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Vous souhaitez transformer votre appartement en centre de détente et de relaxation ? C'est possible grâce à ce superbe coussin de sol.  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willst du dein Appartement zu einem Ort der Ruhe und Entspannung machen? Jetzt kannst du es tun, mit diesem hervorragenden Bodenkissen.   [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Vuoi fare del tuo appartamento il centro dell'ozio e del relax? Ora è possibile grazie a questo pregevole cuscino da pavimento!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Quieres convertir tu apartamento en un centro de relajación y tranquilidad? ¡Ahora ya puedes conseguirlo con este maravilloso cojín de suelo!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">あなたのアパートを、心地よくくつろげる空間にしませんか？今ならこの素敵な座布団で、あなたの思いは叶います！  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">여러분의 아파트를 편안하게 쉴 수 있는 라운지로 바꾸고  싶으세요? 이제 이 훌륭한 바닥 방석으로 꾸며 보세요!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Want to deck out your apartment as centre for lounging and relaxation? Now you can with this excellent floor pillow!   [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">想讓你家變成休息放鬆的地方嗎？這個超讚的靠枕馬上讓你美夢成真！  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">想讓你家變成休息放鬆的地方嗎？這個超讚的靠枕馬上讓你美夢成真！  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Want to deck out your apartment as center for lounging and relaxation? Now you can with this excellent floor pillow!   [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>