<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Valor Landscape Painting</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Peinture de paysage Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Valor-Landschaftsgemälde</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Paesaggio Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Paisaje de Valor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">風景画 ベイラー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Valor 풍경화</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Valor Landscape Painting</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Vaｌor風景畫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Valor風景畫</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Valor Landscape Painting</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This painting depicts a Valor area of operation known as Copper Hills. The artist does a great job capturing the rugged beauty of the environment. Purchase this painting today and bring the feeling of the great outdoors, indoors. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce tableau représente une zone d'opérations de Valor, connue sous le nom de Copper Hill. L'artiste rend magnifiquement la beauté déchiquetée de l'environnement. Achetez cette peinture et faites entrer les grands espaces dans votre salon. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Gemälde zeigt ein Valor-Einsatzgebiet, das als Copper Hills bekannt ist. Der Künstler hat die raue Schönheit der Umgebung gut eingefangen. Kaufen Sie dieses Gemälde noch heute und bringen Sie die große weite Welt in Ihr kleines Zuhause. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo dipinto raffigura una zona operativa della Valor detta Copper Hills. L'artista ha fatto un ottimo lavoro nel delineare la bellezza irregolare dell'ambiente. Acquistatelo per portare un senso di aria aperta nella vostra abitazione. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este cuadro representa una zona de operaciones de Valor conocida como Copper Hills. El artista ha capturado la singular belleza del entorno a la perfección. Compra este cuadro ya mismo e incorpora la belleza del exterior al interior de tu apartamento. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">コッパー丘というベイラー作戦区域を題材にした作品。自然の厳しさ、美しさがよく表現されている。 ベイラーの信念が描写された秀作。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">코퍼 힐로 알려진 Valor의 작전지역을 그린 작품입니다. 주변 경관의 거친 아름다움을 재현하고 있습니다. 야외의 운치를 실내로 고스란히 들여올 수 있는 기회입니다. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This painting depicts a Valor area of operation known as Copper Hills. The artist does a great job capturing the rugged beauty of the environment. Purchase this painting today and bring the feeling of the great outdoors, indoors. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這幅畫描繪出Valor地區Copper Hills的一部分。作者成功地抓住這環境險峻卻美妙的一面。購買這幅畫並將美妙的戶外風景帶進家中吧。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這幅畫描繪出Valor地區Copper Hills的一部分。作者成功地抓住這環境險峻卻美妙的一面。購買這幅畫並將美妙的戶外風景帶進家中吧。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This painting depicts a Valor area of operation known as Copper Hills. The artist does a great job capturing the rugged beauty of the environment. Purchase this painting today and bring the feeling of the great outdoors, indoors. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>