<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Female01_Hands_bi_soldier_Re</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Black Irem Brigade Gloves (Replica, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Gants de la Brigade Noire Irem (Réplique, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">"Black Irem Brigade"-Handschuhe (Replik, F)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guanti della Brigata Black Irem (replica, da donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guantes del Escuadrón Irem Negro (réplica, M)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブラックアイレム団戦闘員　手袋（レプリカ・女性）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블랙 아이렘단 전투원 장갑 (레플리카, 여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Combatant of the Black Irem Brigade - Gloves (Replica/Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">黑色Irem團戰鬥員 手套（複製品/女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">黑色Irem團戰鬥員 手套（複製品/女用）</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Black Irem Brigade Gloves (Replica, F)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">Female01_Hands_bi_soldier_Re_description</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Gloves worn by combatants in the Black Irem Brigade to make sure they leave no fingerprints behind when conducting their nefarious activities. They also have been designed with an adhesiveness that allows combatants to climb buildings with ease.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Gants portés par les combattants de la Brigade Noire Irem pour être sûrs de ne laisser aucune empreinte derrière eux quand ils exercent leurs activités malfaisantes. Ils ont aussi été créés avec une adhésivité qui permet aux combattants d'escalader les immeubles aisément.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Handschuhe, die von den Kämpfern der Black Irem Brigade getragen werden,  damit sie keine Fingerabdrücke bei ihren ruchlosen Aktivitäten hinterlassen. Desweiteren wurden sie mit einer Haftfähigkeit ausgestattet, mit denen sich Gebäude leicht erklimmen lassen.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Guanti indossati dai combattenti della Brigata Black Irem per garantire che nessuna impronta digitale venga lasciata nei luoghi delle loro operazioni. Sono dotati inoltre di una pellicola adesiva che permette a chi li indossa di arrampicarsi su palazzi con grande facilità.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Guantes utilizados por los combatientes del Escuadrón Irem Negro para asegurarse de que no dejan huellas dactilares después de realizar sus malvadas actividades. Su diseño incluye además un componente adhesivo que permite a los combatientes escalar edificios con facilidad.[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブラックアイレム団の戦闘員たちが指紋を残さずに作業を行うために着用する手袋。滑らかなものには吸い付くように密着する特徴があり、この機能によって戦闘員たちは、垂直なビルの壁を登ることができる。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블랙 아이렘단의 전투원들이 지문을 남기지 않고 작업할 수 있도록 착용하는 장갑. 미끄러운 것에는 달라붙듯 밀착하는 특징이 있어, 이 기능 때문에 전투원들은 수직 빌딩의 벽을 오를 수 있다.[#Legal]
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Gloves used by Combatants of the Black Irem Brigade in order to keep from leaving fingerprints. Specially made to stick onto smooth surfaces, Combatants use these gloves to scale vertical building walls.[#Legal]
</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">黑色Irem團的戰鬥員們為了在工作中不留下指紋而戴的手套。具有可吸附光滑物的特徵，此功能使戰鬥員們能夠攀爬垂直的大樓牆壁。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">黑色Irem團的戰鬥員們為了在工作中不留下指紋而戴的手套。具有可吸附光滑物的特徵，此功能使戰鬥員們能夠攀爬垂直的大樓牆壁。[#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Gloves worn by combatants in the Black Irem Brigade to make sure they leave no fingerprints behind when conducting their nefarious activities. They also have been designed with an adhesiveness that allows combatants to climb buildings with ease.[#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>