<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Raven Footlocker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Malle Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Raven-Truhe</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Scarpiera Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Baúl de Raven</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ベッドトランクケース レーヴン</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Raven 락커</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Raven Footlocker</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raven裝備箱</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raven裝備箱</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Raven Footlocker</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The shrewd and intelligent designs of Raven's furniture may showcase form over function, but who says a footlocker can't be bulletproof? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La conception astucieuse et intelligente des meubles Raven met peut-être plus l'accent sur la forme que sur la fonction, mais qui a dit qu'une malle ne pouvait pas être pare-balles? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das scharfsinnige, intelligente Design der Raven-Möbel ist ein Paradebeispiel für die Form-vor-Funktion-Philosophie... Aber es spricht auch nichts dagegen, dass eine Truhe kugelsicher ist, oder? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il disegno sofisticato e intelligente dell'arredamento Raven sembra mirare all'ostentazione più che alla funzionalità, ma questa scarpiera potrebbe anche essere a prova di proiettili... [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">El inteligente y sofisticado diseño de los muebles de Raven da preferencia a la estética por encima de la función pero ¿quién dice que un baúl no puede ser antibalas? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">合理的なレーヴンの家具は形より機能重視。防弾ケースも役に立つ日が必ずくる。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">많은 기술이 접목된 최신 Raven 디자인입니다. 물론 외관을 너무 중시한다는 지적을 받을 수도 있지만, 생각해보면 방탄 락커는 누구에게나 하나씩은 필요하지 않을까요? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The shrewd and intelligent designs of Raven's furniture may showcase form over function, but who says a footlocker can't be bulletproof? [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Raven的傢具設計精細而醒目。可能有人懷疑其形式優於實際，但誰說裝備箱不可以擁有防彈功能？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Raven的傢具設計精細而醒目。可能有人懷疑其形式優於實際，但誰說裝備箱不可以擁有防彈功能？ [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The shrewd and intelligent designs of Raven's furniture may showcase form over function, but who says a footlocker can't be bulletproof? [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>