<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Mansion Door</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Doors to other parts of the Mansion. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">garage</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">\nLooking to display your automotive wealth and maybe even unlock a few gilded treasures? You will be able to shortly.\n\nComing soon: The PlayStation®Home Mansion Garage, complete with built-in furniture to start you off and a unique set of gold virtual gifts to give your guests. Check for it in the Estates Store. Collect them all and acquire the ultimate PlayStation®Home personal space.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">\nVous aimeriez exposer vos précieux bolides et, pourquoi pas, débloquer quelques trésors cachés au passage ? Votre rêve est sur le point de devenir réalité. \n\nBientôt disponible : le garage du manoir PlayStation®Home, déjà meublé et avec en prime un assortiment unique de cadeaux en or virtuel à offrir à vos invités. Jetez-y un œil dans la boutique Estates. Collectez tous les éléments et créez l'espace personnel PlayStation®Home ultime.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">\nDu möchtest deine teuren Schlitten zur Schau stellen und vielleicht sogar ein paar goldene Schätze freischalten? All das ist schon bald möglich!\n\nIn Kürze verfügbar: die Garage der PlayStation®Home-Villa! Voll ausgestattet, damit du direkt loslegen kannst. Mit einzigartigen virtuellen Geschenken aus Gold für deine Gäste. Halte im Estates Store Ausschau nach diesem tollen Angebot! Sammle sie alle und erhalte den ultimativen persönlichen PlayStation®Home-Bereich.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">\nNon vedi l'ora di sfoggiare i tuoi bolidi e sbloccare preziosi oggetti dorati? L'attesa sta per finire.\n\nÈ in arrivo il Garage della PlayStation®Home Mansion, già arredato e fornito di uno speciale set di regali virtuali in oro per i tuoi ospiti. Disponibile nel negozio Estates. Completa la collezione e goditi uno spazio personale PlayStation®Home da favola.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">\n¿Deseas demostrar tu poderío automovilístico y puede que hasta desbloquear unos cuantos tesoros dorados? Pronto podrás.\n\nPróximamente: el garaje de la mansión de PlayStation®Home, entregado con su mobiliario ya integrado y un conjunto de premios virtuales de oro para tus distinguidos invitados. Búscalo en la tienda Estates. Colecciónalos todos y consigue el espacio personal de PlayStation®Home definitivo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">\n愛車を飾る場所を探していますか。もうじき出来ます！\n\nセレブハウス：ガレージ。セレブハウスを購入された方には初めて入場された際に記念のホームリワードが配布されます。また、特典としてフレンドにホームリワードをプレゼントすることができます。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">\n멋진 자동차들을 뽐내고, 몇 가지 숨겨진 비밀을 밝혀내고 싶으신가요? \n\nPlayStation®Home 맨션 차고는 완벽한 장비와 친구들에게 선물할 수 있는 황금 리워드를 갖추고 있답니다. 쇼핑몰에서 확인하시고, 모두 수집하여 진정한 최고의 PlayStation®Home 퍼스널 스페이스를 장만하십시오.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">\nLooking to display your automotive wealth and maybe even unlock a few gilded treasures?\n\nThe PlayStation®Home Mansion Garage, complete with built-in furniture to start you off and a unique set of gold virtual gifts to give your guests. Check for it in the Shopping Mall. Collect them all and acquire the ultimate PlayStation®Home personal space.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">\n想展示你的汽車收藏，甚至解開一些珍貴寶藏？\n\nPlayStation®Home豪華別墅車庫內置家具讓你馬上享受，並有一套獨特的黃金虛擬禮物送給你的賓客。在Shopping Mall可得知相關情報。收集全部，取得終極的PlayStation®Home個人空間。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">\n想展示你的汽車收藏，甚至解開一些珍貴寶藏？\n\nPlayStation®Home豪華別墅車庫內置家具讓你馬上享受，並有一套獨特的黃金虛擬禮物送給你的賓客。在Shopping Mall可得知相關情報。收集全部，取得終極的PlayStation®Home個人空間。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">\nLooking to display your automotive wealth and maybe even unlock a few gilded treasures? You will be able to shortly.\n\nComing soon: The PlayStation®Home Mansion Garage, complete with built-in furniture to start you off and a unique set of gold virtual gifts to give your guests. Check for it in the Estates Store. Collect them all and acquire the ultimate PlayStation®Home personal space.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">pool</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">\nWant to hit up the infinity pool, chill out in the pool house, or just watch the sailboats on the ocean? You will be able to shortly.\n\nComing soon: The PlayStation®Home Mansion Infinity Pool, complete with built-in furniture to start you off and a unique set of gold virtual gifts to give your guests. Check for it in the Estates Store. Collect them all and acquire the ultimate PlayStation®Home personal space.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">\nUn petit plongeon dans la piscine panoramique, un moment de détente dans le pool-house et une vue sans pareille pour admirer les bateaux qui voguent sur l'océan, ça vous tente ? La piscine panoramique du manoir PlayStation®Home est fournie meublée et avec un assortiment unique de cadeaux en or virtuel à offrir à vos invités. Jetez-y un œil dans la boutique Estates. Collectez tous les éléments et créez l'espace personnel PlayStation®Home ultime.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">\nDu möchtest in den Unendlichen Pool springen, im Pool-Haus abhängen oder einfach nur die Segelboote auf dem Meer beobachten? All das ist schon bald möglich!\n\nIn Kürze verfügbar: der Unendliche Pool der PlayStation®Home-Villa. Voll ausgestattet, damit du direkt loslegen kannst. Mit einzigartigen virtuellen Geschenken aus Gold für deine Gäste. Halte im Estates Store Ausschau nach diesem tollen Angebot! Sammle sie alle und erhalte den ultimativen persönlichen PlayStation®Home-Bereich.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">\nTi piacerebbe fare un bel tuffo nella piscina a sfioro, per poi rilassarti comodamente in veranda guardando le navi che solcano l'oceano? L'attesa sta per finire.\n\nÈ in arrivo la Piscina a sfioro della PlayStation®Home Mansion, già arredata e fornita di uno speciale set di regali virtuali in oro per i tuoi ospiti. Disponibile nel negozio Estates. Completa la collezione e goditi uno spazio personale PlayStation®Home da favola.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">\n¿Quieres probar la piscina infinita, relajarte en la casa de la piscina o simplemente ver los barcos surcando el océano? Pronto podrás.\n\nPróximamente: la piscina infinita de la mansión de PlayStation®Home, entregada con su mobiliario ya integrado y un conjunto de premios virtuales de oro para tus distinguidos invitados. Búscala en la tienda Estates. Colecciónalos todos y consigue el espacio personal de PlayStation®Home definitivo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">\nプールでゆったりと過ごしたいですか。もうじき出来ます！\n\nセレブハウス：インフィニティプール。セレブハウスを購入された方には初めて入場された際に記念のホームリワードが配布されます。また、特典としてフレンドにホームリワードをプレゼントすることができます。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">\n영원의 풀장에서 하루의 일과를 마무리하고 싶으십니까? 바다 위를 떠도는 배를 바라보며 생각에 잠기는 건 어떤가요? \n\nPlayStation®Home 맨션 영원의 풀장은 완벽한 장비와 친구들에게 선물할 수 있는 황금 리워드를 갖추고 있답니다. 쇼핑몰에서 확인하시고, 모두 수집하여 진정한 최고의 PlayStation®Home 퍼스널 스페이스를 장만하십시오.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">\nWant to hit up the infinity pool, chill out in the pool house, or just watch the sailboats on the ocean?\n\nThe PlayStation®Home Mansion Infinity Pool, complete with built-in furniture to start you off and a unique set of gold virtual gifts to give your guests. Check for it in the Shopping Mall. Collect them all and acquire the ultimate PlayStation®Home personal space.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">\n想跳進無邊際泳池、在泳池小屋休息，或只是看著大海上的帆船？\n\nPlayStation®Home豪華別墅無邊際泳池內置家具讓你馬上享受，並有一套獨特的黃金虛擬禮物送給你的賓客。在Shopping Mall可得知相關情報。收集全部，取得終極的PlayStation®Home個人空間。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">\n想跳進無邊際泳池、在泳池小屋休息，或只是看著大海上的帆船？\n\nPlayStation®Home豪華別墅無邊際泳池內置家具讓你馬上享受，並有一套獨特的黃金虛擬禮物送給你的賓客。在Shopping Mall可得知相關情報。收集全部，取得終極的PlayStation®Home個人空間。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">\nWant to hit up the infinity pool, chill out in the pool house, or just watch the sailboats on the ocean? You will be able to shortly.\n\nComing soon: The PlayStation®Home Mansion Infinity Pool, complete with built-in furniture to start you off and a unique set of gold virtual gifts to give your guests. Check for it in the Estates Store. Collect them all and acquire the ultimate PlayStation®Home personal space.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">first_floor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">\nWant to relax in an extravagant space filled with the rarest items around such as gold appliances and your very own tiger?\n\nThe PlayStation®Home Mansion Ground Floor, complete with built-in furniture to start you off, a tiger, indoor water fountain, and a unique set of gold virtual gifts to give your guests. Check for it in the Estates Store.\n\nCollect them all and acquire the ultimate PlayStation®Home personal space.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">\nVous cherchez un espace extravagant où vous détendre, décoré des articles les plus rares tels que des appareils électriques en or ou un véritable tigre ? \n\nLe rez-de-chaussée du manoir PlayStation®Home est fait pour vous ! Découvrez ses meubles luxueux, son tigre féroce, sa fontaine intérieure, mais aussi un assortiment unique de cadeaux en or virtuel à offrir à vos invités. Jetez-y un œil dans la boutique Estates. \n\nCollectez tous les éléments et créez l'espace personnel PlayStation®Home ultime.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">\nDu möchtest in einem extravaganten Bereich relaxen, der mit den wertvollsten Dingen ausgestattet ist, die es überhaupt gibt, wie beispielsweise goldenen Küchenutensilien oder einem eigenen Tiger? Das Erdgeschoss der PlayStation®Home-Villa ist komplett eingerichtet, damit du gleich alles hast. Er wird von einem Tiger bewacht, verfügt über einen Indoor-Springbrunnen und einzigartige virtuelle Geschenke aus Gold für deine Gäste. Halte im Estates Store Ausschau nach diesem tollen Angebot! Sammle sie alle und erhalte den ultimativen persönlichen PlayStation®Home-Bereich.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">\nNon vedi l'ora di rilassarti in un eclettico spazio traboccante di fantastiche rarità, come elettrodomestici in oro e una tigre personale?\n\nNon lasciarti sfuggire il pianterreno della PlayStation®Home Mansion, già arredato e completo di tigre, fontana interna e uno speciale set di oggetti virtuali in oro per i tuoi ospiti. Disponibile nel negozio Estates.\n\nCompleta la collezione e goditi uno spazio personale PlayStation®Home da favola.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">\n¿Quieres relajarte en un espacio extravagante lleno de los objetos más singulares, como embellecedores de oro y tu propio tigre?\n\nLa planta baja de la mansión de PlayStation®Home, entregada con su mobiliario ya integrado, un tigre, una fuente de interior y un conjunto de premios virtuales de oro para tus distinguidos invitados. Búscala en la tienda Estates.\n\nColecciónalos todos y consigue el espacio personal de PlayStation®Home definitivo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">\n虎や金の家電がある豪華な内装のパーソナルスペースに過ごしたいですか。もうじき出来ます！\n\nセレブハウス：一階。セレブハウスを購入された方には初めて入場された際に記念のホームリワードが配布されます。また、特典としてフレンドにホームリワードをプレゼントすることができます。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">\n가장 진귀한 아이템들로 채워진 환상적인 스페이스에서 휴식을 취하고 싶으십니까?\nPlayStation®Home 맨션 1층은 완벽한 장비와 호랑이, 분수, 그리고 친구들에게 선물할 수 있는 황금 리워드를 갖추고 있답니다. 쇼핑몰에서 확인하시고, 모두 수집하여 진정한 최고의 PlayStation®Home 퍼스널 스페이스를 장만하십시오.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">\nWant to relax in an extravagant space filled with the rarest items around such as gold appliances and your very own tiger?\n\nThe PlayStation®Home Mansion First Floor, complete with built-in furniture to start you off, a tiger, indoor water fountain, and a unique set of gold virtual gifts to give your guests. Check for it in the Shopping Mall.\n\nCollect them all and acquire the ultimate PlayStation®Home personal space.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">\n想在一個放滿黃金器具和你的專用老虎等奇異物品的奢華空間裡輕鬆一下？\n\nPlayStation®Home豪華別墅1樓內置各種家具讓你馬上享受，包括一隻老虎、室內噴泉及一套獨特的黃金虛擬禮物送給你的賓客。在Shopping Mall可得知相關情報。收集全部，取得終極的PlayStation®Home個人空間。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">\n想在一個放滿黃金器具和你的專用老虎等奇異物品的奢華空間裡輕鬆一下？\n\nPlayStation®Home豪華別墅1樓內置各種家具讓你馬上享受，包括一隻老虎、室內噴泉及一套獨特的黃金虛擬禮物送給你的賓客。在Shopping Mall可得知相關情報。收集全部，取得終極的PlayStation®Home個人空間。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">\nWant to relax in an extravagant space filled with the rarest items around such as gold appliances and your very own tiger?\n\nThe PlayStation®Home Mansion First Floor, complete with built-in furniture to start you off, a tiger, indoor water fountain, and a unique set of gold virtual gifts to give your guests. Check for it in the Estates Store.\n\nCollect them all and acquire the ultimate PlayStation®Home personal space.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">second_floor</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">\nHeading upstairs to check out the game room, relax in your office, or catch a sweeping view of the ocean from the master bedroom? You will be able to shortly.\n\nComing soon: The PlayStation®Home Mansion Second Floor, complete with built-in furniture to start you off, two interactive games, and a unique set of gold virtual gifts to give your guests. Check for it in the Estates Store. Collect them all and acquire the ultimate PlayStation®Home personal space.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">\nMontez à l'étage et amusez-vous dans votre salle de jeux, détendez-vous dans votre bureau ou admirez la vue incomparable que la chambre principale offre sur l'océan. Vous en rêviez ? Nous l'avons fait. \n\nBientôt disponible : le premier étage du manoir PlayStation®Home, déjà meublé et avec en prime un assortiment unique de cadeaux en or virtuel à offrir à vos invités. Jetez-y un œil dans la boutique Estates. Collectez tous les éléments et créez l'espace personnel PlayStation®Home ultime.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">\nDie erste Etage betreten, die Spielelounge entdecken, im Büro entspannen oder einen Blick auf das Meer erhaschen … All das ist schon bald möglich.\n\nIn Kürze verfügbar: die erste Etage der PlayStation®Home-Villa! Komplett eingerichtet, damit du gleich alles hast: zwei interaktive Spiele und einzigartige virtuelle Geschenke aus Gold für deine Gäste. Halte im Estates Store Ausschau nach diesem tollen Angebot! Sammle sie alle und erhalte den ultimativen persönlichen PlayStation®Home-Bereich.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">\nTi piacerebbe salire al primo piano, divertirti nella sala dei giochi, rilassarti nel tuo studio e ammirare la maestosità dell'oceano dalla stanza da letto principale? L'attesa sta per finire.\n\nÈ in arrivo il Primo piano della PlayStation®Home Mansion, già arredato e completo di due giochi interattivi uno speciale set di regali virtuali in oro per i tuoi ospiti. Disponibile nel negozio Estates. Completa la collezione e goditi uno spazio personale PlayStation®Home da favola.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">\n¿Subes para probar la sala de juegos, relajarte en tu oficina o disfrutar de la más maravillosa de las vistas desde el dormitorio principal? Pronto podrás.\n\nPróximamente: la primera planta de la mansión de PlayStation®Home, entregada con su mobiliario ya integrado, dos juegos interactivos y un conjunto de premios virtuales de oro para tus distinguidos invitados. Búscala en la tienda Estates. Colecciónalos todos y consigue el espacio personal de PlayStation®Home definitivo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">\n上の階から海を見たり、ゲームルームでリラックスしてみませんか。もうじき出来ます！\n\nセレブハウス：二階。セレブハウスを購入された方には初めて入場された際に記念のホームリワードが配布されます。また、特典としてフレンドにホームリワードをプレゼントすることができます。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">\n자신만의 아케이드에서 게임을 즐기고, 멋진 침실에서 바다의 장관을 바라보고 싶으십니까? \n\nPlayStation®Home 맨션 2층은 완벽한 장비와 두 종류의 게임, 그리고 친구들에게 선물할 수 있는 황금 리워드를 갖추고 있답니다. 쇼핑몰에서 확인하시고, 모두 수집하여 진정한 최고의 PlayStation®Home 퍼스널 스페이스를 장만하십시오.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">\nHeading upstairs to check out the game room, relax in your office, or catch a sweeping view of the ocean from the master bedroom?\n\nThe PlayStation®Home Mansion Second Floor, complete with built-in furniture to start you off, two interactive games, and a unique set of gold virtual gifts to give your guests. Check for it in the Shopping Mall. Collect them all and acquire the ultimate PlayStation®Home personal space.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">\n想到樓上看看遊戲室、在辦公室裡放鬆或在主人睡房欣賞廣闊的大海景色？\n\nPlayStation®Home豪華別墅2樓內置各種家具讓你馬上享受，包括兩款互動遊戲及一套獨特的黃金虛擬禮物送給你的賓客。在Shopping Mall可得知相關情報。收集全部，取得終極的PlayStation®Home個人空間。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">\n想到樓上看看遊戲室、在辦公室裡放鬆或在主人睡房欣賞廣闊的大海景色？\n\nPlayStation®Home豪華別墅2樓內置各種家具讓你馬上享受，包括兩款互動遊戲及一套獨特的黃金虛擬禮物送給你的賓客。在Shopping Mall可得知相關情報。收集全部，取得終極的PlayStation®Home個人空間。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">\nHeading upstairs to check out the game room, relax in your office, or catch a sweeping view of the ocean from the master bedroom? You will be able to shortly.\n\nComing soon: The PlayStation®Home Mansion Second Floor, complete with built-in furniture to start you off, two interactive games, and a unique set of gold virtual gifts to give your guests. Check for it in the Estates Store. Collect them all and acquire the ultimate PlayStation®Home personal space.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>