<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Park personal space</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Parc : espace personnel</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Park: persönlichen Raum</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Parco: spazio personale</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Parque: espacio personal</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Park personal space</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Whether you prefer to chill out by the fountain, or dance with your friends in the music pavilion,  there is always a good reason to come and visit this peaceful art-déco public park! Contains a go-kart racing game, a rythm-action game, and the Space Crash arcade cabinet. Playing the games will get you rewards![#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Préfererez-vous vous relaxer devant la fontaine, ou danser avec vos amis dans le kiosque à musique? Autant de bonnes raisons d'apprécier ce paisible parc public de style art-déco. Contient un jeu de course de karts et un jeu de danse, tous deux avec des prix à gagner! Contient également le jeu d'arcade "Space Crash". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Ob zum Chillen am Brunnen, oder Tanz mit Freunden im Musikpavillon bevorzugen, gibt es immer einen guten Grund zu kommen, und besuchen Sie diese ruhige Art-déco Park! Enthält eine Go-Kart-Rennspiel und eine Tanzspiel, mit Belohnungen, sowie den Space Crash Arcade-Automat. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Se si preferisce rilassarsi accanto alla fontana, o ballare con i tuoi amici nel padiglione della musica, c'è sempre un buon motivo per venire a visitare questo tranquillo parco pubblico art-déco! Contiene un gioco di corse di go-kart, e  un gioco di ballo, con  premi. Contiene anche il cabinato arcade "Space Crash". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¿Prefiere relajarse delante de la fuente, y bailar con tus amigos en el quiosco de música? Tantas buenas razones para disfrutar de este tranquilo parque público de estilo art deco. Contiene un juego de carreras de karts, e un juego de baila, con premios! También contiene el juego de arcade "Space Crash". [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Whether you prefer to chill out by the fountain, or dance with your friends in the music pavilion,  there is always a good reason to come and visit this peaceful art-déco public park! Contains a go-kart racing game, a rythm-action game, and the Space Crash arcade cabinet. Playing the games will get you rewards![#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>