<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Billabong - Lite Hearted Bazaar Denim Shorts - Blue Daze (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Billabong - Shorts en jean Lite Hearted Bazaar - Bleu pervenche (Femme)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Billabong - Lite Hearted Bazaar Jeansshorts - Blau (Damen)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Billabong - Lite Hearted Bazaar Pantaloncini in denim - Blu (Donna)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Billabong - Short vaquero Lite Hearted Bazaar - Azul deslumbrante (Mujer)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Our Lite Hearted Bazaar denim shorts show you just how hot distressed details can be. Featuring heavy frayed hems, hand sanding and ripped seams that give a hardcore edge to the exotic Ikat print. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Nos shorts en denim délavé et vieilli Lite Hearted Bazaar sont vraiment hyper tendance. Avec leurs ourlets à franges, leur aspect délavé à la main et leurs coutures déchirées, l'imprimé exotique Ikat s'offre un côté un peu grunge. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Unsere Lite Hearted Bazaar Jeansshorts machen deutlich, wie attraktiv der abgewetzte Look sein kann. Mit stark ausgefransten Säumen, handgeschliffenem Stoff und ausgerissenen Nähten sind diese Shorts ideal für echte Hardcore-Fans. Einen weiteren Akzent setzt der exotische Ikat-Druck. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">I nostri pantaloncini in denim Lite Hearted Bazaar sono la prova di quanto siano trendy i dettagli con effetto consumato. Presentano orlo molto sfilacciato, sabbiatura a mano e cuciture strappate che offrono un look alternativo alla stampa Ikat esotica. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Nuestro short vaquero Lite Hearted Bazaar es la prueba de lo sexy que los detalles descoloridos pueden ser. Presenta bajos muy deshilachados, lijado a mano y costuras rasgadas, que le dan un acabado radical al exótico estampado ikat. [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>