<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Nobility 5-piece Set (Pink, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set noblesse de 5 pièces (rose, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">5-teiliges Adel-Set (rosa, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set nobiltà 5 elementi (rosa, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de cinco artículos nobles (rosa, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">貴族の服５点セット（ピンク・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Nobility 5-piece Set (Pink, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 5-piece clothing set for a woman of nobility with hat, hairstyle, dress, gloves and high heels.\nDefense Strength: (None)~★\nGorgeousness: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Noble Brim Hat (Pink, Women) (Head Accessory)\n- Braided Bob Hairstyle (Women) (Head)\n- Noble Dress (Pink, Women) (Outfits)\n- Noble Gloves (Pink, Women) (Hands)\n- Noble High Heels (Pink, Women) (Feet)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 5 pièces de vêtements pour une femme noble avec un chapeau, une coupe de cheveux, une robe, des gants et des talons hauts.\nDéfense : (Sans)~★\nSplendeur : ★★★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Chapeau à bord large de noble (rose, femme) (Accessoire de tête)\n- Coupe de cheveux au carré tressée (femme) (Tête)\n- Robe de noble (rose, femme) (Tenues)\n- Gants de noble (roses, femme) (Mains)\n- Talons hauts de noble (roses, femme) (Pieds)\n\n* En achetant ce set, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 5-teiliges Set für eine Dame von Adel, das einen Hut mit Krempe, eine Frisur, ein Kleid, Handschuhe und Stöckelschuhe enthält.\nVerteidigung: (keine)~★\nPracht: ★★★\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Hut einer Adeligen mit Krempe (rosa, für Frauen) (Kopfbedeckung)\n- Bob-Frisur mit Flechtzopf (für Frauen) (Kopf)\n- Kleid einer Adeligen (rosa, für Frauen) (Outfits)\n- Handschuhe einer Adeligen (rosa, für Frauen) (Hände)\n- Stöckelschuhe einer Adeligen (rosa, für Frauen) (Füße)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set abbigliamento da nobildonna composto da 5 elementi con cappello, acconciatura, abito, guanti e scarpe con tacchi alti.\nDifesa: (nulla)~★\nAvvenenza: ★★★\nQuesto set include i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Cappello a falda larga da nobildonna (rosa, da donna) (Accessorio per la testa)\n- Acconciatura a caschetto con trecce (da donna) (Cappelli)\n- Abito da nobildonna (rosa, da donna) (Aspetti)\n- Guanti da nobildonna (rosa, da donna) (Mani)\n- Scarpe con i tacchi alti da nobildonna (rosa, da donna) (Piedi)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella rispettiva categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de cinco prendas para una mujer de la nobleza, que incluye pamela, peinado, vestido, guantes y zapatos de tacón.\nDefensa: (ninguno)~★\nHermosura: ★★★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n- Pamela noble (rosa, mujer) (Accesorio de cabeza)\n- Peinado media melena con trenzas (mujer) (Cabeza)\n- Vestido noble (rosa, mujer) (Trajes)\n- Guantes nobles (rosas, mujer) (Manos)\n- Zapatos nobles de tacón (rosas, mujer) (Pies)\n\n* Adquiriendo este conjunto, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">帽子、髪型、ドレス、手袋、ハイヒールを含む、女性貴族風の服装５点セット。\n防御力：　（なし）～★\nゴージャス度：★★★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・貴族のつば広帽子（ピンク・女性）/ヘッドアクセサリ\n・三つ編みボブヘアスタイル（女性）/頭\n・貴族のドレス（ピンク・女性）/組み合わせ\n・貴族の手袋（ピンク・女性）/手\n・貴族のハイヒール（ピンク・女性）/靴\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">*Not Localized* Object Description [#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 5-piece clothing set for a woman of nobility with hat, hairstyle, dress, gloves and high heels.\nDefense Strength: (None)~★\nGorgeousness: ★★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Noble Brim Hat (Pink, Women) (Head Accessory)\n- Braided Bob Hairstyle (Women) (Head)\n- Noble Dress (Pink, Women) (Outfits)\n- Noble Gloves (Pink, Women) (Hands)\n- Noble High Heels (Pink, Women) (Feet)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
