<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Stan the Salesman Hat</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Chapeau de Stan the Salesman</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Stan, der Verkäufer, Hut</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Cappello Stan il Venditore</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Sombrero de Stan the Salesman</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Stan the Salesman Hat (M)</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This is the hat of a used ship salesman. This baby is just the thing for you. This hat is fit for a king! Once your friends see you they won't be able to get you out of their minds. It’s always wise to keep your head warm and your ego HOT! Hey, that’s my motto! It really is! How can I sell something so dear? How? Because a deal’s a deal! That’s my other motto! Good luck! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">C'est le chapeau d'un vendeur de bateaux d'occasion. Ce bijou est juste ce qu'il vous faut. Ce couvre-chef conviendrait à un roi ! Quand vos amis vous verront, ils ne seront pas près de vous oublier. Il est toujours judicieux de se garder la tête au chaud et l'amour-propre REMONTÉ ! C'est ma devise ! Je vous assure ! Pourquoi vendre une chose qui me soit si chère ? Pourquoi ? Parce que les affaires sont les affaires ! C'est mon autre devise ! Bonne chance ! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das ist der Hut eines Verkäufers für gebrauchte Schiffe. Dieses edle Stück passt dir wie angegossen und ist eines Königs würdig! Ein unvergesslicher Anblick für deine Freunde. Auch ist es klug, seinen Kopf warm und sein Ego ANGESAGT zu halten! Hey, das ist mein Motto! Ja, wirklich! Wie ich dazu komme, so etwas Liebgewonnenes zu verkaufen? Nun, Geschäft ist nun mal Geschäft! Das ist mein anderes Motto! Mach's gut! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Questo è il cappello di un venditore di navi usate. Quest'accessorio fa proprio per te. Questo cappello è degno di un re! Quando ti vedranno i tuoi amici non riusciranno a staccarsi la tua immagine dalla loro mente.  È sempre saggio tenere calda la propria testa a ancora più CALDO il proprio ego! Ehi, questo è il mio motto! Lo è davvero! Come posso vendere così, mio caro? Come? Perché un affare è un affare! È il mio altro motto! Buona fortuna! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este es el sombrero de un vendedor de barcos usados. Esta preciosidad es justo lo que necesitas. ¡Este sombrero es apto para un rey! En cuanto te vean tus amigos no van a poder quitárselo de la cabeza. ¡Siempre es buena idea mantener la cabeza calentita y el ego ARDIENDO! ¡Oye, ese es mi lema! ¡De verdad que lo es! ¿Cómo puedo vender algo tan preciado? ¡Porque un trato es un trato! ¡Ese es mi otro lema! ¡Buena suerte! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This is the hat of a used ship salesman. This baby is just the thing for you. This hat is fit for a king! Once your friends see you they won't be able to get you out of their minds. It’s always wise to keep your head warm and your ego HOT! Hey, that’s my motto! It really is! How can I sell something so dear? How? Because a deal’s a deal! That’s my other motto! Good luck! [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>