<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">Mandarin High Heels &amp; Flats Set (Black with Gold Thread, Women)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Set d'Escarpins et de Ballerines Style Mandarin (noirs avec fils dorés, femme)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Chinesische High-Heels &amp; Ballerinas-Set (schwarz mit goldenem Garn, für Frauen)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Set di scarpe cinesi con tacchi alti e ballerine (nere con decorazione dorata, da donna)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de zapatos planos y de tacón estilo mandarín (negro con hilo dorado, mujer)</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">チャイナハイヒール＆パンプスセット（金糸黒・女性）</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">Mandarin High Heels &amp; Flats Set (Black with Gold Thread, Women)</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">A 2-item set with black high-heels and flats, embroidered with gold flowers and butterflies.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nStylishness: ★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Mandarin High Heels (Black with Gold Thread, Women) (Shoes)\n- Mandarin Flats (Black with Gold Thread, Women) (Shoes)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">Un set de 2 objets avec des escarpins et ballerines noirs brodés de papillons et de fleurs dorés.\nDéfense : ★\nStyle : ★★\nCe set inclut les objets suivants :\n\n- Escarpins Style Mandarin (noirs avec fils dorés, femme) (Chaussures)\n- Ballerines Style Mandarin (noires avec fils dorés, femme) (Chaussures)\n\n* Après achat, chaque objet sera ajouté à sa catégorie respective.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">Ein 2teiliges Set von schwarzen High-Heels und Ballerinas, die mit goldenen Blumen und Schmetterlingen verziert sind. \nVerteidigung: ★\nEleganz: ★★\nDieses Set beinhaltet die folgenden Gegenstände:\n\n- Chinesische High-Heels (schwarz mit goldenem Garn, für Frauen) (Schuhe)\n- Chinesische Ballerinas (schwarz mit goldenem Garn, für Frauen) (Schuhe)\n\n* Bei Erwerb wird jeder Gegenstand der entsprechenden Kategorie hinzugefügt.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">Un set di due pezzi composto da scarpe nere con tacchi alti e ballerine, ricamate con farfalle e fiori dorati.\nDifesa: ★\nRaffinatezza: ★★\nQuesto set comprende i seguenti oggetti:\n\n- Scarpe cinesi con tacchi alti (nere con decorazione dorata, da donna) (scarpe)\n- Ballerine cinesi (nere con decorazione dorata, da donna) (scarpe)\n\n* Acquistando questo elemento, verrà aggiunta ogni voce sopra elencata nella specifica categoria.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">Juego de dos artículos con zapatos negros planos y de tacón, adornados con flores doradas y mariposas.\nDefensa: ★\nBuen gusto: ★★\nEste juego incluye los siguientes artículos:\n\n-Zapatos de tacón estilo mandarín (negros con hilo dorado, mujer) (zapatos)\n-Zapatos planos estilo mandarín (negros con hilo dorado, mujer) (zapatos)\n\n*Adquiriendo este juego, cada artículo se añadirá a su correspondiente categoría.[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">金色の花と蝶の刺繍が入った、黒いハイヒールと低いヒールのパンプスの２点セット。\n防御力：　★\nセクシー度：　★★\n本セットには、下記アイテムが含まれています。\n\n・チャイナハイヒール（金糸黒・女性）/靴\n・チャイナパンプス（金糸黒・女性）/靴\n\n※購入すると、該当カテゴリに各アイテムが追加されます。[#Legal]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR"/>
		<LANG ID="en-SG"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK"/>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW"/>
		<LANG ID="en-US">A 2-item set with black high-heels and flats, embroidered with gold flowers and butterflies.\nDefensive Strength: ★\nStylishness: ★★\nThis set includes the following items:\n\n- Mandarin High Heels (Black with Gold Thread, Women) (Shoes)\n- Mandarin Flats (Black with Gold Thread, Women) (Shoes)\n\n* Upon purchase, each item will be added to the applicable category.[#Legal]</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
