<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-GB" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">goToShop</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[TRIANGLE] nDreams Shop</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[TRIANGLE] Boutique</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[TRIANGLE] Kaufstation</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[TRIANGLE] Negozio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[TRIANGLE] Punto de comercio</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[TRIANGLE] nDreamsショップ</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[TRIANGLE] nDreams 샵</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[TRIANGLE] nDreams Shop</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[TRIANGLE] nDreams 商店</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[TRIANGLE] nDreams 商店</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[TRIANGLE] nDreams Shop</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">toExit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">[DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">[DECLINE]  Quitter</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">[DECLINE]  Verlassen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">[DECLINE]  Esci</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">[DECLINE]  Salir</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">[DECLINE] 終了</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">[DECLINE] 나가기</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">[DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">[DECLINE] 退出</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">[DECLINE] 退出</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">[DECLINE] Exit</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Information Point</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Centre d'information</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Informationspunkt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Punto informazioni</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Punto de información</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">情報ポイント</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">정보 포인트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Information Point</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">資訊點</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">資訊點</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Information Point</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Information Point [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Centre d'information [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Informationspunkt [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Punto informazioni [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Punto de información [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">情報ポイント [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">정보 포인트 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Information Point [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">資訊點 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">資訊點 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Information Point [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">piazza_1st</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Welcome to the islands of Aurora!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Bienvenue aux îles d'Aurora !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Willkommen auf den Inseln von Aurora!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Ti do il benvenuto alle isole di Aurora!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">¡Te damos la bienvenida a las islas de Aurora!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラ島へようこそ！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Aurora의 섬들에 오신 것을 환영합니다!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Welcome to the islands of Aurora!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">極光群島歡迎你！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">極光群島歡迎你！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Welcome to the islands of Aurora!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">piazza_2nd</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Aurora is an ever changing world that is updated regularly. There's lots to do in Aurora and lots of FREE rewards to be had!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le monde d'Aurora est en constante évolution, avec des mises à jour régulières. Il y a beaucoup à faire dans Aurora, avec de nombreuses récompenses GRATUITES !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Aurora ist eine Welt, die ständig im Wandel ist und regelmäßig aktualisiert wird. In Aurora ist immer viel zu tun und viele KOSTENLOSE Belohnungen erwarten dich!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Aurora è un mondo in continuo cambiamento che è aggiornato regolarmente. Ci sono un sacco di cose da fare ad Aurora e un sacco di ricompense GRATUITE da ricevere!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Aurora es un mundo en constante cambio y que se actualiza con regularidad. Hay montones de cosas que hacer en Aurora y muchísimos premios que podrás conseguir.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">オーロラは定期的にアップデートされることで常に変わりゆく世界です。オーロラでは楽しいことがたくさんあります、そして無料で手に入る報酬もいっぱいあります！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">Aurora는 주기적으로 업데이트되는 시시각각 변화하는 세상입니다. Aurora에서는 할 일도 많고 다양한 무료 보상도 주어집니다!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Aurora is an ever changing world that is updated regularly. There's lots to do in Aurora and lots of FREE rewards to be had!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">極光群島是一個定期更新且不斷變化的世界。在極光群島可完成許多任務，還可獲得許多免費獎品！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">極光群島是一個定期更新且不斷變化的世界。在極光群島可完成許多任務，還可獲得許多免費獎品！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Aurora is an ever changing world that is updated regularly. There's lots to do in Aurora and lots of FREE rewards to be had!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">piazza_3rd</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">OrbRunner - Track down as many orbs as possible, the higher the score the more XP you earn.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">OrbRunner - récupérez autant d'orbes que possible : plus votre score est élevé, plus vous obtenez de points de XP.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">OrbRunner - Finde so viele Orbs wie möglich. Je höher die Punktzahl, desto mehr EP verdienst du.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Acchiappa le sfere: rintraccia quante più sfere possibile, più alto è il punteggio e più XP guadagnerai.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">OrbRunner: recoge el mayor número de Orbs posible: cuanto mayor sea la puntuación, ¡más EXP conseguirás!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">OrbRunner - オーブを集めれば集めるほどスコアが上がり、経験値をたくさん稼ぐことができます。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">OrbRunner - 최대한 많은 오브를 찾아서 많은 점수를 획득할 수록 그에 따른 XP를 얻을 수 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">OrbRunner - Track down as many orbs as possible, the higher the score the more XP you earn.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">OrbRunner - 盡可能尋找更多能量球，得分越高，您就能贏取更多經驗值。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">OrbRunner - 盡可能尋找更多能量球，得分越高，您就能贏取更多經驗值。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">OrbRunner - Track down as many orbs as possible, the higher the score the more XP you earn.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">piazza_4th</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The OMG Trap-O-Matic - Head to the trap, set it, come back 24 hours later and see what you have caught. It could be XP, a locomotion item or even a new apartment!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le jeu Trap-O-Matic - Placez votre piège et revenez au bout de 24 heures pour trouver votre prise, comme notamment des points de XP, un objet de Transport ou même un nouvel appartement !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Die OMG Trap-O-Matic - Begib dich zur Falle, stelle sie auf, komm 24 Stunden später wieder und sieh nach, was du erwischt hast. Das könnten EP, ein Fortbewegungsmittel oder sogar ein neues Apartment sein!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Trap-O-Matic: dirigiti alla trappola, piazzala, torna 24 ore dopo e scopri cos'hai catturato. Potrebbero essere XP, un oggetto di locomozione o persino un nuovo appartamento!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Tramp-a-mática: ve a la trampa, colócala y regresa 24 horas después para ver qué ha caído. Podría ser EXP, un artículo de locomoción o, incluso, ¡un apartamento nuevo!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">トラップ大作戦 - 罠のある所へ行って罠を仕掛けたら、24時間後に戻ってきましょう。何がかかっているかはお楽しみに。経験値、ロコモーションアイテム、もしかしたら新しいアパートかもしれません！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">OMG 트랙-오-마틱 - 트랩으로 가서 설치하고 24시간 뒤에 돌아와서 무엇이 걸렸는지 확인하세요. XP나 이동 아이템 또는 새로운 아파트를 얻게 될 지도 몰라요!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The OMG Trap-O-Matic - Head to the trap, set it, come back 24 hours later and see what you have caught. It could be XP, a locomotion item or even a new apartment!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">「超級陷阱」 - 前往陷阱進行設定，24 小時後再來看看您的所獲之物。可能是經驗值或者旅行物品，甚至可能是一所新公寓！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">「超級陷阱」 - 前往陷阱進行設定，24 小時後再來看看您的所獲之物。可能是經驗值或者旅行物品，甚至可能是一所新公寓！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The OMG Trap-O-Matic - Head to the trap, set it, come back 24 hours later and see what you have caught. It could be XP, a locomotion item or even a new apartment!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">piazza_5th</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Gateway - Check out what’s hot in the world of nDreams via The Gateway, plus find out which products can boost your XP.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">La passerelle - Venez voir ce qui se passe du côté de chez nDreams par le biais de la passerelle, et découvrez quels produits peuvent booster votre XP.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das Tor - sieh dir an, was es Neues gibt in der Welt von nDreams. Über das Tor findest du auch heraus, welche Produkte deine EP verbessern.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'ingresso: dai un'occhiata alle ultime novità di nDreams tramite L'ingresso e scopri quali prodotti possono incrementare i tuoi XP.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">La entrada: aquí podrás ver qué es lo que más mola de nDreams y enterarte de qué productos potencian la EXP.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ゲートウェイ - ゲートウェイを通じてnDreamsの世界の最新トレンドをチェック。どんな製品が経験値アップをしてくれるかも忘れずに確認しよう。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">게이트웨이 - 게이트웨이를 통해 nDreams 세계에 어떤 일들이 벌어지는지 확인하세요. 또한 어떤 제품이 XP를 높여주는지 파악할 수도 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">The Gateway - Check out what’s hot in the world of nDreams via The Gateway, plus find out which products can boost your XP.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">The Gateway - 透過「The Gateway」看看 nDreams 世界的流行物品，然後找出可以增加您經驗值的物品。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">The Gateway - 透過「The Gateway」看看 nDreams 世界的流行物品，然後找出可以增加您經驗值的物品。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Gateway - Check out what’s hot in the world of nDreams via The Gateway, plus find out which products can boost your XP.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">piazza_6th</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Blimps - Soar above the skies of Aurora. Blimps can be played competitively as a game of tag, or just float around and enjoy the view - it's up to you.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Blimps - Dominez le ciel d'Aurora. Il est possible de jouer à Blimps comme on joue au loup, ou de simplement planer en admirant la vue - à vous de décider.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Blimps - Schwebe durch die Lüfte über Aurora. Blimps können zum Spielen von Markieren verwendet werden - oder du kannst mit ihnen einfach die Aussicht genießen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Dirigibili: solca i cieli sopra Aurora. Puoi usare i dirigibili in maniera competitiva, giocando a Ce l'hai, o semplicemente volare in giro e goderti la vista. Decidi tu.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Dirigibles: surca los cielos de Aurora. Con los dirigibles, podrás jugar a un juego de marcar o pasearte y disfrutar la vista, ¡lo que prefieras!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ブリンプ - オーロラの空へ高く舞い上がれ。ブリンプは追いかけっこゲームとして競い合うこともできれば、ただ自由に飛び回って景色を楽しむこともできるゲームです。すべてはあなた次第。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">블림프 - Aurora 상공으로 날아오르세요. 블림프는 상대편과 경쟁해서 태그하는 게임으로 플레이할 수도 있고, 아니면 아름다운 풍경을 구경하면서 떠다닐 수도 있습니다. 선택은 자유입니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Blimps - Soar above the skies of Aurora. Blimps can be played competitively as a game of tag, or just float around and enjoy the view - it's up to you.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">軟式飛艇 - 在極光群島上空飛行。軟式飛艇可以捉迷藏的形式進行比賽，或只是四處環遊欣賞景觀 -一切由您決定。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">軟式飛艇 - 在極光群島上空飛行。軟式飛艇可以捉迷藏的形式進行比賽，或只是四處環遊欣賞景觀 -一切由您決定。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Blimps - Soar above the skies of Aurora. Blimps can be played competitively as a game of tag, or just float around and enjoy the view - it's up to you.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">piazza_7th</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sky Fishing - Dangle your rod over the edge of Aurora and see what you can catch. Some have even said they caught a glimpse of the mysterious Colossus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Pêche du ciel - Testez les eaux d'Aurora et tentez de faire une prise. On raconte que le mystérieux Colosse s'y trouve.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sky Fishing - Wirf deine Angel über den Rand von Aurora aus - mal sehen, was du erwischst. Manche behaupten sogar, sie hätten einen Blick auf den geheimnisvollen Koloss erhaschen können.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Pesca del cielo: lancia la canna oltre i confini di Aurora e osserva cosa puoi pescare. C'è chi dice di aver intravisto il misterioso Colosso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Pesca espacial: deja la caña de pescar colgando por el borde de Aurora y mira a ver qué pica el anzuelo. Dicen que hay gente que han visto a un misterioso coloso.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スカイフィッシイング - オーロラのへりで釣り糸を垂らし、何がかかるか試してみよう。中には伝説のコロッサスの姿を見たという人もいますよ。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">스카이 피싱 - Aurora의 끝에 낚시대를 던져두고 어떤 것이 잡히는지 확인하세요. 신비로운 콜로서스의 모습을 포착한 이들도 있다고 하더군요.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sky Fishing - Dangle your rod over the edge of Aurora and see what you can catch. Some have even said they caught a glimpse of the mysterious Colossus.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">空中釣魚 - 在極光群島邊緣懸掛魚杆，看看您能捕獲到什麽。據說有人看到過神秘巨人。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">空中釣魚 - 在極光群島邊緣懸掛魚杆，看看您能捕獲到什麽。據說有人看到過神秘巨人。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sky Fishing - Dangle your rod over the edge of Aurora and see what you can catch. Some have even said they caught a glimpse of the mysterious Colossus.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">piazza_8th</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">With 130 levels to progress through as you gain XP, plus over 30 FREE rewards available, Aurora is the place to return to - visit daily to gain even more XP!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">130 niveaux sont à disposition pour gagner des points de XP, avec plus de 30 récompenses GRATUITES, faisant d'Aurora un lieu des plus attirants - passez-y chaque jour pour accumuler vos points de XP !</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit 130 Levels, in denen du EP gewinnen kannst, und mehr als 30 KOSTENLOSEN Belohnungen ist Aurora DER Ort an den es sich zurückzukehren lohnt - am besten täglich für noch mehr EP!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Con 130 livelli tra cui farsi strada guadagnando XP e 30 ricompense GRATUITE a disposizione, Aurora è il luogo perfetto in cui tornare: visitaci ogni giorno per guadagnare ancora più XP!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con 130 niveles por los que podrás avanzar a medida que consigas EXP, más 30 premios GRATUITOS disponibles, Aurora es el lugar al que siempre hay que volver. ¡Ven a diario para conseguir aún más EXP!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">経験値を獲得していくことで上がるレベルの上限が130になり、無料の報酬も30種類以上に増えました。オーロラは何度来ても楽しい場所、毎日訪れてもっともっと経験値をゲットしよう！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">XP를 획득하면서 최대 130 레벨까지 진행할 수 있으며 30개가 넘는 무료 보상이 제공되는 Aurora는 돌아올 때마다 새로운 것을 얻을 수 있는 곳입니다. 매일 방문해서 더 많은 XP를 획득하세요!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">With 130 levels to progress through as you gain XP, plus over 30 FREE rewards available, Aurora is the place to return to - visit daily to gain even more XP!</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">隨著 130 個關卡的逐級通過，您獲得的經驗值將不斷提升，您還可以獲得 30 多個免費獎品，極光群島是絕對是必返之地，每天造訪可獲得更多經驗值！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">隨著 130 個關卡的逐級通過，您獲得的經驗值將不斷提升，您還可以獲得 30 多個免費獎品，極光群島是絕對是必返之地，每天造訪可獲得更多經驗值！</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">With 130 levels to progress through as you gain XP, plus over 30 FREE rewards available, Aurora is the place to return to - visit daily to gain even more XP!</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">piazza_id</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Information Point</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Centre d'information</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Informationspunkt</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Punto informazioni</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Punto de información</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">情報ポイント</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">정보 포인트</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Information Point</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">資訊點</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">資訊點</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Information Point</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>