<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Drey Ruby Red Vintage Lace Top</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Top Vintage en Dentelle Drey Rouge Rubis</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Rubinrotes Drey Retro-Spitzenhemd</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Maglia di pizzo vintage Drey rosso rubino</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Camiseta de encaje vintage rojo rubí de Drey</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">【Drey】ヴィンテージレーストップ　ルビーレッド</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">"드레이" 루비 레드 빈티지 레이스 탑 (여성)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Drey Ruby Red Vintage Lace Top (Women)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">Drey深紅色復古蕾絲上衣 (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">Drey深紅色復古蕾絲上衣 (女用)</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Drey Ruby Red Vintage Lace Top</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">With its feminine vintage style and classic shaping this 3/4 sleeve top works as an elegant update for the season. The ruche neck detail adorned with a love heart necklace creates a classy feminine style. Team with the vintage lace skirt for the perfect party dress. \n\n Fabric: Vintage Lace\n Composition: 100% cotton\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Avec son style vintage féminin et sa forme classique, ce top à manches 3/4 est un atout élégant pour cette saison. Le col ruché paré d'un collier en forme de cœur donne un style féminin particulièrement sophistiqué. A porter avec une jupe vintage en dentelle pour un ensemble de soirée idéal. \n\n Tissu : Dentelle Vintage\n Tissu : 100 % coton\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Mit dem femininen Retro-Look und der klassischen Form ist dieses Top mit 3/4-Ärmeln eine elegante Bereicherung für jede Garderobe. Der Rüschen-Ausschnitt mit Herzhalskette setzt einen sehr weiblichen Akzent. In Kombination mit dem Retro-Spitzenrock das perfekte Party-Outfit. \n\n  Stoff: Retro-Spitze\n Material: 100% Baumwolle\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Con il suo stile vintage estremamente femminile e il taglio classico, questa maglia con manica a 3/4 è un modo elegante per rinnovare il tuo guardaroba di stagione. Il colletto con ruche impreziosito da una collana con un cuore darà un tocco estremamente femminile al tuo stile. Abbinala alla gonna di pizzo vintage e avrai il completo perfetto per le feste. \n\n  Tessuto: pizzo vintage\n  Composizione: 100% cotone\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Con su femenino estilo vintage y forma clásica, esta camiseta de mangas tres cuartos es una elegante pieza de moda para esta temporada. Adornado con una gargantilla de corazón, el detalle del cuello plisado crea un elegante estilo femenino.  Combínalo con la falda de encaje vintage y crearás un vestido de fiesta perfecto. \n\n Tela: encaje vintage\n Composición: 100% algodón\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">エレガントな形状に女性らしいヴィンテージ商品です。ハートネックレスもついてさらに女性らしさアップです。レーススカートなどと合わせてパーフェクトなパーティードレスにしちゃいましょう。\n\n 素材：ヴィンテージレース、コットン１００％\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">여성스러운 빈티지 스타일과 클래식한 형태로, 이 7부 소매의 탑은 계절에 맞는 우아한 상품이에요. 러브 하트 목걸이에 루시 목 장식으로 멋지고 여성스러운 스타일을 연출합니다. 빈티지 레이스 스커트를 받혀 입으면 파티 드레스로도 딱이죠. \n\n 직물재질: 빈티지 레이스\n 직물구성: 100% 면\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">With its feminine vintage style and classic shaping this 3/4 sleeve top works as an elegant update for the season. The ruche neck detail adorned with a love heart necklace creates a classy feminine style. Team with the vintage lace skirt for the perfect party dress. \n\n Fabric: Vintage Lace\n Composition: 100% cotton\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">這件七分袖上衣擁有柔美的復古風格和古典造型，為當季服飾增添優雅氣息。頸部褶飾配上心形項鍊，塑造古典女性風格。加上復古蕾絲裙，參加宴會絕對完美無缺。\n\n 布料：復古蕾絲\n 材質：100%純棉\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">這件七分袖上衣擁有柔美的復古風格和古典造型，為當季服飾增添優雅氣息。頸部褶飾配上心形項鍊，塑造古典女性風格。加上復古蕾絲裙，參加宴會絕對完美無缺。\n\n 布料：復古蕾絲\n 材質：100%純棉\n [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">With its feminine vintage style and classic shaping this 3/4 sleeve top works as an elegant update for the season. The ruche neck detail adorned with a love heart necklace creates a classy feminine style. Team with the vintage lace skirt for the perfect party dress. \n\n Fabric: Vintage Lace\n Composition: 100% cotton\n [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>