<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">White Stilettos with Black Denim Shorts and Leggings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Talons aiguilles blancs avec short en jean noir et leggings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Weiße Stilettos mit Schwarzen Denim-Shorts und Leggings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Tacchi a spillo bianchi con shorts di jeans blu e leggings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Zapatos de tacón blancos con pantalones cortos vaqueros negros y mallas</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">白のハイヒール　黒のデニムショートパンツとレギンス</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">흰색 하이힐과 블랙 데님 반바지, 레깅스</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">White Stilettos with Black Denim Shorts and Leggings</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">白色细高跟配黑色牛仔短裤和打底裤</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">白色細高跟配黑色牛仔短褲和打底褲</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">White Stilettos with Black Denim Shorts and Leggings</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sexy Stilettos available in a variety of colours - mix and match, find the perfect pair for any outfit [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Talons aiguilles disponibles en plusieurs couleurs - trouvez la paire idéale en coordonnant les couleurs à volonté [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Sexy Stilettos in verschiedenen Farben verfügbar - kombiniere und finde das perfekte Paar für dein Outfit [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Sexy tacchi a spillo disponibili in una varietà di colori, fai i tuoi abbinamenti e trova il paio perfetto per ogni completo [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Zapatos de tacón sexis, disponibles en varios colores. Mezcla y combina para encontrar el par perfecto para cada conjunto. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">セクシーなハイヒールが選べるカラーバリエーションで登場。気分に合わせて、いろんな服とのコーディネートを楽しもう。 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">다양한 컬러를 믹스 앤 매치할 수 있는 섹시한 하이힐 - 어떤 옷에나 어울리는 완벽한 쌍을 찾아보자. [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sexy Stilettos available in a variety of colors - mix and match, find the perfect pair for any outfit [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">以多种色彩出售的性感细高跟 - 混合搭配，找到适合任何装备的组合 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">以多種色彩出售的性感細高跟 - 混合搭配，找到適合任何裝備的組合 [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sexy Stilettos available in a variety of colors - mix and match, find the perfect pair for any outfit [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>