<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LOCALISATION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" default_language="en-US" xmlns="http://home.scedev.net/schema/object">
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kName</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">The Alien Invasion Ultimate Bundle</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Le pack ultime Alien Invasion</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Das ultimative Alien Invasion-Paket</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Il Pacco Finale di Invasione Aliena</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lote Supremo de la Invasión Alienígena</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">The Alien Invasion Ultimate Bundle</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">kDesc</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This LOOT™ exclusive bundle includes all 11 Alien Invasion featured items: Male Alien Avatar from Fornax, Female Alien Avatar from M81, The Adam Android, The Eve Android, Cooper Alien Avatar,  Paris Alien Avatar, along with the Fornax and M81 Evolving Alien Avatars that turn into the King and Queen Swarm Avatars! Plus, since we're so incredibly radical, we also threw in the Alien Invasion Lava Lamp!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Ce pack exclusif de  LOOT™ comprend les 11 articles d'Alien Invasion : l'avatar masculin alien de Fornax, l'avatar féminin alien de M81, l'androïde Adam, l'androïde Eve, l'avatar alien Cooper,  l'avatar alien Paris, accompagnés des avatars alien évolutifs de Fornax et M81 qui se transforment en avatars roi et reine ! Et comme on est vraiment fous, on a même ajouté la lampe à lave Alien Invasion !  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses exklusive LOOT™-Paket umfasst alle 11 Artikel aus Alien Invasion: männlicher Alien-Avatar aus Fornax, weiblicher Alien-Avatar aus M81, Adam-Android, Eva-Android, Cooper Alien-Avatar, Paris Alien-Avatar, zusammen mit dem Fornax und dem Evolving Alien-Avataren aus M81, die sich in die Königs- und Königin-Schwarm-Avatare verwandeln! Und da wir so unglaublich radikal sind, gibt es die Alien Invasion-Lavalampe noch als Zugabe!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'esclusivo pacco  di  LOOT™ include tutti  gli 11 articoli presentati di Invasione Aliena:  Avatar Maschile Alieno Da Fornax, Avatar Femminile Alieno Da M81, L'Androide Adamo, L'Androide Eva, Avatar Alieno Cooper, Avatar Alieno Paris , insieme agli  Avatar Alieni che si evolvono Fornax e M81 che si trasformano negli Avatar  Re e Regina Swarm! In più,  visto che vogliamo esagerare, ci abbiamo messo anche la Lampada di Lava Invasione Aliena! [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Este lote exclusivo de LOOT™ contiene los 11 componentes de la Invasión Alienígena: El avatar masculino alienígena de Fornax, el avatar femenino alienígena de M81, el androide Adán, el androide Eva, el avatar alienígena Cooper, el avatar alienígena Paris, junto a los avatares alienígenas  Fornax y M81 que se transforman en los avatares del Rey y la Reina Swarm! Además, como somos tan increíblemente radicales, ¡añadimos la lámpara de lava de la Invasión Alienígena!  [#Legal]</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This LOOT™ exclusive bundle includes all 11 Alien Invasion featured items: Male Alien Avatar from Fornax, Female Alien Avatar from M81, The Adam Android, The Eve Android, Cooper Alien Avatar,  Paris Alien Avatar, along with the Fornax and M81 Evolving Alien Avatars that turn into the King and Queen Swarm Avatars! Plus, since we're so incredibly radical, we also threw in the Alien Invasion Lava Lamp!  [#Legal]</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>